<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/sap-next-gen/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP and the EU TUMO Convergence Center Team Up to Boost Digital Education]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/sap-eu-tumo-convergence-center-digital-education</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/sap-eu-tumo-convergence-center-digital-education</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP and the EU TUMO Convergence Center are helping students and recent graduates understand, utilize, and shape digital technologies.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1712136a51fe7abe9956a3c324ab5b20621fe243a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1712136a51fe7abe9956a3c324ab5b20621fe243a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1712136a51fe7abe9956a3c324ab5b20621fe243a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP and the EU TUMO Convergence Center Team Up to Boost Digital Education" src="./media_1712136a51fe7abe9956a3c324ab5b20621fe243a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-and-the-eu-tumo-convergence-center-team-up-to-boost-digital-education">SAP and the EU TUMO Convergence Center Team Up to Boost Digital Education</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="test-drive-sap-learning-hub-today-with-a-free-trial">Test drive SAP Learning Hub today with a free trial</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/td/sap-learning-hub.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) and the <a href="https://www.convergence.center/">EU TUMO Convergence Center for Engineering and Applied Science</a>, which helps bridge the gap between higher education and industry in Armenia, today said they launched a strategic collaboration aimed at helping university students and recent graduates understand, utilize and shape digital technologies.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“Innovation is what supercharges any science and technology ecosystem, and our collaboration with SAP deploys an innovation platform that is full of promise, not only from an industry perspective but also in terms of leading-edge research and education,” TUMO chief development officer Pegor Papazian said.</p>
  <p>As part of this collaboration, the EU TUMO Convergence Center is now an associate member of the <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/innovation/next-gen-innovation-platform/university-alliances.html">SAP University Alliances program</a>. As such, it will have access to SAP software and learning content, and a partnership with the SAP network, including SAP Next-Gen Labs around the world.</p>
  <p>The SAP Innovation Center Network in Potsdam, Germany, has developed 22 <a href="https://blogs.sap.com/2021/09/27/sap-innovation-center-network-invites-university-students-to-solve-real-world-business-technical-challenges/">innovation exploration challenges</a> for <a href="https://www.convergence.center/tumo-labs">TUMO Labs</a>, a technology, applied science and engineering education hub that is part of the EU TUMO Convergence Center. Students can explore emerging topics such as the future of self-service, augmented access control or augmented extended planning and analysis. In close collaboration with experts at the SAP Innovation Center Network, they will work to formulate proven and validated solutions to industry challenges. The expected outcomes range from user interface mockups and use-case ideas to data exploration and prototype code.</p>
  <p>“Students have the opportunity to put their creativity to work and connect research ideas to real-world business challenges,” said Lukasz Ostrowski, development manager at the SAP Innovation Center Network in Potsdam. “Working with educational institutions like TUMO Labs offers us the chance to find new talent and shape the next generation of enterprise software together.”</p>
  <p>The EU TUMO Convergence Center is currently registering for SAP learning resources, including SAP Learning Hub, <a href="https://learninghub.sap.com/academicedition/registration">academic edition</a> and SAP Learning Hub, <a href="https://learninghub.sap.com/next-gen">edition for SAP Next-Gen</a>. Plans to expand the collaboration are being evaluated and could include <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/innovation/next-gen-innovation-platform/young-thinkers.html">SAP Young Thinkers</a> programs, an SAP Next-Gen Lab in the EU TUMO Convergence Center and a research collaboration with TUMO Labs Berlin.</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="http://news.sap.com/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP on Twitter at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Media Contact:</strong> Benjamin Nickel, +49 170 4920616, <a href="mailto:benjamin.nickel@sap.com">benjamin.nickel@sap.com</a>, CET<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>Any statements contained in this document that are not historical facts are forward-looking statements as defined in the U.S. Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995. Words such as “anticipate,” “believe,” “estimate,” “expect,” “forecast,” “intend,” “may,” “plan,” “project,” “predict,” “should” and “will” and similar expressions as they relate to SAP are intended to identify such forward-looking statements. SAP undertakes no obligation to publicly update or revise any forward-looking statements. All forward-looking statements are subject to various risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results to differ materially from expectations. The factors that could affect SAP’s future financial results are discussed more fully in SAP’s filings with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (“SEC”), including SAP’s most recent Annual Report on Form 20-F filed with the SEC. Readers are cautioned not to place undue reliance on these forward-looking statements, which speak only as of their dates.<br>© 2021 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-innovation-center-network</category>
            <category>product/sap-learning-hub</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-next-gen</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-university-alliances</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Launches Free Student Offering: SAP Learning Hub, Edition for SAP Next-Gen]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/05/launch-sap-learning-hub-edition-for-sap-next-gen</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/05/launch-sap-learning-hub-edition-for-sap-next-gen</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The new SAP Learning Hub, edition for SAP Next-Gen, provides knowledge and opportunities to the next generation of talent.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>product/sap-learning-hub</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-next-gen</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-training-and-adoption</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-university-alliances</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>