<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/un-sdgs/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Empowering Africa's Future: Bridging the Teacher Gap through Digital Education and Upskilling]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/teacher-gap-africa-world-teachers-day-2023</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/teacher-gap-africa-world-teachers-day-2023</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[For World Teachers' Day 2023, SAP shines a spotlight on Africa Code Week and the importance of honoring all educators. Read more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>non-sap-event/africa-code week</category>
            <category>news-tag/life-at-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/un-sdgs</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Impact of New Human Rights Due Diligence Legislation on SAP]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/06/human-rights-due-diligence-legislation-sap</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/06/human-rights-due-diligence-legislation-sap</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Adhering to the new human rights due diligence standards, SAP is analyzing and understanding our impact on human rights in its entirety.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/un-sdgs</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Act Now, Together, Through Pro Bono Consulting]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/together-act-now-pro-bono-consulting</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/together-act-now-pro-bono-consulting</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Together Act Now was the theme for the 2022 UN International Volunteer Day. Learn how SAP employees participate.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/life-at-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-social-sabbatical</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
            <category>news-tag/un-sdgs</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Customers and Online Shoe Retailers Put Their Best Foot Forward for Climate]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/footprint-technologies-best-foot-forward-for-climate</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/footprint-technologies-best-foot-forward-for-climate</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Startup Footprint Technologies is helping customers and online retailers put their best foot forward to support the climate. Learn how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-partneredge</category>
            <category>news-tag/un-sdgs</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Expo 2020: Making a Difference with Sustainability, Inclusion, and Experience]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/expo-2020-sustainability-inclusion-experience</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/expo-2020-sustainability-inclusion-experience</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[From October 2021 until March this year, over 20 million people have made their way to Dubai for Expo 2020. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-extreme-series</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/un-sdgs</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Buying and Selling Renewable Energy Enables Communities across Europe to Become More Independent and Sustainable]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/09/exnaton-buying-and-selling-renewable-energy</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/09/exnaton-buying-and-selling-renewable-energy</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Thanks to an innovative solution developed by Exnaton, you can take your surplus solar energy to the market. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_19c8daa63aba95e847020c46340b735287f3308a9.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_19c8daa63aba95e847020c46340b735287f3308a9.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_19c8daa63aba95e847020c46340b735287f3308a9.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Buying and Selling Renewable Energy Enables Communities across Europe to Become More Independent and Sustainable" src="./media_19c8daa63aba95e847020c46340b735287f3308a9.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="buying-and-selling-renewable-energy-enables-communities-across-europe-to-become-more-independent-and-sustainable">Buying and Selling Renewable Energy Enables Communities across Europe to Become More Independent and Sustainable</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Going to market is an age-old activity when it comes to buying and selling goods – from cash crops to cattle, everything under the sun has been traded in some form or another. Now, you can even take your surplus solar energy to the market, thanks to an innovative solution developed by a team of young Swiss entrepreneurs.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“There is no life on earth without the sun, and it’s there for everyone,” said Anselma Wörner, COO and one of the three cofounders of Exnaton, a Swiss company that develops software for communities trading renewable energy in local neighborhoods.</p>
  <p>Wörner was explaining how her company created a smart energy system at the recent <a href="https://tacinsights.eventsair.com/international-sap-conference-for-utilities-2022/conference-brochure">International Conference for Utilities, presented by SAP and TAC Events</a> in Munich, Germany. “We have a new generation of prosumers – people who consume and produce their own energy – who are using new connected technologies and renewable power like solar to exchange energy through the grid.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="become-a-sustainable-intelligent-enterprise-with-sap-solutions">Become a sustainable, intelligent enterprise with SAP solutions</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/sustainability.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="sun-powered">Sun Powered</h2>
  <p>Humans have always depended on the sun for light, heat, and food, and its all-encompassing power has influenced cultures and religions around the world. Although advances in technology have decreased our dependence, the importance of solar energy in our efforts to reduce our carbon footprint is a reminder that we still depend on it for survival. That’s why the cofounders picked the name <a href="https://www.exnaton.com/about-us">Exnaton</a> for their enterprise. Looking for a word that connects “energy” and “exchange,” they hit upon the Egyptian pharaoh Akhenaten (pronounced Echnaton) who raised the status of the sun above that of all other gods and created an early monotheism that briefly became a state religion.</p>
  <p>The goal of Exnaton is to help integrate prosumers into the grid. Currently, the legal framework is very complex, and there is no clear ROI for them. There are no feed-in tariffs or policy mechanisms designed to accelerate investment in renewable energy technologies by offering long-term contracts to renewable energy producers.</p>
  <p>“At the moment, there is no value for the community, and we want to change that,” said Wörner, who is responsible for fundraising, data science, and recruiting at Exnaton. “What most people don’t realize is that renewable energy is not always produced when it’s needed most. So, when it is available, prosumers should be able to sell their energy directly.”</p>
  <p>People who own solar panels could actually sell a lot of energy to other households, if only they had the means. Wörner and her team believe it should be as easy to sell to other consumers as it is to sell any other products on the market. “Prosumers are faced with fragmented solutions, complex regulations, and frustrating user experiences. What they need are simple solutions, trusted local providers, and proactive community and user groups,” she explained.</p>
  <h2 id="community-centric">Community Centric</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="thrive-in-a-time-of-energy-transition-with-utilities-management-systems-that-support-a-sustainable-future">Thrive in a time of energy transition with utilities management systems that support a sustainable future</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/energy-utilities.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Enter Exnaton’s EnergyCommunity software add-on for <a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/energy-utilities.html">SAP for Utilities</a> solutions, which won an <a href="https://www.sap.com/idea-place/sap-innovation-awards/submission-details-2022.html?idea_id=2903">SAP Innovation Award</a> in the Partner Paragon category together with Best Practice Consulting (BPC) and is now available on SAP Store. This user-centric extension enables utility companies to empower prosumers to buy and sell energy within their local communities and also track all relevant data.</p>
  <p>Here’s how it works. Any prosumers in the community can sell their solar energy to any consumers in the grid. The EnergyCommunity tracks their energy data and informs them exactly where the energy is coming from and how much CO2 it is generating. The utility company can easily bill these energy exchanges with their regular SAP billing system thanks to the integration offered by Exnaton in working with the SAP system integrator BPC. At the same time, the utility company can sell additional hardware installations to members of the community, making it an attractive option for all parties.</p>
  <p>“The EnergyCommunity makes it easy to exchange energy within the community. Participating in their local community creates a closer bond between people, and the platform provides a new customer channel for the utility company,” said the technology expert, who has a PhD in Information Systems. “At the end of the day, with Exnaton’s energy sharing software-as-a-service platform, energy suppliers can offer their customers more independence.”</p>
  <p>Exnaton is responding to the challenge faced by prosumers who currently have no possibility to sell their extra energy directly on the market and the one faced by utilities companies as they realize they must offer new models as they transition to renewables with a decentralized approach. A number of utility companies are already running the solution in communities across Germany, Austria, Luxemburg, and Switzerland, and the goal is to expand to other European countries where there is a strong regulatory framework. More importantly, the solution enables energy companies to equip their customers for a <a href="/topics/sustainability">sustainable future</a>.</p>
  <h2 id="future-focused">Future Focused</h2>
  <p>Over 733 million people on the planet still don’t have access to affordable, sustainable energy, which is why providing energy is goal seven on the list of the <a href="https://sdgs.un.org/goals">UN Sustainable Development Goals</a>. For Exnaton, goal seven is its core business, but at the same time, it is equally committed to goal 11, developing sustainable cities and communities; goal 12, enabling responsible production and consumption; and goal 13, taking urgent action to combat climate change and its impact.</p>
  <p>The good news, according to the recent <a href="https://ec.europa.eu/commission/presscorner/detail/en/ip_21_5554">State of the Energy Union</a> report, is that renewables overtook fossil fuels as the number one power source in the European Union for the first time in 2020. Renewables generate 38% of electricity, compared to 37% for fossil fuels. Also, at least two million people in the EU are already involved in more than 7,700 energy communities, and engagement is rising. Energy communities have also contributed up to 7% of nationally installed capacities of renewables, estimated at 6.3 GW.</p>
  <p>For Wörner and the team at Exnaton, producing energy where it is consumed decreases the dependence of the region on imported resources. Energy from the sun is practically limitless, and it more than covers the entire demand of the planet. With advances in technology and solutions like the EnergyCommunity, households and small businesses benefit from electricity powered by the sun, making renewable energy accessible and cost effective. What could be more natural, sensible, or sustainable?</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em><a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2022/08/31/buying-and-selling-their-own-renewable-energy-makes-prosumers--more-independent-and-sustainable/?sh=7aa6082d492f">This article was first published on forbes.com</a>.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/renewable-energy</category>
            <category>sap-award/sap-innovation-awards</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-store</category>
            <category>news-tag/un-sdgs</category>
            <category>industry/utilities</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Why the Skills Mismatch Is a Global Challenge]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/09/skills-mismatch-global-challenge</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/09/skills-mismatch-global-challenge</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The skills mismatch is largely attributed to under-education. Learn more about what SAP is doing through programs and partnerships to help.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/generation-unlimited</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/un-sdgs</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Platform for Sustainable Success]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/09/sustainable-success-technology-platform</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/09/sustainable-success-technology-platform</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A technology platform can help in achieving sustainable success through accurate, holistic insight across an organization and supply chain.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-at-unga</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/un-sdgs</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP at UNGA 77: Driving Positive Business Transformation for People and Planet]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/09/sap-at-unga-77-positive-business-transformation-people-planet</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/09/sap-at-unga-77-positive-business-transformation-people-planet</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Get the details on SAP's participation in UNGA 77, taking place September 13-27 at the United Nations headquarters in New York City.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-at-unga</category>
            <category>news-tag/un-sdgs</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Grameen Nippon Empowers Women to End Poverty with Microloans]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/grameen-nippon-empowers-women-end-poverty-microloans</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/grameen-nippon-empowers-women-end-poverty-microloans</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A microfinancing program by Grameen Nippon that runs on SAP solutions supports entrepreneurship and helps women become independent.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-extreme-series</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-one-billion-lives</category>
            <category>news-tag/un-sdgs</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Achieving Net-Zero Is More Than Setting Targets]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2022/05/achieving-net-zero-more-than-setting-targets</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2022/05/achieving-net-zero-more-than-setting-targets</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Achieving net-zero is a global imperative. With the right tools and solutions, any company can make and keep its sustainability commitments.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/executive-blog</category>
            <category>non-sap-event/wef-davos</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/un-sdgs</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP's Vision for Supporting Business Transformation and the Workforce of the Future]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/vision-business-transformation-workforce-of-the-future</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/vision-business-transformation-workforce-of-the-future</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP has a vision for supporting the workforce of the future as humanity enters one of its most transformative phases. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/opensap</category>
            <category>non-sap-event/wef-davos</category>
            <category>product/sap-learning-hub</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-training-and-adoption</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-university-alliances</category>
            <category>news-tag/un-sdgs</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bringing Our Best to the World: Celebrating 10 Years of Societal Impact Through SAP Social Sabbatical]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/01/sap-social-sabbatical-celebrates-10-years</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/01/sap-social-sabbatical-celebrates-10-years</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[For a decade, the award-winning SAP Social Sabbatical program has brought the company's best out to the world to accelerate social business.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11a05509ca8d00f896d2d297fe73cce982f13bc6b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11a05509ca8d00f896d2d297fe73cce982f13bc6b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_11a05509ca8d00f896d2d297fe73cce982f13bc6b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Bringing Our Best to the World: Celebrating 10 Years of Societal Impact Through SAP Social Sabbatical" src="./media_11a05509ca8d00f896d2d297fe73cce982f13bc6b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="bringing-our-best-to-the-world-celebrating-10-years-of-societal-impact-through-sap-social-sabbatical">Bringing Our Best to the World: Celebrating 10 Years of Societal Impact Through SAP Social Sabbatical</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>The world has grappled with access to quality education for decades — a situation further complicated by the momentum of advancing technologies and, as a result, the ever-changing skills needed to succeed in the world.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>And just when we think we have figured out a <a href="https://sdgs.un.org/goals/goal4">framework</a>, a path forward to “solve the solvable” issues like education through the United Nations’ Sustainable Development Goals (UN SDGs), a global pandemic wipes out educational gains made over the last 20 years.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>The Global Business Coalition for Education confirms that before COVID-19,<br>260 million children were out of primary and secondary school — and<br>75 million had their education interrupted by conflicts and emergencies. Because of<br>the pandemic, 1.6 billion children were forced out of the classroom.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Today we are confronted with both the harsh reality of life and an opportunity for a better tomorrow. <a href="/topics/covid-19">COVID-19</a> has willed the world to prioritize and focus efforts on what matters most.</p>
  <p>On January 24, SAP joins organizations across the world in recognition of <a href="https://en.unesco.org/commemorations/educationday">International Day of Education</a>. We reflect upon the important role education plays for a sustainable future and <a href="http://www.sap.com/csr">SAP Corporate Social Responsibility’s</a> efforts to power equitable access to education and workforce readiness initiatives.</p>
  <p>After a decade of bringing our best to the world to accelerate social business, join us in celebrating the impact achieved in this area through the award-winning <a href="http://www.sap.com/socialsabbatical">SAP Social Sabbatical</a> initiative.</p>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15625fe928213f3128e3442a26bbe6bec70703359.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15625fe928213f3128e3442a26bbe6bec70703359.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_15625fe928213f3128e3442a26bbe6bec70703359.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Social Sabbatical - Celebrating 10 years of impact!" src="./media_15625fe928213f3128e3442a26bbe6bec70703359.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://youtu.be/6goZ_9AlkDw">SAP Social Sabbatical – Celebrating 10 years of impact!</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>For the past 50 years, SAP has guided organizations to become intelligent, sustainable enterprises. SAP Social Sabbatical has embraced this approach. By connecting employees and their skills to social sector organizations through pro bono consulting, we expedite world-changing solutions.</p>
  <p>The portfolio of programs, executed in partnership with <a href="https://www.pyxeraglobal.org/">PYXERA Global</a><u>,</u> offers unique triple impact and delivers long-term sustainable benefits to client organizations, SAP participants, and the company. Our celebration honors this community, which includes 1,371 SAP employees who have worked alongside 453 nonprofit and social enterprise clients spanning 52 countries. Collectively, we have positively impacted more than 6 million people worldwide since 2012.</p>
  <p><a href="https://www.youth4jobs.org/">Youth4Jobs</a> is a nonprofit organization based in Hyderabad, India. The organization creates education and employment opportunities for youth with disabilities that in turn delivers sustainable change for their families. In February 2019, Youth4Jobs hosted SAP Social Sabbatical participants, and challenged them to improve the organization’s business development strategy.</p>
  <p>Founder and CEO Meera Shenoy shared, “The three SAP consultants adopted our passion for inclusion quickly and became part of the larger Youth4Jobs family, understanding our challenges and our transformational work. They also gave us a peek into the amazing processes of SAP in every area, be it recruitment, marketing, or customer cycle.” Shenoy believes that beyond the direct outcome of the project, her team was able to embrace these critical skills which continue to serve the organization and accelerate their incredible work.</p>
  <p>Recently, SAP CSR partnered with <a href="https://60decibels.com/">60 Decibels</a>, an end-to-end impact measurement company, to conduct a study on the SAP Social Sabbatical. Eight-six percent of clients affirmed that participation in the program had a positive long-term impact on the beneficiaries they serve. One program director in Romania shared, “The work that we did together allowed us to build a scaled system to train teachers we serve for free and better prepare them for online teaching during the pandemic and afterwards. Significantly more teachers are now enrolled with our courses and activities than before.”</p>
  <h2 id="our-journey-ahead">Our Journey Ahead</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="choose-both-profitability-and-sustainability-with-sap">Choose both profitability and sustainability with SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/purpose-and-sustainability.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The last decade has demonstrated that pro bono consulting delivers truly transformative and lasting change. Throughout 2022, we are thrilled to bring you additional learnings from our decade of impact study with 60 Decibels to showcase the benefits realized by social sector clients, employees who participate, and SAP overall.</p>
  <p>The strategy for SAP Social Sabbatical, initiated in 2012 as part of SAP’s response to the education crisis, is now evolving to also address the company’s pursuits around zero emissions and zero waste, while continuing to focus on zero inequality. We look forward to sharing more inspiration, innovation, and real solutions from our journey — past, present, and, most importantly, our future.</p>
  <p>For more information, please visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/socialsabbatical">sap.com/socialsabbatical</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Jennifer Beason is global program director of Social Entrepreneurship at SAP.</em><br><em>Hemang Desai is global program director of the SAP Social Sabbatical portfolio at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/purpose</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-social-sabbatical</category>
            <category>news-tag/un-sdgs</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Getting Human Rights Right in Business]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/human-rights-day-2021</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/human-rights-day-2021</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[For Human Rights Day, learn how SAP plays its part to promote human rights across operations, the supply chain, and product life cycles.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10b4989a338af7b0203107351c8599f576eeb9f96.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10b4989a338af7b0203107351c8599f576eeb9f96.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_10b4989a338af7b0203107351c8599f576eeb9f96.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Getting Human Rights Right in Business" src="./media_10b4989a338af7b0203107351c8599f576eeb9f96.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="getting-human-rights-right-in-business">Getting Human Rights Right in Business</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="support-equality-with-social-responsibility-solutions-from-sap">Support equality with social responsibility solutions from SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/sustainability/social-responsibility.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Today is Human Rights Day, a <a href="https://www.un.org/en/observances/human-rights-day">day to commemorate</a> the United Nations General Assembly’s adoption of the Universal Declaration of Human Rights. December 10 is a day to celebrate inalienable rights and freedoms that apply to all people.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“[H]uman rights are for all of us, all the time: whoever we are and wherever we are from; no matter our class, our opinions, our sexual orientation,” former UN Secretary-General Ban Ki-moon once said.</p>
  <p>Especially in these challenging times, fighting to secure human rights is a key responsibility for governments, civil society, and businesses alike — and it is clear that collectively we need to do more given that inequalities, discrimination, forced and child labor, unsafe working conditions, unfair pay, and further human rights abuses persist in today’s economy.</p>
  <p>The UN <a href="https://www.business-humanrights.org/en/blog/16-june-2021-un-guiding-principles-at-10/">took stock</a> earlier this year on the occasion of the 10th anniversary of the UN Guiding Principles on Business and Human Rights (UNGPs) and found that progress has been made to promote corporate respect for human rights, yet more efforts are needed to accelerate implementation of the UNGPs as outlined in their <a href="https://www.ohchr.org/Documents/Issues/Business/WG/ungps10plusroadmap.pdf">road map for the next decade</a> launched last week.</p>
  <p>At SAP, we are fully committed to playing our part and to respect and promote human rights across our operations, extended supply chain, and product life cycle. The respect for human rights is central to our long-term commitment to sustainability and the <a href="http://www.sap.com/unglobalgoals">UN Sustainable Development Goals</a>, as well as core to how we execute on our purpose to help the world run better and improve people’s lives.</p>
  <p>I therefore welcome the uptake in legislative action around the world, particularly in Europe, which I hope to see become consistent globally and well thought out. Businesses and investors across the globe are backing this, with the <a href="https://www.business-humanrights.org/en/latest-news/uk-businesses-and-investors-call-for-new-human-rights-due-diligence-law/">list of statements calling for mandatory human rights and environmental due diligence</a> steadily growing. In addition, public support is overwhelming: over <a href="https://corporatejustice.org/news/poll-shows-overwhelming-public-support-for-eu-law-to-hold-companies-liable/">80% of citizens from across multiple EU countries want strong laws</a> to hold companies liable for overseas human rights and environmental violations.</p>
  <p>With stakeholder demand and legislation surging, companies have to make human rights a priority if they have not already. While it might be obvious that there is no way around it from a rational or ethical perspective, how to make it real and integrate human rights as part of your corporate sustainability journey is not a trivial thing.</p>
  <p>Depending on the industry and the countries in which a company is operating, its impact on individual human rights varies. Complexity is added when looking across the entire value chain, which at SAP starts with our employees and respecting their rights but of course extends to our ecosystem of suppliers, customers, partners, and to the communities in which we work and live.</p>
  <p>The challenge of getting this right and complying with relevant legislation is increasing. Therefore we have established a new human rights due diligence project at SAP to lead by example, take our <a href="https://www.sap.com/integrated-reports/2020/en.html?pdf-asset=82fad7fb-d17d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff&#x26;page=103">existing human rights commitment statement, governance, disclosure, and processes</a> to the next level, and to learn from our own adoption along the way.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-news-and-coverage-from-cop26">Read news and coverage from COP26</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/topics/cop26">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>At the same time, we have been working to expand our solution offering to support our customers’ human rights ambitions. Questions we seek to address within this twofold approach cover a range: How do we prevent workplace accidents and safeguard safety? How do we identify and reduce discrimination and inequality in our workforce? How do we ensure compliant working hours and payment structures for all our entire workforce — both internal employees and our external workforce? How do we avoid purchasing products and raw materials that were produced involving forced or child labor?</p>
  <p>Digital innovation can be a force for good in this regard and help identify and prevent negative business-related impacts on human rights. For example, aggregated analysis and reporting of human resources (HR) data as provided by <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm/hxm-suite.html">SAP SuccessFactors Human Experience Management Suite</a> allows you to gain insights into the composition of the workforce — including who is hired, developed, rewarded, and promoted — as a foundation to build a diverse, equitable, and inclusive workforce. Making risk assessment and due diligence part of the procurement process with <a href="https://www.ariba.com/about/procure-with-purpose">SAP Ariba</a> solutions is another example and contributes to detecting and eradicating forced and child labor, among others.</p>
  <p>Yet, we also need to address potential risks and make sure that our technology, such as artificial intelligence (AI), does not violate human rights. To help ensure that our software is only used in line with ethical standards, we have have developed <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2018/09/940c6047-1c7d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff.html#page=2">guiding principles for AI</a> and set up global AI ethics policy and governance.</p>
  <p>Avoiding harm and complicity in human rights abuses is at the heart of respecting human rights. However, there is more we can do to do good and promote human rights in a positive way. With programs like <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=exBl8h4QTBU">5 &#x26; 5 by ’25</a>, SAP aims to foster social procurement and to direct five percent of SAP’s addressable procurement spend with social enterprises and five percent with diverse businesses by 2025.</p>
  <p>SAP is furthermore committed to inclusive, <a href="https://www.sap.com/dmc/exp/2021-04-74301-unglobalgoals/Quality_Education">quality education</a>, and strives to include all people in the digital economy. In 2020, together, we engaged 2.3 million youth and trained 117,000 teachers in our digital skills programs that spanned 113 countries. These, together with further initiatives focused on diversity, equity, and social justice, contribute to our ambition to <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/purpose-and-sustainability.html">chase zero inequality</a>.</p>
  <p>But is that enough? Certainly not!</p>
  <p>In celebration of Human Rights Day 2021 and its theme, “<a href="https://standup4humanrights.org/HumanRightsDay2021/en/equality.html">All Human, All Equal</a>,” I invite everyone to join in to #standup4humanrights. All of us are called upon to follow the appeal: “By committing to reduce inequality by advancing all human rights for everyone, we can overcome global economic, social, health, and environmental crises and conflict, and build societies where all people rise together by sharing power, resources, and opportunities equally.”</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Daniel Schmid is chief sustainability officer of SAP SE.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/un-sdgs</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Integrating Climate Action End to End]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/integrating-climate-action-end-to-end</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/integrating-climate-action-end-to-end</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn how SAP is tackling climate action by embedding sustainability into its portfolio and across its purpose, strategy, and operations.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10563aea73452ab4df96f0b3c9ac9b08a7bf73965.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10563aea73452ab4df96f0b3c9ac9b08a7bf73965.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_10563aea73452ab4df96f0b3c9ac9b08a7bf73965.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Integrating Climate Action End to End" src="./media_10563aea73452ab4df96f0b3c9ac9b08a7bf73965.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="integrating-climate-action-end-to-end">Integrating Climate Action End to End</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>The climate emergency has reached a new peak. To help accelerate the transformation toward a low-carbon, circular future, SAP is embedding sustainability end to end in its portfolio, as well as across its purpose, vision, strategy, and business operations.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Climate change is widespread, rapid, and intensifying, with some trends now irreversible, according to the recent <a href="https://www.ipcc.ch/report/ar6/wg1/">6th Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change (IPCC) report</a>.</p>
  <p>The science is clear: unless immediate, fast, and large-scale action is taken to reduce emissions, the average global temperature is likely to reach, or cross, the 1.5° C warming threshold within 20 years. The alarming results are already with us, ranging from droughts and heat waves to wildfires and devastating flooding worldwide.</p>
  <p>While much hope is focused on a green recovery, the window of opportunity is closing fast. The latest report from the International Energy Agency (IEA) predicts that energy-related <a href="https://www.iea.org/reports/global-energy-review-2021/co2-emissions">carbon emissions are on course to surge again by 1.5 billion tons in 2021</a>, an increase of nearly 5% year-over-year and the second-largest in history, taking us back to pre-COVID-19 peak levels.</p>
  <p>The urgency to dramatically change course and accelerate decarbonization has never been higher. But only when businesses are moving beyond their siloed approaches, commitments, and climate pledges to fully embrace sustainability and embed these ambitions in an integrated way will we be able to drive the systemic change needed.</p>
  <p>It is a journey toward embedding sustainability across everything we do.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="register-today-for-the-upcoming-sap-sustainability-day">Register today for the upcoming SAP Sustainability Day</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://events.sap.com/sap-sustainability-summit/en/home">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="moving-away-from-add-on-to-core">Moving Away From Add-On to Core</h2>
  <p>Companies need to avoid thinking of sustainability as only an add-on to their strategies and operations. They need to integrate it across the business. Rather than defining a separate sustainability strategy, it is crucial to <a href="https://insights.sap.com/environmental-sustainability-affects-competitiveness/">set a corporate business strategy that is sustainable</a>.</p>
  <p>A first step toward SAP realizing this was linking sustainability to our purpose of helping the world run better and improving people’s lives. The objective: create positive economic, environmental, and social impact within <a href="https://stockholmresilience.org/research/planetary-boundaries.html">planetary boundaries</a> with special focus on climate action, circular economy, social responsibility, and holistic steering and reporting.</p>
  <p>This is reflected not only in the updated SAP vision to “reinvent how the world runs as a network of intelligent, sustainable enterprises,” but also in the executive compensation that rewards Executive Board members for customer loyalty, employee commitment, and SAP’s carbon impact, along with financial performance.</p>
  <h2 id="enabling-climate-action-through-technology">Enabling Climate Action Through Technology</h2>
  <p>The IPCC report has once again highlighted that harnessing the innovation power of enterprises has to be at the center of fighting climate change. For SAP, this means using digitalization to contribute to the United Nations Sustainable Development Goals (UN SDGs), <a href="https://www.sap.com/dmc/exp/2021-04-74301-unglobalgoals/Climate_Action">including #13, Climate Action</a>.</p>
  <p>In collaboration with customers and partners, SAP is working to optimize material, financial, and energy flows throughout end-to-end business processes in order to address planetary and social challenges. For example, <a href="/2020/06/climate-21-track-greenhouse-gas-emissions">the company’s multi-year Climate 21 program</a> helps build analytical and transactional capabilities into enterprise applications that can help SAP customers understand and minimize the greenhouse gas footprint of their products and operations along their value chains.</p>
  <p>During the <a href="https://events.sap.com/sap-sustainability-summit/en/home">SAP Sustainability Summit</a> in April, <a href="/2021/06/sapphire-now-sustainability-management-by-sap">sustainability management by SAP</a> was introduced, providing an expanded portfolio of sustainability-specific solutions, including <a href="/2021/09/sap-product-footprint-management-launch">SAP Product Footprint Management</a>, which has been available since September 2021. There is more to come with the releases of the <a href="https://blogs.sap.com/2021/05/21/helping-business-thrive-in-a-circular-economy/">SAP Responsible Design and Production</a> and SAP Sustainability Control Tower solutions in the next months, as will be shown during <a href="https://events.sap.com/sap-sustainability-summit/en/home">SAP Sustainability Day October 28</a></p>
  <p><a href="https://sap.io/">SAP.iO</a> Foundries locations Berlin and Munich are fostering startup innovation by setting up the <a href="/2021/03/sapio-sustainable-future-cohort-accenture">Sustainable Future program</a> together with Accenture. The equity-free program is designed to propel digital transformation in four target areas: carbon tracking and trading, resource efficiency, climate risk tracking and mitigation, and circular economy.</p>
  <h2 id="setting-ambitious-targets">Setting Ambitious Targets</h2>
  <p>In addition to harnessing innovation, the climate emergency calls for bold targets for decarbonization. By mid-2021, countries representing around 65% of global carbon dioxide emissions and more than 70% of the world economy have made ambitious commitments to carbon neutrality. The U.S, the European Union, Japan, the Republic of Korea, and others — in total 126 countries — have pledged carbon neutrality by 2050; China says it will do so before 2060.</p>
  <p>The private sector also needs to step up. More than 1,900 companies, including SAP in 2017, have set emissions reduction targets grounded in climate science through the <a href="https://sciencebasedtargets.org/about-the-science-based-targets-initiative/">Science Based Targets initiative</a>.</p>
  <p>In 2019, SAP raised its commitment and adopted a <a href="/2019/07/sap-emissions-reduction-targets">1.5° C science-based emissions reduction targets</a> aligned with a net-zero future. However, the journey started much earlier; back in 2009, SAP set the first goal of reducing its global carbon emissions to the year-2000 level by 2020. <a href="/2018/03/sap-integrated-report-2020-targets-met-early">This target was met at the end of 2017</a>, even though SAP grew more than fourfold over the period.</p>
  <p>The next milestone is 2023, when SAP aims to be <a href="/2021/03/sap-carbon-neutrality-goal-2023">carbon neutral in its own operations</a> – two years earlier than previously envisaged. This includes all direct (Scope 1), indirect (Scope 2), and selected categories of value chain (Scope 3) carbon emissions, such as business flights, employee commuting, paper consumption, and external data centers (co-locations and hyperscalers).</p>
  <h2 id="monitoring-and-reporting">Monitoring and Reporting</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="chasing-zero-the-future-can-be-greener-cleaner-and-more-equal">Chasing Zero: The future can be greener, cleaner, and more equal</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/purpose-and-sustainability.html#chasing-zero">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>It is essential to measure and monitor progress on the path toward achieving these targets. For example, SAP has increasingly embraced holistic steering and reporting because connecting financial and pre-financial performance leads to better management decisions and business success.</p>
  <p>SAP’s sustainability and annual reports were merged into the <a href="http://www.sapintegratedreport.com">SAP Integrated Report</a> in 2012. Since then, both material and immaterial value creation have been at the center of the company’s reporting and have been placed on an equal footing. Besides key financial information, environmental progress, workforce information, and social investments have been made transparent. In addition, an internal sustainability dashboard allows employees to explore the key sustainability key performance indicators (KPIs), such as women in management and carbon emissions by their country, location, and line of business, with updates every quarter.</p>
  <p>Our reporting shows that in 2020, SAP was able to overachieve by 43% on its target for net carbon emissions in 2020, generating 135 kilotons instead of the anticipated 238 kilotons. This trend continued in the first half of 2021, during which SAP’s carbon emissions totaled 45 kilotons compared to 90 kilotons in the first half of 2020 (-37%).</p>
  <p>The low emissions level is a consequence of the ongoing <a href="/covid-19">COVID-19</a> pandemic, as well as the introduction of <a href="/2021/06/pledge-to-flex-future-of-work-at-sap">Pledge to Flex</a>, which enables a more flexible mix of remote and onsite work. SAP believes this trend will continue and has just announced in its <a href="https://www.sap.com/docs/download/investors/2021/sap-2021-half-year-report.pdf">2021 half-year report</a> that it has lowered its 2021 carbon emissions outlook from 145 kilotons to a range of 90-110 kilotons.</p>
  <h2 id="taking-action-measures-of-implementation">Taking Action: Measures of Implementation</h2>
  <p>To become <a href="/2017/05/sap-to-go-carbon-neutral-by-2025">carbon neutral in its own operations by 202</a>3, SAP is following a three-pillar approach: <strong>avoid</strong>, <strong>reduce</strong>, <strong>compensate</strong>.</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Avoid:</strong> Whenever possible, SAP aims to avoid the creation of greenhouse gases. This is a top priority, supported by, for example, using virtual telecommunication instead of business flights.</li>
    <li><strong>Reduce:</strong> If greenhouse gas emissions cannot be avoided, SAP aims to drive efficiency and reduce all types of emissions; for example, building efficiency, data center operations, carpooling and car sharing, and e-mobility.</li>
    <li><strong>Compensate:</strong> SAP has extended its compensation models for travel. For business flights, it has introduced an internal carbon price to offset related carbon emissions. If greenhouse gas emissions cannot be eliminated altogether, SAP aims to reduce them through innovations in the areas of building efficiency, data center operations, carpooling, and car sharing, as well as e-mobility. For example, SAP has powered its own data centers and facilities with 100% renewable electricity since 2014, implemented an environmental management system with ISO 14001 certification in more than 30 countries and ISO 50001 at headquarters, adopting green IT initiatives in order to foster sustainable IT equipment usage and promoting tools such as <a href="https://www.ecosia.org/">Ecosia</a> as a default search engine.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>In 2020, SAP implemented additional energy and climate measures within its operations, ranging from opening a new office with energy-efficient design in Australia and implementing more efficient data center technology in Germany to introducing a bike fleet at SAP Hungary as well as a flexible mobility budget in Germany and installation of photovoltaic systems in Austria.</p>
  <p>For emissions that cannot yet be reduced or avoided, SAP thirdly invests in high-quality carbon credits. For example, <a href="/2020/08/sap-lcf-investment-livelihoods-carbon-funds">SAP has been a long-term investor of the Livelihoods Carbon Funds (LCF) since 2012</a>. SAP has also donated funds to restore ecosystems and improve people’s lives. In support of the UN Decade on Ecosystem Restoration 2021-2030, SAP recently joined the 1t.org corporate alliance, which aims to conserve, restore, and grow trees worldwide, with a <a href="/2021/07/enhancing-sustainability-people-technology-21-million-trees">pledge to plant 21 million trees by the end of 2025</a>.</p>
  <p>I am proud that SAP’s efforts to combat climate change and to strengthen its transparent reporting are <a href="/2021/01/corporate-knights-cdp-sap-top-esg-ratings">externally recognized</a>. The non-profit organization CDP included SAP on its <a href="https://www.cdp.net/en/companies/companies-scores?cid=9205306762&#x26;adgpid=95799580520&#x26;itemid=&#x26;targid=kwd-870315494871&#x26;mt=b&#x26;loc=9041983&#x26;ntwk=g&#x26;dev=c&#x26;dmod=&#x26;adp=&#x26;gclid=EAIaIQobChMIxpSS4e_Z7gIVjLh3Ch2xkAciEAAYASAAEgLpJPD_BwE">A List 2020</a>, thereby granting us the top rating for leading in environmental transparency and action.</p>
  <h2 id="partnering">Partnering</h2>
  <p>SAP recognizes that strong partnerships are an invaluable asset in tackling climate change. This is why we became a founding member of the European Green Digital Coalition and joined the World Economic Forum Stakeholder Capitalism Coalition and CEO Climate Leaders as well as the World Business Council for Sustainable Development (WBCSD), complementing our previous engagements with the UN Global Compact, the We Mean Business Coalition, the Value Balancing Alliance, the Ellen MacArthur Foundation, and many more.</p>
  <p>In addition, we signed the <a href="https://eur01.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.wemeanbusinesscoalition.org%2Fg20-2021%2F&#x26;data=04%7C01%7Cpreeti.srivastav%40eu.asahibeer.com%7C6b7d2eeaddaf447c6e2e08d97822af12%7C7ef011f8898a4d0182329087b2c2abaf%7C0%7C0%7C637672913526232765%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJWIjoiMC4wLjAwMDAiLCJQIjoiV2luMzIiLCJBTiI6Ik1haWwiLCJXVCI6Mn0%3D%7C3000&#x26;sdata=jX%2BiZ7Ipm3Wm9sXEgD6AbZ%2BWKk%2B4sePJIfTDXi7qNEI%3D&#x26;reserved=0">business letter to the G20</a> calling for greater climate ambition and we launched <a href="/topics/chasing-zero">Chasing Zero</a>, a new initiative that will feature executive thought leadership, best practices, and insights into a sustainability-related transformation of SAP and its global ecosystem to achieve zero emissions, zero waste, and zero inequality. The transition to a circular economy remains central to our vision for a world of zero waste and plastic free oceans by 2030. Consequently, we support stronger circular economy policies, such as the Worldwide Fund for Nature’s OneSource Coalition and the Ellen MacArthur Foundation’s Extended Producer Responsibility endorsement.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Daniel Schmid is chief sustainability officer of SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/climate-21</category>
            <category>product/sap-product-footprint-management</category>
            <category>product/sap-responsible-design-and-production</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
            <category>news-tag/un-sdgs</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Launching the Wheel of Purpose with UNCTAD]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/unctad-wheel-of-purpose</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/unctad-wheel-of-purpose</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP's collaboration on the Wheel of Purpose with UNCTAD provides a powerful example of purpose-driven public-private partnership.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15a8d984f3057fba51e82e2f1a29e4bd2d6e8dfa0.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15a8d984f3057fba51e82e2f1a29e4bd2d6e8dfa0.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_15a8d984f3057fba51e82e2f1a29e4bd2d6e8dfa0.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Launching the Wheel of Purpose with UNCTAD" src="./media_15a8d984f3057fba51e82e2f1a29e4bd2d6e8dfa0.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="launching-the-wheel-of-purpose-with-unctad">Launching the Wheel of Purpose with UNCTAD</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>What if you had a “blueprint to achieve a better and more sustainable future for all?” Would you execute on it? And how would you leverage the power of collaboration to scale and accelerate your efforts?</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In 2015, the United Nations (UN) General Assembly provided humanity with this <a href="https://sdgs.un.org/goals">blueprint for a better and more sustainable future</a> through a collection of 17 goals, known today as the UN Sustainable Development Goals (<a href="/topics/un-sdgs">SDGs</a>). They include ending poverty, promoting good health and well-being, reducing inequalities, supporting responsible consumption and production, and more.</p>
  <p>The 17th SDG, “partnerships for the goals,” urgently calls on the public and private sectors, non-governmental organizations (NGOs), and citizens to come together to strengthen the implementation of the SDGs.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="saps-purpose-is-to-help-the-world-run-better-and-improve-peoples-lives-with-sustainability-at-the-core">SAP’s purpose is to help the world run better and improve people's lives with sustainability at the core</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/purpose-and-sustainability.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="public-and-private-sector-collaboration">Public and Private Sector Collaboration</h2>
  <p>At SAP, in alignment with <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/purpose-and-sustainability.html">our purpose</a> to help the world run better and improve people’s lives, with sustainability at the core, we value the opportunity to work alongside organizations driving meaningful impact.</p>
  <p>Our commitment to a more sustainable future inspired the sustainability team and a team of designers and engineers at SAP to develop a gamified, educational experience tied to the SDGs: the <a href="https://unctad.org/wheelofpurpose">Wheel of Purpose</a>. This innovative showcase, which runs on SAP technology, brings to life SAP’s commitment to the SDGs and encourages purpose-driven conversations among employees, customers, and partners.</p>
  <p>The <a href="https://unctad.org/">UN Conference on Trade and Development</a> (UNCTAD) expressed interest in the Wheel of Purpose because of its ease of use and ability to engage users virtually. This led to a public-private partnership to further develop and amplify the reach of the Wheel of Purpose, using it to showcase UNCTAD’s vision to bring about sustainable prosperity for all through trade.</p>
  <p>In the upcoming UNCTAD Youth Forum (September 16-17), the UNCTAD 15 Conference in Barbados (October 3-7), and the World Investment Forum (October 18-22), organizers will embed the Wheel of Purpose into virtual programming.</p>
  <p>“Sustainable development is a complex challenge, but it is a responsibility shared by everyone,” says Arlette Verploegh, UNCTAD chief of communications and external relations. “We need tools that humanize and explain different pathways to sustainability. The Wheel of Purpose does that. Applied to UNCTAD’s work, it showcases what we do in a simple, gamified way. The wheel is at once educational and inspirational to our audiences and reinforces our commitment to the 2030 Agenda.”</p>
  <h2 id="technology-as-a-tool-for-change">Technology as a Tool for Change</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="build-sustainability-directly-into-your-core-business-processes-with-sap">Build sustainability directly into your core business processes with SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/sustainability.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>At SAP, we make sustainability core to business and we believe in the disruptive power of innovative technology and its critical role in creating tangible impact for the UN SDGs. Not only can SAP solutions enable the integration of sustainability insights into business processes, but they can also educate the public, raise awareness, and help us achieve joint sustainability goals alongside our global ecosystem of customers and partners.</p>
  <p>“Our collaboration on the Wheel of Purpose with UNCTAD provides a powerful example of purpose-driven partnership between the public and private sector,” says Daniel Schmid, chief sustainability officer, SAP. “We are excited to amplify the reach of this engaging digital showcase and inform others about how UNCTAD and SAP engage in meaningful efforts to accelerate the UN’s global agenda.”</p>
  <p>Explore the <a href="https://unctad.org/wheelofpurpose">Wheel of Purpose here</a>, and share it with your network to spark the conversations that motivate tangible action for the SDGs. Only in partnership can we create the transformational change required to bring about “peace and prosperity for people and the planet.”</p>
  <p>For more information on the SDGs:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Read the <a href="http://www.sap.com/unglobalgoals">SAP &#x26; UN Global Goals</a> web book, which launched in 2016, to explore tangible examples of how SAP, our customers, and our partners leverage the enabling power of digitalization to contribute to the SDGs.</li>
    <li>Sign up for a free openSAP course, <a href="https://open.sap.com/courses/sbi2">Sustainability Through Digital Transformation</a>, which covers sustainability frameworks, including the SDGs, and how companies can use digitization to contribute to achieving them.</li>
  </ul>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
            <category>news-tag/un-sdgs</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Turning a Passion for Travel into an Obsession with Purpose]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/the-world-within-us-passion-travel-purpose</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/the-world-within-us-passion-travel-purpose</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP employee Anina Monteforte combined her passions to found the social enterprise The World Within Us. Learn her story.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/redefining-youth</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
            <category>news-tag/un-sdgs</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Meet and Code Celebrates Five Years of Coding Impact]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/meet-and-code-five-years-impact</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/meet-and-code-five-years-impact</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jul 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Five years after its founding, Meet and Code continues to empower youth to shape their digital future through coding. Learn how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/un-sdgs</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sustainability Management by SAP: Enabling Tomorrow Starts Today]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/06/sapphire-now-sustainability-management-by-sap</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/06/sapphire-now-sustainability-management-by-sap</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Sustainability management by SAP supports organizations on the journey to becoming sustainable enterprises. Read the news from SAPPHIRE NOW.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/circular-economy</category>
            <category>news-tag/climate-21</category>
            <category>product/sap-product-footprint-management</category>
            <category>product/sap-responsible-design-and-production</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
            <category>news-tag/un-sdgs</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP and Accenture Join Forces to Help Enterprises Become More Sustainable]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/sap-accenture-more-sustainable-enterprises</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/sap-accenture-more-sustainable-enterprises</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In support of more sustainable enterprises, Accenture and SAP are expanding their partnership to help companies unlock new value and grow.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_111fc2de51a7c6d48aca6568d9f8dd292604349ae.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_111fc2de51a7c6d48aca6568d9f8dd292604349ae.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_111fc2de51a7c6d48aca6568d9f8dd292604349ae.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP and Accenture Join Forces to Help Enterprises Become More Sustainable" src="./media_111fc2de51a7c6d48aca6568d9f8dd292604349ae.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-and-accenture-join-forces-to-help-enterprises-become-more-sustainable">SAP and Accenture Join Forces to Help Enterprises Become More Sustainable</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><em>Where there’s a will, there’s a way</em>. This proverb dating back to the 1600s could not be more appropriate today as enterprises around the world grapple with the biggest business challenge of our lifetimes: creating a sustainable future.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Unsurprisingly, many companies are daunted by the seemingly insurmountable challenges, so SAP and Accenture are taking action to help them.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="catch-up-on-the-virtual-sap-sustainability-summit">Catch up on the virtual SAP Sustainability Summit</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://events.sap.com/sap-sustainability-summit/en/home">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="the-right-time">The Right Time</h2>
  <p>By now, we all know we must radically change the way businesses run, our impact on the environment, and the inequalities in society. That’s the only way to ensure a lifestyle that allows us to meet our current needs without compromising the ability of future generations to meet theirs.</p>
  <p>The signs are everywhere. Consumers are increasingly aware about the negative environmental impact of products and services, such as fast fashion, single-use plastics, food waste, and excessive packaging. They are demanding accountability and responsible business models from their favorite brands. Governments are increasing regulations around carbon emissions and waste management and are demanding manufacturers to take responsibility for their impact on the environment.</p>
  <p>Enterprises are under pressure from investors to include their environmental, societal, and governance (ESG) factors in their financial performance reports. And finally, employees are increasingly vocal about the environmental policies and actions of their employers. Businesses know they need to act, but few are rising to the challenge.</p>
  <p>A study by Accenture found while the United Nations (UN) Global Compact’s Sustainable Development Goal (SDG) program has challenged companies to enhance their commitment to the UN SDGs, only 25% have set goals aligned to societal or environmental needs. Although CEOs acknowledge the universal call-to-action to achieve a better and more sustainable future for all, less than 50% have implemented sustainability into their operations.</p>
  <h2 id="the-challenge">The Challenge</h2>
  <p>As a survey of business drivers and actions to improve the environment at planetary scale conducted by SAP Insights revealed there are numerous barriers. Almost 7,500 CEOs and other business leaders from 16 industries around the globe participated in the survey. The top three reasons they cited for not moving ahead were lack of clarity on how to embed sustainability in business processes and IT systems, lack of clarity on how potential actions would align with strategy, and difficulty proving return on investment. Other factors include lack of funding, lack of expertise, or lack of support from senior management.</p>
  <p>The challenges are daunting, which is why solving sustainability issues is not something individual corporations or governments can do alone. The way ahead involves <a href="https://insights.sap.com/government-business-civil-society-fast-track-circularity/">cooperation and collaboration</a>. In this decade of delivery, partnerships are crucial.</p>
  <h2 id="a-will-and-a-way">A Will and a Way</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-the-news-accenture-and-sap-extend-partnership-to-help-companies-lead-in-the-circular-economy">Read the news: Accenture and SAP Extend Partnership to Help Companies Lead in the Circular Economy</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/04/accenture-sap-partnership-accelerate-sustainability">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Accenture and SAP, for example, <a href="/2021/04/accenture-sap-partnership-accelerate-sustainability">have just announced they are expanding their long-term engagement</a> to help companies embed sustainability across the full spectrum of their business operations. This will help unlock new value and realize long-term growth.</p>
  <p>By combining SAP technology with Accenture’s <a href="http://www.accenture.com/sustainabilityservices">Sustainability Services</a>, the partners plan to jointly create new solutions that can empower companies to accelerate their progress on decarbonizing their supply chains and capture their share of the projected $4.5 trillion economic growth that the <a href="https://www.palgrave.com/us/book/9781349959679">circular economy could bring</a>.</p>
  <p>Together, Accenture and SAP will develop the new SAP Responsible Production and Design solution, which will help companies consume fewer resources and build sustainability within the design process. It will also enable companies to apply analytics to the operational, asset, and process data collected across the value chain. Such an integrated view will help them determine clear sustainability goals and metrics across business processes.</p>
  <p>As a result, companies will be able to reduce the costs of compliance and extended producer responsibility (EPR) regulation by designing and producing products with <a href="https://insights.sap.com/circularity-creates-value-from-waste/">more recycled content and less waste</a>.</p>
  <p>Accenture also supports SAP’s <a href="https://community.sap.com/topics/climate21">Climate 21</a> initiative, which allows companies in any industry to use analytics to measure and minimize carbon dioxide (CO<sub>2</sub>) emissions and lower the carbon footprint across the product life cycle. Adding sustainability metrics across the supply chain provides an integrated view of environmental savings and helps optimize operations.</p>
  <p>This type of co-innovation could help solve some of the barriers cited in the SAP Insights survey. Embedding sustainability in business processes and IT systems and measuring return on investment (ROI) gives enterprises a better understanding of how to fund their sustainability efforts. With time and success companies can gain expertise, set aside funds, and engage senior leadership to support their sustainability journey.</p>
  <h2 id="call-to-action">Call to Action</h2>
  <p>The Accenture study identifies three things leaders anywhere in any industry can do to start implementing and scaling plans of action to address climate change, social inequalities, and resource availability.</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Raise ambition and impact:</strong> Leaders must drive change in their own organizations, and through the disruption of market systems.</li>
    <li><strong>Change collaboration:</strong> Key players must connect in new ways because meaningful transformation is not a solo sport.</li>
    <li><strong>Redefine responsible leadership:</strong> Leaders must embrace their role as change agents to champion the sustainability agenda.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>To learn more about the SAP and Accenture partnership for a sustainable future, join the virtual <a href="https://events.sap.com/sap-sustainability-summit/en/home">SAP Sustainability Summit</a>, taking place April 28-29. The event will focus on how companies are reducing their environmental footprints and managing limited resources productively while steering and reporting their businesses holistically.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Follow me on Twitter: <a href="https://twitter.com/magyarj">@magyarj</a></em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/accenture</category>
            <category>news-tag/circular-economy</category>
            <category>news-tag/climate-21</category>
            <category>news-tag/climate-change</category>
            <category>news-tag/un-sdgs</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Joins World Business Council for Sustainable Development to Innovate in Global Decarbonization Effort]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/sap-joins-wbcsd-global-decarbonization</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/sap-joins-wbcsd-global-decarbonization</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP has joined the World Business Council for Sustainable Development (WBCSD) as innovation partner. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_12e52ba8efa72574cf8018a601d2f5c6afab9e93a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_12e52ba8efa72574cf8018a601d2f5c6afab9e93a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_12e52ba8efa72574cf8018a601d2f5c6afab9e93a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Joins World Business Council for Sustainable Development to Innovate in Global Decarbonization Effort" src="./media_12e52ba8efa72574cf8018a601d2f5c6afab9e93a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-joins-world-business-council-for-sustainable-development-to-innovate-in-global-decarbonization-effort">SAP Joins World Business Council for Sustainable Development to Innovate in Global Decarbonization Effort</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="catch-up-on-the-virtual-sap-sustainability-summit">Catch up on the virtual SAP Sustainability Summit</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://events.sap.com/sap-sustainability-summit/en/home">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced it has joined the <a href="http://www.wbcsd.org">World Business Council for Sustainable Development (WBCSD)</a> as an innovation partner in <a href="https://www.wbcsd.org/Programs/Climate-and-Energy/Climate/SOS-1.5/News/WBCSD-launches-new-Pathfinder-to-enable-Scope-3-emissions-transparency-and-accelerate-decarbonization">WBCSD’s Value Chain Carbon Transparency Pathfinder</a>.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The initiative is dedicated to enhancing transparency in corporate carbon emissions with the objective to ultimately decarbonize supply chains. The announcement was made at the <a href="https://events.sap.com/sap-sustainability-summit/en/home">SAP Sustainability Summit</a> virtual event.</p>
  <p>The membership accelerates SAP’s momentum in sustainability leadership and innovation. Last year, SAP announced <a href="/2020/06/sapphire-now-innovations-supply-chain-industry-sustainability">the Climate 21 program</a> to help companies understand, minimize and disclose the full carbon footprints of their products and services.</p>
  <p>“We are supporting businesses of all sizes and industries in determining the carbon footprint across their operations and supply chains down to the individual product level by embedding the corresponding capabilities into our core enterprise software systems,” said Christian Klein, CEO and member of the Executive Board of SAP SE. “By partnering with WBCSD and other forward-thinking companies, we will jointly find new ways to collect and share product carbon footprint data with their customers and consumers, which will give them a real competitive advantage while accelerating global decarbonization efforts.”</p>
  <p>WBCSD is a global, CEO-led organization dedicated to accelerating the transition to a sustainable world. At the core of the network are its six work programs, including climate, energy and circular economy, which focus on helping realize the Sustainable Development Goals (SDGs) set by the United Nations General Assembly in 2015. WBCSD invites businesses, standards-setting bodies, technology experts and other decarbonization initiatives to join the Carbon Transparency Pathfinder in helping develop an effective model to help decarbonize industry through data transparency.</p>
  <p>“We’re glad to be counting on SAP’s support, drive and expertise across our programs and projects – especially in the Carbon Transparency Pathfinder, which is a perfect initiative for SAP because their software and data management solutions are used by many of the world’s largest companies to run complex supply chain and manufacturing operations,” said Peter Bakker, president and CEO, WBCSD. “We look forward to innovating with SAP and other members to make real, tangible progress on sustainable development and climate action for a more sustainable world in line with the recently released <a href="http://www.timetotransform.biz">Vision 2050</a>.”</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP on Twitter at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <p>Visit <a href="http://www.wbcsd.org">WBCSD</a>. Follow WBCSD on <a href="https://twitter.com/wbcsd">Twitter</a> and <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/wbcsd">LinkedIn</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>About WBCSD</strong></p>
  <p>WBCSD is a global, CEO-led organization of over 200 leading businesses working together to accelerate the transition to a sustainable world. We help make our member companies more successful and sustainable by focusing on the maximum positive impact for shareholders, the environment and societies. Their member companies come from all business sectors and all major economies, representing a combined revenue of more than USD $8.5 trillion and 19 million employees. Their global network of almost 70 national business councils gives our members unparalleled reach across the globe. Since 1995, WBCSD has been uniquely positioned to work with member companies along and across value chains to deliver impactful business solutions to the most challenging sustainability issues. The organization is a leading voice of business for sustainability, united by a vision of a world where more than 9 billion people are all living well, within planetary boundaries, by 2050. <a href="http://www.wbcsd.org">www.wbcsd.org</a></p>
  <p><strong>About SAP</strong></p>
  <p>SAP’s strategy is to help every business run as an intelligent enterprise. As a market leader in enterprise application software, we help companies of all sizes and in all industries run at their best: 77% of the world’s transaction revenue touches an SAP system. Our machine learning, Internet of Things (IoT), and advanced analytics technologies help turn customers’ businesses into intelligent enterprises. SAP helps give people and organizations deep business insight and fosters collaboration that helps them stay ahead of their competition. We simplify technology for companies so they can consume our software the way they want – without disruption. Our end-to-end suite of applications and services enables business and public customers across 25 industries globally to operate profitably, adapt continuously, and make a difference. With a global network of customers, partners, employees, and thought leaders, SAP helps the world run better and improve people’s lives. For more information, visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/">www.sap.com</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Note to editors:</strong><br>To preview and download broadcast-standard stock footage and press photos digitally, please visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/photos">www.sap.com/photos</a>. On this platform, you can find high resolution material for your media channels. To view video stories on diverse topics, visit <a href="http://www.sap-tv.com">www.sap-tv.com</a>. From this site, you can embed videos into your own Web pages, share video via email links, and subscribe to RSS feeds from SAP TV.</p>
  <p><strong>For customers interested in learning more about SAP products:</strong><br>Global Customer Center: +49 180 534-34-24<br>United States Only: 1 (800) 872-1SAP (1-800-872-1727)</p>
  <p><strong>For more information, press only:</strong><br>Bettina Wunderle, +49 7544 970 538, <a href="mailto:bettina.wunderle@sap.com">bettina.wunderle@sap.com</a>, CET<br>Stacy Ries, +1 (484) 619-0411, <a href="mailto:stacy.ries@sap.com">stacy.ries@sap.com</a>, ET<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>Any statements contained in this document that are not historical facts are forward-looking statements as defined in the U.S. Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995. Words such as “anticipate,” “believe,” “estimate,” “expect,” “forecast,” “intend,” “may,” “plan,” “project,” “predict,” “should” and “will” and similar expressions as they relate to SAP are intended to identify such forward-looking statements. SAP undertakes no obligation to publicly update or revise any forward-looking statements. All forward-looking statements are subject to various risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results to differ materially from expectations. The factors that could affect SAP’s future financial results are discussed more fully in SAP’s filings with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (“SEC”), including SAP’s most recent Annual Report on Form 20-F filed with the SEC. Readers are cautioned not to place undue reliance on these forward-looking statements, which speak only as of their dates.<br>© 2021 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.<br>Please consider our <a href="https://www.sap.com/corporate/en/legal/privacy.html">privacy policy</a>. If you received this press release in your e-mail and you wish to unsubscribe to our mailing list please contact <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a> and write Unsubscribe in the subject line.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/climate-21</category>
            <category>news-tag/un-sdgs</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Accenture and SAP Extend Partnership to Help Companies Accelerate Sustainability Transformation, Drive New Sources of Value and Lead in the Circular Economy]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/accenture-sap-partnership-accelerate-sustainability</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/accenture-sap-partnership-accelerate-sustainability</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[To accelerate sustainability, SAP and Accenture are expanding their decades-long partnership to help companies to unlock new value.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/accenture</category>
            <category>news-tag/circular-economy</category>
            <category>news-tag/climate-21</category>
            <category>news-tag/un-sdgs</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sustainable Business Is Better Business for All]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/sap-and-accenture-sustainability-better-business</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/sap-and-accenture-sustainability-better-business</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP and Accenture are committed to working together and with customers to make sustainability ambitions a reality. Learn more about how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16958860638d1cb15960c1b14b8ecc6ccf1606de3.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16958860638d1cb15960c1b14b8ecc6ccf1606de3.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_16958860638d1cb15960c1b14b8ecc6ccf1606de3.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Sustainable Business Is Better Business for All" src="./media_16958860638d1cb15960c1b14b8ecc6ccf1606de3.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sustainable-business-is-better-business-for-all">Sustainable Business Is Better Business for All</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Sustainability is the business challenge of our lifetimes.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Customers are increasingly educated and demand products and services that minimize negative environmental impact. Investors are integrating climate risk in their portfolio strategies. Government regulation is on the rise around the world, affecting carbon emissions, waste management, product design, and producer responsibility. Employees are increasingly vocal about their employer’s environmental policies and actions, making it challenging for businesses to recruit top talent without a genuine environmental vision and track record.</p>
  <p>Based on Accenture research*, enterprises with high ratings for environmental and social governance (ESG) performance attained operating margins nearly four-times higher than those with low ESG ratings and generated annual total returns to shareholders that were double their peers. According <a href="https://www.accenture.com/us-en/insights/strategy/ungcceostudy">Accenture and United Nations (UN) Global Compact research</a>, 54% of CEOs agree sustainability is critical to the future success of their organizations, and 71% of investors believe the <a href="/covid-19">pandemic</a> will accentuate global policies to tackle risks related to climate change.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="catch-up-on-the-virtual-sap-sustainability-summit">Catch up on the virtual SAP Sustainability Summit</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://events.sap.com/sap-sustainability-summit/en/home">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="from-periphery-to-core">From Periphery to Core</h2>
  <p>Enterprises must show accountability through ESG performance and manage end-to-end operations responsibly. By reimagining its business model, any company can operate in an intelligent way, minimize negative environmental impact, and unleash a new dimension of enterprise resource planning (ERP). Decision-makers can use this intelligence to design better products, create engaging experiences, and equip employees to do their best work by eliminating busywork. They can create an efficient, ethical, and adaptable supply chain, reaching beyond organizations and first-tier suppliers to proactively manage performance and risks with trading partners around the world.</p>
  <p>Just like any other core business function, sustainability performance must also be managed in real time and integrated into wider business decision making. True, integrated reporting will go hand-in-hand with ESG management, and information transparency will provide a solid foundation to optimize financial results and sustainability performance together.</p>
  <p>Most companies have a long way to go before they move beyond the basics of simply reporting ESG performance to actively steering their business operations toward ambitious sustainability goals. While the UN Global Compact’s SDG Ambition program has challenged companies to enhance their commitment to the UN Sustainable Development Goals (SDGs), only <a href="https://www.accenture.com/us-en/insights/strategy/ungcceostudy">25% have set goals</a> aligned to societal or environmental needs. Although CEOs acknowledge the universal call-to-action to achieve a better and more sustainable future for all, <a href="https://www.accenture.com/us-en/insights/strategy/ungcceostudy">less than 50% have implemented sustainability</a> into their operations.</p>
  <h2 id="words-into-actions">Words into Actions</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-the-power-of-partnership-with-sap">Learn more about the power of partnership with SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/partner.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1990c15effec3554d7ecb9b3e997d769082f31fb7.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1990c15effec3554d7ecb9b3e997d769082f31fb7.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1990c15effec3554d7ecb9b3e997d769082f31fb7.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Graphic: SAP and Accenture Sustainability Goals" src="./media_1990c15effec3554d7ecb9b3e997d769082f31fb7.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="800" height="950">
    </picture>If we plan to deliver on the UN SDGs by 2030, the performance of every process and product must be measured, managed, and delivered against sustainability goals. It is an imperative that spans across the value chain – from companies’ key design decisions to product lifecycle management.
  </p>
  <p>SAP and Accenture believe that steering a company holistically – by looking not only at financials, but also at the social and green bottom lines – leads to better management decisions and more resiliency in their value chain. SAP S/4HANA helps companies to drive bottom line profitability through operational efficiency, top line growth and adaptability. It offers flexible business model innovation and transparency into its green line environmental responsibility. SAP and Accenture’s goal is to make sustainability profitable and profitability sustainable.</p>
  <p>To achieve this, enterprises must integrate sustainability into the heart of their strategy and core business systems. This is the rationale behind the collaboration between SAP and Accenture, which focuses on innovation, development, and scaling sustainability across four go-to-market sustainability initiatives:</p>
  <p><strong>SDG Ambition: Scaling Business Impact for Decade of Action</strong></p>
  <p>The first of these initiatives is our partnership with the UN Global Compact on the SDG Ambition. Announced at the World Economic Forum 2020 in Davos with 3M as Patron Sponsor, SAP and Accenture are rolling out the SDG Ambition <a href="https://newsroom.accenture.com/news/un-global-compact-in-partnership-with-accenture-and-sap-and-with-3m-as-patron-sponsor-launch-sdg-ambition-guidance-to-accelerate-business-action-to-achieve-the-sdgs.htm">Benchmarks and Guidance</a> through the <a href="https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2021/02/08/2170997/0/en/New-programme-to-accelerate-business-action-on-the-Sustainable-Development-Goals-starts-with-600-companies-in-65-countries.html">UNGC Accelerator Program</a>. This includes how to implement these goals at a systemic level and how to develop new capabilities powered by SAP technologies. As of today, more than 600 companies have already signed up for the program.</p>
  <p>SAP and Accenture are working together to co-innovate and develop new SAP solutions that address sustainability and enhance existing core technologies. Both new and existing systems have a role to play in the other three joint sustainability initiatives.</p>
  <p><strong>Circular Economy: Taking Action Toward a Zero-Waste Economy</strong></p>
  <p>The power of SAP and Accenture’s partnership enables their customers to better manage material flows through their supply chains and innovate business processes to accelerate the circular economy. The initial focus is on packaging in the consumer goods and retail industries, specifically accelerating the development and delivery of the SAP Responsible Design and Production solution. Designing and promoting reusable products to address waste management is a fundamental principle of the circular economy.</p>
  <p><strong>Decarbonization: Enabling Our Customers to Contribute to a Zero-Carbon Economy</strong></p>
  <p>SAP and Accenture are working together to offer intelligent technologies that help companies – especially in natural resources, energy, and utilities – account, analyze, manage, and ultimately reduce carbon emissions. If companies cannot account for and manage total carbon emissions, they could lose their competitive edge. Solutions such as the <a href="/2020/06/decade-delivery-climate-21">Climate 21 initiative</a> and SAP Product Footprint Management help companies to embed sustainability as a new dimension of success into their analytical and transactional applications to enable ERP and intelligent enterprise to optimize their resources not only of an individual enterprise but across value chains for the entire product life cycle.</p>
  <p><strong>Startups: Collaborating with Innovators to Create a Positive Impact on Both Society and Business</strong></p>
  <p>Accenture and SAP are also tapping into their respective global innovation networks to nurture and engage startups through a <a href="https://sap.io/sustainablefuture/">sustainability focused startup program</a> to help address climate action, carbon reporting, and circular economy challenges across industries. Together, SAP and Accenture will leverage this rich source of creativity to help solve our customers’ biggest sustainability challenges.</p>
  <h2 id="helping-companies-become-twin-transformers">Helping Companies Become “Twin Transformers”</h2>
  <p>Untapped value exists at the intersection of digital technologies and sustainability, though only a few companies – referred to <a href="https://www.accenture.com/us-en/insights/strategy/european-double-up">as “Twin Transformers” by Accenture</a> – already link the two.</p>
  <p>From now on, twin transformation – directing innovation investment to initiatives that combine sustainability impact and the power of technology as opposed to splitting resources between advancing sustainability and technology deployment – will be critical to success. Companies that harness emerging technologies while finding new sources of value and pushing for green operations will gain a competitive advantage.</p>
  <p>Our customers provide daily proof of just how relevant our solutions are. Together, SAP and Accenture are committed to working with customers to make their sustainability ambitions a reality.</p>
  <p>We are showcasing our vision to jointly build a sustainable future at the <a href="https://events.sap.com/sap-sustainability-summit/en/home">SAP Sustainability Summit</a> on April 28 and 29. Stay tuned for updates!</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><em>Jan Gilg is president of SAP S/4HANA at SAP.</em><br><em>Peter Lacy is chief responsibility officer and Global Sustainability Services lead at Accenture.</em></p>
        <p><em>*Source: Research analysis by Arabesque S Ray</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/accenture</category>
            <category>product/sap-responsible-design-and-production</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/un-sdgs</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[QuartaVista Brings Sustainability to Balance Sheets]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/quartavista-sustainability-balance-sheets</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/quartavista-sustainability-balance-sheets</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Apr 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Sustainability success in monetary terms on balance sheets has proved difficult. Enter QuartaVista, an innovation project led by SAP.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_13d4799d9c7d36981521745d11ece997b26f8d7fc.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_13d4799d9c7d36981521745d11ece997b26f8d7fc.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_13d4799d9c7d36981521745d11ece997b26f8d7fc.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="QuartaVista Brings Sustainability to Balance Sheets" src="./media_13d4799d9c7d36981521745d11ece997b26f8d7fc.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="quartavista-brings-sustainability-to-balance-sheets">QuartaVista Brings Sustainability to Balance Sheets</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Across the globe, people are taking to the streets demanding climate action. Consumers are becoming more deliberate in their purchase decisions and politicians are taking measures like the <a href="https://ec.europa.eu/clima/policies/eu-climate-action_en">European Green Deal</a> and the <a href="https://sdgs.un.org/goals">United Nations Sustainable Development Goals</a> (UN SDGs).</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The winds of change are blowing through the financial world too. One prominent example is Larry Fink, CEO of investment management company Blackrock, who said in <a href="https://www.blackrock.com/corporate/investor-relations/2020-larry-fink-ceo-letter">his 2020 letter to shareholders</a> that “climate risk is investment risk.”</p>
  <p>Businesses, too, are expected to operate more sustainably. So far, however, expressing sustainability successes in monetary terms — in the balance sheet — has not been easy. Enter <strong>QuartaVista</strong>, an <a href="/2020/11/quartavista-accounting-sustainability">innovation project led by SAP</a> and funded by the German Federal Ministry of Labor and Social Affairs.</p>
  <p>“The idea behind QuartaVista is to measure corporate success not only in financial terms, but to integrate other dimensions in the balance sheet, such as ecology, knowledge, and society,” says Reiner Bildmayer, QuartaVista project manager at SAP.</p>
  <p>The project ran from November 2018 to February 2021 and recently presented its results at a closing event in Berlin.</p>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ac8432eb71d29c8a2195762030e7d9cf942f8eab.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ac8432eb71d29c8a2195762030e7d9cf942f8eab.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1ac8432eb71d29c8a2195762030e7d9cf942f8eab.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="QuartaVista – Four Perspectives" src="./media_1ac8432eb71d29c8a2195762030e7d9cf942f8eab.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://youtu.be/sc6zy8PGo6I">QuartaVista – Four Perspectives</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><em>Video by Angela Klose</em></p>
  <h2 id="pioneer-work">Pioneer Work</h2>
  <p>The QuartaVista methodology was jointly developed by SAP and Regionalwert AG, Freiburg, a citizen shareholder company that channels citizens’ money to build up regional sustainable enterprises. What’s new about QuartaVista is that sustainable business practices, as well as risks, are shown on the assets or the liabilities side of the balance sheet.</p>
  <p>The first prerequisite for this was to translate sustainability efforts into quantifiable metrics.</p>
  <p>“Within the project, we developed 180 sustainability KPIs, thus creating the basis to capture these values in the balance sheet,” explains Christian Hiss, founder and CEO of Regionalwert AG, Freiburg.</p>
  <p>One example is knowledge retention. According to the QuartaVista methodology, training new employees does not only incur costs to the company. Instead, the knowledge that is built up and retained can be booked as an asset in the balance sheet.</p>
  <p>The partners involved in the QuartaVista project were seed producer <a href="https://www.bingenheimersaatgut.de/de">Bingenheimer Saatgut</a>, <a href="https://www.bodan.de/">organic food wholesaler BODAN</a>, organic grain product manufacturer <a href="https://bohlsener-muehle.de/">Bohlsener Mühle</a>, and <a href="https://www.regionalwert-ag.de/">Regionalwert AG Freiburg</a>. They tested the methodology in practice. SAP’s role was to map the QuartaVista accounting approach to a dashboard. In addition, <a href="https://cognostics.com/">Cognostics</a>, an artificial intelligence-enhanced software specialist and the charitable research and teaching organization <a href="https://www.parmenides-foundation.org/">Parmenides Foundation</a> visualized the KPIs in a forecast tool.</p>
  <p>“QuartaVista has built a prototype that demonstrates how sustainability KPIs can be integrated in the accounting process and in corporate management as well,” says Annika Woltjen, QuartaVista project lead at BODAN.</p>
  <p>“We broke it down into the smallest details, which is what ultimately sets this project apart,” Bildmayer shares.</p>
  <p>Holistic corporate management involves combining financial and non-financial key figures, adds Martin Heinig, head of New Ventures and Technologies at SAP, at the event in Berlin. “You have to collect the data, make it assessable and comparable. In this respect, QuartaVista has taken a big step in the right direction.”</p>
  <h2 id="true-prices">True Prices</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-more-accounting-for-sustainability-with-quartavista">Read more: Accounting for Sustainability with QuartaVista</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2020/11/quartavista-accounting-sustainability">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>One example of how QuartaVista might play out in practice is prices.</p>
  <p>“QuartaVista gives us the opportunity to reach true prices,” stresses Philip Luthardt, sustainability manager at Bohlsener Muehle. “It is a chance for producers of organic products to show how much value we add to society as a whole.”</p>
  <p>Isabelle Sanchez, commercial manager at Bingenheimer Saatgut, believes that price transparency helps to drive customer acceptance: “When we explain the values we are creating and what goes into the product, then consumers are more likely to agree.” As an example, she cites organically created seedfast varieties, whose seeds spawn the same plants repeatedly. This saves consumers from having to buy new seeds in the following year.</p>
  <p>“What is cheap today is expensive tomorrow,” explains Jenny Lay-Kumar, QuartaVista project lead at Regionalwert AG, Freiburg. “Adding risks and damage to the balance sheet, as well as crediting efforts toward sustainability, means much more than just making products more expensive. It means realigning the market economy based on a new way of measuring success.”</p>
  <p>QuartaVista does not necessarily mean making organically produced products more expensive. “Sustainable management is an investment that is capitalized as an asset in the balance sheet. If QuartaVista is implemented, I can achieve completely different prices,” Hiss concludes.</p>
  <h2 id="experimentation-and-thinking-space">Experimentation and Thinking Space</h2>
  <p>Even though the project has now officially concluded, it is not the end of the line, but rather a starting point. The partners are determined to drive their methodology forward in collaboration with businesses, academia, and politicians. A lot of work remains to be done; the project was set up as an experimentation and thinking space.</p>
  <p>“We have a tool with which we can practice thinking. We can do something and see the results of our actions. This is the beginning of a larger change, not only in finance,” Professor Karin Graeslund from the Wiesbaden Business School and German-speaking SAP User Group DSAG, said at the closing event.</p>
  <p>“We opened up a wealth of potential with QuartaVista. We are determined to continue,” Bildmayer emphasizes.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>“QuartaVista – Navigation system for value orientated companies” is one of 17 projects initiated by the “New Quality of Work Initiative”, with interdisciplinary experimental spaces funded by the German Federal Ministry of Labor and Social Affairs. Term: November 2018 – February 2021.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/un-sdgs</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Accelerates Climate Protection to Achieve Carbon-Neutrality by 2023]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/03/sap-carbon-neutrality-goal-2023</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/03/sap-carbon-neutrality-goal-2023</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP has announced its intention to achieve carbon-neutrality by the end of 2023, two years earlier than previously stated.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_19d36522df6973ef89439b8c7028f4f5c82fbe843.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_19d36522df6973ef89439b8c7028f4f5c82fbe843.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_19d36522df6973ef89439b8c7028f4f5c82fbe843.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Accelerates Climate Protection to Achieve Carbon-Neutrality by 2023" src="./media_19d36522df6973ef89439b8c7028f4f5c82fbe843.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-accelerates-climate-protection-to-achieve-carbon-neutrality-by-2023">SAP Accelerates Climate Protection to Achieve Carbon-Neutrality by 2023</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-the-2020-sap-integrated-report">Read the 2020 SAP Integrated Report</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="http://www.sapintegratedreport.com/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced its intention to become carbon-neutral in its own operations by the end of 2023 – two years earlier than previously stated. This announcement coincided with the publication of <a href="http://www.sapintegratedreport.com/">SAP’s Integrated Report 2020</a>.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Last year, the company reduced its greenhouse gas (GHG) emissions more than planned, mainly due to changes in the way its 100,000 employees across the world worked and traveled during the <a href="/covid-19">COVID-19</a> pandemic.</p>
  <p>A sharp decline in business flights contributed significantly to SAP’s reduced carbon footprint in 2020. With employees working predominantly from home, carbon emissions caused by the daily commute and the operation of office buildings fell. As a result, SAP was able to overachieve by 43% on its target for reducing net carbon emissions in 2020, generating 135 kilotons (kt) instead of the anticipated 238 kt. By way of comparison, SAP’s emissions in 2019 were 300 kt. By accelerating faster toward carbon-neutral operations, SAP anticipates the current development and underscores its role as a front-runner in climate protection.</p>
  <p>In striving to become carbon-neutral, SAP takes into account all of its direct and indirect emissions, as well as selected emissions arising in the supply chain, including those linked to business flights, business travel in rental cars and third-party data centers. The company uses the approach of first avoiding, second reducing and third compensating emissions. Whenever possible, SAP aims to avoid the creation of GHGs through a variety of business practices, such as using telecommunication technologies rather than traveling. If emissions cannot be avoided, SAP leverages innovations, such as energy-efficient lighting in offices, efficient cooling systems in data centers and alternative mobility solutions. Lastly, SAP offsets unavoidable emissions by supporting climate projects and working with partners who meet the gold standard advanced by <a href="https://www.goldstandard.org/">The Gold Standard Foundation</a> or equivalent quality standards. In addition, SAP continuously drives new corporate initiatives, such as putting an internal carbon price on business flights.</p>
  <p>Since 2017, SAP has also been pursuing a <a href="/2019/07/sap-emissions-reduction-targets">science-based climate target</a> certified by the Science Based Targets initiative (SBTi) to make its own contribution to limiting global warming to 1.5°C above preindustrial levels. While its zero-carbon goal applies chiefly to its own operations, SAP’s science-based climate target also encompasses the upstream and downstream value chain. SAP has been using 100% renewable energy to power all of its data centers since 2014. Thanks to its <a href="/2014/03/sap-greens-its-cloud-will-power-data-centers-and-facilities-with-100-percent-renewable-electricity-in-2014">green cloud</a>, SAP can offer customers cloud solutions that are carbon-neutral.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP supports the <a href="http://www.sap.com/unglobalgoals">Sustainable Development Goals</a> set in 2015 by the United Nations General Assembly, focusing particularly on goal 13, Climate Action. Here, SAP’s greatest strength lies in its ability to help its more than 400,000 customers worldwide implement climate protection measures through offerings such as the <a href="/2020/06/launch-sap-carbon-product-carbon-footprint-analytics">Climate 21</a> program. Together with customers and partners, SAP will provide more information on solutions in this context as well as on the circular economy, holistic steering and reporting at the virtual <a href="https://events.sap.com/sap-sustainability-summit/en/home">SAP Sustainability Summit</a> taking place on April 28–29, 2021.</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="http://news.sap.com/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP on Twitter at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Media Contact:</strong> Bettina Wunderle, +49 7544 970538, <a href="mailto:bettina.wunderle@sap.com">bettina.wunderle@sap.com</a>, CET<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>Any statements contained in this document that are not historical facts are forward-looking statements as defined in the U.S. Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995. Words such as “anticipate,” “believe,” “estimate,” “expect,” “forecast,” “intend,” “may,” “plan,” “project,” “predict,” “should” and “will” and similar expressions as they relate to SAP are intended to identify such forward-looking statements. SAP undertakes no obligation to publicly update or revise any forward-looking statements. All forward-looking statements are subject to various risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results to differ materially from expectations. The factors that could affect SAP’s future financial results are discussed more fully in SAP’s filings with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (“SEC”), including SAP’s most recent Annual Report on Form 20-F filed with the SEC. Readers are cautioned not to place undue reliance on these forward-looking statements, which speak only as of their dates.<br>© 2021 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-neutrality</category>
            <category>news-tag/un-sdgs</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[New Program to Accelerate Business Action on the Sustainable Development Goals Starts with 600 Companies in 65 Countries]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/sdg-ambition-accelerator-accelerate-business-action</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/sdg-ambition-accelerator-accelerate-business-action</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The UN Global Compact SDG Ambition Accelerator will drive business engagement on SDGs with support of Accenture, SAP, and 3M. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1aa5e6b20c52e6ff800ac3b2e14f9ec4a21956c84.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1aa5e6b20c52e6ff800ac3b2e14f9ec4a21956c84.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1aa5e6b20c52e6ff800ac3b2e14f9ec4a21956c84.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="New Program to Accelerate Business Action on the Sustainable Development Goals Starts with 600 Companies in 65 Countries" src="./media_1aa5e6b20c52e6ff800ac3b2e14f9ec4a21956c84.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="new-program-to-accelerate-business-action-on-the-sustainable-development-goals-starts-with-600-companies-in-65-countries">New Program to Accelerate Business Action on the Sustainable Development Goals Starts with 600 Companies in 65 Countries</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong><em>UNITED NATIONS, New York</em></strong> — A new program focused on accelerating business performance on the Sustainable Development Goals (<a href="/topics/un-sdgs">SDGs</a>) starts this week, engaging more than 600 companies in 65 countries with a combined annual revenue of US$1 trillion.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="explore-how-sap-supports-the-un-sdgs">Explore how SAP supports the UN SDGs</h3>
      </div>
      <div>
        <ul>
          <li><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/dmc/exp/2019-08-unglobalgoals/index.html">Learn more</a></strong></li>
        </ul>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="united-nations-global-compact-sdg-ambition-accelerator-will-drive-business-engagement-on-sdgs-in-companies-with-support-of-accenture-sap-and-3m">United Nations Global Compact SDG Ambition Accelerator will drive business engagement on SDGs in companies with support of Accenture, SAP and 3M.</h2>
  <p>First announced last year by UN Secretary-General António Guterres at the World Economic Forum in Davos, SDG Ambition Accelerator is an initiative that challenges and supports participating companies of the UN Global Compact in setting ambitious corporate sustainability targets and accelerating the integration of the SDGs into core business management.</p>
  <p>The SDG Ambition Accelerator Program is a six-month learning journey for corporate executives being delivered through UN Global Compact Networks based in 30 countries. More than 1,150 representatives from participating companies, employing 7.9 million people, will join to assess current performance, risk areas and new opportunities across their business. This will help companies take more ambitious business actions toward achieving the SDGs by 2030. Outcomes from the first round of the Accelerator will be presented at the annual UN Global Compact Leaders Summit on June 15–16, 2021.</p>
  <p>The SDG Ambition Accelerator challenges and supports companies to:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Strategically prioritize sustainability issues where they can have the greatest impact through their operations, products and services, and across the value chain</li>
    <li>Set ambitious goals and identify critical pathways to achieve them</li>
    <li>Integrate SDG-related business goals and outcomes into core business management processes</li>
    <li>Design technology systems to track progress on the goals across business units or functions</li>
  </ul>
  <p><strong>Sanda Ojiambo, CEO and Executive Director of UN Global Compact,</strong> said: “By engaging hundreds of companies of all sizes and sectors from around the world, the UN Global Compact SDG Ambition Accelerator is working to mobilize a truly global movement of responsible enterprises to accelerate progress toward embedding sustainability into core business strategies and operations—not only for the benefit of society but for their own benefit as well.”</p>
  <p><a href="https://www.accenture.com/us-en/insights/strategy/ungcceostudy">Research</a> from Accenture Strategy and the UN Global Compact shows that despite private sector progress on the SDGs, only 21% of CEOs felt that business was playing a critical role in contributing toward the SDGs. Similarly, according to the <a href="https://www.unglobalcompact.org/library/5747#:~:text=(2020)-,UN%20Global%20Compact%2020th%2DAnniversary%20Progress%20Report%3A%20Uniting%20Business,in%20the%20Decade%20of%20Action&#x26;text=Broadly%2C%20the%20report%20finds%20that,create%20the%20world%20we%20want.">UN Global Compact’s annual Progress Report</a>, only 39% of companies believed they had targets ambitious enough to fully meet the SDGs.</p>
  <p><strong>Julie Sweet, CEO of Accenture</strong>, said: “As we face the urgent challenges of rebuilding the global economy and tackling climate change, this is the moment for every business to take bold action and become a sustainable business with their customers and across their enterprises and supply chains. The SDG Ambition Accelerator will help companies embed sustainability into their core at greater speed and scale to make meaningful, measurable progress toward achieving the SDGs.”</p>
  <p><strong>Christian Klein, CEO of SAP,</strong> said: “In the future, profitability and sustainability will go hand in hand, with the latter becoming a dimension of corporate decision-making just like cost or growth. By combining our areas of expertise, we help businesses around the world to establish the foundational infrastructure they need to measure and actively steer their progress toward achieving the SDGs.”</p>
  <p><strong>Michael Roman, Chairman and CEO of 3M,</strong> said: “The COVID-19 pandemic has deeply impacted all of our lives and underscored the critical role that science and the business community have in solving global challenges. 3M is pleased to partner with the United Nations and other leading organizations to build a collaborative approach to improving lives around the world. We hope the SDG Ambition Accelerator will inspire other companies to join us in working to make this a Decade of Action.”</p>
  <p>More information on the SDG Ambition Accelerator <a href="https://unglobalcompact.org/take-action/sdg-ambition">can be found here</a>.</p>
  <h2 id="notes-to-editors">Notes to Editors:</h2>
  <p><strong>About the United Nations Global Compact</strong></p>
  <p>As a special initiative of the UN Secretary-General, the United Nations Global Compact is a call to companies everywhere to align their operations and strategies with Ten Principles in the areas of human rights, labour, environment and anti-corruption. Our ambition is to accelerate and scale the global collective impact of business by upholding the Ten Principles and delivering the Sustainable Development Goals through accountable companies and ecosystems that enable change. With more than 12,000 companies and 3,000 non-business signatories based in over 160 countries, and 69 Local Networks, the UN Global Compact is the world’s largest corporate sustainability initiative — one Global Compact uniting business for a better world.</p>
  <p>For more information, follow <a href="http://www.twitter.com/globalcompact">@globalcompact</a> on social media and visit our website at <a href="http://unglobalcompact.org/">unglobalcompact.org</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>About Accenture</strong></p>
  <p>Accenture is a global professional services company with leading capabilities in digital, cloud and security. Combining unmatched experience and specialized skills across more than 40 industries, we offer Strategy and Consulting, Interactive, Technology and Operations services — all powered by the world’s largest network of Advanced Technology and Intelligent Operations centers. Our 514,000 people deliver on the promise of technology and human ingenuity every day, serving clients in more than 120 countries. We embrace the power of change to create value and shared success for our clients, people, shareholders, partners and communities. Visit us at <a href="http://www.accenture.com">www.accenture.com</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>About SAP</strong></p>
  <p>As a market leader in enterprise application software, SAP helps companies of all sizes and in all industries run at their best. Our machine learning, Internet of Things (IoT) and advanced analytics technologies turn businesses into intelligent enterprises and SAP applications and services enable business and public customers across 25 industries globally to operate profitably and adapt continuously. With a global network of customers, partners, employees and thought leaders, SAP helps the world run better and improve people’s lives. For more information, visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/">www.sap.com</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>About 3M</strong></p>
  <p>At 3M, we apply science in collaborative ways to improve lives daily as our employees connect with customers all around the world. Learn more about 3M’s creative solutions to global challenges at <a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&#x26;l=en&#x26;o=3035350-1&#x26;h=3473145368&#x26;u=https%3A%2F%2Fc212.net%2Fc%2Flink%2F%3Ft%3D0%26l%3Den%26o%3D3011299-1%26h%3D1746104322%26u%3Dhttp%253A%252F%252Fwww.3m.com%252F%26a%3Dwww.3M.com&#x26;a=www.3M.com">www.3M.com</a> or on Twitter <a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&#x26;l=en&#x26;o=3035350-1&#x26;h=657146043&#x26;u=https%3A%2F%2Fc212.net%2Fc%2Flink%2F%3Ft%3D0%26l%3Den%26o%3D3011299-1%26h%3D3077527875%26u%3Dhttps%253A%252F%252Ftwitter.com%252F3M%26a%3D%25403M&#x26;a=%403M">@3M</a> or <a href="https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&#x26;l=en&#x26;o=3035350-1&#x26;h=2148209928&#x26;u=https%3A%2F%2Fc212.net%2Fc%2Flink%2F%3Ft%3D0%26l%3Den%26o%3D3011299-1%26h%3D2291369930%26u%3Dhttps%253A%252F%252Ftwitter.com%252F3MNews%26a%3D%25403MNews&#x26;a=%403MNews">@3MNews</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Contacts:</strong> Alex Gee, UN Global Compact, <a href="mailto:ex@mackworthassociates.com">ex@mackworthassociates.com</a>, <a href="mailto:media@unglobalcompact.org">media@unglobalcompact.org</a><br>Julie Bennink, Accenture, +1 (312) 693-7301, <a href="mailto:julie.l.bennink@accenture.com">julie.l.bennink@accenture.com</a><br>Susan Miller, SAP, +1 (610) 661-9225, <a href="mailto:susan.miller@sap.com">susan.miller@sap.com</a><br>Lauren Cox, 3M, +1 (612) 403-7112, <a href="mailto:lcox@mmm.com">lcox@mmm.com</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/un-sdgs</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Corporate Champions for Education: A Perspective from the Field]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/videos/corporate-champions-for-education-a-perspective-from-the-field</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/videos/corporate-champions-for-education-a-perspective-from-the-field</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Corporate Champions for Education is a multi-company pro bono program led by SAP and PYXERA Global to support digital inclusion. The program sent a cohort...]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1cb21bf8327bb3baef82d3c26d48dedc3278661df.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1cb21bf8327bb3baef82d3c26d48dedc3278661df.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1cb21bf8327bb3baef82d3c26d48dedc3278661df.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_1cb21bf8327bb3baef82d3c26d48dedc3278661df.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="640" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="corporate-champions-for-education-a-perspective-from-the-field">Corporate Champions for Education: A Perspective from the Field</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1cb21bf8327bb3baef82d3c26d48dedc3278661df.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1cb21bf8327bb3baef82d3c26d48dedc3278661df.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1cb21bf8327bb3baef82d3c26d48dedc3278661df.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_1cb21bf8327bb3baef82d3c26d48dedc3278661df.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="640" height="360">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PdmTWzIHhTU">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PdmTWzIHhTU</a></p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Corporate Champions for Education is a multi-company pro bono program led by SAP and PYXERA Global to support digital inclusion.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The program sent a cohort with team members from SAP, WE Communications and Niagara Bottling to Bogota, Colombia, to work with local not-for-profits in advancing their educational mission. This video provides one team member’s perspective from the field.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/video</category>
            <category>news-tag/pyxera-global</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/un-sdgs</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>