<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/sap-hana/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[CallidusCloud to SAP: Evolution to Running Better Smarter and Faster]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/calliduscloud-to-sap-evolution</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/calliduscloud-to-sap-evolution</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is excited to help CallidusCloud customers make the strategic move to the SAP SuccessFactors portfolio. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sales-performance-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-hana</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[VMware Builds Trust Through a Positive Seller Experience]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/06/vmware-builds-trust-positive-seller-experience</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/06/vmware-builds-trust-positive-seller-experience</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[VMware embarked on an initiative to modernize its incentive compensation management tools and processes, implementing SAP Commissions.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_19b84561a38e1a51128d381b67642d6fa28a050bb.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_19b84561a38e1a51128d381b67642d6fa28a050bb.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_19b84561a38e1a51128d381b67642d6fa28a050bb.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="VMware Builds Trust Through a Positive Seller Experience" src="./media_19b84561a38e1a51128d381b67642d6fa28a050bb.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="vmware-builds-trust-through-a-positive-seller-experience">VMware Builds Trust Through a Positive Seller Experience</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>VMware, a software giant founded in 1998, has significantly influenced the information technology market, offering businesses both large and small a vast array of virtualization, networking, storage, security, and digital workplace products and services. One of the driving forces behind VMware’s mission to help customers accelerate innovation is <a href="/topics/sales-performance-management">its sales team</a>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>With several acquisitions in recent years, the number of sellers at VMware dramatically increased. Yet the company did not have a reliable means of paying everyone accurately and on time. The company knew it needed to improve the experience for its sellers to maximize business performance.</p>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18ac25bf39ae42c1c7459ea8b6011f799304db41b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18ac25bf39ae42c1c7459ea8b6011f799304db41b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_18ac25bf39ae42c1c7459ea8b6011f799304db41b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="VMware Drives Winning Sellers Experiences in the Cloud" src="./media_18ac25bf39ae42c1c7459ea8b6011f799304db41b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://youtu.be/5ie1lpncmtA">VMware Drives Winning Sellers Experiences in the Cloud</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="the-burden-of-legacy-tools">The Burden of Legacy Tools</h2>
  <p>For years VMware had been burdened by legacy tools that not only impacted seller productivity but also caused significant inefficiencies when it came to business operations. Reporting capabilities were limited and the company couldn’t support payouts for multiple metrics, which was problematic as the company transitioned to a model of both license and subscription sales.</p>
  <p>In addition, introducing new plans or emphasizing specific products or geographies was highly manual, requiring significant time and effort. This impacted VMware’s ability to adapt to business needs quickly enough to remain competitive.</p>
  <h2 id="the-companys-transformation-journey">The Company’s Transformation Journey</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="motivate-sales-shape-behavior-and-increase-revenue-with-sap-commissions">Motivate sales, shape behavior, and increase revenue with SAP Commissions</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/commissions.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>VMware embarked on an initiative to modernize its incentive compensation management tools and processes, implementing <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/commissions.html">SAP Commissions</a>.</p>
  <p>The decision to implement SAP Commissions at VMware was based on many factors, namely the need to improve payment accuracy, gain more sophisticated reporting capabilities, and strengthen auditing capabilities.</p>
  <p>Leaders at VMware across HR, sales ops, finance, and IT agreed that what the company required was a system that was both flexible and scalable – one that was purpose-built to handle change and provided the kind of transparency that the company’s 9,000 sellers would love.</p>
  <p>According to Anushree Kalra, director, IT Engineering at VMware, “We used to have more than 700 compensation plans that were very difficult to manage at scale. Our goal with the modernization project was to reduce the number of comp plans to less than 50 and make it easy to change plans or add new ones. That’s exactly what we did.”</p>
  <p>The company successfully implemented SAP Commissions in nine months, ahead of the proposed one-and-a-half-year plan, which included the switch from Oracle to SAP HANA.</p>
  <h2 id="realizing-the-benefits-of-a-modern-tool">Realizing the Benefits of a Modern Tool</h2>
  <p>According to Kalra, VMware now has a streamlined incentive compensation management process complimented by a system that’s capable of accommodating various compensation plans and multiple metrics for commissions. The company now changes plans every six months and can adapt to market conditions much more quickly.</p>
  <p>“Best of all, with SAP Commissions we have a tool that allows us to pay our sellers accurately and on time,” said Kalra. “In fact, the time required for commission calculations and the time for processing commissions for VMware has been reduced from several days to a few hours.”</p>
  <p>This is due in large part to workflows and approvals that were made much easier with SAP Commissions. Now VMware can confidently process commissions at scale even as the dynamics of its sales organization change.</p>
  <p>The benefits of more robust reporting capabilities have also been significant. The solution helps provide personalized dashboards, allowing sellers to access the information they need – how, when, and where they want. This means VMware can load plans for sellers and instantly provide them visibility into their commissions. The company says this has helped to build trust among sellers, which has had a direct impact on satisfaction and retention.</p>
  <p>With better operational reporting, the company is also more efficient, according to Kalra. Now, finance has what it needs for forecasting and setting quotas, for example.</p>
  <p>Looking forward, Kalra says the team at VMware is excited about having a tool that helps to provide strategic direction for the enterprise. It’s another way VMware is leveraging technology advancements to accelerate business growth and success.</p>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/commissions.html">Learn more about the SAP Commissions solution.</a></div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>Lara Albert is global vice president for Solution Marketing at SAP SuccessFactors.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/sales-performance-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-hana</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How an Entire Region Is Benefiting from a Brazilian NGO’s Firefighting Efforts]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/brigada-carcara-brazilian-ngo-firefighting-efforts</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/brigada-carcara-brazilian-ngo-firefighting-efforts</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A geo-referencing, image recording, and real-time data platform from SAP helps Brigada Carcará fight fires, rescue bees, and plant trees.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-extreme-series</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-hana</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ITZBund and SAP Bring AI to German Federal Agencies]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/06/itzbund-sap-bring-ai-to-german-federal-agencies</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/06/itzbund-sap-bring-ai-to-german-federal-agencies</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The ITZBund and SAP joined forces to accelerate the digital transformation of the German Federal Office of Administration with an AI platform.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>product/sap-data-intelligence</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-hana</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Take: Data Analysis Makes Your Game—and Your Bridge—Better]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/01/the-take-data-analysis-sports-enertainment-infrastructure</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/01/the-take-data-analysis-sports-enertainment-infrastructure</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With sensors being applied across many industry now, data analysis can make your game—and your bridge—better. Get SAP's take.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_131275ae7e1d01a8ede65a430c2f3c9bcd78386bf.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_131275ae7e1d01a8ede65a430c2f3c9bcd78386bf.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_131275ae7e1d01a8ede65a430c2f3c9bcd78386bf.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="The Take: Data Analysis Makes Your Game—and Your Bridge—Better" src="./media_131275ae7e1d01a8ede65a430c2f3c9bcd78386bf.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="the-take-data-analysis-makes-your-gameand-your-bridgebetter">The Take: Data Analysis Makes Your Game—and Your Bridge—Better</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>What’s News</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>From “Jeopardy!” to hockey to infrastructure and supply chain, the sheer volume of data created each day has endless possibilities to help improve our lives.</p>
  <p>Nearly 10 years ago, sports fans began feasting on new types of statistics made possible by SAP HANA, an in-memory database, which could serve up those numbers in real time. The lightning-fast technology could scale to accommodate the millions of sports fans without crashing websites disappointing them.</p>
  <p>In more recent years, the methods for collecting data have grown to include RFID tags, sensors, and photos. Today, <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/07/60b94918-f27d-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">hockey stats</a> are collected by sensors embedded in hockey pucks that can travel more than 100 mph and on player jerseys.</p>
  <p>“We are now able to give fans a near-real-time experience, meaning under two seconds,” said Daniel Beringer, SAP global head of technology for global sponsorships.</p>
  <p>Even the iconic U.S. television game show “Jeopardy!” is using similar technology to provide game stats that track how fast contestants click their hand buzzers, according to the Wall Street Journal.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-hana-advanced-analytics-on-multimodel-data-on-premise-and-in-the-cloud">SAP HANA: Advanced analytics on multimodel data, on premise and in the cloud</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hana.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="saps-take">SAP’s Take</h2>
  <p>But entertainment is just the tip of the data iceberg.</p>
  <p>“Sensors are being applied in pretty much every industry right now, some more and some less, and all that data has to be processed, it has to be taken care of,” Beringer said.</p>
  <p>In supply chain management, sensors can be attached to goods to produce immediate feedback on their movements. Consumers use this common technology to track their packages, but more sophisticated version can be used to track movements, manufacturing inputs and finished products.</p>
  <p>“That’s obviously not the same speed as a hockey puck,” he said. “But it goes in the same direction. There you could obviously take all that data in the supply chain and try to find optimization potential or just simply statistics, measuring the whole supply chain in a much, much better way.”</p>
  <p>In April 2021, data from sensors installed on a bridge in Norway alerted engineers of unusual movement from vibrations emanating from the nearly 80-year-old Stavå Bridge. Like so many older bridges worldwide, the concrete arch bridge was built for less than half the traffic volume and loads it now experiences. Thanks to the sensors, engineers were able to safely shut down the bridge and start repairs before a catastrophic failure occurred.</p>
  <p>Sensors can collect and monitor data — including temperature, traffic, material and weather — that infrastructure is subjected to and additional technology can be used to analyze it and predict problems or maintenance requirements.</p>
  <p>“Any anomalies can trigger a warning that a failure or even a catastrophic failure may be imminent,” Beringer said. “If you see it early enough, then you can better prioritize which bridge you repair or replace first and which ones have a longer lifespan.”</p>
  <p><a href="/2019/09/runway-by-sap-returns-nyfw-badgley-mischka">Fashion</a> and pharmaceuticals also are using similar technology to find out what dress will sell or where drugs are being shipped. The potential uses are as endless.</p>
  <p>“It’s like a Pandora’s box,” he said. “You open it, and then you don’t know where you really end up.”</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Contact:</strong> Joellen Perry, Head of <a href="/press-room">Global Public Relations</a>, SAP<br>+1 (626) 265-0370, <a href="mailto:joellen.perry@sap.com">joellen.perry@sap.com</a>, PST</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/perspective</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-hana</category>
            <category>news-tag/the-take</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Innovation Challenge: How to Make the Extraordinary Happen]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/innovation-challenge-make-extraordinary-happen</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/innovation-challenge-make-extraordinary-happen</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Innovation is immensely powerful when driving transformative change. SAP Innovation Awards celebrate those that've taken this lesson to heart.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_178431ff0f2c3efa5a2c191ea2f1455f4a21ff21a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_178431ff0f2c3efa5a2c191ea2f1455f4a21ff21a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_178431ff0f2c3efa5a2c191ea2f1455f4a21ff21a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="The Innovation Challenge: How to Make the Extraordinary Happen" src="./media_178431ff0f2c3efa5a2c191ea2f1455f4a21ff21a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="the-innovation-challenge-how-to-make-the-extraordinary-happen">The Innovation Challenge: How to Make the Extraordinary Happen</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>One of the most important lessons of the last two years has been the power of innovation when driving genuinely transformative change. With SAP Innovation Awards, we celebrate individuals and organizations that have taken this lesson to heart with a mix of ingenuity, SAP technology, and the support of knowledgeable experts.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Innovations are always top of mind for companies – especially SAP customers. But you won’t find them musing future-minded technology trends such as quantum computing, neural interfaces, or nanotechnology. Instead, they are accomplishing extraordinary feats and delivering meaningful outcomes with existing technology and expertise.</p>
  <p>Certainly, every business has a story of exceptional innovation to tell. And I am proud to share those of our customers – some of which were recognized by <a href="https://www.sap.com/idea-place/sap-innovation-awards.html">SAP Innovation Awards</a> in 2021 for making the world better with assistance from SAP Services and Support offerings.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-sap-innovation-awards">Learn more about SAP Innovation Awards</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/idea-place/sap-innovation-awards.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="enhancing-scale-and-performance-for-heavy-data-workloads">Enhancing Scale and Performance for Heavy Data Workloads</h2>
  <p>When under pressure to meet regulatory requirements, deliver higher margins, and improve customer experiences, companies must improve how they manage increasing volumes of data. But all too often, the limitation of an on-premise landscape does not allow the flexibility, agility, speed, and cost-effectiveness to meet that challenge.</p>
  <p>For one of the SAP Innovation Award winners, the answer was found in a proof of concept created through a joint effort between SAP and Google Cloud. <a href="https://www.sap.com/idea-place/sap-innovation-awards/submission-details-2021.html?idea_id=2376">PayPal Holdings</a> (PayPal), which adopted Google Cloud as its core IT partner, chose a combination of Google Cloud and SAP S/4HANA for financial products subledger on a 96 TB scale-out configuration of SAP HANA. The innovation leveraged Google Cloud’s expertise in building scalable, distributed systems and SAP’s relentless focus on delivering mission-critical business process automation.</p>
  <p>Bringing the best of SAP and Google Cloud engineering together, PayPal can benefit from groundbreaking capabilities with higher performance, lower costs, and more flexibility. The technology platform company now runs one of the world’s largest scale-out clusters of SAP HANA. And in return, it accelerated query runtime by 40 times through parallelization, reduced its memory footprint by 78% with dynamic data-tiering techniques, and experienced 24 weeks of continuous operations with zero downtime.</p>
  <h2 id="achieving-health-goals-through-process-standardization">Achieving Health Goals Through Process Standardization</h2>
  <p>During <a href="/covid-19">the COVID-19 pandemic</a>, businesses were concerned with maintaining operational continuity and keeping pace with demand while ensuring a safe and healthy environment for their workforce. However, as one of our award finalists discovered, a complex IT infrastructure involving multiple disparate enterprise resource planning (ERP) systems prevented the ability to run as quickly as possible.</p>
  <p>The European division of <a href="https://www.sap.com/idea-place/sap-innovation-awards/submission-details-2021.html?idea_id=2471">American Air Filter Company</a> addressed this issue by deploying cloud-based solutions to standardize processes and support localization requirements for different countries. With <a href="https://www.sap.com/services/support-plans/preferred-success-cloud.html">SAP Preferred Success</a>, <a href="https://www.sap.com/services/implementation/implementation-pkg.html">SAP Value Assurance</a>, and SAP development experts, the division consolidated 13 ERP systems into a single instance of SAP S/4HANA Cloud and gained the agility to achieve meaningful change.</p>
  <p>American Air Filter Company harmonized processes and gained a single view of the truth, providing more transparent and streamlined operations across all business areas. Additionally, its simplified IT infrastructure costs less to maintain and enables the business to take advantage of intelligent technologies to innovate new offerings.</p>
  <h2 id="setting-new-standards-with-embedded-analytics">Setting New Standards with Embedded Analytics</h2>
  <p>Every organization reaches a point where homegrown, mainframe-based business information systems must be replaced to enhance decision-making and enable higher standards for data governance, quality, and security. But the first step is not necessarily ripping out the legacy technology and implementing a completely new architecture, which in most cases can become too operationally disruptive and costly.</p>
  <p>For 2021 finalist <a href="https://www.sap.com/idea-place/sap-innovation-awards/submission-details-2021.html?idea_id=2036">Pennsylvania State University</a> (Penn State), expert guidance from SAP Enterprise Support services was needed to help upskill its IT team and pave the way for cutting-edge embedded analytics. The university worked with <a href="https://support.sap.com/en/offerings-programs/enterprise-support/enterprise-support-advisory-council.html">SAP Enterprise Support Advisory Council</a> to build a strong foundation in analytics, including through remote, recorded individual and group webinars, to support its digital transformation journey.</p>
  <p>Penn State relied on the <a href="https://support.sap.com/en/offerings-programs/enterprise-support/enterprise-support-academy/value-maps.html">SAP Enterprise Support value maps</a> for SAP Analytics solutions to help close any digital skills gaps. The organization engaged with experts, posting questions in value map forums and arranging collaborative sessions with peers. Plus, it used the <a href="https://cal.sap.com/">SAP Cloud Appliance Library</a> tool to help demonstrate and trial innovative data analytics and reporting tools, conduct scoping and sandboxing exercises, and create a proof of concept.</p>
  <p>Relating training material to workflows and real project scenarios enabled Penn State’s employees to apply knowledge more readily and apply feedback as they adopted SAP S/4HANA embedded analytics. And with access to experts who truly understand its challenges, Penn State’s administration staff now has the necessary skills to adapt and run embedded analytics, which will influence how it runs the university.</p>
  <h2 id="transforming-for-agility-speed-and-success">Transforming for Agility, Speed, and Success</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="discover-how-sap-can-help-enable-your-outcome-driven-business-imperatives">Discover how SAP can help enable your outcome-driven business imperatives</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/services/premium-engagement.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>During any significant organizational change such as a merger, acquisition, or spin-off, most companies find that their legacy landscape is too complex, lacking in technical depth, redundant, or costly to maintain. Another finalist, <a href="https://www.sap.com/idea-place/sap-innovation-awards/submission-details-2021.html?idea_id=2145">Hewlett Packard Enterprise</a> (HPE), is no stranger to this challenge.</p>
  <p>When HPE’s parent company, the Hewlett-Packard Company, spun off in 2015, the business needed to simplify applications and processes enterprise-wide to fulfill the world’s growing need for cloud services and intelligent technology. HPE implemented a wide variety of solutions and services to create a solid foundation for the business and enhance IT with powerful next-generation technologies. The <a href="https://www.sap.com/services/premium-engagement/maxattention.html?sort=latest_desc">SAP MaxAttention</a> program provided the guidance necessary to help validate, plan, execute, and test the design of its infrastructure.</p>
  <p>As a result of its efforts with SAP, HPE reduced recommitments to orders after removing the legacy processes that had resulted in rescheduled jobs. The company improved on-time delivery by focusing on its partners and helping them improve their shipping performance. Today, 99.5% of HPE’s customer orders are delivered on time, up from 90% in the past.</p>
  <h2 id="trailblazing-the-future-with-innovation">Trailblazing the Future with Innovation</h2>
  <p>All these stories are exceptional examples of how SAP customers are shaping their innovation effort to trailblaze a future of ongoing productivity and growth. And I am proud that my experts, who support SAP Services and Support offerings, are playing a key role in our customers’ success.</p>
  <p>Throughout the year, I hear our customers express their gratitude to my team of experts for helping them realize their potential as intelligent enterprises. Recently, I read a quote from SAP Innovation Award finalist <a href="https://www.sap.com/idea-place/sap-innovation-awards/submission-details-2021.html?idea_id=2118">Delivery Hero</a> that I think best sums up the best of what we offer.</p>
  <p>“Thanks to guidance from SAP Services and Support and the Intelligent Enterprise Institute, we better understand the dependency of customer experience on our delivery processes,” said Sebastian McClintock, global director of Customer Experience at Delivery Hero. “Leveraging SAP S/4HANA, Experience Management solutions from SAP and Qualtrics, and machine learning models, we now know how to improve data flows and best use our data to meet customers’ needs.”</p>
  <h2 id="do-you-have-a-story-to-tell">Do You Have a Story to Tell?</h2>
  <p>Such change is hard work, and extraordinary results deserve to be told. That’s why we host SAP Innovation Awards every year. It allows us to celebrate organizations that are improving business processes, providing faster and more effective customer service, making a difference for current and future employees, and more.</p>
  <p>And we invite all of you – especially if you selected services and support from SAP as your partner or co-partner – to submit a nomination. The call for nominations to <a href="https://www.sap.com/idea-place/sap-innovation-awards.html">SAP Innovation Awards 2022</a> is open now, but only for a few more months. Share your story with us!</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Oliver Huschke is vice president and global head of Marketing and Communications for Services and Support at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-enterprise-support</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-hana</category>
            <category>sap-award/sap-innovation-awards</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-maxattention</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-preferred-success</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP HANA Named a Leader in “Multimodel Data Platforms” by Independent Research Firm]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/sap-hana-a-leader-multimodel-data-platforms</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/sap-hana-a-leader-multimodel-data-platforms</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is a Leader in “The Forrester Wave™: Multimodel Data Platforms, Q3 2021,” a report that analyzed SAP HANA. Get the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ba8832b9396a43ef35f521bcc608647c3423ebd9.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ba8832b9396a43ef35f521bcc608647c3423ebd9.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1ba8832b9396a43ef35f521bcc608647c3423ebd9.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP HANA Named a Leader in “Multimodel Data Platforms” by Independent Research Firm" src="./media_1ba8832b9396a43ef35f521bcc608647c3423ebd9.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-hana-named-a-leader-in-multimodel-data-platforms-by-independent-research-firm">SAP HANA Named a Leader in “Multimodel Data Platforms” by Independent Research Firm</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-multimodel-processing">Learn more about multimodel processing</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hana/features/multi-model.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced it has been positioned as a Leader in “The Forrester Wave™: Multimodel Data Platforms, Q3 2021.”</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Forrester Research Inc., a leading global research and advisory firm, researched, analyzed and scored 15 vendors and named SAP a Leader. The report analyzed <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hana.html">SAP HANA</a> and noted its “outstanding support for transactions, queries, analytics, and search across hybrid and multi-cloud environments….” The 26 scoring criteria employed by Forrester Research covered three categories: Current Offering, Strategy and Market Presence. SAP scored five out of five in 17 of the 26 evaluation criteria.</p>
  <p>The report states that SAP “leverages a mature in-memory platform to support any multimodel workload” and “has a solid vision that focuses on the distributed SAP HANA multimodel data platform for unified data and analytics for any cloud, supporting all data and all workloads and leveraging advanced AI/ML and self-service capabilities.”</p>
  <p>The Forrester report points out that “reference customers spoke highly about the performance, versatility, all-in-one integrated development environment, and platform flexibility.” The report vendor profile concludes that “SAP is a good fit for applications that need high-performance, low-latency access to multimodel data to support various workloads.”</p>
  <p>“As businesses continue evolving and adapting to market conditions, they are benefiting from SAP HANA and SAP HANA Cloud by harnessing its multimodel data types within a single database platform, helping guide their future to more predictable outcomes,” said SAP HANA Database &#x26; Analytics President Irfan Khan. “We believe Forrester’s recognition of SAP as a Leader in this evaluation is testament to our robust data solutions and the benefit we bring to our customers.”</p>
  <p>An integral part of <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">SAP Business Technology Platform</a>, SAP HANA and SAP HANA Cloud allow businesses to leverage SAP’s single, unified multimodel database that stores, processes and analyzes geospatial, graph, JavaScript Object Notation (JSON) documents and more data types into one solution. Customers can access real-time advanced analytics and gain situational awareness by analyzing data in context, so they have the opportunity to respond to critical situations faster.</p>
  <p>Learn more about <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hana/features/multi-model.html">smart multimodel processing in SAP HANA</a> and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hana/cloud.html">SAP HANA Cloud</a>. To learn more about SAP’s ranking, <a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/dg/forresterwave-mmdp/index.html">read the full report here</a> and <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/pulse/sap-hana-leader-according-forrester-multimodel-data-platforms-khan/?trackingId=F5ktixHJRDWRyLef5Q4LlA%3D%3D">executive blog here</a>.</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="http://news.sap.com/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP on Twitter at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Media Contacts:</strong> Scott Malinowski, +1 (617) 538-6297, <a href="mailto:scott.malinowski@sap.com">scott.malinowski@sap.com</a> ET<br>Julia Fargel, +1 (650) 276-8964, <a href="mailto:julia.fargel@sap.com">julia.fargel@sap.com</a>, PT<br><a href="mailto:SAP%20Press%20Room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>Any statements contained in this document that are not historical facts are forward-looking statements as defined in the U.S. Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995. Words such as “anticipate,” “believe,” “estimate,” “expect,” “forecast,” “intend,” “may,” “plan,” “project,” “predict,” “should” and “will” and similar expressions as they relate to SAP are intended to identify such forward-looking statements. SAP undertakes no obligation to publicly update or revise any forward-looking statements. All forward-looking statements are subject to various risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results to differ materially from expectations. The factors that could affect SAP’s future financial results are discussed more fully in SAP’s filings with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (“SEC”), including SAP’s most recent Annual Report on Form 20-F filed with the SEC. Readers are cautioned not to place undue reliance on these forward-looking statements, which speak only as of their dates.<br>© 2021 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>news-tag/forrester</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-hana</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Vodafone Is Changing the World of Telecommunications from the Inside Out]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/05/vodafone-group-telecommunications-sap-solutions</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/05/vodafone-group-telecommunications-sap-solutions</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 May 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Vodafone Group created a single digital core for the entire business based on SAP S4/HANA to gain greater consistency everywhere it operates.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16822df66158e2206f5da710120b1243898efd0bf.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16822df66158e2206f5da710120b1243898efd0bf.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_16822df66158e2206f5da710120b1243898efd0bf.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="How Vodafone Is Changing the World of Telecommunications from the Inside Out" src="./media_16822df66158e2206f5da710120b1243898efd0bf.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="how-vodafone-is-changing-the-world-of-telecommunications-from-the-inside-out">How Vodafone Is Changing the World of Telecommunications from the Inside Out</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>It is hard to imagine a technology that has changed the modern world more than the smartphone. Every day, millions of us use a single device to talk with friends, take videos, share photos, check e-mail, get driving directions, or go shopping. It’s been a global revolution.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As one of the world’s largest telecommunications companies, Vodafone Group connects more than 300 million people across the globe. And company leaders fully believe that tomorrow’s communications services will continue to transform our lives in powerful ways.</p>
  <p>Vodafone is already preparing for this future by making significant changes – and it is starting from within.</p>
  <h2 id="looking-for-global-consistency">Looking for Global Consistency</h2>
  <p>“Vodafone has been growing in recent years to strengthen its portfolio of services and expand into new geographies,” says Ignacio Garcia, CIO of Corporate Information Systems at Vodafone Group. But, as Garcia explains, much of this growth has been through acquisitions, resulting in various system landscapes and often inconsistent business practices throughout the group of companies.</p>
  <p>“We needed to operate as a single global organization and drive further innovation across the entire business,” Garcia adds. “To do that, we needed to run our company with a consistent, digital-first focus.” This realization led to big changes at Vodafone.</p>
  <p>The company migrated its complex and disparate enterprise resource planning (ERP) environment to a single digital core based on <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/s4hana-erp.html?btp=e479f1e4-7ee5-4e94-abfc-84a0233a3fb8">SAP S/4HANA</a>. “And we built on this solid foundation with SAP SuccessFactors, SAP Ariba, and SAP Concur solutions,” adds Holger Grewe, head of Corporate Transformation at Vodafone Group.</p>
  <p>Grewe – who has played a key leadership role in this project – points out that Vodafone benefited from some strong relationships along the way. This included implementation support from Accenture, SAP Services and Support, and customer success experts from SAP.</p>
  <p>“This was a massive transformation, covering more than twenty countries,” reports Grewe. “And SAP was by our side throughout the journey, supporting us with a <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/customer-involvement/customer-first.html">Customer First approach</a>.”</p>
  <h2 id="driving-needed-change">Driving Needed Change</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="discover-how-sap-empowers-telecommunications-providers">Discover how SAP empowers telecommunications providers</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/telecommunications.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The impact of the project on Vodafone’s operations has been huge.</p>
  <p>“We now have one data model that is standard across the footprint,” Grewe says. And Vodafone is simplifying the workplace for its more than 100,000 employees by digitizing business areas such as HR, travel and expense, and supply chain.</p>
  <p>Garcia estimates that Vodafone has standardized more than 80% of its core business processes and boosted automation levels to over 60%. “And it’s not the endgame,” remarks a smiling Garcia. “This is just the beginning.”</p>
  <p>In addition, Garcia notes that new capabilities like <a href="https://insights.sap.com/what-is-machine-learning/">machine learning</a> and advanced analytics will help Vodafone develop the next generation of products and services.</p>
  <h2 id="building-a-digital-future-at-vodafone-group">Building a Digital Future at Vodafone Group</h2>
  <p>Innovation will be crucial as <a href="https://www.vodafone.com/our-purpose">Vodafone looks ahead</a> to achieve specific goals for improving lives.</p>
  <p>By 2025, for example, the company wants to:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Connect over 50 million people and their families to mobile money services</li>
    <li>Bring mobile to an additional 20 million women in Africa and Turkey</li>
    <li>Support 10 million young people in learning the digital skills needed to thrive in the digital economy</li>
    <li>Connect 150 million vehicles to <a href="https://insights.sap.com/what-is-iot-internet-of-things/">the Internet of Things (IoT)</a></li>
  </ul>
  <p>Vodafone is confident that today’s transformation will enable the company to build a digital future that works for everyone. “These changes are helping Vodafone work as one company,” Grewe says, “so people around the world will stay better connected.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="test-drive-sap-s4hana-today">Test drive SAP S/4HANA today</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/s4hana-erp.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="to-hear-more-from-ignacio-garcia-and-holger-grewe-about-the-changes-at-vodafone-group-watch-this-video-also-check-out-these-videos-on-vodafones-experience-with-sap-successfactors-sap-concur-and-sap-ariba-solutions-as-well-as-sap-maxattention-services">To hear more from Ignacio Garcia and Holger Grewe about the changes at Vodafone Group, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/intelligent-enterprise.html?campaigncode=CRM-YD21-SOC-CUSTREF&#x26;video=d07a8f9f-df7d-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b">watch this video</a>. Also check out these videos on Vodafone’s experience with <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm.html?campaigncode=CRM-YD21-SOC-CUSTREF%E2%80%A2&#x26;video=ba32689d-df7d-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b">SAP SuccessFactors</a>, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/e-procurement/travel-expense-management.html?campaigncode=CRM-YD21-SOC-CUSTREF&#x26;video=eae78f9f-df7d-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b">SAP Concur</a> and <a href="https://www.ariba.com/?campaigncode=CRM-YD21-SOC-CUSTREF&#x26;video=2c7d909f-df7d-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b">SAP Ariba</a> solutions, as well as <a href="https://www.sap.com/uk/services/premium-engagement/maxattention.html?sort=latest_desc?campaigncode=CRM-YD21-SOC-CUSTREF&#x26;video=84788d9f-df7d-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b">SAP MaxAttention</a> services.</h3>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-concur</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-hana</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/service-industries</category>
            <category>industry/telecommunications</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Iren Innovates Invoice Processing with SAP Business Technology Platform]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/iren-innovates-invoice-processing-sap-btp</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/iren-innovates-invoice-processing-sap-btp</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Iren leverages SAP Business Technology Platform for a supplier portal with a frictionless, chatbot-supported invoice processing experience.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-apphaus</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-erp</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-hana</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Appoints Irfan Khan President of SAP HANA and Analytics]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/irfan-khan-appointed-president-sap-hana-analytics</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/irfan-khan-appointed-president-sap-hana-analytics</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Irfan Khan has been appointed president of SAP HANA and Analytics, responsibile for the database, data management and analytics portfolio.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_169fb1fdc98145fa5f7b83ca43ed211fe616d1de6.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_169fb1fdc98145fa5f7b83ca43ed211fe616d1de6.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_169fb1fdc98145fa5f7b83ca43ed211fe616d1de6.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Appoints Irfan Khan President of SAP HANA and Analytics" src="./media_169fb1fdc98145fa5f7b83ca43ed211fe616d1de6.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-appoints-irfan-khan-president-of-sap-hana-and-analytics">SAP Appoints Irfan Khan President of SAP HANA and Analytics</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="simplify-access-to-data-and-insights-with-sap">Simplify access to data and insights with SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/analytics.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced that is has named Irfan Khan, previous president of SAP’s Platform and Technologies, president of SAP HANA and Analytics.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In his new role, Khan will be responsible for the global development, product and solution management of the company’s entire database, data management and analytics portfolio. He will focus on ensuring that SAP continues to innovate and lead in the database and analytics space, powering SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP), to help customers turn data into actionable business insights. SAP BTP includes SAP HANA, the SAP HANA Cloud data platform, and the SAP Data Intelligence, SAP Analytics Cloud and SAP Data Warehouse Cloud solutions, as well as application development and integration and intelligent technologies. Khan will report to Juergen Mueller, chief technology officer and member of the SAP Executive Board.</p>
  <p>“Irfan brings a rare blend of go-to-market and product development expertise to the role,” Mueller said. “His unique perspective of customers and partners will be a tremendous asset to the continuous development of the SAP HANA database and analytics offerings. His two-plus decades of domain experience will support our customers in achieving their business objectives, no matter how far they are in their digital transformation journey.”</p>
  <p>As president of SAP’s Platform and Technologies business, Khan led global sales and go-to-market (GTM) for SAP’s database, data management and analytics assets. Over the past decade, Khan has held various senior executive positions across GTM functions, including global head of SAP’s Database and Data Management organization and chief technology officer for SAP’s global field organization. Khan joined SAP in 2010 via SAP’s acquisition of Sybase, where he was chief technology officer.</p>
  <p>Read more about Khan’s experience and role <a href="https://blogs.sap.com/?p=1264751">here</a>.</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="http://news.sap.com/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP on Twitter at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Media Contact:</strong> Scott Malinowski, +1 (781) 852-3822, <a href="mailto:scott.malinowski@sap.com">scott.malinowski@sap.com</a>, ET<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>Any statements contained in this document that are not historical facts are forward-looking statements as defined in the U.S. Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995. Words such as “anticipate,” “believe,” “estimate,” “expect,” “forecast,” “intend,” “may,” “plan,” “project,” “predict,” “should” and “will” and similar expressions as they relate to SAP are intended to identify such forward-looking statements. SAP undertakes no obligation to publicly update or revise any forward-looking statements. All forward-looking statements are subject to various risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results to differ materially from expectations. The factors that could affect SAP’s future financial results are discussed more fully in SAP’s filings with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (“SEC”), including SAP’s most recent Annual Report on Form 20-F filed with the SEC. Readers are cautioned not to place undue reliance on these forward-looking statements, which speak only as of their dates.<br>© 2021 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>topic/data-analytics</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-hana</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Personalized Cancer Therapy]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/videos/personalized-cancer-therapy</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/videos/personalized-cancer-therapy</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Jutta Vinzent was diagnosed with ovarian cancer in 2011. After an operation and several chemotherapy treatments, Vinzent used the tumor analysis with the Molecular Health...]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>content-type/video</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-hana</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>