<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/product/sap-analytics-cloud/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Game On: Business Builders Prepares Future Business Leaders for a Data-Driven World]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/business-builders-sap-university-alliances</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/business-builders-sap-university-alliances</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Business Builders, built from a partnership between SAP University Alliances and HEC Montréal, is where education meets real-world needs.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-university-alliances</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Expands Business AI Portfolio with Meta Open-Source Models]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-business-ai-meta-open-source-models</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-business-ai-meta-open-source-models</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is integrating Meta Llama 2 and Meta Llama 3 models into generative AI hub to enable customers to create dashboards based on rich content.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How SAP BTP Becomes the Trusted Platform for Business AI]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/sap-btp-strategy-paper-trusted-platform-business-ai</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/sap-btp-strategy-paper-trusted-platform-business-ai</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP BTP will further evolve to become the trusted business AI platform for SAP-centric landscapes. Learn more in the SAP BTP strategy paper.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-build</category>
            <category>product/sap-integration-suite</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Esports Powerhouse Team Liquid Wins Big with SAP Business AI]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/esports-powerhouse-team-liquid-wins-big-with-sap-business-ai</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/esports-powerhouse-team-liquid-wins-big-with-sap-business-ai</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With a generative AI model trained on SAP AI Core, Team Liquid is maximizing their chances at the League of Legends Championship Series.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/esports</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-sponsorships</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Partnerships Help Customers Successfully Navigate a Data-Driven World]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/partnerships-help-customers-navigate-data-driven-world</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/partnerships-help-customers-navigate-data-driven-world</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP partners can deploy SAP Datasphere and SAP Analytics Cloud to provide data access, effective planning, and trusted AI across operations.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16fa40a8c4f0c1be7eb9eaf1afe27075d1230ec25.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16fa40a8c4f0c1be7eb9eaf1afe27075d1230ec25.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_16fa40a8c4f0c1be7eb9eaf1afe27075d1230ec25.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Partnerships Help Customers Successfully Navigate a Data-Driven World" src="./media_16fa40a8c4f0c1be7eb9eaf1afe27075d1230ec25.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="partnerships-help-customers-successfully-navigate-a-data-driven-world">Partnerships Help Customers Successfully Navigate a Data-Driven World</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>In the modern business environment, the critical need to effectively harness data is undeniable. Companies that fail to become data-driven risk falling behind in a world where agility and informed decision-making are paramount. In the recent <a href="https://www.sap.com/events/data-unleashed.html">SAP Data Unleashed</a> event we explored strategies to help organizations access data from any source, transform planning and analysis with a business data fabric, and foster trusted artificial intelligence (AI) across their businesses. Central to this transformation are <a href="/topics/ecosystem">SAP partners</a>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>For decades, our partners have leveraged their industry expertise and technological know-how to bring immense value to companies of all sizes. They possess a rare fusion of deep industry insights and technological expertise, which they leverage to guide businesses through the delicate process of modernization while ensuring that the essence of their identity remains intact.</p>
  <p>We recently <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/partners.html#trending">asked several of our strategic SAP partners</a> how they’re helping customers take better advantage of their organization’s data. Our partners have observed a significant shift in the way data is perceived and utilized. It’s no longer just a byproduct of business operations but a core asset that, when effectively distributed and made accessible, can revolutionize customer experiences and enable a more strategic, company-wide approach to decision-making.</p>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11f5934a69f41fbb435d136fc80e11b26ab8eb2f5.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11f5934a69f41fbb435d136fc80e11b26ab8eb2f5.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_11f5934a69f41fbb435d136fc80e11b26ab8eb2f5.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Partners Bring Out Your Best as a Data-Driven Organization" src="./media_11f5934a69f41fbb435d136fc80e11b26ab8eb2f5.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://youtu.be/Cj3BF9-9I30">SAP Partners Bring Out Your Best as a Data-Driven Organization</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>However, the mere availability of data is not a panacea. The crux of the matter is transforming data into actionable insights. This is where our partners excel, mapping out advanced use cases and facilitating the transition to cutting-edge platforms like SAP Datasphere and SAP Analytics Cloud. These solutions can empower organizations to evolve into entities where data is not just present but central to every action and decision.</p>
  <p>The practical implications of data are vast and deeply rooted in the operational successes of our clients. AI, for instance, is a frontier rich with potential, but its success is inextricably linked to the quality and accessibility of data. Recognizing this, SAP partners are investing in building AI capabilities that can not only propel new business functions but also deliver substantial value.</p>
  <p>Another key area of focus for our partners is the concept of a business data fabric, which is critical in developing a flexible enterprise architecture. Such an architecture allows for co-innovation and customization of solutions, ensuring that data is not just an afterthought but a driving force in business operations.</p>
  <p>The journey toward a data- and AI-centric business model is an ongoing one, marked by evolving needs, emerging challenges, and a relentless pursuit of innovation. The ultimate aim is to convert potential into lasting business success.</p>
  <p>The essence of our relationship with our partners is rooted in a shared vision. We are united in our pursuit of discovery, innovation, and improvement as we navigate the future together. Be sure to <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/partners.html#trending">watch the videos</a> with our seven strategic partners and discover how the <a href="https://www.sap.com/partners.html">SAP partner ecosystem</a> can help your company become a data-driven organization.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Karl Fahrbach is chief partner officer at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-partners-are-helping-their-clients-solve-critical-business-challenges">SAP partners are helping their clients solve critical business challenges</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/partners.html#trending">Discover how</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>topic/data-analytics</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-datasphere</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Biggest Opportunity for Businesses Today: Using the Right Business Data]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2024/03/business-opportunity-use-the-right-business-data</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2024/03/business-opportunity-use-the-right-business-data</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Having a central hub for data is more critical than ever. Updates to SAP Datasphere empower businesses with more innovations.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10cb3ea6ef420b80f58847074323ded1ddf40b734.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10cb3ea6ef420b80f58847074323ded1ddf40b734.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_10cb3ea6ef420b80f58847074323ded1ddf40b734.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="The Biggest Opportunity for Businesses Today: Using the Right Business Data" src="./media_10cb3ea6ef420b80f58847074323ded1ddf40b734.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="the-biggest-opportunity-for-businesses-today-using-the-right-business-data">The Biggest Opportunity for Businesses Today: Using the Right Business Data</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>There is no doubt that generative AI for business will transform every aspect of how business is done. But the reality is that generative AI is only as good as the data that it’s trained on.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>While data may be the fuel powering the engine of AI, it’s good data that’s the real game changer. With good data, a company can automate processes — freeing up their people to do the most impactful work — and analyze the most important variables facing their business to create intelligent insights.</p>
  <p>That’s where a datasphere comes in. It makes data more complete and logical by understanding the different relationships within a company’s data. And that’s what can truly bring out the best in any business today.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="deliver-seamless-and-scalable-access-to-mission-critical-business-data">Deliver seamless and scalable access to mission-critical business data</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/datasphere.html">Explore SAP Datasphere</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Having a central hub for data is more critical than ever. It allows our customers to better model their business across all SAP business applications. That’s exactly why we introduced <strong>SAP Datasphere</strong> last year to empower businesses with insights they need – based on the right data – in the context of their business. Since then, generative AI has disrupted and simplified even more business processes, and data capture is no different. This week <a href="/2024/03/future-of-data-driven-business-new-sap-datasphere-capabilities">we announced new generative-AI features in SAP Datasphere that will transform enterprise planning</a> through simplified data landscapes and more-intuitive data interaction.</p>
  <p>Why is this important? Because having a unified data view that simplifies the data landscapes while retaining context and logic is what enables businesses to adapt faster to market changes and make better decisions. It’s also a more efficient way of working. Because while you’re busy pulling data together, competitors are circling your customers.</p>
  <p>I am constantly speaking with our customers about the value of SAP Datasphere. It’s a data architecture that harmonizes mission-critical data across an organization. I hear amazing outcomes they’re able to achieve: from PwC breaking down silos in the different countries where it stores sensitive data so its workforce can access it more efficiently and securely for customers, to the Lufthansa Group taking data from different parts of its operations like aircraft, HR, and procurement, to see how decisions from one could impact the other.<br><br>With our additional news this week, such as making our generative AI copilot Joule available in SAP Analytics Cloud and expanding our partnership with Collibra to help our customers meet compliance, privacy, and regulatory requirements related to AI as they evolve, we’re making it easier to find the right data and use it to drive deeper insights, more efficiencies, faster growth, and more trust in their business.</p>
  <p>While PwC and Lufthansa show what’s possible today with a simplified data fabric, imagine what is about to become possible when you infuse it with the power of generative AI that understands your business – and then learns from that data. This has the potential to deliver exponential value from your data.</p>
  <p>Or think of it this way: years ago, the biggest differentiators for businesses were price, location, products, and services. Today, and especially in the years ahead, it could very well be how effectively a business is training their AI models. That’s why building the right data fabric is one of the most important investments any business can make today.</p>
  <p>It’s been said that the best way to predict the future is to invent it. And in an era where data is being created exponentially, I believe that those businesses that can separate the signal from the noise when it comes to their data will be the ones that invent the future in an AI-first world.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Scott Russell is a member of the Executive Board of SAP SE.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="take-a-guided-tour-and-experience-firsthand-the-power-of-business-data-with-sap-datasphere">Take a guided tour and experience firsthand the power of business data with SAP Datasphere</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/datasphere/guided-experience.html">Start now</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/blog/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/blog/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/blog/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/blog/article-read-more</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/executive-blog</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-datasphere</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unleashing the Latest SAP Data and Analytics Innovations]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/latest-sap-data-and-analytics-innovations-sap-data-unleashed</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/latest-sap-data-and-analytics-innovations-sap-data-unleashed</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP has shared the latest innovations in data and analytics. Read on to learn more about the company's transformative announcements.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1025728cedc072568e25830043a6185f08eca8f64.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1025728cedc072568e25830043a6185f08eca8f64.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1025728cedc072568e25830043a6185f08eca8f64.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Unleashing the Latest SAP Data and Analytics Innovations" src="./media_1025728cedc072568e25830043a6185f08eca8f64.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="unleashing-the-latest-sap-data-and-analytics-innovations">Unleashing the Latest SAP Data and Analytics Innovations</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Today at <a href="/">SAP Data Unleashed</a>, SAP proudly announced the latest innovations in data and analytics.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Read on to learn more about these transformative announcements, which will enable businesses to unlock new potential in the areas of data management, AI-driven planning, and analytics.</p>
  <h2 id="access-insights-wherever-your-data-resides">Access Insights Wherever Your Data Resides</h2>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>SAP Datasphere Knowledge Graph</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP Datasphere knowledge graph will enable organizations to better represent their real-world use of data, leading to more effectively leveraging it for generative AI and better reasoning.</p>
  <p>As data is onboarded, transformed, and integrated in SAP Datasphere, SAP Datasphere knowledge graph automatically creates an ontology representing the relationships in the data, including the inherent business context from SAP application sources like SAP S/4HANA. This is then available to be extended and augmented via an ontology editor to reflect specific attributes within an organization. Finally, the data in SAP Datasphere is automatically applied to this ontology to create a knowledge graph that allows the data to be processed as a semantic web of relationships, drawing new insights from connections that are otherwise difficult to follow.</p>
  <p>These knowledge graphs are better suited for answering complex, often open-ended questions. For example, a marketing manager might ask a question like: “What type of campaign for mountain bikes works best for my highest performing cities with a population over 1 million?”</p>
  <p>Knowledge graphs can provide better context to large language models (LLMs) and prevent AI-generated “hallucinations.” SAP Datasphere knowledge graph will enable organizations to unleash the power of AI for even the most complex queries.</p>
  <p>The effort and cost of manually creating knowledge graphs is typically very high. SAP Datasphere knowledge graph overcomes this by pre-populating the knowledge graphs using all the valuable content already available in SAP Datasphere. The knowledge graph can then be used with Joule, SAP’s generative AI co-pilot, allowing business users to ask both open-ended and specific questions and get instant and well-documented answers. Sign up for a preview of SAP Datasphere knowledge graph via the link below.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15c1af20ba8e68937af5d24f99fac41cebc44dce7.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15c1af20ba8e68937af5d24f99fac41cebc44dce7.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_15c1af20ba8e68937af5d24f99fac41cebc44dce7.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_15c1af20ba8e68937af5d24f99fac41cebc44dce7.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="576">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>Auto-generated knowledge graphs enable AI to answer complex, open-ended questions</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>SAP HANA Cloud Vector Engine</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>With the next release of SAP HANA Cloud, a vector capability will be added to existing multi-model capabilities, allowing customers to gain value from all relevant types of business data using a single database. The inclusion of a vector engine further enables customers to build <a href="https://pages.community.sap.com/topics/hana/intelligent-data-applications">intelligent data applications</a> that combine the natural intuition of human interaction with powerful machine learning and multi-model processing capabilities.</p>
  <p>The vector engine in SAP HANA Cloud provides the ability to store and compare vectors using SQL. Determining similarity between vectors enables use cases such as retrieval-augmented generation (RAG), recommendations, classifications, clustering, and more. Key benefits of SAP HANA Cloud vector engine include:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Simplify data architecture and security with a single multi-model database with SQL interaction</li>
    <li>Gain new insights by combining spatial, graph, JSON, and relational data with vector queries</li>
    <li>Easily incorporate vector use cases in solutions based on the HANA Cloud ecosystem (clients, Python libraries, CAP, etc.)</li>
    <li>Integrate with open-source community tools such as LangChain via plug-ins</li>
  </ul>
  <p>SAP HANA Cloud vector engine is currently in public preview and is planned for general availability in late Q1 2024.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Simplified Consumption of Data Products in SAP Datasphere</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Data products facilitate self-service access to data as a product and enable data sharing across application boundaries. Data consumers need an easy way to explore, understand, and activate the data needed to perform their tasks — and data providers need an easy way to publish their assets and make them available to data consumers.</p>
  <p>SAP is innovating in this space with an improved user experience that drives data sharing at scale. This starts with published data products, whether produced by SAP line-of-business applications, industry solutions, or third parties, and follows with simple consumption in SAP Datasphere.</p>
  <p>In SAP Datasphere, customers will find ready access to SAP and non-SAP data products and easily install them into their SAP Datasphere instance. The procedure establishes relevant connections and creates the necessary artifacts in SAP Datasphere without the user having to enter those details. Key to this is making data provisioning easier via metadata, which are described via the Open Resource Directory (ORD) protocol. The experience will be harmonized within SAP Datasphere by bringing catalog and the data product installation closely together. Visit <a href="https://roadmaps.sap.com/board?range=FIRST-LAST&#x26;PRODUCT=73555000100800002141&#x26;q=data%20products#Q1%202024">SAP Road Map Explorer</a> for the latest updates.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15b1605af3a6110198283ea2725e4e982d88adc28.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15b1605af3a6110198283ea2725e4e982d88adc28.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_15b1605af3a6110198283ea2725e4e982d88adc28.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_15b1605af3a6110198283ea2725e4e982d88adc28.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="576">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>Data products available in catalog enhances the experience and productivity of data users</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>SAP Datasphere Semantic Onboarding Enhancements</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Semantic onboarding provides a seamless import of semantically rich objects from SAP S/4HANA and SAP BW/4HANA into SAP Datasphere. Now, we are taking the next step by adding support for SAP HANA Cloud and SAP data products through the same unified onboarding experience.</p>
  <p>Customers will be able to combine their SAP HANA Cloud modeling approach with SAP Datasphere by importing calculation views into the data layer of SAP Datasphere. This preserves the semantic information such as measures, attributes, hierarchies, aggregations, and currencies/units, while keeping SAP HANA Cloud and SAP Datasphere objects in sync — allowing customers to leverage their prior investments in SAP HANA modeling.</p>
  <p>Likewise, semantic onboarding of SAP data products will enable inheritance of business context from SAP line-of-business applications and industry solutions. By providing the semantics of the source systems and transferring that into the business data fabric as a foundation, SAP Datasphere drastically improves the analytic workflow and accelerates and simplifies data-driven insights.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Collibra AI Governance Integration with SAP Solutions</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The SAP and Collibra partnership enables end-to-end data governance and delivers trusted data to all users across the business data fabric. As more tasks and decisions are automated by AI within critical business processes, the need to extend governance to AI has also become apparent.</p>
  <p>The partnership with Collibra is being expanded to address the data and AI governance needs of joint customers via Collibra AI Governance. We will build tailored integrations between Collibra AI Governance and SAP solutions to connect the data used for AI with the models themselves in a single platform, allowing enterprises to track and manage their AI development efforts.</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Customers will better understand data lineage and metadata of SAP data that is utilized in AI modeling. With that, users can see what data their AI models were trained on to ensure that the data is accurate and from a trusted source.</li>
    <li>Customers will benefit from a single view to understand what AI models exist in their organization, and what data is being used to power them. AI/machine learning models created with SAP technology will be registered with the Collibra AI Governance platform.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>This extension of the SAP partnership with Collibra will increase transparency and accountability for organizations, and help ensure that regulatory, compliance, and privacy policies are being met. More importantly, it will build user trust by preventing biased decision-making, inaccurate recommendations, and other risks arising from AI.</p>
  <p>Together, SAP and Collibra will help joint customers address the data and AI governance needs across their organizations. Collibra AI Governance was <a href="https://www.collibra.com/us/en/company/newsroom/press-releases/collibra-introduces-collibra-ai-governance">launched last week</a> and is available to interested customers.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>SAP Datasphere Confluent Integration</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Core to the SAP data strategy is providing customers with the ability to interoperate with the world’s leading data and AI vendors through an open data ecosystem. To this end, the newly enhanced Confluent integration enables real-time streaming of data to and from SAP Datasphere.</p>
  <p>First, the outbound capabilities were extended by taking advantage of Confluent’s proprietary schema registry capabilities. Second, the Confluent schema registry will be used to enable seamless consumption of Confluent data within SAP Datasphere.</p>
  <p>The integration is specifically tailored to Confluent and provides a superior user experience for joint customers. It allows connections on the application level without additional custom application development. The integration is a pre-established replication flow in SAP Datasphere, which already includes delta and real-time processing natively. This makes the process very efficient as it does not force customers to load all the data at every step, but only when data has changed.</p>
  <p>The first integration for data ingestion into Kafka and Confluent is generally available. Additional capabilities for Confluent specific outbound and inbound integration will be generally available at the end of Q1 and Q3, respectively.</p>
  <h2 id="transform-planning-with-a-business-data-fabric">Transform Planning with a Business Data Fabric</h2>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>SAP Analytics Cloud for Planning Deep Integration to SAP Datasphere</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP Datasphere and SAP Analytics Cloud for planning will be more closely integrated to expand the business data fabric to planning use cases. SAP Analytics Cloud planning models can be deployed into SAP Datasphere, bringing plan and actuals data together for real-time steering.</p>
  <p>Through a reduction in both data footprint and modeling efforts, SAP Analytics Cloud extends planning functionality via SAP Datasphere and its native capabilities for transformation and integration. This reduces the complexity and risk inherent in storing multiple copies of data which is prevalent today.</p>
  <p>SAP Analytics Cloud for planning will have live access to actual and plan data for extended planning and analysis scenarios, including the live usage of master data. With this, SAP Datasphere will become the platform on which planning processes and tools can integrate.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14d5d8f4cd6ea2a14b3cb7d88fc159719e39722c7.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14d5d8f4cd6ea2a14b3cb7d88fc159719e39722c7.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_14d5d8f4cd6ea2a14b3cb7d88fc159719e39722c7.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_14d5d8f4cd6ea2a14b3cb7d88fc159719e39722c7.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="558">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>In this example, third-party inflation data from the World Bank (blue box) is provisioned through Datasphere to help planners do scenario planning with SAP Analytics Cloud compass</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP is the only vendor to offer a business data fabric that seamlessly integrates planning and therefore covers the entire technology stack required to transform data into insights and future actions. Visit <a href="https://roadmaps.sap.com/board?PRODUCT=67838200100800006884&#x26;q=seamless&#x26;range=CURRENT-LAST#;INNO=1FA75F34ABA51EDEADDAB4FD3ACC8288">SAP Road Map Explorer</a> for the latest updates.</p>
  <h2 id="foster-trusted-ai-across-your-business">Foster Trusted AI Across Your Business</h2>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>SAP Analytics Cloud Generative AI Co-Pilot</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP customers will embrace the power of generative AI to create and simulate business plans in SAP Analytics Cloud. With the power of Joule, planning and analytics professionals can leverage generative AI capabilities in a wide range of business processes. Activities such as data discovery, dashboard creation, planning model maintenance, and more are benefitting from a boost in core capabilities and an unmatched user experience.</p>
  <p>With the power of natural language processing, end users can easily run analytical queries, simulate driver impacts, plan resource allocations, and auto-generate dashboards and calculations. For example, a business user seeking to understand why gross margins declined in the latest version of a plan could query Joule, which could automatically look through previous plan iterations and attached comments, and uncover the fact that planners were estimating higher commodity costs.</p>
  <p>SAP’s investment in AI and its understanding of the context of business data provides truly limitless potential in unleashing the world of planning and analytics.</p>
  <p>A preview of Joule co-pilot functionality in SAP Analytics Cloud is planned to be available in Q2 2024. Sign up for the preview via the link below.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_135bdf52547a43026234fdf26c84defd9f04f1334.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_135bdf52547a43026234fdf26c84defd9f04f1334.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_135bdf52547a43026234fdf26c84defd9f04f1334.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_135bdf52547a43026234fdf26c84defd9f04f1334.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="574">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>With Joule co-pilot, planning and analytics professionals can prompt Joule to analyze all aspects of extended planning and create new analytical views on the fly, provisioned specially for individual user types</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>SAP Analytics Cloud Compass</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In an increasingly volatile business climate, it is essential to create operational and financial plans and provision BI insights with risk mitigation in mind. This requires the ability to simulate uncertainties and the probability of their impact. Knowing how uncertainties in commodity prices, labor costs, or production volumes will hit your operational expenses or revenue means that companies can quickly prepare and plan counter measures for any scenario.</p>
  <p>SAP Analytics Cloud compass provides Monte Carlo simulation capabilities with a business user-friendly interface. This enables non-technical users to perform real-time multi-variate analysis without prior IT setup or advanced statistical skills.</p>
  <p>Users can perform business simulations directly in SAP Analytics Cloud at a fraction of the time and effort required to perform similar analysis manually. Scenario modeling capabilities will allow comparisons between assumptions, and the reporting of impact variances provides real-time insight, concept validation, and reveals the sensitivity of the drivers chosen. Now customers can identify their major drivers and combinations over time, enabling a better understanding of the dynamics between the data, and how to continuously simulate better and faster. With compass, customers can face the future with confidence.</p>
  <p>A preview of SAP Analytics Cloud compass is planned to be available at the end of Q3 2024. Sign up for the preview via the link below.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b407deea790db28d0775959ab3574632b1f5e085.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b407deea790db28d0775959ab3574632b1f5e085.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1b407deea790db28d0775959ab3574632b1f5e085.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_1b407deea790db28d0775959ab3574632b1f5e085.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>SAP Analytics Cloud compass showing distribution of impact probability on the operating income based on a simulation of uncertainty in inputs such as inflation or other relevant drivers.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="get-started-today">Get Started Today</h3>
  <p>Begin your path toward unlocking the full potential of your business data with SAP Datasphere. Embrace the opportunity to seamlessly integrate and activate your data landscape, propelling your business into a new era of insights and efficiency. Start now and transform how your organization leverages data with SAP Datasphere.</p>
  <p>Start your journey today to bring out your best with SAP data and AI:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><a href="https://www.sap.com/registration/trial.4d48ec23-eadf-4399-8595-ac3f9c66c64f.html">Take a complete tour and try the latest features of SAP Datasphere</a> with the 30-day guided experience.</li>
    <li><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/datasphere/migration.html">Begin your SAP Business Warehouse cloud modernization journey</a> with a free assessment and special offers.</li>
    <li><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/oth/business-data-fabric/index.html?campaigncode=CRM-YJ24-BTP-2560577&#x26;source=blog-glo">Save on costs and learn how to implement a business data fabric architecture</a> with the Total Cost of Ownership study and getting started package</li>
    <li><a href="https://events.sap.com/dataunleashed-previews/en/home">Sign up today for an early preview</a> of the upcoming SAP Datasphere and SAP Analytics Cloud features</li>
  </ul>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Irfan Khan is chief product officer and president for SAP HANA Database &#x26; Analytics.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="deliver-seamless-and-scalable-access-to-mission-critical-business-data">Deliver seamless and scalable access to mission-critical business data</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/datasphere.html">Explore SAP Datasphere</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-data-unleashed</category>
            <category>product/sap-datasphere</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Data Unleashed: The Future Belongs to Data-Driven Organizations]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/future-belongs-to-data-driven-organizations-sap-data-unleashed</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/future-belongs-to-data-driven-organizations-sap-data-unleashed</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With the latest updates to SAP Datasphere, SAP is empowering data-driven organizations to bring out their best. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-data-unleashed</category>
            <category>product/sap-datasphere</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Shapes the Future of Data-Driven Business Transformation with Innovations that Equip Customers to Succeed in the Era of AI]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/future-of-data-driven-business-new-sap-datasphere-capabilities</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/future-of-data-driven-business-new-sap-datasphere-capabilities</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New SAP Datasphere capabilities will drive deeper insights, faster growth and more efficiency in the era of AI. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ca92906e5e003a06f25ac5a8b837a5576894477a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ca92906e5e003a06f25ac5a8b837a5576894477a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1ca92906e5e003a06f25ac5a8b837a5576894477a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Shapes the Future of Data-Driven Business Transformation with Innovations that Equip Customers to Succeed in the Era of AI" src="./media_1ca92906e5e003a06f25ac5a8b837a5576894477a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-shapes-the-future-of-data-driven-business-transformation-with-innovations-that-equip-customers-to-succeed-in-the-era-of-ai">SAP Shapes the Future of Data-Driven Business Transformation with Innovations that Equip Customers to Succeed in the Era of AI</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced transformative data innovations that will help customers harness the full power of their data to drive deeper insights, faster growth and more efficiency in the era of AI. New capabilities in the SAP Datasphere solution, including new generative-AI features, transform enterprise planning through simplified data landscapes and more-intuitive data interaction.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“Capturing data to make better decisions is an enterprise technology imperative that’s become increasingly critical as AI – which relies on quality data – revolutionizes every aspect of business,” said Juergen Mueller, SAP Chief Technology Officer and member of the Executive Board. “Our newest SAP Datasphere innovations, as well as an expanded partnership with Collibra, represent a quantum leap in our ability to help customers drive intelligent business transformations through data.”</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="deliver-seamless-and-scalable-access-to-mission-critical-business-data">Deliver seamless and scalable access to mission-critical business data</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/datasphere.html">Explore SAP Datasphere</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>At the heart of these announcements is the business data fabric, an architecture that helps ensure data is not just an asset but also the core underpinning of strategic initiatives. The innovations and partnership announced today equip organizations to deliver meaningful data to data consumers – with business context and logic intact.</p>
  <p>“We have decided to leverage SAP Datasphere for a modern business data fabric architecture in conjunction with our SAP S/4HANA landscape. It allows us to effectively establish a modern data analytics platform that enables a business self service capability on the basis of trusted data and data models,” said Achim Welter, Senior Director ERP, Digital &#x26; IT Strategy, Hershey’s.</p>
  <p>Today’s SAP Datasphere innovations help customers achieve a unified data view that simplifies their data landscapes while retaining context and logic – enabling them to adapt faster to market changes and make more-efficient decisions. From new copilot and vector database capabilities that help ensure business context remains constant in generative AI outputs to a new knowledge graph that helps uncover insights and patterns in complex data, SAP’s data innovations help ensure customers have the full power of their data at their fingertips.</p>
  <p>Today’s key innovations include:</p>
  <h2 id="generative-ai-copilot-and-ai-governance">Generative-AI Copilot and AI Governance</h2>
  <p>SAP’s generative-AI assistant, the <a href="https://www.sap.com/joule">Joule</a> copilot, is now coming to the SAP Analytics Cloud solution to automate the creation and development of reports, dashboards, plans and more. This automation is enabled by the <strong>SAP HANA Cloud vector engine capabilities,</strong> which combine the power of large language models with the relevant data of your organization – helping ensure business context is a constant for generative-AI outputs.</p>
  <p>Incorporating generative AI across the business isn’t possible without trusted and governed data. To provide organizations with a solution to govern the policies, processes and practices of AI, SAP is announcing an <strong>expansion of our partnership with Collibra</strong> to integrate Collibra’s AI Governance with SAP data assets. This can help provide transparency and accountability for organizations and help ensure regulatory, compliance and privacy policies are met.</p>
  <h2 id="discover-hidden-insights-and-patterns-with-knowledge-graph">Discover Hidden Insights and Patterns with Knowledge Graph</h2>
  <p>With the new <strong>SAP Datasphere knowledge graph,</strong> organizations can discover hidden insights and patterns across their applications and systems. This enables both technical and business users to deeply understand the relationships between data, metadata and business processes, as well as boost the effectiveness of machine learning and large language models.</p>
  <h2 id="unified-and-advanced-planning-and-analytics">Unified and Advanced Planning and Analytics</h2>
  <p>The new SAP Datasphere integration with SAP Analytics Cloud offers a single data management system and advanced analytics to power cross-organizational planning. Planners can leverage a single flexible model to break down silos between planning using one tool for data preparation, modeling and planning.</p>
  <p>Additionally, business users can use the <strong>new compass</strong> capability in SAP Analytics Cloud to realize better outcomes in planning and analytics through data-driven simulation. It enables organizations to run complex simulations using a chat interface to evaluate predictive outcomes and continually adjust controllable variables to find the optimal plan.</p>
  <p>This supports customers to transform their planning by unifying financial, operational, supply chain and workforce planning with native connection to SAP applications and third-party data.</p>
  <p>To learn more, please read: <strong><a href="/">Unleashing the Latest SAP Data and Analytics Innovations</a></strong>.</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="take-a-guided-tour-and-experience-firsthand-the-power-of-business-data-with-sap-datasphere">Take a guided tour and experience firsthand the power of business data with SAP Datasphere</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/datasphere/guided-experience.html">Start now</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>About SAP</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP’s strategy is to help every business run as an intelligent, sustainable enterprise. As a market leader in enterprise application software, we help companies of all sizes and in all industries run at their best: SAP customers generate 87% of total global commerce. Our machine learning, Internet of Things (IoT), and advanced analytics technologies help turn customers’ businesses into intelligent enterprises. SAP helps give people and organizations deep business insight and fosters collaboration that helps them stay ahead of their competition. We simplify technology for companies so they can consume our software the way they want – without disruption. Our end-to-end suite of applications and services enables business and public customers across 26 industries globally to operate profitably, adapt continuously, and make a difference. With a global network of customers, partners, employees, and thought leaders, SAP helps the world run better and improve people’s lives. For more information, visit <a href="http://www.sap.com">www.sap.com</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Note to editors:</strong><br>To preview and download broadcast-standard stock footage and press photos digitally, please visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/photos">www.sap.com/photos</a>. On this platform, you can find high resolution material for your media channels.</p>
  <p><strong>For customers interested in learning more about SAP products:</strong><br>Global Customer Center: +49 180 534-34-24<br>United States Only: 1 (800) 872-1SAP (1-800-872-1727)</p>
  <p><strong>For more information, press only:</strong><br>Julia Fargel, +1 (650) 276-8964, <a href="mailto:julia.fargel@sap.com">julia.fargel@sap.com</a>, PT<br>Martin Gwisdalla, +49 (6227) 767 275, <a href="mailto:martin.gwisdalla@sap.com">martin.gwisdalla@sap.com</a>, CET<br><a href="mailto:SAP%20Press%20Room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>This document contains forward-looking statements, which are predictions, projections, or other statements about future events. These statements are based on current expectations, forecasts, and assumptions that are subject to risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results and outcomes to materially differ. Additional information regarding these risks and uncertainties may be found in our filings with the Securities and Exchange Commission, including but not limited to the risk factors section of SAP’s 2023 Annual Report on Form 20-F.<br>© 2024 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.<br>Please consider our <a href="https://www.sap.com/corporate/en/legal/privacy.html">privacy policy</a>. If you received this press release in your e-mail and you wish to unsubscribe to our mailing list please contact <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a> and write Unsubscribe in the subject line.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-data-unleashed</category>
            <category>product/sap-datasphere</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Palm Oil and SAP Software Give Ugandan Farmers New Hope]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/kopgt-sap-ugandan-oil-palm-farmers</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/kopgt-sap-ugandan-oil-palm-farmers</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The Kalangala Oil Palm Growers Trust (KOPGT) works with SAP software to support Ugandan oil palm farmers sustainably. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/agribusiness</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-rural-sourcing-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cloud Technology Empowers Ugandan Island Community]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/videos/cloud-technology-empowers-ugandan-island-community</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/videos/cloud-technology-empowers-ugandan-island-community</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[KOPGT, which educates farmers on improved agricultural practices, recognized the need for a digital solution to meet the rising demand for palm oil and chose SAP Rural Sourcing Management.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/video</category>
            <category>industry/agribusiness</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-one</category>
            <category>product/sap-rural-sourcing-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Is a Leader in the 2023 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Financial Planning Software]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/sap-leader-2023-gartner-magic-quadrant-financial-planning-software</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/sap-leader-2023-gartner-magic-quadrant-financial-planning-software</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[We are proud to announce that Gartner has recognized SAP as a Leader in its 2023 Magic Quadrant for Financial Planning Software.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_12c0f62a0c1bea8cebafaf88b1a2478cf4d11b899.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_12c0f62a0c1bea8cebafaf88b1a2478cf4d11b899.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_12c0f62a0c1bea8cebafaf88b1a2478cf4d11b899.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Is a Leader in the 2023 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Financial Planning Software" src="./media_12c0f62a0c1bea8cebafaf88b1a2478cf4d11b899.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-is-a-leader-in-the-2023-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-financial-planning-software">SAP Is a Leader in the 2023 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Financial Planning Software</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>We are proud to announce that Gartner has recognized SAP as a Leader in its <a href="https://www.gartner.com/reprints/?id=1-2FU0XES5&#x26;ct=231206&#x26;st=sb">2023 Magic Quadrant for Financial Planning Software</a>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>At SAP, our commitment extends beyond traditional financial planning and analysis (FP&#x26;A), reaching across the entire enterprise of financial professionals. To achieve a comprehensive FP&#x26;A transformation, organizations need effortless access to crucial finance data, regardless of its location. In a landscape where financial information is dispersed across various applications, files, and systems – both on premise and in the cloud – organizations often expend significant resources on extracting, rebuilding, and integrating their financial data to deliver forecasts and simulations.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-analytics-cloud-make-decisions-without-doubt">SAP Analytics Cloud: Make decisions without doubt</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/cloud-analytics.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>By harnessing cutting-edge FP&#x26;A software tools and adopting strategic approaches, organizations can seamlessly explore, connect, integrate, govern, and orchestrate their planning and analysis. SAP’s solutions for financial planning and analysis can provide a reliable foundation for finance information, delivering trustworthy, pertinent, and timely financial insights. This can streamline finance data, helping to maximize business information potential. Simultaneously, it can foster an analytics-driven approach to planning and decision-making. Our primary solution for financial planning and analysis is <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/cloud-analytics/features/planning.html">SAP Analytics Cloud</a>. This solution is part of <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">SAP Business Technology Platform</a> (SAP BTP).</p>
  <p>Gartner evaluated 16 vendors and named SAP a Leader based on our “ability to execute” and “completeness of vision.” We believe this recognition serves as an acknowledgment of SAP’s continued commitment to providing our customers with world-class financial planning software.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1db92051bee73b9bb29a5433d2213c41cc9f52bab.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1db92051bee73b9bb29a5433d2213c41cc9f52bab.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1db92051bee73b9bb29a5433d2213c41cc9f52bab.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_1db92051bee73b9bb29a5433d2213c41cc9f52bab.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="570" height="592">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>This graphic was published by Gartner, Inc. as part of a larger research document and should be evaluated in the context of the entire document. The Gartner document is available upon request from SAP here. Click to enlarge.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="future-proof-your-organization-with-sap-solutions-for-xpa">Future-Proof Your Organization with SAP Solutions for xP&#x26;A</h2>
  <p>Our focus on accelerating planning and analysis (xP&#x26;A) is achieved by integrating with SAP S/4HANA Cloud and other SAP applications. This integration helps enable swift planning cycles, providing live access to actuals and plans. Customers can use our solutions to help extend their planning and analysis across the enterprise to facilitate seamlessly connected financial, workforce, sales, and supply chain plans. By adopting this approach, SAP customers can react quickly to changes and increase decision-making agility and performance no matter what events unfold.</p>
  <p>A pivotal aspect of our approach involves harnessing the power of artificial intelligence (AI) and machine learning for everyday planning. With a single click, our users can activate predictive analytics, allowing for insights with greater ease and speed. The AI capabilities within SAP Analytics Cloud are helping organizations unlock the full potential of their data and derive greater value from analytics and planning. With these capabilities, planners can model a wide range of scenarios and generate more accurate forecasts and plans.</p>
  <p>We are committed to instilling unwavering confidence in plans by meticulously ensuring the trustworthiness of data. Leveraging the powerful combination of <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/datasphere.html">SAP Datasphere</a> and SAP Analytics Cloud, we go beyond traditional boundaries to help harmonize planning data seamlessly across SAP and third-party sources, presenting natively integrated plans that can form a reliable foundation for strategic decision-making.</p>
  <p>This approach has yielded tangible benefits for organizations such as <a href="https://www.sap.com/asset/dynamic/2023/06/34b2b0e8-797e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Watco</a> and <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/customer-stories/roche.html">F. Hoffmann-La Roche AG</a>. These SAP Analytics Cloud customers have experienced firsthand the transformative impact of having their planning data seamlessly integrated, resulting in enhanced precision and efficacy in their planning and analysis endeavors. With our holistic approach, we help pave the way for you to navigate the complex landscape of financial planning with confidence, working to ensure your business decisions are backed by a foundation of accurate and planning-ready data.</p>
  <h2 id="next-steps">Next Steps</h2>
  <p>SAP is dedicated to advancing financial planning and analysis through our suite of financial planning software tools. Our commitment is reflected in the seamless transformation of financial data into actionable insights at scale for our customers. If you’re poised to unlock the full potential of your financial data and elevate your FP&#x26;A capabilities, explore the next steps with the resources provided:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Visit our <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/financial-management/financial-planning-analysis-fpa.html">financial planning and analysis page</a></li>
    <li>Try the free <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/financial-management/financial-planning-analysis-fpa/guided-experience.html">financial planning and analysis guided experience</a></li>
    <li>Read the full, complimentary <a href="https://www.gartner.com/reprints/?id=1-2FU0XES5&#x26;ct=231206&#x26;st=sb">Gartner Magic Quadrant for Financial Planning Software</a> report</li>
  </ul>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Dan Yu is senior vice president of SAP Business Technology Platform.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Gartner, Magic Quadrant for Financial Planning Software, Regina Crowder, Matthew Mowrey, Vaughan Archer, 5 December 2023<br>Gartner does not endorse any vendor, product or service depicted in its research publications and does not advise technology users to select only those vendors with the highest ratings or other designation. Gartner research publications consist of the opinions of Gartner’s Research &#x26; Advisory organization and should not be construed as statements of fact. Gartner disclaims all warranties, expressed or implied, with respect to this research, including any warranties of merchantability or fitness for a particular purpose.<br>GARTNER is a registered trademark and service mark of Gartner, Inc. and/or its affiliates in the U.S. and internationally, Magic Quadrant is a registered trademark of Gartner, Inc. and/or its affiliates and is used herein with permission. All rights reserved.</p>
  <p>Top image courtesy of SAP employee Laurentia-Iulia Pavel.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/financial-management</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/magic-quadrant</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Digital Transformation Helps Companies Keep Promises]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/digital-transformation-helps-keep-promises-blue-diamond</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/digital-transformation-helps-keep-promises-blue-diamond</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Innovation Award winner Blue Diamond Growers transformed for brand success, enhanced customer relationships, and supply chain visibility.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/consumer-goods-cpg</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>sap-award/sap-innovation-awards</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Esports: Team Liquid’s Masters of Data]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/esports-team-liquid-masters-of-data</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/esports-team-liquid-masters-of-data</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP solutions help Team Liquid succeed at the Dota 2 and League of Legends World Championships. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15daec53a13fbbf487bab50b2abd4b35529f13efe.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15daec53a13fbbf487bab50b2abd4b35529f13efe.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_15daec53a13fbbf487bab50b2abd4b35529f13efe.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Esports: Team Liquid’s Masters of Data" src="./media_15daec53a13fbbf487bab50b2abd4b35529f13efe.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="esports-team-liquids-masters-of-data">Esports: Team Liquid’s Masters of Data</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>This October and November, gaming fans around the globe can enjoy two of the most prestigious and exciting <a href="/topics/esports">esports</a> tournaments: The League of Legends World Championship – also known as Worlds – in South Korea and The International, the annual Dota 2 World Championship in Seattle, Washington.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>It’s a special thrill for Team Liquid fans, as both teams – the Dota 2 and the League of Legends squad – have qualified for the championships and will compete for the title. We tapped into our connection with Team Liquid and had the exclusive opportunity to talk to two team members, <strong>Haitham “Haitham” Algbory, head analyst of the League of Legends team</strong>, and <strong>Mathis “Jabbz” Friesel, assistant coach and analyst of the Dota team</strong>, about how they prepare the teams for the world championships and what role SAP technology plays for the teams to perform at their top level.</p>
  <h2 id="about-sap-and-team-liquid">About SAP and Team Liquid</h2>
  <p>With SAP being the official innovation partner of Team Liquid, the two companies developed a close partnership of co-innovation focused on Team Liquid’s Dota 2 and League of Legends teams. These two multiplayer online battle arena games are highly complex and data-intensive esports. Together with Team Liquid, SAP is co-developing software to help Team Liquid analyze its performance and apply more precision in areas like match preparation, team and player performance, scouting, and others. Read more <a href="https://www.sap.com/asset/dynamic/2023/07/c4e4d3c9-807e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">here</a>.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_146ad53e5c6d85798326e3514162a214869983c15.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_146ad53e5c6d85798326e3514162a214869983c15.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_146ad53e5c6d85798326e3514162a214869983c15.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_146ad53e5c6d85798326e3514162a214869983c15.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="400" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em><a href="https://twitter.com/tbHaitham">Haitham “Haitham” Algbory</a>, head of Analytics &#x26; Data for Team Liquid’s League of Legends Team</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>A big part of what SAP brings to Team Liquid is <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/hana.html">SAP HANA Cloud</a>, which helps make data analysis for both League of Legends and Dota a lot easier. The database allows the analysts to focus less on gathering data and more on analyzing it. Both Jabbz and Haitham have been working in this field for a long time, and there are things that they can do now that they never could before, thanks to a tool specifically made for esports data analysis.</p>
  <p>“I support both the general manager and the coaching staff with scouting new talent,” Haitham said. “The way I do that is by providing periodic solo queue and scrim reports and end-of-season scouting reports. When it comes to the Academy teams of the East Regions, at the same time, we just track the players that are in the scene in general and we see their improvement based off the metrics that we have set in our tools.”</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1fc0e7e2f4de3f3ba1c19914ddcfb1f5a969cb35f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1fc0e7e2f4de3f3ba1c19914ddcfb1f5a969cb35f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1fc0e7e2f4de3f3ba1c19914ddcfb1f5a969cb35f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_1fc0e7e2f4de3f3ba1c19914ddcfb1f5a969cb35f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="200" height="280">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em><a href="https://twitter.com/jabbz1301">Mathis “Jabbz” Friesel</a>, coach and head analyst for Team Liquid’s Dota 2 Team</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>On the League of Legends side, SAP HANA Cloud is Haitham’s primary tool for scouting. But that’s not what Jabbz uses the data for. For Team Liquid Dota, the data is more match-focused.</p>
  <p>“For us, SAP HANA Cloud has more of a different function,” Jabbz said. “We use it mostly for performance-related things. I think the big advantage we have with the database is that we can actually import any public game that we want. Let’s say things have changed in a recent patch; we can make sure that we’re always up-to-date with how the meta is evolving. We also get to have a replay of every tournament game, so we can pick up all the information we need from any game, especially during live events. This is incredibly helpful. By having this tool available, you can quickly see how teams are adapting, how teams are thinking. I save a lot of time getting that information, whereas before I would have to open up the replays in the game and manually scroll through everything.”</p>
  <p>According to Haitham, being able to use real gameplay clips to corroborate the data – and vice versa – often helps build a stronger case for whatever argument he’s trying to make. Players are more inclined to believe the data once they have a reference point, which then allows them to gain a deeper understanding of the game.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="team-liquid-mining-rich-esports-data-to-help-players-managers-and-teams-compete-and-win">Team Liquid: Mining rich esports data to help players, managers, and teams compete and win</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/asset/dynamic/2023/07/c4e4d3c9-807e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“With SAP, we have a lot of good [visualization] tools,” Haitham said. “We have an entire map tool that will just visualize where the wards are and what the movement is looking like. In addition, we have SAP Analytics Cloud that gives us an opportunity to build charts and graphs for the players. I would use videos or clips that are important to show the opponent’s style, and then I support that with the maps or graphs from the SAP tools.”</p>
  <p>For some, all these details might sound small, even insignificant. However, any coach or analyst will tell you that at the highest level of esports, the difference lies in the details. When pretty much every player is equal in skill, it’s those minor advantages that matter – which makes data analysis an important factor for success. After all, a close win is still a win. Both Haitham and Jabbz point to “the small margins” as the reasons why they love their roles as analysts.</p>
  <p>“Personally, I work on my own goal to help others achieve theirs at the same time,” Haitham said. “Seeing how players are able to use science while playing video games, to beat opponents that they may not be able to without that kind of information…it just makes everything worthwhile.”</p>
  <p>“I agree. I think it’s always very satisfying to give information to the guys that they wouldn’t pick up on,” Jabbz added. “I guess we’re very similar in that regard. I also enjoy helping the guys and that’s what gives me the joy in this job. I don’t necessarily have to see myself in the limelight or at the front of the stage, but I really just like seeing my friends succeed.”</p>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18e500dd487b8be270a967b15b532213f90828dbe.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18e500dd487b8be270a967b15b532213f90828dbe.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_18e500dd487b8be270a967b15b532213f90828dbe.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Team Liquid: Masters of Data" src="./media_18e500dd487b8be270a967b15b532213f90828dbe.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://youtu.be/5BZYCILkR6o">Team Liquid: Masters of Data</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>Isabelle Schuhmacher is director of Global Sponsorships at SAP.<br>Christian Kreidt is storytelling lead for Global Sponsorships at SAP.</p>
        <p>Photos courtesy of Team Liquid.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-sap-news-delivered-right-to-your-inbox">Get the latest SAP news delivered right to your inbox</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/nl/sap-news-center-newsletter/index.html">Sign up</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/data-analytics</category>
            <category>news-tag/database-and-data-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/esports</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-hana-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-sponsorships</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How HCLTech Uses SAP BTP Innovations to Combat Water Scarcity]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/hcltech-uses-sap-btp-combat-water-scarcity</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/hcltech-uses-sap-btp-combat-water-scarcity</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP partner and global tech company HCLTech is tackling the problem of water scarcity with its AquaSphere solution. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/blockchain</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-datasphere</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sustainable Coffee: Farming for a Better Future]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/sustainable-coffee-agri-evolve-farming-for-future</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/sustainable-coffee-agri-evolve-farming-for-future</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Agri Evolve is a social enterprise that uses SAP digital technology to improve established supply chains for coffee cherries in Uganda.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/agribusiness</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-rural-sourcing-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Kemira Leaps Forward with SAP and cbs Corporate Business Solutions]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/kemira-leaps-forward-with-sap-and-cbs</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/kemira-leaps-forward-with-sap-and-cbs</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Industrial enterprise Kemira launched its digital business process platform based on SAP with help from cbs Corporate Business Solutions.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/chemicals</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-datasphere</category>
            <category>product/sap-integration-suite</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Roche Connects Asset Data to Contextualize and Improve Every Decision]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/roche-asset-data-contextualize-improve-decisions</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/roche-asset-data-contextualize-improve-decisions</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Pharmaceutical company Roche has been improving its asset management and maintenance processes with the help of SAP solutions.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f4368188f69034eaee3b53188d1e3cd047f4908b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f4368188f69034eaee3b53188d1e3cd047f4908b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1f4368188f69034eaee3b53188d1e3cd047f4908b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Roche Connects Asset Data to Contextualize and Improve Every Decision" src="./media_1f4368188f69034eaee3b53188d1e3cd047f4908b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="roche-connects-asset-data-to-contextualize-and-improve-every-decision">Roche Connects Asset Data to Contextualize and Improve Every Decision</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>In a recent webinar, Iago Accioli, project manager of Assets at Roche, discussed how the pharmaceutical company has been improving its asset management and maintenance processes from a broader supply chain perspective.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="https://www.roche.com/about/">Roche</a> is one of the world’s largest biotech companies, a leading provider of in-vitro diagnostics and a global supplier of transformative, innovative solutions across major disease areas.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="find-a-balance-between-performance-cost-and-risk-with-sap-asset-performance-management">Find a balance between performance, cost, and risk with SAP Asset Performance Management</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/apm.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="cost-as-a-main-driver-for-asset-intensive-organizations">Cost as a Main Driver for Asset-Intensive Organizations</h2>
  <p>“As a pharmaceutical company, Roche was founded more than 100 years ago in Basel, Switzerland, with both pharma and diagnostics divisions. We are in the middle of an <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/s4hana.html">SAP S/4HANA</a> journey with the goal to harmonize business processes on all sites and divisions around the world,” said Accioli.</p>
  <p>To <a href="/topics/asset-management">manage assets</a> under volatile conditions effectively, just like other asset-intensive organizations, Roche focuses on <strong>reducing maintenance cost</strong> and <strong>increasing asset reliability</strong>, which are key to its customers and patients.</p>
  <p>The challenge is “the handover from original manufacturer to engineering to maintenance and how to interact with each other,” explained Accioli. “We resolve this with these business process harmonization initiatives.”</p>
  <h2 id="risk-resilience-as-an-investment-for-the-future">Risk Resilience as an Investment for the Future</h2>
  <p>SAP suggests three strategies to help companies manage their business holistically, including cost, speed, profit, customer service, and risk:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Connecting supply chains</strong> to the entire business so that information insight flows go quickly from operations to manufacturing, design, and into the business to respond to disruptions</li>
    <li><strong>Contextualizing information</strong> during the work process to equip users with technology to get real-time insights and make decisions during the business process to increase impact</li>
    <li><strong>Collaborating externally</strong> with suppliers, asset operators, OEMs, and logistics providers to ensure that information is flowing beyond the internal network to set up a risk-resilient business while mitigating risk</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="closing-the-loop-between-strategy-and-execution">Closing the Loop Between Strategy and Execution</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="watch-a-video-to-learn-more-about-enterprise-asset-management">Watch a video to learn more about enterprise asset management</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2020/10/9870e39a-b97d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Managing costs and increasing equipment reliability is a major factor and closing the loop between asset strategy and maintenance execution, such as to make assets more reliable and connected to maintenance execution considering different asset type, is a big opportunity.</p>
  <p>“Five to 10 years ago, reliability engineering became a shining topic at Roche, and we discussed where to start, how much we spend on maintenance, what our most important assets were, and where we should spend more energy and money. We standardized processes to classify our equipment into different asset criticalities – high, medium, and low – and, based on each category, we established a maintenance strategy,” explained Accioli.</p>
  <p>“Afterwards, we looked for a tool that would best suit Roche given the amount of data. Now we have an asset and maintenance strategy in place that is reflected in our system. In 2019, we started harmonizing our processes and were pleased that SAP solutions could support us,” he continued.</p>
  <p>In particular, Roche looked to:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/asset-strategy-performance.html">SAP Asset Strategy and Performance Management</a>, which helps with performing criticality evaluations directly in the SAP system instead of spreadsheets. With criticality results reflected in the system, the maintenance strategy can result in preventive maintenance plans. “Roche is in the middle of the journey. No sites are live yet,” said Accioli. Roche is also enabling access to its service providers to get design insights and improve collaboration.</li>
    <li><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/asset-manager.html">SAP Service and Asset Manager</a>, which enables maintenance plans and work orders to be accessible to maintenance technicians so that they can make instant material reservations and get access to maintenance manuals on mobile devices.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>“I expect a significant <strong>decrease of maintenance execution</strong> as we can plan our work better thanks to a mobile-supported solution,” said Accioli. “The experience with the solution is quite good.”</p>
  <p>Roche was already using SAP at different sites with its own work order types and data model, but it was not automated and connected.</p>
  <p>“We also intend to migrate to <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/apm.html">SAP Asset Performance Management</a>, a successor cloud-based application, where Roche’s enhancement ideas have been incorporated,” explained the manager.</p>
  <h2 id="connected-asset-data-helps-contextualize-business-decisions">Connected Asset Data Helps Contextualize Business Decisions</h2>
  <p>For contextualizing every business process through the eyes of maintenance, it is necessary to converge enterprise IT data with equipment and sensor data to run analyses based on algorithms and machine learning technology. Accioli explained: “Being able to schedule maintenance activities is a substantial improvement for maintenance organizations. To monitor both targets and results, we are using <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/cloud-analytics/features.html">SAP Analytics Cloud</a>, which has many good capabilities. We are developing maintenance KPIs with the insights we get from artificial intelligence (AI) and rolling these back into the asset strategy and reliability process. These are particularly good tools.”</p>
  <h2 id="effective-collaboration-across-the-ecosystem-to-build-a-collaborative-supply-chain">Effective Collaboration Across the Ecosystem to Build a Collaborative Supply Chain</h2>
  <p>“For Roche, sharing information and effective collaboration with asset providers and across our ecosystem is particularly important. Vendors and different equipment suppliers must exchange and collaborate on asset data. Operators and service providers should be able to use the network but also manage the work order process,” said Accioli.</p>
  <p>To summarize, the key benefits of SAP Asset Strategy and Performance Management and SAP Service and Asset Manager Accioli sees are:</p>
  <p><strong>SAP Asset Strategy and Performance Management:</strong></p>
  <ul>
    <li>Defining which maintenance strategy applies to which classification of equipment</li>
    <li>Maintaining assessments in the system</li>
    <li>Generating criticality based on assessments</li>
    <li>Reflecting reliability-centered maintenance in the system, including decision trees and supportive templates</li>
  </ul>
  <p><strong>SAP Service and Asset Manager:</strong></p>
  <ul>
    <li>Being a digitized, automated, paperless solution</li>
    <li>Being able to work offline</li>
    <li>Having all maintenance data at hand in one place</li>
  </ul>
  <p>Listen to the webinar recording <a href="https://event.on24.com/eventRegistration/console/apollox/mainEvent?&#x26;eventid=4174635&#x26;sessionid=1&#x26;username=&#x26;partnerref=&#x26;format=fhvideo1&#x26;mobile=&#x26;flashsupportedmobiledevice=&#x26;helpcenter=&#x26;key=56D188F6DDC0731803732D04D9287E5F&#x26;newConsole=true&#x26;nxChe=true&#x26;newTabCon=true&#x26;consoleEarEventConsole=false&#x26;text_language_id=en&#x26;playerwidth=748&#x26;playerheight=526&#x26;eventuserid=616413864&#x26;contenttype=A&#x26;mediametricsessionid=533671932&#x26;mediametricid=5886174&#x26;usercd=616413864&#x26;mode=launch">here</a>. In addition, watch this <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/asset-management-eam.html?video=9870e39a-b97d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff">overview video</a> to learn how to maximize asset health and performance with SAP Intelligent Asset Management solutions and read what <a href="https://www.sap.com/asset/dynamic/2022/09/77fdedf5-7bbb-4ed6-bc18-1d3febe209ca.html">benefits other enterprises achieved</a>. To know more about the role of service and asset management in your industry, <a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/dg/idc-info-brief-on-service-excellence/index.html">download this complimentary paper from IDC</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Karin Fent is senior director of Global Customer Success Digital Supply Chain at SAP.</em><br><em>Top photo credit: Roche</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/asset-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/enterprise-asset-management</category>
            <category>industry/life-sciences</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Standard Chartered Gains Agility with Total Workforce Management]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/standard-chartered-total-workforce-solution</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/standard-chartered-total-workforce-solution</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Standard Chartered uses total workforce management with SAP SuccessFactors and SAP Fieldglass for one view of permanent and external workers.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/banking</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/external-workforce-management</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fieldglass</category>
            <category>sap-award/sap-innovation-awards</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-employee-central</category>
            <category>news-tag/total-workforce-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Immediate Impacts of Video Data Stories]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/06/immediate-impacts-of-video-data-stories</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/06/immediate-impacts-of-video-data-stories</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Innovation Center Network is creating a solution that gives business users video data stories on activities relevant to their roles.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10243be8ae363277c6bd409d6e30d14f26e1ae31a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10243be8ae363277c6bd409d6e30d14f26e1ae31a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_10243be8ae363277c6bd409d6e30d14f26e1ae31a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="The Immediate Impacts of Video Data Stories" src="./media_10243be8ae363277c6bd409d6e30d14f26e1ae31a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="the-immediate-impacts-of-video-data-stories">The Immediate Impacts of Video Data Stories</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>When it comes to offering audiences engaging and easy-to-consume content, platforms like Instagram and TikTok lead the way. In the world of business, too, storytelling-on-the-go has huge potential. SAP Innovation Center Network is creating a solution that helps address this opportunity.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“We want to enable companies to share business insights fast and in a fresh and immediate way,” says Michael Wittmann, senior developer at <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/innovation/icn.html">SAP Innovation Center Network</a>, on the rationale behind the data storytelling solution he and his team are working on.</p>
  <p>The purpose is to provide business users with short, animated “video data stories” about the key activities relevant to their individual roles.</p>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1410d1fd13d29b717e5aedbf0a9a0f05f3c0d034e.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1410d1fd13d29b717e5aedbf0a9a0f05f3c0d034e.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1410d1fd13d29b717e5aedbf0a9a0f05f3c0d034e.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Video Data Stories: The Smartest Way to Stay Updated" src="./media_1410d1fd13d29b717e5aedbf0a9a0f05f3c0d034e.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=G0yrL-E9p5A">Video Data Stories: The Smartest Way to Stay Updated</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Eye-catching videos that are 10 to 15 seconds long will mean that users won’t have to refer to dashboards or wade through reports as they do today. Built-in templates for the most common business processes will enable anyone to create their own video data story and link it to their data sources. No design or programming experience is required.</p>
  <p>The solution’s video data stories apply the same user experience principles as other content-sharing platforms. New videos are displayed in chronological order, and viewers can navigate easily through the different parts of a story or skip entire stories that are not relevant to them.</p>
  <p>By incorporating animated visualizations, users can show changes in data over a specific time period dynamically. If more details are needed, they can point the audience to the right people and include links to the data sources and applications.</p>
  <p>“One potential use case is sales reporting,” says Wittmann. Here, the solution has a predefined template that can be used to generate a personalized story for each sales accountant, showing how sales figures have changed over a defined period and including highlights and historical comparisons.</p>
  <p>“Other information, such as headcount growth, quarterly earnings, and fact sheets for communications and sales, can also be shared through video storytelling in a far more compelling way than in PDF files or PowerPoint,” continues Wittmann.</p>
  <p>The same applies to many of the e-mail notifications that land in our inboxes. Though not every notification needs a video data story. “It’s about finding the right balance,” notes Wittmann. “Instead of separate alerts for each event, you might receive a daily summary of the most important updates on a particular topic.”</p>
  <p>In principle, video data stories can translate their insights into animated videos like those on Instagram. Users can decide for which events and applications video data stories are generated. “For some scenarios, daily or weekly updates are best. For others, it might be when a particular threshold is exceeded or when other kinds of exceptions occur,” explains Wittmann.</p>
  <p>It is hard to imagine any department that would not benefit from this type of storytelling. Yet what might at first seem highly generic is in fact very individual.</p>
  <p>“Right now, business software is clearly moving toward hyper-personalization,” says Wittmann. “That is why we want our video data stories to be used not just to share generic content but also to be tailorable to the individual viewer.”</p>
  <p>Examples of personalized content could be team members’ birthdays and reports indicating how many of a manager’s direct reports have completed the latest compliance training.</p>
  <p>“At the moment, we’re still defining the product,” says Wittmann. “We are working on a first version of an <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform.html">SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP)</a> service that can generate videos from different applications. We have also teamed up with colleagues from <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/cloud-analytics.html">SAP Analytics Cloud</a> to create an initial integration function for exporting video data stories directly from an analytics story.”</p>
  <p>At SAP, Wittmann and his team have been working mainly with the Customer, Competitive, and Market Insights (CMI) team. In an early prototype, stories were generated weekly for a specific solution area to see which topics were seeing the most customer demand.</p>
  <p>In another pilot project, the team is testing personalized video data stories for the sales organization. Here, account executives receive stories with updates on the specific customers they serve.</p>
  <p>“We are really keen to trial the solution with customers to learn which use cases they might have, how they want to tell those stories, and where we can best integrate this capability,” says Wittmann.</p>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div>To find out more about video data stories, get in touch with us at <a href="mailto:icn@sap.com">icn@sap.com</a>.</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>Jeanette Rohr is a brand journalist at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-innovation-center-network</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Data and Analytics Solutions Earn Multiple 2023 Best Of Awards from TrustRadius]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/06/sap-data-and-analytics-solutions-trustradius-awards</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/06/sap-data-and-analytics-solutions-trustradius-awards</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP data and analytics solutions have won multiple Best Of awards from TrustRadius, recognizing our excellence in the industry. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/data-analytics</category>
            <category>news-tag/database-and-data-management</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-datasphere</category>
            <category>product/sap-hana-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/trustradius</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[AI Built for Business]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/sap-sapphire-business-ai</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/sap-sapphire-business-ai</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Turning AI technology advancement into business impact remains a challenge for many companies, SAP's unique approach to AI can help.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/financial-management</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/microsoft</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-digital-assistant</category>
            <category>product/sap-extended-warehouse-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>product/sap-signavio-process-manager</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-transportation-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP and Google Cloud Expand Partnership to Build the Future of Open Data and AI for Enterprises]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/sap-google-cloud-expanded-partnership-open-data-ai-enterprises</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/sap-google-cloud-expanded-partnership-open-data-ai-enterprises</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP and Google Cloud are introducing an open data offering designed to simplify data landscapes and unleash the power of business data.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/google-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/machine-learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-datasphere</category>
            <category>product/sap-hana-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Three Key Highlights from the Gartner Data & Analytics Summit 2023]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/three-key-highlights-gartner-data-analytics-summit</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/three-key-highlights-gartner-data-analytics-summit</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[At the Gartner Data & Analytics Summit attendees explored recent data and analytics trends, technologies, and strategies, like SAP Datasphere.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/data-analytics</category>
            <category>news-tag/data-fabric</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-datasphere</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sports and the Metaverse: A Revolutionary Convergence for Inclusion]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/sports-and-metaverse-revolutionary-convergence-inclusivity</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/sports-and-metaverse-revolutionary-convergence-inclusivity</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With the metaverse taking shape, corporations can now use intelligent software to create virtual sporting worlds for inclusivity. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>news-tag/esports</category>
            <category>news-tag/metaverse</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-hana-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-sports-one</category>
            <category>industry/sports-entertainment</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Vodafone Builds Its Future-Ready Workforce on Cloud HR Foundations]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/vodafone-builds-cloud-hr-foundations</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/vodafone-builds-cloud-hr-foundations</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Vodafone Group Plc implements SAP SuccessFactors solutions as its cloud HR foundation for improved efficiency and employee engagement.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fieldglass</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-learning</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-work-zone</category>
            <category>sap-event/successconnect</category>
            <category>news-tag/total-workforce-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP a Leader in New IDC MarketScape for Worldwide Enterprise Planning]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/01/idc-marketscape-worldwide-enterprise-planning-sap-a-leader</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/01/idc-marketscape-worldwide-enterprise-planning-sap-a-leader</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is a leader in the IDC MarketScape for Worldwide Enterprise Planning, Budgeting, and Forecasting Applications 2022 Vendor Assessment.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/enterprise-performance-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sustainable Salmon Farming and the Future of Digital Procurement]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/evonik-industries-digital-procurement</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/evonik-industries-digital-procurement</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Digitalization frees up procurement to stay on top of fast-changing market conditions, including finding suppliers in unexpected disruptions.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>industry/chemicals</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/digitalization</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Great Resignation Points to a Serious Sustainability Issue]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/great-resignation-serious-sustainability-issue</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/great-resignation-serious-sustainability-issue</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The Great Resignation is a sustainability warning to companies that have not focused on culture and leadership for a while. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/people-sustainability</category>
            <category>news-tag/qualtrics</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-workforce-analytics</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Measuring the Carbon Footprint of Employees Can Help You Make More Informed and Strategic Business Decisions]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/measuring-employee-carbon-footprint-business-decisions</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/measuring-employee-carbon-footprint-business-decisions</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Executives can make informed decisions when considering the social and actual carbon footprint of employees in planning. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/experience-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/people-sustainability</category>
            <category>news-tag/qualtrics</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-product-footprint-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-employee-central</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-people-analytics</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-workforce-analytics</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>