<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/fashion/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Celebrating People’s Differences with Inclusive Fashion]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/06/celebrating-differences-inclusive-fashion</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/06/celebrating-differences-inclusive-fashion</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The fashion industry is just one example of how SAP helps customers stay ahead of market dynamics and industry innovation and convergence.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/fashion</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-experience-center</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Power of Personalization in an Increasingly Digital World]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/power-of-personalization-in-increasingly-digital-world</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/power-of-personalization-in-increasingly-digital-world</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Personalization, enabled by SAP solutions, can build relationships, increase customer lifetime value, and enhance customer engagement.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/fashion</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
            <category>product/sap-commerce-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-customer-data-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-emarsys-customer-engagement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-experience-center</category>
            <category>product/sap-intelligent-returns-management</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-retail</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[From Plastic Waste to Sustainable Fashion with SAP Technology]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/from-plastic-waste-to-sustainable-fashion</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/from-plastic-waste-to-sustainable-fashion</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP technology can enable the transformation of environmental challenges into integral parts of a circular, sustainable fashion industry.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15595eab68610ea118c43af38c7b0ee3298792db4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15595eab68610ea118c43af38c7b0ee3298792db4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_15595eab68610ea118c43af38c7b0ee3298792db4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="From Plastic Waste to Sustainable Fashion with SAP Technology" src="./media_15595eab68610ea118c43af38c7b0ee3298792db4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="from-plastic-waste-to-sustainable-fashion-with-sap-technology">From Plastic Waste to Sustainable Fashion with SAP Technology</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="helping-consumers-retailers-and-the-environment">Helping Consumers, Retailers, and the Environment</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/07/sap-intelligent-returns-management-consumers-retailers-environment">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>For decades it has been clear that the Earth’s climate is changing and our influence on the environment is undisputed. The latest UN (IPCC) <a href="https://news.un.org/en/story/2021/08/1097362">report</a> is the most dire warning ever issued on climate change and a wake-up call for all of us to realize that we can only ensure a sustainable future by taking action.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As a frontrunner in the sustainability movement, SAP has a crucial role to play as an exemplar – such as <a href="/2021/03/sap-carbon-neutrality-goal-2023">committing to become carbon neutral by 2023</a> – as well as in helping businesses unlock their potential growth. This is possible through optimizing circular business models with practical and scalable SAP solutions such as <a href="https://youtu.be/AGLb0VzHRO4">SAP Product Footprint Management</a>, which enables companies to account for greenhouse gas emissions in their end-to-end business processes. While SAP’s focus is on innovations that help customers become more sustainable, we as individuals should lead by example by taking steps that lead to a more sustainable living, such as using alternative modes of transportation or reducing single-use plastics.</p>
  <p>Following the vision of a <a href="https://insights.sap.com/what-is-circular-economy/">circular economy</a>, businesses and individuals are advised to set the focus on repurposing and reusing materials, following a cycle of make, use, return, and reuse.</p>
  <p>Achieving circular business models requires completely rethinking supply and value chains across industries to create end-to-end transparency. In the quest to turn waste into value, SAP developed <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/agriculture-supply-chain-mgmt.html?btp=f206a795-9c52-4614-91ea-8928281922e2">SAP Rural Sourcing Management</a>, a solution that can improve visibility into resources across value chains, helping companies understand, control, and manage their impact on the environment. For example, it is estimated that the fashion industry is responsible for <a href="https://www.downtoearth.org.in/news/environment/fashion-industry-may-use-quarter-of-world-s-carbon-budget-by-2050-61183">10% of global carbon emissions</a>, and, according to UNFCCC, the sector’s emissions are to <a href="https://unfccc.int/news/fashion-industry-un-pursue-climate-action-for-sustainable-development">rise by more than 60% by 2030</a> if transformation towards a sustainable fashion industry fails to materialize soon.</p>
  <p>A great use case where the SAP Rural Sourcing Management solution helps streamline the journey to a circular economy is through a sustainable network of businesses, connecting plastic waste collectors in Ghana with recycling companies, manufacturers, brands, and consumers of fashion. In Africa <a href="/2020/10/minimize-plastic-waste-in-ghana-domestic-recycling">less than 20% of plastic waste is being recycled</a>, while the European Union sets a target of 50% by 2025. Ghana has committed to turn this issue into an opportunity by creating a domestic recycling industry that creates jobs as well as supports a clean environment. In urban areas of countries such as Ghana, waste collecting is a means of survival. However, many urban dwellers have poor visibility into the market price of the collected materials, leaving them vulnerable to imposed pricing.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="the-balance-sheet-blind-spot-how-sustainability-affects-competitiveness-and-profits">The Balance Sheet Blind Spot: How Sustainability Affects Competitiveness and Profits</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://insights.sap.com/environmental-sustainability-affects-competitiveness/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Through the implementation of <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/agriculture-supply-chain-mgmt.html?btp=f206a795-9c52-4614-91ea-8928281922e2">SAP Rural Sourcing Management</a>, waste collectors in Ghana can directly connect to waste aggregators to receive a fair and transparent wage. The plastic resources are then handed over to the recycling companies to transform it into reusable resources. Being transported to different factories and manufacturers, plastic can be used in the production of fashion items. Using <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/logistics-business-network.html">SAP Logistics Business Network</a>, full traceability can be achieved along the entire supply chain to help ensure expectations and standards for sustainable production and fair conditions are met.</p>
  <p>To connect and manage the business operations steps within any fashion business, SAP supports brands and retailers that want to capture and control the value of products after sale with recommerce. The aim is to enable and connect recommerce-specific business processes that include buying back, managing, and reselling pre-owned inventory, as well as tracking key financial, customer, and sustainability performance indicators. Any fashion brand can maintain visibility and control re-commerce business to fully capture the opportunities at stake – a profitable reselling business, positive environmental impact, customer acquisition, and expansion of the customer lifetime value.</p>
  <p>SAP technology provides solutions that can transform serious environmental challenges, such as plastic waste, into integral parts of the circular economy. It can bring people and businesses with shared values together to jointly create a more sustainable value chain, where products are used, returned, reused, and given a new purpose.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Katrin Lehmann is head of Customer Innovation and Maintenance at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-emissions</category>
            <category>industry/consumer-goods-cpg</category>
            <category>news-tag/fashion</category>
            <category>product/sap-product-footprint-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Innovative Tech Helps Carhartt Meet Customer Demand]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/03/carhartt-innovative-tech-customer-demand</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/03/carhartt-innovative-tech-customer-demand</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Behind the scenes at Carhartt, technology transformation with SAP became crucial to keep up with fast-paced growth. Hear their story.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_163ce6b3539a057f2c0d6cee58f4632e958447132.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_163ce6b3539a057f2c0d6cee58f4632e958447132.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_163ce6b3539a057f2c0d6cee58f4632e958447132.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Innovative Tech Helps Carhartt Meet Customer Demand" src="./media_163ce6b3539a057f2c0d6cee58f4632e958447132.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="innovative-tech-helps-carhartt-meet-customer-demand">Innovative Tech Helps Carhartt Meet Customer Demand</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>What do hard workers on the job site have in common with A-list celebrities? <a href="https://www.carhartt.com/">Carhartt</a>. From construction workers and farmers to firefighters and tradespeople, some of the hardest-working people on the planet rely on Carhartt. Now, perhaps surprisingly, rappers, movie stars, and models are also choosing Carhartt to make a fashion statement.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“When a celebrity wears our product, it certainly creates a buzz around the company,” said Carhartt CIO John Hill. “It raises brand awareness and exposes products that some consumers may not be aware of.”</p>
  <p>Behind the scenes, technology transformation became crucial for Carhartt to keep up with fast-paced growth. So, after more than 130 years in business and continued growth in popularity, it became imperative for U.S.-based company to transform both its apparel offerings and its business foundation.</p>
  <p>“It’s important to realize that Carhartt was as far away from a virtual company as you could be,” Hill said. “We quickly realized that not only did we need to transform our technology, but also the processes that the technology was enabling. We identified hundreds of pain points that existed across that value chain. And if we can get rid of those pain points with SAP technology, ultimately we were going to provide a better experience for our associates and our customers.”</p>
  <p>After thoroughly researching different options, Carhartt realized tapping the power of SAP’s intelligent enterprise was the best solution. Yet this hugely innovative upgrade coincided with one of the biggest challenges of our time; believe it or not, Carhartt went live during the worst of the pandemic.</p>
  <h2 id="closing-shop-was-never-an-option">Closing Shop Was Never an Option</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="video-for-carhartt-happy-customers-benefit-from-a-digitally-native-brand-experience">Video: For Carhartt, Happy Customers Benefit from a Digitally Native Brand Experience</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/covid-19/back-to-best.html?=campaigncode=CRM-YD21-SOC-CUSTREF&#x26;video=1ccc2b2a-d57d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>It was a top priority for Carhartt to remain open and provide a frictionless shopping experience for customers, ensuring there was no downtime and no negative impacts on business. “At the end of the day, the brand needs to be able to react to the demands of those customers. Ultimately the customer doesn’t care what it takes to deliver,” said Hill.</p>
  <p>With his office closed, Hill’s technology team prepared to go live while they worked from their homes.</p>
  <p>“You can’t underestimate the challenge of doing a large scale of digital transformation, while you’re growing the business at the pace we are, and still serving customers,” said Hill.</p>
  <p>Yet, he shares that bringing SAP technology online proved easy.</p>
  <p>“Frankly, the harder thing in dealing with a pandemic has been there’s no blueprint of how to plan,” Hill shared. “We were taking down our revenue on a weekly basis, and then increasing it the next week. So it was a very difficult year from that perspective. The actual technology transformation felt like a more normal course of business during the year.”</p>
  <h2 id="strained-supply-chains">Strained Supply Chains</h2>
  <p>Businesses across the planet share Carhartt’s forecasting challenges.</p>
  <p>“People know what they want and they want it when they want it,” said President of SAP North America DJ Paoni. “And they know how they want it. Every customer in every industry has acknowledged that <a href="/covid-19">COVID-19</a> has put the maturing of the global economy on fast-forward. So those companies that have a more sophisticated digital technology are certainly able to pivot faster and connect with their customers on a whole new level.”</p>
  <p>Carhartt believes further investment in digital technologies is a winning strategy that will also provide a fantastic experience for customers.</p>
  <p>“So far, we implemented SAP solutions to support our retail businesses,” said Hill. “This year, we will be implementing solutions to support our wholesale and our direct-to-consumer e-commerce business. I believe that the marketplace has continued to reward those customers that deliver not only a great product, but also a digitally native experience.”</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <table>
          <thead>
            <tr>
              <th colspan="2">Promo</th>
            </tr>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td>
                <h3 id="understand-tomorrows-trends-drive-personalized-shopping-and-run-a-sustainable-fashion-business">Understand tomorrow’s trends, drive personalized shopping and run a sustainable fashion business</h3>
              </td>
              <td><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/fashion-apparel.html">Learn more</a></strong></td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
        <h3 id="meet-carhartt-cio-john-hill-and-hear-the-advicehe-shares-with-his-peers-on-getting-real-with-sap">Meet Carhartt CIO John Hill and hear the advicehe shares with his peers on <a href="https://www.sap.com/covid-19/back-to-best.html?=campaigncode=CRM-YD21-SOC-CUSTREF&#x26;video=1ccc2b2a-d57d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff">Getting Real with SAP</a>.</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2021/03/24/innovative-tech-helps-carhartt-meet-customer-demand/?sh=654825a85117">This story originally appeared on SAP BrandVoice on Forbes</a>.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="make-your-organization-more-resilient-and-agile-in-todays-challenging-environment-get-back-to-best-with-sap">Make your organization more resilient and agile in today’s challenging environment: Get back to best with SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/covid-19/back-to-best.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/accenture</category>
            <category>news-tag/back-to-best</category>
            <category>industry/consumer-goods-cpg</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/e-commerce</category>
            <category>news-tag/fashion</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Three Steps to Circularity in Fashion Retail]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/01/three-steps-circularity-sustainable-fashion-retail</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/01/three-steps-circularity-sustainable-fashion-retail</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Disruptions in 2020 have moved us to a new era of sustainable fashion retail. Learn how companies are finding innovative ways to circularity.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/circular-economy</category>
            <category>industry/consumer-goods-cpg</category>
            <category>news-tag/fashion</category>
            <category>news-tag/nrf</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Fashion Retailers Test Their Limits During a Pandemic]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/01/fashion-retail-during-covid-rtailers-test-limits</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/01/fashion-retail-during-covid-rtailers-test-limits</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[For fashion retail during COVID-19, questions about demand arose. Learn how SAP solutions can help address them.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/consumer-goods-cpg</category>
            <category>news-tag/fashion</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>