<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/innovation/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Four SAP Customers Are Successfully Driving Transformation in Their Businesses]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-sapphire-sap-customers-drive-business-transformation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-sapphire-sap-customers-drive-business-transformation</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In their SAP Sapphire keynote, Scott Russell and Thomas Saueressig talked to four customers about using SAP to deliver high-value results.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c4521f798d991573b94b36fd1f60cfe20d3399cf.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c4521f798d991573b94b36fd1f60cfe20d3399cf.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1c4521f798d991573b94b36fd1f60cfe20d3399cf.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="How Four SAP Customers Are Successfully Driving Transformation in Their Businesses" src="./media_1c4521f798d991573b94b36fd1f60cfe20d3399cf.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="how-four-sap-customers-are-successfully-driving-transformation-in-their-businesses">How Four SAP Customers Are Successfully Driving Transformation in Their Businesses</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>This week at SAP Sapphire, four industry-leading companies joined SAP Executive Board Members Scott Russell and Thomas Saueressig on stage in Orlando to discuss how they are using SAP technology to deliver high-value results for their businesses.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="taking-business-to-the-next-level-in-the-era-of-ai">Taking Business to the Next Level in the Era of AI</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/events/sapphire/news-guide.html">Read the news guide</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Russell told the crowd that customer stories and conversations is what SAP Sapphire is all about, saying that what makes the event special is having “a collective group that comes together, both here in the room and virtually, and being able to understand how SAP can bring out your best.”</p>
  <p>Russell emphasized that the news from SAP Sapphire is a “demonstration of our commitment to continually innovate, to continually strive to bring more creative value to your business.”</p>
  <p>He noted that a perfect example of this is the announcement that <a href="/2024/06/sap-enters-agreement-to-acquire-walkme">SAP has entered into an agreement to acquire WalkMe</a>, a leader in digital adoption platforms. Reflecting on the acquisition, Russell said “We are obsessed not only about great applications and great platforms to deliver value for your business, we also care passionately about the transformation journey to get there.”</p>
  <p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/live/ZZ1yFoALzAs?si=mbPWUzgttHga-_PR">Embed from www.youtube.com</a></p>
  <p>As Chief Revenue Officer, Russell noted that every day 300 million people log on to SAP cloud applications to run their businesses. “And obviously we can never take that for granted,” he said. “You have choice, you have options. We strive to be at our best to help you be at yours. The way we measure success is in your terms, because ultimately [as a] market leader in business AI, we hold ourselves to the highest standards. Why? Because that’s what you expect.”</p>
  <p>A big part of the transformation journey many customers are taking is moving to the cloud with RISE with SAP. “We are super proud of our cloud journey and [that] we are helping you transform your business,” Russell said. “More than 6,000 customers have already moved to RISE with SAP. Of those 6,000 customers in the last 12 months, over 1,000 have already gone live.”</p>
  <h2 id="puretech-scientific-speed-and-scalability-is-key">PureTech Scientific: Speed and Scalability is Key</h2>
  <p>Russell was first joined on stage by Brian Hardee, CIO of <a href="https://www.puretechscientific.com/">PureTech Scientific LLC</a>, a global leader in the production of glycolic acid used in a variety of industries and applications. As a recent carve-out by a private equity owner from a much larger global manufacturer, PureTech had to quickly migrate its operations to its own systems. But without an IT team of its own this was initially a daunting challenge. The new company chose SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition because of its many benefits.</p>
  <p>“For us, it was an easy choice because first, we have no IT team,” Hardee said. “We have no internal training team, and we also had a very tight timeline with respect to the exit. So, we needed a solution that would enable us to move forward with speed, efficiency, and scalability. I could be confident that the infrastructure was being managed and secure. And that left us with an awesome choice for growth as well.”</p>
  <p>Scalability and rapid implementation were key factors in the choice of GROW with SAP, Hardee noted: “It was a great fit and gave us a platform for scalability for future bolt-ons, acquisitions, and so forth. So that’s the main reason. And SAP has an awesome suite of tools that enable that rapid implementation. And there was no other way we were going to do it without an internal IT team and without the access to the training material and the testing and so on.”</p>
  <p>And speaking of rapid implementation, PureTech went live on SAP in just 15 weeks, standardizing a business with an 85-year history on a common platform. Hardee gave some advice on how to make a project successful: “Use the tool set that SAP provides – SAP Activate methodology does work! And if you have the opportunity, sign up for the SAP Preferred Success program because it gives you a direct line to someone in SAP so that if you or your integrator doesn’t know the answer, SAP can point you to the right direction very quickly. So that helps with the speed of transformation.”</p>
  <h2 id="tropicana-brands-group-all-about-agility-and-time">Tropicana Brands Group: All About Agility and Time</h2>
  <p>Tropicana is a household name to many consumers, known chiefly for its juice and other beverage products. But while the brand is more than 75 years old, <a href="https://www.tropicanabrandsgroup.com/">Tropicana Brands Group</a> is just a bit over two years old, having been recently spun-off as a stand-alone group.</p>
  <p>Jeff Lischett, CIO of the US$3 billion organization, joined Russell to talk about how his company relied on RISE with SAP to make its “Project Harvest” IT separation and transformation project successful.</p>
  <p>Lischett noted that speed and agility was the key value proposition for the project. “We needed a platform that was able to accelerate, move with us, pivot with us, as we were going through this in a very accelerated timeline,” he said. “When you bring the technology and couple it with the unified business architecture powered by SAP, the choice for us was clearly RISE with SAP. Tropicana really needed a fit for purpose. Where we came from was going to be entirely different than where we were going, and this modern ERP, in terms of leaner, simpler, more streamlined ways of working, was really at the core of what we needed across the value chain.”</p>
  <p>Tropicana Brands Group took its European business operations live on SAP just 11 months after it started the design work, followed by North America three months later. “That was pressure testing!” Lischett said. “In just over a year, we had a fully implemented, end-to-end digital core and technology foundation for Tropicana Brands. We have a technology and a platform now that is really going to – no pun intended – rise to meet the challenge of our growth ambition.”</p>
  <p>“Ruthless prioritization” and change management were key to the project’s success, Lischett said. “I’m the biggest evangelist and advocate of change management,” he said. “You need it. You need it at the front, you need it during, you need it at the end. One thing that I would’ve probably done slightly differently is [to have] stayed with it longer at the end.”</p>
  <p>Tropicana is already seeing the impact of the project and specifically its focus on a clean core. “The most impactful value we’ve seen [goes] back to that clean core,” Lischett said. “Just in the months that followed, the ability to … bring the development forward, to build on top of the core that we have with enhancements and optimizing at a speed ratio that you just haven’t seen.”</p>
  <p>When asked about what role AI will play in his company, Lischett focused mainly on the human side of the technology. “Ironically, from the standpoint of being a technologist … AI in my mind, in terms of how I lead it, [needs to be] human-centered first and foremost, ensuring that we’ve got the right culture, responsible use, and effective use,” he said. “The gift of time is really the value creator that I see in AI and being able to work more efficiently and being able to take that time and translate it into what matters to you.”</p>
  <h2 id="responsibly-enabling-critical-systems">Responsibly Enabling Critical Systems</h2>
  <p>Russell handed over the stage to Saueressig, who recently launched the <a href="/2024/04/cloud-transformation-adoption-revolution-expectations-outcomes-meet">new Customer Services &#x26; Delivery Board area</a>. Saueressig noted that 25% of the world’s commerce already runs through more than 6,000 RISE with SAP customers worldwide, and that SAP supports the most critical business processes on the planet.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <picture>
          <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1dc5f09272052858aaeb01a0eec06423efb162249.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
          <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1dc5f09272052858aaeb01a0eec06423efb162249.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
          <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1dc5f09272052858aaeb01a0eec06423efb162249.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
          <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_1dc5f09272052858aaeb01a0eec06423efb162249.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="683">
        </picture>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>With that comes “the responsibility and the accountability to provide you with the most reliable and secure infrastructure,” Saueressig said. “That’s the reason why we co-engineered together with our partners from AWS, Microsoft Azure, Google Cloud Platform, and many others, to ensure that you have the highest level of quality and availability.”</p>
  <p>Echoing the theme of speed and adaptability, he noted that fast adoption of technology is critical. “Today, it’s not about the big fish that eats the small fish, it’s about the fast fish that eats the slow,” he cited. “At the end of the day, [our] ambition is to transform your system landscape to create a more flexible architecture, which enables fast adoption of innovations and ultimately, value realization. … And we take our responsibility seriously to really help you thrive in this ever-changing environment.”</p>
  <h2 id="fresenius-se-from-complexity-to-standardization">Fresenius SE: From Complexity to Standardization</h2>
  <p>Ingo Elfering, CIO of global healthcare conglomerate <a href="https://www.fresenius.com/">Fresenius</a>, knows something about speed: his team migrated 29 system landscapes containing more than 134 systems in less than 15 months. He joined Saueressig on stage to provide some insights into his company’s transformation project.</p>
  <p>As a company that has grown through many acquisitions, Fresenius had a highly heterogenous IT landscape. “We never quite integrated them,” Elfering said. “So, a really complex landscape …, [with] all sorts of interfaces and other applications attached to it. That was our starting point.”</p>
  <p>Fresenius’ management realized the company needed to change and become more efficient and effective to set itself up for ongoing success. It went all-in, doing four major transformations at the same time. As Elfering noted, “We not only did the RISE with SAP migration, we also did a complete cloud migration of our data centers worldwide; an outsourcing with a partner to become a more global team; and a global change of our network, including a whole bunch of security additions into our space.”</p>
  <p>Since it works in the healthcare and pharmaceutical space, Fresenius has a lot of regulatory requirements that it must adhere to, making the project more challenging than it might be in other industries. “You do a lot more technical documentation, testing, and so forth. So, from that perspective, regulations like GxP, good manufacturing or critical infrastructure, they were new to SAP in that instance in RISE with SAP. And we did it together. And I find that quite remarkable.”</p>
  <p>The <a href="/2023/06/fresenius-rise-with-sap-moves-sap-systems-cloud">new system has now been live</a> for just over a year and the company has seen many benefits. “We have a better speed on the underlying systems,” Elfering said. “We have a new infrastructure stack that works well. The main benefit for us will come as we [reinvent] the company. … We have some systems that doubled and tripled in size. So, it’s possible to leverage SAP quite quickly in these types of environments. From that perspective, I’m very happy with where we are. … We now have all the foundations in place to be able to execute our next phase of changes, our consolidation, our simplification, and in the cloud.”</p>
  <p>Finally, Elfering believes that healthcare is an area where AI can make a significant difference. “Healthcare always has been data-rich and insights-poor. … And the only way to get there, in our opinion at least, is to be on a cloud-based infrastructure in the first place. Because otherwise you don’t have the same performance or capabilities.”</p>
  <h2 id="clean-core-drives-agility">Clean Core Drives Agility</h2>
  <p>The idea of a “clean core” and a unified, simplified system underlies all these customer transformation stories. And it’s even more important in the context of agility and adaptability when it comes to taking advantage of the latest innovations in AI.</p>
  <p>“It’s super important for us to be clear that the clean core is not just for the sake of the clean core,” Saueressig said. “It’s a means to get to an innovation- and upgrade-ready system to be able to embrace these innovations. Because at the end of the day, legacy systems often have this technical depth that limits agility.”</p>
  <p>Saueressig admitted that even SAP has struggled with this, noting that the company had millions of lines of custom code in its systems. An internal analysis of all SAP customers showed that more than 65% of their custom code was unused in the past 12 months. “Code is also a liability, not just an asset,” he said. “And this is something we need to actively work against.”</p>
  <h2 id="hitachi-high-tech-corporation-clean-and-simple-benefits">Hitachi High-Tech Corporation: Clean and Simple Benefits</h2>
  <p>Saueressig invited Takuya Sakai, general manager of the Digital Transformation Business Group at <a href="https://www.hitachi-hightech.com/">Hitachi High-Tech</a>, on the stage to talk more about the benefits of system simplification and clean core. In 2019, Hitachi High-Tech <a href="https://www.sap.com/asset/dynamic/2023/07/d237f8b9-7e7e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">initiated a project</a> to simplify its business processes and digitize its management information. With its existing business processes fragmented across overseas sales offices, headquarters, and manufacturing sites, the organization needed to change to accelerate its business and set itself up for future growth. It chose SAP S/4HANA to help it build its new foundation for ongoing growth.</p>
  <p>Hitachi was running SAP R/3 but had significantly customized it with 9,000 add-ons across four instances, resulting in a lot of custom code. This resulted in many errors every day and large operational costs every year, Sakai said. And with the cost of validating so many add-ons, the company only did a major version update once in 12 years.</p>
  <p>To move to a more standardized and flexible system, Hitachi High-Tech adopted a two-tier architecture model. Taking advantage of development flexibility, the company deployed SAP S/4HANA Cloud Private Edition for its headquarters and group companies in Japan and SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition for its overseas sales offices. The adoption of SAP S/4HANA Cloud allows Hitachi High-Tech to take advantage of the functionality offered by SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP) for application development, data management, automation, integration, analytics, and AI.</p>
  <p>With the new system, Hitachi High-Tech reduced its 9,000 add-ons to just 750, allowing it to easily upgrade its ERP core. “Upgrading our old ERP took about a year and a half from the planning stage,” Sakai said. “However, with clean core, we can now do an upgrade every year in about 40 days. An upgrade every year keeps the clean core fresh and means new features can be delivered to our business quickly, like AI or process automation.”</p>
  <p>But achieving – and keeping – a clean core “requires patience,” Sakai said. Executives must understand the purpose of the transformation project and employees must overcome the pain that comes with a transformation project. “This is the most difficult thing,” he said. “The IT department must properly understand the new technology and suggest how to use it correctly. Then together we embark on the journey to the transformation.”</p>
  <h2 id="supporting-business-transformation-and-accelerating-time-to-value">Supporting Business Transformation and Accelerating Time to Value</h2>
  <p>Accelerating and improving time-to-value for customers is very important to SAP, according to Saueressig.</p>
  <p>“We are now bringing together all of our assets … in a seamless, end-to-end tool chain,” he said. “We want to holistically support your business transformation according to the dimensions of applications, data, processes, and people, which means we bring together and fully integrate SAP LeanIX for the IT landscapes and architecture, SAP Signavio for process management, SAP Cloud Application Lifecycle Management for application management and operational aspects, SAP BTP for integrations, and SAP Build for extensions, but also our telemetry tools, which we can leverage in the cloud.”</p>
  <p>Saueressig’s passion and ambition is to help customers drive innovation adoption. He noted that RISE with SAP is more than just a technical migration: it’s an offering for holistic business transformation as a service to accelerate value realization.</p>
  <p>“Ultimately, we want to help you to bring the best out of our entire holistic portfolio,” he said. “We want to help you to transform, realize agility at scale, achieve more across the entire value chain, and fundamentally transform operations with sustainability at the core. And this is something where I feel that we have a huge opportunity together to make that a reality.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-news-and-coverage-from-sap-sapphire-in-2024">Get the latest news and coverage from SAP Sapphire in 2024</h3>
        <p><em><a href="/topics/sap-sapphire">Read more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/grow-with-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[End-to-End Innovation Is Key to Bringing Out Your Best]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-sapphire-innovation-key-to-bring-out-your-best</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-sapphire-innovation-key-to-bring-out-your-best</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In their keynote, Juergen Mueller and Muhammad Alam demoed and discussed the latest innovations out of SAP Sapphire in 2024.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e38256295162fd6aa4582f624a1a9f11f0f8543b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e38256295162fd6aa4582f624a1a9f11f0f8543b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1e38256295162fd6aa4582f624a1a9f11f0f8543b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="End-to-End Innovation Is Key to Bringing Out Your Best" src="./media_1e38256295162fd6aa4582f624a1a9f11f0f8543b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="end-to-end-innovation-is-key-to-bringing-out-your-best">End-to-End Innovation Is Key to Bringing Out Your Best</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>In their SAP Sapphire Orlando keynote, Executive Board Members Muhammad Alam, SAP Product Engineering, and Juergen Mueller, chief technology officer, shared how the latest SAP innovations will help businesses drive true, end-to-end digital transformation and address their toughest business challenges.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="taking-business-to-the-next-level-in-the-era-of-ai">Taking Business to the Next Level in the Era of AI</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/events/sapphire/news-guide.html">Read the news guide</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In the keynote, which featured several real-world product demos by SAP employees, Alam and Mueller touted the value of SAP’s best-of-breed solutions with an outlook of what the next 50 years of innovation by SAP may look like.</p>
  <p>Who better to inspire the keynote than Hasso Plattner, co-founder and recently retired chairman of the SAP Supervisory Board, who both Alam and Mueller invoked during the session. To spell out SAP’s legacy and vision for the future, Mueller quoted <a href="/2024/05/hasso-plattner-olaf-scholz-farewell-tributes">Plattner’s farewell message</a>: “Keep innovating, keep pushing boundaries, and keep making a difference in the lives of our customers and the world at large.”</p>
  <h2 id="keep-innovating">Keep Innovating</h2>
  <p>To kick off his first SAP Sapphire appearance as the head of SAP Product Engineering, Alam began by describing the importance of harnessing innovation to deliver an end-to-end picture across all business functions and unlock true value.</p>
  <p>Simply put, businesses exist to build and deliver products and services to customers, he explained. But the materials, assets, people, and processes that come together to achieve this task is far from simple. “The reality is that each part of the business is deeply and intricately connected to all the others,” Alam said, meaning a pain point in one area impacts the rest. That’s why SAP’s modular cloud ERP approach is so successful: “We allow our customers to drive true digital transformation as opposed to running systems integration projects disguised as digital transformation,” he added.</p>
  <p>Alam presented <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/grow.html">GROW with SAP</a> as an example of this composability and extensibility, as it can work for and scale to many sizes and types of business. And now, SAP Sales Cloud and Concur Expense are natively integrated into GROW with SAP, making the offering even more comprehensive. Sinit Foto, product manager for UX, Cloud ERP at SAP, joined Alam on stage to show how GROW with SAP and SAP Business AI can help achieve integrated processes, demoing use cases such as communicating with customers about sales quotes, creating expense reports, and supporting financial analyses. In fact, Alam announced that SAP is implementing the demoed application internally to manage sales worldwide. And Mueller emphasized: “We are committed to helping you in this transformative AI moment by creating business outcomes that were unthinkable before. That’s why we’re embedding SAP Business AI deeply in our processes and analytics.”</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <picture>
          <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ab1b55bf13f95fe3a6b47084f96d918d20d0b6d4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
          <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ab1b55bf13f95fe3a6b47084f96d918d20d0b6d4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
          <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1ab1b55bf13f95fe3a6b47084f96d918d20d0b6d4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
          <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_1ab1b55bf13f95fe3a6b47084f96d918d20d0b6d4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="683">
        </picture>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="keep-pushing">Keep Pushing</h2>
  <p>AI was woven throughout the entire keynote, with both Alam and Mueller discussing <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence.html">SAP’s strategy and product enhancements in this space</a>. AI must be high value, easy to adopt into the flow of work, and trustworthy for it to truly transform how we do business, Alam said. “Equally important is whether it’s done in a way where it keeps your data secure and private – and is executed in a responsible manner,” he added. “And that is really the core promise of SAP Business AI.”</p>
  <p>There’s no doubt that AI is a powerful technology, which is why it’s essential that businesses view it as a “responsibility” not just an “opportunity,” Alam said. Megan Fife, executive solution advisor for SAP SuccessFactors, showed how SAP executes on its responsible, reliable, and relevant business AI by demoing how SAP’s AI copilot Joule in SAP SuccessFactors HCM can help fill skills gaps and collaborate across teams, among other meaningful tasks. Key to this endeavor is <a href="/2024/06/joule-microsoft-copilot-unified-work-experience">SAP’s expanded partnership with Microsoft announced earlier in the day</a>, which Scott Guthrie, executive vice president of Cloud and AI at Microsoft, discussed with Alam on stage.</p>
  <p>Mueller echoed the importance of responsible AI, saying that the technology depends highly on data that is reliable and that allows customers to look at their business end-to-end. Here, SAP Datasphere and SAP Spend Control Tower – which was demoed by Orla Cullen, product marketing manager for Data and Analytics at SAP – can help simplify data management and view and manage spend and sustainability data holistically.</p>
  <p>This transformation is supported by <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform.html">SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP)</a>, and Mueller demonstrated the newest generative AI features in SAP Analytics Cloud, SAP Integration Suite, and SAP Build solutions. He showed how Joule can help create and summarize financial reports for controlling teams; generate integration flows between SAP and non-SAP applications; and create custom skills and content based on specific business needs. Greater insights, faster reaction times, and increased productivity are the result. Soon, Mueller added, it will even be possible to enhance and extend Joule’s knowledge by creating custom skills using SAP Build and having the copilot interact with data housed in SAP and non-SAP systems, helping businesses run even more efficiently.</p>
  <p>SAP BTP is the key to being “innovation-ready,” maintaining a clean core, and tailoring standard offerings to unique needs, Mueller explained. More than 24,000 companies running live on SAP BTP, including Blue Diamond Growers and Lufthansa Technik, can attest to this.</p>
  <p>“SAP BTP’s extensibility and enterprise automation capabilities can help businesses turn process insights into actual improvements,” Mueller said. Cecilia Huergo, product manager for SAP BTP, showed this in her demo on how identifying improvement opportunities, realizing needed changes while maintaining a clean core, and gaining an up-to-date view of your IT landscape can be enabled with the combined power of SAP Signavio solutions, SAP LeanIX,, SAP BTP, and ABAP Cloud.</p>
  <h2 id="keep-making-a-difference">Keep Making a Difference</h2>
  <p>The innovations demoed and discussed in Alam and Mueller’s keynote, in addition to <a href="/2024/06/sap-sapphire-news-business-ai-enterprise-cloud-portfolio-cutting-edge-partnerships">the many others announced at SAP Sapphire in 2024</a>, are just the latest steps forward in SAP’s journey to bringing out the best in its customers. “The future is here, and it’s defined by those who innovate first,” Mueller said. “And we are here to give you the right tools at hand, such that you can be a leader not just today, but also tomorrow.”</p>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d468a3b0b7b4a96babee63b887b0c66d1bdc61b2.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d468a3b0b7b4a96babee63b887b0c66d1bdc61b2.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1d468a3b0b7b4a96babee63b887b0c66d1bdc61b2.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Why AI Means Being In The Cloud" src="./media_1d468a3b0b7b4a96babee63b887b0c66d1bdc61b2.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://youtu.be/EnxihshouTE">Why AI Means Being In The Cloud</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Gillian Hixson is an integrated communications specialist at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-news-and-coverage-from-sap-sapphire-in-2024">Get the latest news and coverage from SAP Sapphire in 2024</h3>
        <p><em><a href="/topics/sap-sapphire">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/grow-with-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Driving Progress in Sustainability, Adoption, and AI: The 2024 SAP Innovation Award Winners]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2024/04/2024-sap-innovation-award-winners</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2024/04/2024-sap-innovation-award-winners</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The 2024 SAP Innovation Award winners have utilized SAP solutions and AI to achieve remarkable results. Learn more about the winners.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/executive-blog</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>sap-award/sap-innovation-awards</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Quantum-Inspired Solution for Enterprise Optimization]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/quantum-inspired-computing-enterprise-optimization</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/quantum-inspired-computing-enterprise-optimization</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP and Fujitsu collaborated to test out Fujitsu’s new quantum-inspired computing solution for optimization. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>news-tag/quantum-computing</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Celebrating the Winners of the Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award 2023]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/celebrating-hasso-plattner-founders-award-winners-2023</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/celebrating-hasso-plattner-founders-award-winners-2023</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP announced the 2023 winners of the Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award, the company’s most prestigious employee recognition.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_13403df4d72b3f7d91e84c8c6f66e21dcbf1a8636.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_13403df4d72b3f7d91e84c8c6f66e21dcbf1a8636.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_13403df4d72b3f7d91e84c8c6f66e21dcbf1a8636.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Celebrating the Winners of the Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award 2023" src="./media_13403df4d72b3f7d91e84c8c6f66e21dcbf1a8636.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="celebrating-the-winners-of-the-hasso-plattner-founders-award-2023">Celebrating the Winners of the Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award 2023</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Last week, to a virtual audience of nearly 50,000 employees, the Executive Board of SAP SE announced the 2023 winners of the Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award, the company’s most prestigious employee recognition.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Three teams were selected for outstanding and innovative projects in the categories Go-to-Market, Operational Excellence, and Products and Technology.</p>
  <p>In 2023, 115 nominations involved more than 750 employees from 35 countries. Eight teams consisting of 81 employees from around the world made it to the final round.</p>
  <p>In honor of the three winning teams, SAP will make donations to three charities selected by the team members. The €30,000 total donation – €10,000 per team – will be split between <a href="https://bettershelter.org/">Better Shelter</a>, <a href="https://wck.org/">World Central Kitchen</a>, and <a href="https://www.embraceglobal.org/">Embrace Global</a>.</p>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_134b71501074e5b151cb81e7d9d054b44ff8f3a67.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_134b71501074e5b151cb81e7d9d054b44ff8f3a67.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_134b71501074e5b151cb81e7d9d054b44ff8f3a67.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Meet the 2023 Hasso Plattner Founders&#x27; Award Winners" src="./media_134b71501074e5b151cb81e7d9d054b44ff8f3a67.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://youtu.be/qzsiBITdf8Y">Meet the 2023 Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award Winners</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="go-to-market-winner">Go-to-Market Winner</h3>
        <h2 id="reimagined-rise-with-sap-business-case-with-sap-signavio-and-sap-value-lifecycle-manager-integration">Reimagined RISE with SAP Business Case with SAP Signavio and SAP Value Lifecycle Manager Integration</h2>
        <p>When shifting to a cloud-first approach, it can be a challenge to pitch the cloud to customers due to the comprehensiveness of the solution spanning across the entire value chain of an enterprise.</p>
        <p>To apply a more streamlined and dependable method for crafting compelling value propositions, the Value Advisory team at SAP implemented the SAP Signavio portfolio of cloud-based business process management solutions within their practice to demonstrate value to customers through data-driven insights.</p>
        <p>The team created a system where business metrics from <a href="https://vlm.cfapps.eu10.hana.ondemand.com/home">SAP Value Lifecycle Manager</a> and process performance data from <a href="https://www.signavio.com/">SAP Signavio solutions</a> were merged and applied to business KPIs to identify cases of suboptimal performance. This allows customers to more easily see the connection between business outcomes and the process capabilities, supported by data.</p>
        <p>The approach offers a robust and repeatable performance diagnostic that can be used to identify, clarify, verify, and amplify value throughout the customer value journey, helping customers better understand the value of the cloud and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/rise.html">RISE with SAP</a>. The innovation helps build customer trust and intimacy while also helping our business operate at scale. To date, this process-driven value management has impacted more than 190 customers.</p>
        <p>“Our future focus involves enhancing usability and capabilities to comprehensively cover the customer value journey,” Nitin Singh, team leader and Value Advisory principal, says. “We extend our sincere gratitude to our leaders for fostering a culture of innovation, our colleagues for experimenting and navigating challenges with us, and prior colleagues whose work paved the way for this journey. We genuinely stand on the shoulders of giants.”</p>
        <h3 id="operational-excellence-winner">Operational Excellence Winner</h3>
        <h2 id="plutus-rate-optimization-and-management">Plutus: Rate Optimization and Management</h2>
        <p>Cloud services are a critical part of SAP’s recent evolution, with the company dedicating extensive time and resources to seamlessly integrate all essential services into the cloud. This effort aims to enhance customer experiences – and Plutus serves as the cornerstone of these endeavors.</p>
        <p>Plutus, which leverages <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform.html">SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP)</a>, is a one-stop solution for major hyperscalers. It’s crafted to empower lines of business by providing smarter and more efficient advice for optimizing cloud services. Plutus can centralize the management of cost optimization and intelligently navigate users through cloud expenses, providing top-notch recommendations and comprehensive end-to-end management. It caters to users’ needs from guidance to execution, helping to ensure cost savings every step of the way.</p>
        <p>The Plutus team used cutting-edge technologies to create a 24/7, fully integrated, user-centric cloud service hub and a smooth user interface platform that can operate across various channels. Plutus provides simplified financial operations processes by offering an intuitive interface across all platforms, working to eliminate pricing disparities and provide reliable cost-saving solutions. These efforts strongly emphasize SAP’s commitment to advancing global digital sustainability through innovative enterprise solutions.</p>
        <p>The solution uses machine learning to provide smart recommendations. The team also plans to integrate a versatile digital chatbot based on generative AI to help ensure seamless and comprehensive user support in the future.</p>
        <p>Plutus allows for a new approach to SAP’s cloud cost optimization strategy, unlocking new avenues for significant cost savings and margin improvements. To date, Plutus has generated over US$920 million in net savings for SAP, with projections reaching $1 billion in Q1 2024. It has also achieved and maintained remarkable, best-in-industry cloud utilization and coverage rates – exceeding 97% and 90%, respectively.</p>
        <p>“Winning the Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award reflects our dedication to teamwork and innovation,” Donghua Chen, Plutus team lead, says. “Our journey to this point has required a lot of hard work. But as we celebrate this achievement, we remain committed to continually analyzing cloud usage to maximize savings for SAP through rate optimization.”</p>
        <h3 id="products--technology-winner">Products &#x26; Technology Winner</h3>
        <h2 id="cap-and-capgpt--sap-cloud-application-programming-model-and-generative-ai">CAP and capGPT – SAP Cloud Application Programming Model and Generative AI</h2>
        <p>The SAP Cloud Application Programming Model (CAP) was started in 2018 as a project to address the lack of guidance for developers building apps on what is now SAP BTP. At first, developers could choose from a huge number of technologies, which made integration with the platform services a relatively high effort.</p>
        <p>As a development framework, CAP automatically solves about 80% of the problems backend developers face – such as multitenancy, expandability, or business features such as localization and translatability. But thanks to CAP’s domain-driven approach, it is no longer necessary to always change the coding in each of those cases. And for special use cases that CAP doesn’t cover, the coding can be easily added to build in this functionality. To help safeguard customers’ investments, CAP offers the possibility to interchange components, such as runtime or the database, without changing the actual implementation.</p>
        <p>CAP, as a centerpiece of Golden Path and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/developer-tools.html">SAP Build Code</a>, is now an integral part of the consumption experience of SAP BTP. Today, thousands of internal and external developers use CAP to build business applications on SAP BTP, driving higher developer productivity and easier SAP BTP service adoption.</p>
        <p>“This award is a great testament to the hard work and dedication of the whole CAP unit and a recognition of the impact we have both internally as well as for our customers and partners,” Ole Lilienthal, team lead, says.</p>
        <p>To make prototyping even easier, in spring 2023, SAP software architect David Kunz applied ChatGPT’s large language model to writing code for business apps.</p>
        <p>capGPT, as the new functionality is called, allows users to write in natural language what they want their app prototype to be able to do. In as little as 30 seconds, they can receive all the code – which previously had to be written by hand – and access the prototype to test it. This can not only save experienced developers an amazing amount of time, but can also enable non-developers to create prototypes of the apps they need. capGPT can also generate user interfaces in addition to backend applications. It will soon be available to customers through integration into SAP Build Code as part of AI-development assistant Joule.</p>
        <p>“Seeing capGPT go from an idea to a Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award winner within a year is a true testament that everything is possible at SAP,” Kunz says. “I feel very proud and I’m energized to continue to push the limits of what generative AI can enable.”</p>
        <p>Photo courtesy of SAP employee Fateh Kassab</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-sap-news-on-linkedin">Connect with SAP News on LinkedIn</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news">Follow us to stay in touch</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>sap-award/hasso-plattner-founders-awards</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Digital Eco-Farming: How SAP Japan Helps Revitalize Rural Communities]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/minano-digital-eco-farm-sap-japan-revitalize-rural-communities</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/minano-digital-eco-farm-sap-japan-revitalize-rural-communities</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The Minano Digital Eco Farm, launched by PSI and SAP Co-Innovation Lab in Japan, is helping the town of Minano revitalize its community.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/agribusiness</category>
            <category>news-tag/digitization</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>news-tag/internet-of-things</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-co-innovation-lab</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Grow with the Latest SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition 2402 Update]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/sap-s4hana-cloud-public-edition-2402-update</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/sap-s4hana-cloud-public-edition-2402-update</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With the SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition 2402 update, we are bringing a new round of exciting innovations. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/enterprise-resource-planning</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>product/sap-intelligent-rpa</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/ux</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Accelerate Innovation with a Clean Core Strategy]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/accelerate-innovation-with-clean-core-strategy</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/accelerate-innovation-with-clean-core-strategy</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With a clean core strategy for business tech, you can stay focused on what matters most to your business. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Celebrates Its Retail Industry Heroes at NRF 2024]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/sap-celebrates-retail-industry-heroes-at-nrf-2024</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/sap-celebrates-retail-industry-heroes-at-nrf-2024</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The SAP Industry Heroes program celebrates companies that leverage technology to transform their business in innovative ways. Read more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a3595d9d5757368b8780b1671a7ab8c8c046f201.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a3595d9d5757368b8780b1671a7ab8c8c046f201.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1a3595d9d5757368b8780b1671a7ab8c8c046f201.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Celebrates Its Retail Industry Heroes at NRF 2024" src="./media_1a3595d9d5757368b8780b1671a7ab8c8c046f201.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-celebrates-its-retail-industry-heroes-at-nrf-2024">SAP Celebrates Its Retail Industry Heroes at NRF 2024</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>In the rapidly evolving landscape of retail, a new breed of heroes has emerged – visionaries that are revolutionizing the industry through their innovative application of technology.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>These pioneers, armed with a potent blend of innovation and determination, are reshaping the shopping experience, driving operational efficiency, and connecting with consumers in unprecedented ways. From leveraging AI and machine learning to implementing augmented reality and blockchain, these retail trailblazers are at the forefront of change, seamlessly integrating cutting-edge technologies to redefine what it means to engage customers and deliver exceptional service.</p>
  <p>We launched the SAP Industry Heroes program in 2023 to celebrate companies that leverage technology to transform their business in innovative ways. Let’s explore the stories of our <a href="/topics/nrf">NRF</a> retail heroes that harnessed the power of technology to transform the traditional retail paradigm into an innovative, customer-centric frontier.</p>
  <p><strong>Birkenstock</strong> worked with SAP on its ongoing objectives to expand retail and wholesale presence while fostering customer growth in line with its renowned legacy of function, quality, and tradition.</p>
  <p><strong>Brand Alley</strong> delved into the rising trend of utilizing advocacy data in marketing strategies, which led to the transformation of brand perspectives on VIP customers and the strategic utilization of advocacy data within paid search and social media campaigns.</p>
  <p><strong>FC Bayern</strong>, equipped with over 8 million fan data records, crafted a detailed profile of its worldwide fan community, encompassing specific preferences and interests. SAP technology played a pivotal role in enabling FC Bayern, one of the most accomplished football clubs globally, to curate what it terms as the “golden fan record.”</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="execute-faster-in-the-world-of-omnichannel-commerce-with-sap">Execute faster in the world of omnichannel commerce with SAP</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/retail.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><strong>Grupo Axo</strong> effectively transitioned to leveraging internal customer data due to the potential extinction of third-party data. Its journey offers insights into standing out from competitors, increasing revenue, fostering stronger customer relationships, and cultivating a more robust, data-driven culture through the utilization of internal customer data.</p>
  <p><strong>Hornbach</strong> achieved real-time retail success, processed over 100,000 orders, and effectively addressed omnichannel challenges with SAP Order Management foundation. Working together with SAP, Hornbach built a composable enterprise.</p>
  <p><strong>Neiman Marcus</strong> harnessed innovative methods and valuable insights to optimize its compensation management. These strategies are reshaping the retail landscape and revolutionizing team incentives within the industry.</p>
  <p><strong>PetSmart</strong>, a prominent pet retailer, encountered obstacles in omnichannel order fulfillment, leading to challenges in financial reconciliation and inventory transparency. By adopting SAP Customer Activity Repository, PetSmart established a robust foundation for omnichannel retail. This implementation significantly enhanced the omnichannel process and elevated overall customer satisfaction levels.</p>
  <p><strong>PVH</strong>, a global apparel company with a brand portfolio that includes Tommy Hilfiger, Calvin Klein, Warner’s, Olga, and True&#x26;Co, is working with SAP to build an IT platform foundation for innovation, modernization, digitalization, and scalability.</p>
  <p><strong>Qurate Retail Group</strong>, known for its innovative strides in the retail sector, leveraged technology to elevate customer experiences, optimize operations, and propel growth together with SAP.</p>
  <p><strong>RD</strong>, Brazil’s top drugstore chain boasting nearly 3,000 stores across the nation, achieved a transformative implementation of SAP technology, which led to streamlined processes and customer-centric advancements, marking a new era of operational excellence.</p>
  <p><strong>Wella Company</strong>, a pioneering force in the beauty industry with 15 distinctive brands, utilizes technology to inspire both consumers and beauty professionals to embrace their authentic selves. Wella Company’s approach of leveraging actionable data to craft tailored solutions strengthens its lifelong relationships across B2C (business-to-consumer), B2B (business-to-business), and D2C (direct-to-consumer) realms.</p>
  <p>SAP celebrates these retailers for their outstanding efforts, collaboration, and dedication in driving successful business outcomes with technology. Join us at NRF 2024 to celebrate these SAP Industry Heroes that will be sharing their stories and learnings at the SAP booth. <a href="https://sap.jifflenow.com/external-request/nrf2024/meeting-request?token=3be51cab20a42cfa8e0b">Schedule an in-person meeting or booth tour with us today</a>.</p>
  <p><a href="/">Read more about our retail and CPG customer stories and wins from 2023.</a></p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Matt Laukaitis is EVP and Global GM for SAP Consumer Industries.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-more-sap-news-and-coverage-from-nrf-2024">Read more SAP news and coverage from NRF 2024</h3>
        <p><em><a href="/topics/nrf">Get the news</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>news-tag/nrf</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[From Sentiments to Solutions: Decoding Business Correspondence with Gen AI]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/decoding-business-correspondence-ai-communication-intelligence</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/decoding-business-correspondence-ai-communication-intelligence</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Communication intelligence is a service on SAP BTP that can analyze, categorize, and correspond to written communication by leveraging AI.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-innovation-center-network</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Power of Collaboration: SAP Celebrates Innovation Award Winners and Opens Submissions for 2024]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/sap-innovation-award-winners-2024-submissions</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/sap-innovation-award-winners-2024-submissions</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Companies leveraging SAP tech have achieved a decade of collaboration and operational excellence, celebrated with the SAP Innovation Awards.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1316a4793c0be932c172b8ef5c5c96203bce86784.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1316a4793c0be932c172b8ef5c5c96203bce86784.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1316a4793c0be932c172b8ef5c5c96203bce86784.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="The Power of Collaboration: SAP Celebrates Innovation Award Winners and Opens Submissions for 2024" src="./media_1316a4793c0be932c172b8ef5c5c96203bce86784.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="the-power-of-collaboration-sap-celebrates-innovation-award-winners-and-opens-submissions-for-2024">The Power of Collaboration: SAP Celebrates Innovation Award Winners and Opens Submissions for 2024</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>In today’s rapidly evolving digital landscape, organizations are embracing a wide range of cloud-based tools, including analytics and artificial intelligence (AI), to drive innovation.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>This was a key message conveyed during the 10th anniversary virtual celebration for the 2023 <a href="/topics/sap-innovation-awards">SAP Innovation Award</a> winners in June. The event highlighted how these technological advancements have revolutionized collaboration with customers and partners worldwide, leading to sustainable and impactful innovation. However, amidst this digital revolution, it is important to recognize that the human touch remains irreplaceable.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="submit-your-ideas-for-the-2024-sap-innovation-awards">Submit your ideas for the 2024 SAP Innovation Awards</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/idea-place/sap-innovation-awards.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>While digital interactions have become commonplace, relying solely on the cloud for customer satisfaction is a misconception. It is the dedicated workers armed with a multitude of software solutions who continue to be the driving force behind transformative change. From manufacturing to supply chain, finance to procurement, it is the ingenuity and expertise of individuals that propel industries and society forward. These real-life transformers are the catalysts for progress, harnessing the power of technology to shape a better future.</p>
  <p>When the first SAP Innovation Awards were launched in 2014, the judges received 27 submissions. This year, the number exceeded 220 across 10 categories, including Sustainability Hero, Industry Leader, Partner Paragon, and Cutting-Edge Genius.</p>
  <p>Check out this <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2023/05/c62e227b-717e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">e-book</a>, which has everything you need to know about the 2023 SAP Innovation Award winners, finalists, honorable mentions, and more.</p>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_144bfb0b2e0177493012f1c783a2d49b025e093af.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_144bfb0b2e0177493012f1c783a2d49b025e093af.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_144bfb0b2e0177493012f1c783a2d49b025e093af.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Innovation Awards: See the Winners and Submit Your Own Ideas" src="./media_144bfb0b2e0177493012f1c783a2d49b025e093af.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LM1tISRzEPQ">SAP Innovation Awards: See the Winners and Submit Your Own Ideas</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="changing-the-world">Changing the World</h2>
  <p>At the celebration, as the winners accepted the accolades for their achievements and addressed each other online, all agreed that, in this post-pandemic period, the goal of technological innovation must transcend simply improving one’s business.</p>
  <p>By their actions, the 2023 SAP Innovation Award winners embody that philosophy.</p>
  <p>For instance, after the war in Ukraine forced more than 8 million people to flee their homeland, professional services corporation <strong>EY (Ernst &#x26; Young)</strong> developed its Emergency Response Application (ERA). The free mobile solution was built using SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP) and enables access to critical and time-sensitive information and directs refugees to resources in 53 cities. The humanitarian undertaking was accomplished in an astonishing six weeks.</p>
  <p>In its mission to develop novel and multifunctional therapeutics for rare cancers and other serious diseases, global biotechnology company <strong>Zymeworks</strong> found that its previous manual system was inefficient and labor-intensive. To remedy that, the company created a single, integrated platform using SAP’s enterprise resource planning (ERP) solutions to support its product commercialization, growth, and expansion strategy – allowing the organization insight into real-time information to make important, data-driven decisions while continuing to save lives.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="congratulating-the-10th-anniversary-sap-innovation-award-winners">Congratulating the 10th Anniversary SAP Innovation Award Winners</h3>
        <p><em><a href="/2023/04/congratulating-10th-anniversary-sap-innovation-award-winners">Read the feature</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In Australia, where the country’s growing aging population has increased the demand for in-home and community-delivered care, <strong>HomeMade</strong> designed a self-service portal leveraging SAP BTP, enabling the elderly to choose providers for services like cleaning and cooking and lead a fulfilling life while reducing administrative overhead.</p>
  <p>And on the Japanese island of Kyushu, where natural disasters are all too frequent, <strong>Oita University</strong> developed an information platform called the Earth Disaster Intelligent System Operational Network (EDiSON), providing accurate and timely data to assist emergency response organizations. The solution uses robust data management, advanced analytics, AI, and machine learning capabilities offered by SAP HANA Cloud, the SAP Analytics Cloud solution, and SAP Business Technology Platform.</p>
  <h2 id="a-sustainable-planet">A Sustainable Planet</h2>
  <p>From the time the 2023 SAP Innovation Awards were announced, judges were “looking for tangible examples of sustainability that are delivering impact, using SAP technologies for good,” said Dorit Shackleton, senior vice president, head of Customer Advocacy and Global Events Marketing at SAP.</p>
  <p>In addition to supplying people in Switzerland’s Basel region with electricity, heat, and drinking water, along with telecom and mobility solutions, <strong>Industrielle Werke Basel (IWB)</strong> produces and sells renewable and CO2-netural energy to achieve climate goals. Using machine learning algorithms, a new adaptable application leveraging SAP Business Technology Platform can predict solar power production with unprecedented accuracy, supporting IWB’s ongoing sustainability drive.</p>
  <p>As host Timo Elliot pointed out, “If you can help with just a small percentage [of reducing the carbon footprint], you can make a big difference to the planet.”</p>
  <p>In trying to reach its environmental, social, and governance (ESG) objectives, Indonesian mining, infrastructure, and oil and gas services company <strong>Petrosea</strong> was frustrated that its old, largely paper-based system complicated the process. By creating a unified platform and utilizing SAP Analytics Cloud, the company now has one source of truth to monitor carbon emissions, waste, and water usage to make informed choices and realize what it calls its 3D strategy – diversification, digitalization, and decarbonization.</p>
  <p>As the 2023 SAP Innovation Award winners continue to bask in the glow of their success, planning for the 2024 festivities is underway. And even organizations that don’t plan to enter will be watching to find inspiration for new ways to improve.</p>
  <p>Join us in celebrating innovation and transformation by sharing your success stories in the <strong>2024 SAP Innovation Awards</strong>! We invite you to submit your transformation stories.</p>
  <p>Together, let’s shape the future of innovation. Participate in the 2024 SAP Innovation Awards and share your remarkable journey with us. Visit our <a href="https://www.sap.com/idea-place/sap-innovation-awards/how-to-enter.html">submissions page</a> to get started!</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Julia Ponzini is a customer marketing senior specialist at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-sap-news-on-linkedin">Connect with SAP News on LinkedIn</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news">Follow Us</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>sap-award/sap-innovation-awards</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[RISE with SAP Accelerates Biotech Innovation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/rise-with-sap-accelerates-innovation-stemcell</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/rise-with-sap-accelerates-innovation-stemcell</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[STEMCELL Technologies is digitally transforming to speed up advanced healthcare discoveries, bringing hope to patients and their families.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/digitalization</category>
            <category>industry/healthcare</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>industry/life-sciences</category>
            <category>news-tag/research-development</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Manufacturers Monetize Beyond Products: As-a-Service Builds Customer Relationships]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/as-a-service-builds-customer-relationships-manufacturing</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/as-a-service-builds-customer-relationships-manufacturing</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[As-a-service business models have helped manufacturers turn services into ongoing revenue streams and build relationships. Learn how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/financial-management</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>news-tag/quote-to-cash</category>
            <category>news-tag/recurring-revenue-models</category>
            <category>product/sap-billing-and-revenue-innovation-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/xaas</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Celebrating the Winners of the 2022 Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/2022-hasso-plattner-founders-award-winners</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/2022-hasso-plattner-founders-award-winners</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Congratulations to the three teams selected as 2022 Hasso Plattner Founders' Award winners! Read to learn more about the innovative projects.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>sap-award/hasso-plattner-founders-awards</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Congratulating the 10th Anniversary SAP Innovation Award Winners]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/congratulating-10th-anniversary-sap-innovation-award-winners</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/congratulating-10th-anniversary-sap-innovation-award-winners</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With immense pleasure and pride, here are the 30 winners of the 10th anniversary SAP Innovation Awards for 2023!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>sap-award/sap-innovation-awards</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The 2023 SAP Innovation Award Finalists Have Been Selected]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/2023-sap-innovation-award-finalists-selected</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/2023-sap-innovation-award-finalists-selected</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With over 220 submissions, we are excited to announce the 2023 SAP Innovation Award finalists. Read to learn more about the 70 finalists.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>sap-award/sap-innovation-awards</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Human Augmentation: Why We Are Still Hunters and Gatherers in the Workplace]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/human-augmentation-workplace-hunters-and-gatherers</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/human-augmentation-workplace-hunters-and-gatherers</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Chief Futurist Martin Wezowski details a human-centric approach to technology, offering an “empathic symbiosis” of people and machines.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Innovation Awards Celebrate Innovation amid Global Challenges]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/sap-innovation-awards-celebrate-innovation-amid-global-challenges</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/sap-innovation-awards-celebrate-innovation-amid-global-challenges</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[We are excited for the 10th anniversary SAP Innovation Awards, honoring pioneers for their innovative use of SAP solutions.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>sap-award/sap-innovation-awards</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How to Set the Course of Business Innovation with Intelligent ERP]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/set-course-of-business-innovation-with-intelligent-erp</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/set-course-of-business-innovation-with-intelligent-erp</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A cloud-based ERP helps organizations prioritize business innovation to keep up with market dynamics and workplace and customer expectations.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
            <category>news-tag/premium-engagement</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[In 2023, SAP Will Continue to Lead the Market in Procurement Innovation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/procurement-innovation-leading-market</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/procurement-innovation-leading-market</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In 2023, SAP intends to lead the market with procurement innovation. Learn how SAP plans to continue to deliver actionable insights.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>news-tag/procure-to-pay</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-spend-connect-live</category>
            <category>news-tag/supplier-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[In the Push for Digital Innovation, Confidence Comes with the Right Platform]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/01/digital-innovation-confidence-right-platform</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/01/digital-innovation-confidence-right-platform</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP partners help customers run confidently with impactful innovations that leverage the suite qualities of SAP Business Technology Platform.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[This Bathroom and Wellness Business Is Growing Strong Thanks to Top Tech and Design]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/eczacibasi-growing-strong-top-tech-and-design</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/eczacibasi-growing-strong-top-tech-and-design</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Eczacibaşi, a Turkish building materials company and industry leader, is digitalizing to drive efficiency and reduce waste. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>product/sap-commerce-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sustainable Salmon Farming and the Future of Digital Procurement]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/evonik-industries-digital-procurement</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/evonik-industries-digital-procurement</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Digitalization frees up procurement to stay on top of fast-changing market conditions, including finding suppliers in unexpected disruptions.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>industry/chemicals</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/digitalization</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Solutions Come to Life at SAP Experience Center 2.0]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/sap-solutions-come-to-life-sap-experience-center-walldorf</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/sap-solutions-come-to-life-sap-experience-center-walldorf</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The updated SAP Experience Center Walldorf was designed to enable a personalized and up-close journey into the added value of SAP software.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-experience-center</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Driving Continuous Innovation with Cloud Application Services]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/continuous-innovation-cloud-application-services</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/continuous-innovation-cloud-application-services</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Cloud application services play a critical role in driving digital transformation and continuous innovation in the cloud. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_142070103f917935adae56fa6e241cee98ad810d0.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_142070103f917935adae56fa6e241cee98ad810d0.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_142070103f917935adae56fa6e241cee98ad810d0.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Driving Continuous Innovation with Cloud Application Services" src="./media_142070103f917935adae56fa6e241cee98ad810d0.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="driving-continuous-innovation-with-cloud-application-services">Driving Continuous Innovation with Cloud Application Services</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>A new <a href="https://ssrn.com/abstract=4082436">study</a> from the <a href="https://ide.mit.edu/">MIT Initiative on the Digital Economy</a> found that transitioning to the cloud is paying off. Revenue growth for public firms adopting cloud technology was 2.3% to 6.9% higher than for non-adopters in the last decade, according to research results. In addition to increased revenues, companies benefit from improved productivity. Operating in a cloud environment enables organizations to use intelligent technologies, such as machine learning and artificial intelligence (AI). They are better equipped to adapt new models to service customers and employees in a hybrid work environment.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>At the same time, moving to the cloud has become more accessible. Companies can find the <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/pulse/cloud-mindset-culture-series-part-1-all-paths-lead-peter-pluim/?trackingId=RFwt9KRhStuDZ%2FVliBuisA%3D%3D">best cloud deployment model</a> based on their existing IT infrastructure as well as data residency requirements. Our customers, for example, can use our SAP data centers, hyperscalers, or their own data centers to host a cloud enterprise resource planning (ERP) environment.</p>
  <p>Operating in a cloud ERP environment is a critical step in an organization’s digital business transformation to become an intelligent, sustainable enterprise. This step is also the springboard to continuous innovation. And this continuous innovation is enabled by the cloud, more specifically by <a href="/topics/sap-cloud-application-services">cloud application services</a>.</p>
  <p>In a nutshell, cloud application services can be defined as value-added services that simplify the end-to-end management of cloud systems by delivering application operations and innovation adoption.</p>
  <p>We designed <a href="https://www.sap.com/services-support/service-offerings/cloud-application-services.html">SAP Cloud Application Services</a> to support all types of SAP cloud deployment models with SAP application management services, SAP managed data services, SAP managed security services, and SAP managed testing services. Each of these four services help drive continuous improvement and quality assurance for cloud solutions with a focus on business outcomes.</p>
  <p>Let’s take a look at managed testing services as an example.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-cloud-application-services-help-free-up-resources-to-focus-on-optimizing-business-outcomes">SAP Cloud Application Services help free up resources to focus on optimizing business outcomes</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/services-support/service-offerings/cloud-application-services.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="innovating-without-compromising-business-continuity">Innovating without Compromising Business Continuity</h2>
  <p>Most global businesses have highly complex and integrated landscapes. They want access to the latest technologies to improve operations and engagements with customers. This could include using AI-based chatbots for customer service, adding mobile payment methods, or having the ability to track their carbon footprint across the entire supply chain. But they also have concerns that introducing these new innovations may cause disruption of existing business operations. Thus, maintaining business continuity at a high quality is paramount when introducing innovations.</p>
  <p>That’s where SAP managed testing services come in. The beauty of the services is that they can improve IT systems and operations in the cloud without compromising business continuity with repeatable and seamless processes for solution adoption, testing, and quality control.</p>
  <p><a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/03/888d99c4-d17d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff.html">SAP managed testing services</a> can prevent disruption and help stabilize critical business processes across releases and other test events. Software quality is tested consistently, accurately, and efficiently with automated testing tools and services that use industry-specific test cases. Higher value services, such as data management, release management, advanced monitoring, and innovation adoption, help stabilize application operations. We offer support for all cloud deployment models with a central focus on flexible and simplified service consumption, which is central to the innovation mindset of our organization.</p>
  <p>In brief, the services can provide the quality assurance and stable foundation that companies need to confidently drive innovation with integration and upgrades to the latest technologies. Having that peace of mind is critical to developing a cloud-first mindset across the entire organization for continuous innovation.</p>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div><a href="https://www.sap.com/services-support/service-offerings/cloud-application-services.html">Learn more about SAP Cloud Application Services.</a></div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>Peter Pluim is president of SAP Enterprise Cloud Services and SAP Sovereign Cloud Delivery &#x26; Operations at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-cloud-application-services</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Industry 4.0 Attracts Workers Whose Entire Lives Are on Their Mobile Device]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/industry-4-0-attracts-workers-whose-entire-lives-are-on-their-mobile-device</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/industry-4-0-attracts-workers-whose-entire-lives-are-on-their-mobile-device</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Manufacturers are transforming factories, hoping next-generation workers come for the cool factor and stay for career-building innovations.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-4-0</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>news-tag/mobile</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Upward Momentum Builds with Digitalization in the Chemicals Industry]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/upward-momentum-digitalization-chemicals-industry</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/upward-momentum-digitalization-chemicals-industry</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With the right approach to digitalization and the help of SAP Advisory Services, the chemicals industry can innovate across the value chain.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f2348930338cde065afdb2512296e4046afc65b8.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f2348930338cde065afdb2512296e4046afc65b8.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1f2348930338cde065afdb2512296e4046afc65b8.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Upward Momentum Builds with Digitalization in the Chemicals Industry" src="./media_1f2348930338cde065afdb2512296e4046afc65b8.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="upward-momentum-builds-with-digitalization-in-the-chemicals-industry">Upward Momentum Builds with Digitalization in the Chemicals Industry</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Chemical companies are on a nonstop roller coaster of market shocks and digital transformation. Sandwiched between feedstock and energy companies and downstream processing industries, they’re predestined to play a vital role in fulfilling business-to-business (B2B) and consumer expectations for sustainable, reliable, innovative, and trusted products and services.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>But rising to the challenge of today’s marketplace – especially increasing raw material and energy prices, margin pressure, supply chain complexity, and regulatory requirements – requires much more than Industry 4.0 initiatives focused on efficiency and price reduction. From operational performance to customer experience, companies must integrate data from across the enterprise into a single source to form sound decisions that make sustainability profitable and profitability sustainable.</p>
  <p>Such a transformation is undoubtedly technology intensive, but the key enablers are also unassailably human. Understanding this reality, many chemical companies rely on the <a href="https://www.sap.com/services-support/service-offerings/business-transformation.html">SAP Advisory Services</a> portfolio, provided by the Business Transformation Services group at SAP, to help transform their operations and gain a competitive edge amid fast global changes.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="transform-your-business-and-unlock-digital-innovation-with-help-from-sap-advisory-services">Transform your business and unlock digital innovation with help from SAP Advisory Services</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/services-support/service-offerings/business-transformation.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="turning-challenges-into-great-opportunities">Turning Challenges into Great Opportunities</h2>
  <p>Competitively addressing turbulence depends on the ability to view transformation through the lens of six fundamental challenges:</p>
  <p><strong>R&#x26;D Pressure across the Product Portfolio</strong> The imperative to resist margin shrinkage, mitigate risks, increase ROI, and boost growth calls for innovative products and services that offer business value and foster close partnerships with customers. By pushing forward the adoption of advanced technologies to drive global R&#x26;D, supplier, and customer collaborations and joint ventures, businesses can prevent commoditization.</p>
  <p><strong>The Need for Vertical Integration</strong> Evolving production facilities with a balance of high efficiency, global scale, flexibility, and intelligent responsiveness allows supply chains to weigh the synergistic benefits of integrated manufacturing plants or industrial parks against the flexibility of smaller plants. As a result, businesses can leverage new opportunities with disruptive business models, such as making raw materials instead of buying them and producing semi-finished or even finished goods.</p>
  <p><strong>Global Supply Chain Complexity</strong> Global supply chains must be secure enough to mitigate volatile market conditions, such as global health emergencies, rising prices for raw materials and energy, and other factors that impact economic conditions. Companies can gain this advantage by establishing commercial and logistical transparency to support optimization and global planning of demand, sales, and operations.</p>
  <p><strong>Hidden Advantages of Business Networks</strong> Business cannot stay competitive in a complex ecosystem alone. They must also scale and optimize their supply chain globally with business networks, such as the <a href="/2021/03/catena-x-automotive-alliance-picks-up-speed">Catena-X Automotive Network</a>. Doing so empowers suppliers, contract and toll manufacturers, joint ventures, and customers to collaborate openly and create new prospects for co-innovating better products and services, improving value chain efficiency, and fueling long-term growth.</p>
  <p><strong>Compliance and Sustainability Urgency</strong> A primary objective for any chemical business is ensuring compliance with industry regulations. Yet, B2B customers also favor suppliers that help meet their own environmental, social, and governance (ESG) mandates. Sustainable businesses and innovations provide balance between these two expectations, creating a highly sought-after competitive edge by gearing products and services towards a circular economy.</p>
  <p><strong>Business Agility</strong> The industry’s dynamic and fast-changing environment of mergers, acquisitions, and divestitures is creating tremendous complexity and pressure for permanent change and adaptation. Chemical companies need to balance industry-wide globalization and centralization while increasing business agility.</p>
  <p>Chemical companies with a digital strategy encompassing all these topics can address industry challenges and seize on market trends in a disruptive manner. Through <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2016/03/d2238cd0-627c-0010-82c7-eda71af511fa.html">digital innovation</a>, businesses can gain new opportunities and capabilities never previously considered possible – including increased speed and efficiency, process automation, and data transparency.</p>
  <h2 id="seizing-the-moment-with-advisory-expertise">Seizing the Moment with Advisory Expertise</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="at-sap-your-success-is-our-goal">At SAP, your success is our goal</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/support.html#services-support-offerings">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>From the perspective of SAP Advisory Services, digitalization is not just another IT term but also a critical business priority. The more intelligent and sustainable a company becomes, the more agile, flexible, and integrated its value chain becomes.</p>
  <p>Advisory experts from SAP can enable chemical companies to turn their fundamental challenges into opportunities with a well-structured, business-driven design. This approach elaborates on the steps of the digital transformation journey – leading to a road map for future architecture design. Each phase of the road map follows an ideal sequence of digital innovation, technology adoption, and industry best practices and leverages the highest value for the company in the short term.</p>
  <p>SAP Advisory Services help organizations evaluate and act on the sentiments of their customers, partners, and employees and improve their environmental impact. Chemical companies can then be well positioned to keep their workforce engaged, increase organizational agility, and deliver the products and services customers need and trust. Furthermore, they can control their varied sources and categories of spending with outstanding finance and operational efficiency and real-time enterprise insight.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_13184d5b5d29ebbc4d371c407a9c86acc71402ad2.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_13184d5b5d29ebbc4d371c407a9c86acc71402ad2.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_13184d5b5d29ebbc4d371c407a9c86acc71402ad2.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_13184d5b5d29ebbc4d371c407a9c86acc71402ad2.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="300" height="283">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p><em>Intelligent enterprise framework</em></p>
  <p>Essentially, chemical companies that work with SAP advisory experts can realize their potential as <a href="https://www.sap.com/intelligent-enterprise.html">intelligent enterprises</a>. They can make confident decisions and drive continuous innovation to adapt, innovate, and overcome challenges while making responsible choices that help reduce waste and emissions and drive long-term growth.</p>
  <p>This business model is accomplished with intelligent technologies, including business networks, a business technology platform, cloud-based infrastructures, and solutions for business process management, experience management, industry cloud, and sustainability management. Additionally, artificial intelligence (AI), blockchain, data platforms, the Internet of Things (IoT), machine learning, predictive analytics, and virtual as well as augmented realities (VR/AR) are embedded in the intelligent technologies to drive end-to-end business processes and decision-making across enterprise domains.</p>
  <h2 id="bringing-to-life-an-intelligent-and-sustainable-network">Bringing to Life an Intelligent and Sustainable Network</h2>
  <p>The pressures on the chemicals industry may be relentless, with shocks coming in from all directions. However, this doesn’t mean businesses cannot find great opportunities in this volatile environment. With the right approach to digitalization, they can transform, innovate, and collaborate across the value chain to build upward momentum and better serve customers as an intelligent and sustainable network.</p>
  <p>Learn more about the <a href="https://blogs.sap.com/2022/09/29/business-and-digital-trends-in-the-chemical-industry/">market trends and business priorities shaping various lines of businesses in the chemical industry</a> and how SAP can help guide the innovation needed to overcome them. Read the series <a href="https://blogs.sap.com/tag/business-digital-trends-in-the-chemical-industry/">“Business and Digital Trends in the Chemical Industry</a>” on SAP Community.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Ornulf Rexin is chief business consultant of Chemicals and Life Sciences for Business Transformation Services at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/chemicals</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/digitalization</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-advisory-services</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Digital Innovations Behind the Booming Life Sciences Industry]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/digital-innovations-life-sciences-industry</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/digital-innovations-life-sciences-industry</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The pandemic has irrevocably disrupted the life sciences industry, revealing a new vision for innovation from cloud-based collaboration.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/covid-19</category>
            <category>news-tag/forrester</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>industry/healthcare</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>industry/life-sciences</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[California’s Low-Cost Insulin Is Symptom of Lifesaving Innovations to Come]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/life-sciences-innovations-to-come</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/life-sciences-innovations-to-come</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Life sciences leaders are connecting data and people to find for more cost-effective disease prevention innovations and lifesaving cures.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digitalization</category>
            <category>industry/healthcare</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>industry/life-sciences</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Investing in an Innovative New Platform Can Provide Fallback for Any Scenario]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/investing-in-an-innovative-new-platform-can-provide-fallback-for-any-scenario</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/investing-in-an-innovative-new-platform-can-provide-fallback-for-any-scenario</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Freudenberg Home and Cleaning Solutions, a 2022 SAP Innovation Award winner, digitalized processes and improved forecasting with SAP BTP.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/covid-19</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>sap-award/sap-innovation-awards</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>