<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/product/sap-extended-warehouse-management/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Named a Leader in the Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Warehouse Management Systems for the 11th Consecutive Year]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/sap-a-leader-2024-gartner-magic-quadrant-wms</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/sap-a-leader-2024-gartner-magic-quadrant-wms</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[For the 11th time, SAP is a Leader in the Magic Quadrant for WMS, based on ability to execute and for the completeness of vision. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ac123a0a67e3b19450c432a63245f50c1e68b889.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ac123a0a67e3b19450c432a63245f50c1e68b889.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1ac123a0a67e3b19450c432a63245f50c1e68b889.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Named a Leader in the Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Warehouse Management Systems for the 11th Consecutive Year" src="./media_1ac123a0a67e3b19450c432a63245f50c1e68b889.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-named-a-leader-in-the-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-warehouse-management-systems-for-the-11th-consecutive-year">SAP Named a Leader in the Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Warehouse Management Systems for the 11th Consecutive Year</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>SAP has been named as a Leader in the 2024 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Warehouse Management Systems. For the 11th consecutive year, SAP is positioned in the Leaders quadrant based on Ability to Execute and Completeness of Vision.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>We believe that this recognition confirms our strategy in logistics, which is based on three pillars:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Connecting every process to facilitate synchronized logistics execution, supporting highly efficient and fast-paced fulfillment cycles through seamless integration with logistics applications like SAP Transportation Management, SAP Business Network for Logistics, etc.</li>
    <li>Collaborating within a diverse ecosystem of system integrators, software partners, hyperscalers, hardware partners, and robotics OEMs, with warehouse management being an integral part of cloud ERP.</li>
    <li>Contextualizing every decision leveraging artificial intelligence (AI) and machine learning to optimize operations and to provide business insights</li>
  </ul>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="keep-pace-with-demand-minimize-costs-and-maintain-sustainable-risk-resilient-warehouse-operations">Keep pace with demand, minimize costs, and maintain sustainable, risk-resilient warehouse operations</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/extended-warehouse-management.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/extended-warehouse-management.html">SAP Extended Warehouse Management</a> (SAP EWM) is an integral part of the overall SAP strategy and gives companies the ability to operate modern warehouses that must respond quickly to changing business conditions. The flexibility of SAP EWM helps manage a high volume of goods and run sustainable, risk-resilient operations with digitized warehouse processes in the cloud including direct control of warehouse automation equipment.</p>
  <p>SAP continues to innovate in SAP EWM based on market analysis and even more importantly based on feedback from our global install base and ecosystem. Recent innovations include cross-process integration in the areas of transportation, production, and quality management, addressing industry-specific requirements, extensibility, and usability.</p>
  <p>SAP EWM combined with SAP Transportation Management and SAP Business Network for Logistics provides a platform for companies to collaborate with their logistics partners to gain end-to-end visibility and insights across their logistics operations.</p>
  <p>Our global partner network — made up of systems integrators, business consultants, and technology providers — helps our customers manage their warehouse management transformations, whether they be system replacements, upgrades, greenfield deployments, or part of larger enterprise transformations.</p>
  <p>“Warehouse Management with SAP EWM is an integral part of our cloud ERP offering,” said Till Dengel, global head of Logistics and Manufacturing Product Marketing at SAP. “Customers use SAP EWM to manage their warehouse operations in 66 countries and 24 industries.”</p>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div>SAP Extended Warehouse Management helped Bridgestone reduce errors, with a new level of productivity and safety.</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>Eric Dyason, National Distribution Manager, Bridgestone New Zealand Ltd.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/extended-warehouse-management.html?campaigncode=CRM-YD24-DSC-2695614&#x26;url_id=magic-quadrant-for-warehouse-management-systems&#x26;rc=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.gartner.com%2Freprints%2F%3Fid%3D1-2HGS0BJ4%26ct%3D240502%26st%3Dsb">Get more details on the latest</a><br><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/extended-warehouse-management.html?campaigncode=CRM-YD24-DSC-2695614&#x26;url_id=magic-quadrant-for-warehouse-management-systems&#x26;rc=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.gartner.com%2Freprints%2F%3Fid%3D1-2HGS0BJ4%26ct%3D240502%26st%3Dsb">Gartner Magic Quadrant for WMS here</a>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Ganesh Wadawadigi is chief product marketing owner for Logistics at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>*Gartner, Magic Quadrant for Warehouse Management Systems, Simon Tunstall, Dwight Klappich, Rishabh Narang, Federica Stufano, 2 May 2024</p>
  <p>GARTNER is a registered trademark and service mark of Gartner, Inc. and/or its affiliates in the U.S. and internationally, MAGIC QUADRANT is a registered trademark of Gartner, Inc. and/or its affiliates and are used herein with permission. All rights reserved.<br>Gartner does not endorse any vendor, product or service depicted in its research publications, and does not advise technology users to select only those vendors with the highest ratings or other designation. Gartner research publications consist of the opinions of Gartner’s research organization and should not be construed as statements of fact. Gartner disclaims all warranties, expressed or implied, with respect to this research, including any warranties of merchantability or fitness for a particular purpose.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/magic-quadrant</category>
            <category>product/sap-extended-warehouse-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Supply Chain Issues Keeping CEOs Up at Night]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2023/11/supply-chain-issues-keeping-ceos-up-at-night</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2023/11/supply-chain-issues-keeping-ceos-up-at-night</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Supply chain issues keep executives up at night, but SAP is working to leverage the power of generative AI for supply chain resilience.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17fce40551915dfea41e19d0bfc190fb085838212.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17fce40551915dfea41e19d0bfc190fb085838212.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_17fce40551915dfea41e19d0bfc190fb085838212.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Supply Chain Issues Keeping CEOs Up at Night" src="./media_17fce40551915dfea41e19d0bfc190fb085838212.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="supply-chain-issues-keeping-ceos-up-at-night">Supply Chain Issues Keeping CEOs Up at Night</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Building risk-resilient supply chains is one of the top issues CEOs are discussing on earning calls and in board rooms around the globe. The issue has gone from one priority among many to business critical. And CEOs are no longer just pursuing lower costs, shorter lead times, and higher quality.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Instead, they are recognizing the need to resolve supply chain disruptions in an integrated way, bridging the silos of various functions and going beyond dealing with supply chain disruptions as they occur.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="a-risk-resilient-and-sustainable-supply-chain-is-one-that-is-connected-contextualized-and-collaborative">A risk-resilient and sustainable supply chain is one that is connected, contextualized, and collaborative</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Taking a macro-view is also something governments have begun doing. Just think of the huge investments to “bring supply chains home”; for example, <a href="https://commission.europa.eu/strategy-and-policy/priorities-2019-2024/europe-fit-digital-age/european-chips-act_en">€43 billion in the EU</a> for semiconductors or <a href="https://www.whitehouse.gov/briefing-room/statements-releases/2023/04/17/fact-sheet-biden-harris-administration-announces-new-private-and-public-sector-investments-for-affordable-electric-vehicles/">$100 billion in the U.S.</a> for sustainable energy. At the same time, diversifying supply chains and complying with new regulations keeps increasing their complexity.</p>
  <p>Companies take various approaches to these challenges, such as de-coupling their supply chains by building up costly inventories for critical components. Another option is reshoring or nearshoring, which brings manufacturing and supplier relationships closer to core markets, ideally in countries with similar political and economic systems. But all of these strategies come with downsides, including the cost of operations in globally competitive markets.</p>
  <p>At SAP, our vision is to embrace interconnected supply chains and optimize material flows — sustainably — with digital technologies. We believe in intelligent strategies to reduce supply chain uncertainties for the long-term by helping industries redefine their operations and by creating value chains that are more intelligent, connected, and responsive.</p>
  <h2 id="supply-chain-convergence-increases-agility">Supply Chain Convergence Increases Agility</h2>
  <p>Companies that resolve supply chain disruptions in an integrated manner bridge the silos of various functions such as procurement, logistics, or manufacturing. That’s how they can truly alleviate the impact to their organizations. Supply chain functions need to work in concert and extend into their ecosystem of suppliers. Even the most accurate supply chain plan is meaningless if material suppliers cannot commit to volumes and lead times. Through integrating supply chain planning, such as demand and supply plans with procurement collaboration, manufacturers have a much stronger strategic lever to avoid downstream shortages.</p>
  <p>At SAP, we call this approach <strong>design-to-operate</strong>. Our strategy is to deeply connect all relevant functions in a supply chain along end-to-end value chains and business processes. Going beyond the four walls of your own enterprise, into your ecosystem of suppliers and sub-suppliers — that’s the ultimate way to tackle supply chain challenges. In the case of supply shortages, for example, it is imperative to analyze the impact to the organization.</p>
  <p>With SAP Integrated Business Planning, <a href="https://blogs.sap.com/2022/07/05/how-network-aware-supply-chain-planning-drives-resiliency/">affected production orders can be quickly identified</a>. Impacted customer orders and revenue at risk are visible and informed actions can be taken to mitigate any shortages, for example, by changing production schedules. The SAP Digital Manufacturing system knows immediately about the changed production plan for the next shifts and adjusts labor and resources accordingly. Logistics departments in SAP Extended Warehouse Management orchestrate the new material flow, <a href="https://blogs.sap.com/2023/04/14/sap-digital-manufacturing-and-ewm-integration-using-manage-staging-2.0-app/">moving the right raw materials into production</a>, and asset maintenance activities are re-scheduled to adhere to the new production priorities.</p>
  <p>As a result, supply chain leaders who follow a design-to-operate paradigm are highly agile and can take critical actions quickly to deal with supply chain disruptions.</p>
  <h2 id="saps-industry-business-networks-a-new-paradigm">SAP’s Industry Business Networks: A New Paradigm</h2>
  <p>Entire industries are recognizing the benefits of going beyond the four walls of their own enterprise. Consider a car company investigating faulty engines coming from one of their production lines. Now imagine it can trace the failure not only to a particular batch of components from one supplier but then dig even deeper to identify faulty basic parts from the supplier’s supplier. Instead of having to recall thousands of vehicles, it needs to recall only a few.</p>
  <p>Solving problems this way requires a mindset for radical collaboration as well as technology for efficient, cross-company data exchange. <a href="https://catena-x.net/en/">Catena-X</a> is an open network that enables just that. It guarantees interoperability by defining common standards. The network is not owned by a single business and data providers keep their data sovereignty. For instance, they define for how long and for which purpose their data can be used. On the other hand, consumers can trust that data comes from a reliable source.</p>
  <p>SAP is one of the founding members of Catena-X, together with five other companies. Since 2020, the initiative has grown to <a href="https://catena-x.net/fileadmin/_online_media_/231012_1_CAT_007_List_of_Members_EN.pdf">170 international auto makers, suppliers, and</a> IT companies. Among them are Germany’s biggest car companies as well as many small and medium enterprises. Catena-X may soon become the industry’s standard.</p>
  <p>Naturally, the <a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/automotive/industry-network-automotive.html">SAP Business Network for the automotive industry</a> is ready for Catena-X. It readily connects Catena-X to SAP’s broad portfolio of automotive IT solutions to trace parts, measure carbon emissions and manage demand, capacity and quality. Recently, SAP announced business networks for more industries, including <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-network/industries.html">high tech, industrial manufacturing, consumer products, and life sciences</a>, with more to come.</p>
  <h2 id="generative-ai-adds-new-types-of-intelligence">Generative AI Adds New Types of Intelligence</h2>
  <p>A key tool in solving supply chain complexity challenges is artificial intelligence (AI). Even before the recent groundbreaking advances in large language models (LLMs) and generative AI, our supply chain solutions have been infused with both “traditional” and “advanced” AI.</p>
  <p>For instance, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/integrated-business-planning.html">SAP Integrated Business Planning for Supply Chain</a> creates demand forecasts based on historical demand patterns, but it also leverages advanced machine learning capabilities to improve forecast demand with point-of-sales data and improve planning quality using self-healing master data and lead time predictions. In the future, generative AI will enable completely new types of intelligent capabilities like these:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Facilitating human-machine interaction:</strong> Users will soon be able to interact with their system much more naturally via our new embedded <a href="/2023/09/joule-new-generative-ai-assistant">generative assistant Joule</a>. For example, they will be able to ask which of customer X’s demands for product Y are still unfilled in Central America. Joule will give the answer, intelligently combining data from various systems and domains because it will be embedded throughout the SAP cloud enterprise portfolio.</li>
    <li><strong>Supporting creativity:</strong> Much like a sparring partner, generative AI can help designers, engineers, and product managers create new product ideas in an innovation cycle and iterate them with SAP Enterprise Product Development.</li>
    <li><strong>Transforming unstructured data:</strong> Consider a truck arriving at a warehouse with inbound cargo. The clerk knows what cargo to expect and this is saved in an SAP system. However, what is really on the truck is written on a loading list, often in paper form. Making this data available digitally has been possible for quite a while and is known as optical character recognition (OCR). What’s new is that generative AI tools can now match the unstructured loading list to the structured data already in the system — in a split second.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>Leveraging AI for companies to scale and sustain business operations will no longer be optional. Consider the increasing labor shortage facing manufacturing companies, among others. They will have a shortfall of up to 85 million employees by 2030 — roughly the population of Germany!</p>
  <p>By automating mundane tasks with advanced AI capabilities, we will bridge the human resources gap and enable experts to focus on what really matters: making data-backed business decisions.</p>
  <p>Human and artificial intelligence work hand in hand — it’s a duet, not a duel.</p>
  <p>We already help our customers build risk-resilient supply chains and deeply connect enterprises to run productive, agile and automated operations. Now, by also leveraging the power of generative AI, we will ensure that supply chain resilience doesn’t have to be something that keeps CEOs up at night.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Thomas Saueressig is a member of the Executive Board of SAP SE, SAP Product Engineering.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/blog/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/blog/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/blog/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/blog/article-read-more</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/executive-blog</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/catena-x</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>product/sap-digital-manufacturing</category>
            <category>product/sap-extended-warehouse-management</category>
            <category>product/sap-integrated-business-planning-for-supply-chain</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Named a Leader in the 2023 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Warehouse Management Systems]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/sap-a-leader-2023-gartner-magic-quadrant-wms</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/sap-a-leader-2023-gartner-magic-quadrant-wms</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is again a Leader in the Gartner Magic Quadrant for WMS, based on ability to execute and for the completeness of vision. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/magic-quadrant</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-network-for-logistics</category>
            <category>product/sap-extended-warehouse-management</category>
            <category>product/sap-transportation-management</category>
            <category>product/sap-warehouse-insights</category>
            <category>product/sap-warehouse-robotics</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[AI Built for Business]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/sap-sapphire-business-ai</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/sap-sapphire-business-ai</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Turning AI technology advancement into business impact remains a challenge for many companies, SAP's unique approach to AI can help.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/financial-management</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/microsoft</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-digital-assistant</category>
            <category>product/sap-extended-warehouse-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>product/sap-signavio-process-manager</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-transportation-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Dutch Car Manufacturer VDL Nedcar Digitalized Yard Operations to Boost Efficiency]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/vdl-nedcar-digitalized-yard-operations-to-boost-efficiency</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/vdl-nedcar-digitalized-yard-operations-to-boost-efficiency</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Read to learn how SAP Yard Logistics helped Dutch car manufacturer VDL Nedcar digitalize yard operations and boost efficiency.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1757ca0c89f98bd920670b0e1192f2aa76882c160.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1757ca0c89f98bd920670b0e1192f2aa76882c160.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1757ca0c89f98bd920670b0e1192f2aa76882c160.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="How Dutch Car Manufacturer VDL Nedcar Digitalized Yard Operations to Boost Efficiency" src="./media_1757ca0c89f98bd920670b0e1192f2aa76882c160.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="how-dutch-car-manufacturer-vdl-nedcar-digitalized-yard-operations-to-boost-efficiency">How Dutch Car Manufacturer VDL Nedcar Digitalized Yard Operations to Boost Efficiency</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>“With a growing number of customers and increasingly complex supply chain processes, VDL needed to replace its legacy system with a modern and flexible IT landscape to support our clear <a href="/topics/industry-4-0">Industry 4.0</a> vision to drive efficiencies and be ready for the future.”</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>These were the words of Pepijn Timmermans, vice president of Digitalization at VDL Nedcar, who I recently had the chance to speak to about how the company modernized and digitalized its yard operations.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="prepare-your-logistics-for-the-future-with-integrated-yard-management">Prepare your logistics for the future with integrated yard management</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/yard-logistics.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="what-is-vdl-nedcar">What Is VDL Nedcar?</h2>
  <p><a href="https://www.vdlnedcar.nl/en">VDL Nedcar</a> is not just the only independent contract manufacturer in the Netherlands but also one of the most advanced vehicle manufacturers in Europe. The 50-year-old company builds high-quality cars for major brands such as BMW, as well as a plug-in hybrid electric vehicle (PHEV) variant of the MINI Countryman. And as a company that banks on strong partnerships and innovation, VDL will also build electric vehicles for their newest customer, the U.S. company Canoo.</p>
  <h2 id="how-to-manage-a-yard-full-of-moving-products">How to Manage a Yard Full of Moving Products</h2>
  <p>VDL Nedcar faced the challenge of managing the movement of vehicles, parts, and materials. “We have 1,000 parts suppliers, 12,000 parts numbers, and seven carriers who bring all these parts by truck to our plant, which results in an inbound of 270 full trucks per day coming in and going out,” Timmermans explained.</p>
  <p>“The automotive industry has a closed loop where packaging material is brought back to the supplier. This means transport can arrive at any moment and within only one hour the driver drops a trailer, picks up another with packaging materials, and leaves the yard,” he added. “We have to manage 350 trailers in our yard. Basically, it’s a warehouse management system for trailers.”</p>
  <p>The process to do this was very manual. When a carrier came in, they picked an empty spot in the yard, filled out papers, and took them to the office where the information was put into the system. This was a very labor-intensive and error-prone process, and, as Timmermans explained, “If we missed only one trailer, the impact could be dramatic and costly.” A missed trailer of a vital part could harm the production processes and even lead to major stoppages of the plant for a full day, which relies on a just-in-time approach.</p>
  <h2 id="the-answer-warehouses-on-wheels">The Answer? Warehouses on Wheels</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-the-document-how-can-automated-inbound-logistics-processes-help-yard-staff-work-more-productively">Read the document "How Can Automated Inbound Logistics Processes Help Yard Staff Work More Productively?"</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/customer-stories.html?search=SAP+yard+logistics&#x26;pdf-asset=ba8be30c-0a7e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b&#x26;page=1#customer-stories-finder">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The answer was to analyze business processes. “We have a very unique inbound logistics supply chain concept. I think we are the only one of the OEMs in Europe who has control of inbound transport fully in our own hands,” Timmermans said. “In our material requirement system, we also integrate the whole of inbound logistics transport planning as part of the <a href="https://insights.sap.com/what-is-mrp/">material requirement planning</a>, which makes us unique and enables us to have very efficient inbound logistics.”</p>
  <p>“We established a ‘warehouse on wheels’ concept, which optimizes our transport efficiency,” he said. “Instead of booking a time slot days ahead with the risk of long waiting times at the gate and manual management of documents in the past, carriers can arrive at our plant 24/7, sign in at the gate, get a parking location assigned for the trailer, and receive a note where to pick up an empty trailer with packaging materials.”</p>
  <h2 id="managing-the-logistics-of-the-yard">Managing the Logistics of the Yard</h2>
  <p>To get full control and transparency of this warehouse on wheels, VDL Nedcar implemented <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/yard-logistics.html">SAP Yard Logistics</a>.</p>
  <p>“Based on <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/yard-logistics.html">SAP Yard Logistics</a> and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/fiori.html">SAP Fiori apps</a>, we developed a solution where our six dock master trucks that drive the trailers from the yard to the loading dock and empty back to the yard can be steered fully automatically,” Timmermans explained. “The trucks are equipped with industrial flat screens and connected to the solution. All movement triggers are visualized for the dock masters and they get automated priorities for which trailer to transport where, including an optimization algorithm to indicate which truck is close to the trailer to be picked up. Getting this process automated and optimized saved one employee per shift.”</p>
  <p>“Previously, we also did a manual weekly inventory of all trailers on the yard for which we needed one man day per week. That has all gone,” he added.</p>
  <p>“SAP Yard Logistics helps us cooperate with our suppliers much better. We have an easier, digitalized, and transparent process at the gate for our carriers, which boosts efficiency, reduces waiting time, and eases administration,” he said.</p>
  <p><strong>Tangible benefits</strong> include:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Increased process transparency</li>
    <li>Reduced administrative effort of one day per week</li>
    <li>Time savings thanks to inventory automation</li>
    <li>Efficiency gains due to automated and digitalized processes on the yard saving one employee per shift</li>
    <li>Reduced waiting time for carriers and enabling them to plan better</li>
    <li>Streamlined and transparent processes at the gate</li>
    <li>Almost no incidents or administrative mistakes</li>
    <li>Standard solution that is integrated with <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/s4hana-erp.html">SAP S/4HANA</a></li>
  </ul>
  <p>“In the future, we plan to connect our yard logistics processes with <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/transportation-logistics.html">SAP Transportation Management</a> to provide a self-service portal for the carriers, automate gate processes with cameras, and leverage <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/extended-warehouse-management.html">SAP Extended Warehouse Management</a> to get full transparency across the entire supply chain,” Timmermans concluded.</p>
  <p>To learn more about how to achieve efficient and sustainable processes with SAP Yard Logistics, <a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/td/sap-yard-logistics-free-trial.html">start your free trial today</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Karin Fent is senior director of Global Customer Success Digital Supply Chain at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/automotive</category>
            <category>industry/travel-transportation</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-4-0</category>
            <category>product/sap-extended-warehouse-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>product/sap-transportation-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Ranked No. 1 in Gartner Market Share Analysis Report and Recognized as a Leader in Transportation and Warehouse Management Systems]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/sap-a-leader-supply-chain-management-transportation-warehouse-management</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/sap-a-leader-supply-chain-management-transportation-warehouse-management</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is ranked the No. 1 supply chain management software vendor by market share in revenue worldwide by Gartner. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1de94c869ef89399d5940ea21e2e295e14b890cee.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1de94c869ef89399d5940ea21e2e295e14b890cee.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1de94c869ef89399d5940ea21e2e295e14b890cee.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Ranked No. 1 in Gartner Market Share Analysis Report and Recognized as a Leader in Transportation and Warehouse Management Systems" src="./media_1de94c869ef89399d5940ea21e2e295e14b890cee.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-ranked-no-1-in-gartner-market-share-analysis-report-and-recognized-as-a-leader-in-transportation-and-warehouse-management-systems">SAP Ranked No. 1 in Gartner Market Share Analysis Report and Recognized as a Leader in Transportation and Warehouse Management Systems</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-customer-centric-products-to-market-faster-and-at-less-cost-with-global-supply-chain-management-software-from-sap">Get customer-centric products to market faster and at less cost with global supply chain management software from SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/supply-chain-management.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced that it is ranked the No. 1 supply chain management software vendor by market share in revenue worldwide in the Gartner® “<a href="https://www.gartner.com/document/4003648?ref=solrAll&#x26;refval=295315829">Market Share Analysis: Supply Chain Management Software, Worldwide, 2020</a>” report.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Vendors were analyzed across procurement, supply chain execution and supply chain planning and, for the second year in a row, SAP ranked No. 1 across all three categories.</p>
  <p>In addition, SAP was also recognized as a Leader in both the “<a href="https://www.gartner.com/document/4003090?ref=solrAll&#x26;refval=299962045">2021 Gartner Magic Quadrant™ for Warehouse Management Systems</a>” report and the “<a href="https://www.gartner.com/document/4000019">2021 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Transportation Management Systems</a>” report. These recognitions illustrate SAP’s continued influence on the future of resilient digital supply chains.</p>
  <p>“In our opinion, this trio of recognitions from Gartner reflects our commitment to improving outcomes for our customers,” said Franz Hero, head of SAP Digital Supply Chain Development. “We’ve worked to ensure they are empowered to rapidly respond to changing market conditions, and that invested commitment is being recognized.”</p>
  <p>The SAP Extended Warehouse Management application helps customers manage high-volume warehouse operations and integrate complex supply chain logistics within their warehouse and distribution processes to deliver visibility and control.</p>
  <p>The SAP Transportation Management application supports customers across all major industries, with a focus on consumer products, agriculture, mining, construction, chemical and retail. The application helps customers dramatically reduce transportation complexity by integrating fleet and logistics management throughout their network.</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="http://news.sap.com/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP on Twitter at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Media Contact:</strong> Angela Feher, +1 (347) 882-1689, <a href="mailto:angela.feher@sap.com">angela.feher@sap.com</a>, ET<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p><em>Gartner, “Market Share Analysis: Supply Chain Management Software, Worldwide, 2020,” Balaji Abbabatulla, Satyam ., Neha Gupta, Amarendra , Christian Titze, Micky Keck, 15 July 2021.</em><br><em>Gartner, “Magic Quadrant for Warehouse Management Systems,” Simon Tunstall, Dwight Klappich, 30 June 2021.</em><br><em>Gartner, “Magic Quadrant for Transportation Management Systems,” Bart De Muynck, Brock Johns, Oscar Sanchez Duran, Carly West, 30 March 2021.</em><br><em>Gartner does not endorse any vendor, product or service depicted in its research publications and does not advise technology users to select only those vendors with the highest ratings or other designation. Gartner research publications consist of the opinions of Gartner’s Research &#x26; Advisory organization and should not be construed as statements of fact. Gartner disclaims all warranties, expressed or implied, with respect to this research, including any warranties of merchantability or fitness for a particular purpose. GARTNER and Magic Quadrant are registered trademarks and service marks of Gartner, Inc. and/or its affiliates in the U.S. and internationally and are used herein with permission. All rights reserved.</em></p>
  <p>Any statements contained in this document that are not historical facts are forward-looking statements as defined in the U.S. Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995. Words such as “anticipate,” “believe,” “estimate,” “expect,” “forecast,” “intend,” “may,” “plan,” “project,” “predict,” “should” and “will” and similar expressions as they relate to SAP are intended to identify such forward-looking statements. SAP undertakes no obligation to publicly update or revise any forward-looking statements. All forward-looking statements are subject to various risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results to differ materially from expectations. The factors that could affect SAP’s future financial results are discussed more fully in SAP’s filings with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (“SEC”), including SAP’s most recent Annual Report on Form 20-F filed with the SEC. Readers are cautioned not to place undue reliance on these forward-looking statements, which speak only as of their dates.<br>© 2021 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>industry/travel-transportation</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-supply-chain</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>product/sap-extended-warehouse-management</category>
            <category>product/sap-transportation-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/warehouse-management</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>