<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/product/sap-business-network-for-logistics/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Named a Leader in the 2024 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Transportation Management Systems]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-named-a-leader-2024-gartner-magic-quadrant-transportation-management-systems</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-named-a-leader-2024-gartner-magic-quadrant-transportation-management-systems</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[For the 10th consecutive year, SAP has been named as a Leader in the 2024 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Transportation Management Systems.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_129328166e826d3a52e6b9854f483cc4a5f36fd9a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_129328166e826d3a52e6b9854f483cc4a5f36fd9a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_129328166e826d3a52e6b9854f483cc4a5f36fd9a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Named a Leader in the 2024 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Transportation Management Systems" src="./media_129328166e826d3a52e6b9854f483cc4a5f36fd9a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-named-a-leader-in-the-2024-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-transportation-management-systems">SAP Named a Leader in the 2024 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Transportation Management Systems</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>For the 10th consecutive year, SAP has been named as a Leader in the 2024 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Transportation Management Systems.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP is positioned in the Leaders Quadrant based on our Ability to Execute and for the Completeness of our Vision.</p>
  <p>We believe that this recognition confirms our strategy in Logistics, which is based on three pillars:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Connecting every process and providing synchronized logistics execution to support highly efficient and fast paced fulfillment cycles</li>
    <li>Collaborating with a single network of carriers, digital forwarders, and visibility providers to spot risks and avoid disruptions and thereby provide best-in-class delivery experience</li>
    <li>Contextualizing every decision, leveraging artificial intelligence (<a href="/topics/artificial-intelligence">AI</a>) and machine learning to optimize operations and to provide business insights</li>
  </ul>
  <p>SAP Transportation Management is an integral part of the overall SAP strategy and gives companies the ability to manage their end-to-end transportation processes from procurement through planning and execution to freight settlement with analytics to support each step.</p>
  <p>We continue to innovate in SAP Transportation Management based on our market analysis and even more importantly based on feedback from our global install base and ecosystem. Recent innovations include advancements in areas like sustainability, planning and optimization, supply chain execution, and generative AI.</p>
  <p>SAP Transportation Management and SAP Business Network for Logistics enable logistics partners to collaborate with each other and provide visibility to all stakeholders throughout the shipment lifecycle and help manage risks as they arise through intelligent insights. We continue to grow SAP Business Network, adding more carriers and additional networks to provide expanded coverage around the world and across all transportation modes.</p>
  <p>As more customers evaluate SAP Transportation Management, we continue to strategically expand our partner network to ensure our customers have access to an ecosystem that supports their operations no matter where they are in the world or how they move their freight. Our global partner network made up of systems integrators, business consultants, and technology providers help our customers manage their transportation transformations, whether they be system replacements, upgrades, greenfield deployments, or part of larger enterprise transformations.</p>
  <p>“Our customers use SAP Transportation Management and SAP Business Network for Logistics to manage transportation operations in more than 20 industries and in every corner of the world,” said Till Dengel, global head of Logistics and Manufacturing Product Marketing at SAP. “Because we look at logistics holistically, clients can confidently confirm their orders, knowing that fulfillment can be executed as promised, since ERP, warehousing, and transportation are always in sync.”</p>
  <p>“Adopting logistics solutions from SAP across our facilities in all our markets allowed us to optimize freight transportation,” said Carlo Noè, Global Process and Applications Manager for Trade, Transport, and Logistics Division at Hitachi Energy Ltd. “We can interact with our stakeholders and carriers in a digital way, helping us manage supply chain risk, enhance agility, and build supply chain resilience.”</p>
  <p>For more details on the latest Gartner Magic Quadrant for TMS <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/transportation-logistics.html?campaigncode=CRM-YD24-DSC-2678872&#x26;url_id=magic-quadrant-for-transportation-management-systems&#x26;rc=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.gartner.com%2Freprints%2F%3Fid%3D1-2H3J1JVF%26ct%3D240327%26st%3Dsb">read the Gartner Reprint here</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Bill King is senior product marketing manager for Logistics at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-transportation-management-reduce-complexity-increase-efficiency-and-improve-agility-for-a-more-sustainable-risk-resilient-supply-chain">SAP Transportation Management: Reduce complexity, increase efficiency, and improve agility for a more sustainable, risk-resilient supply chain</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/transportation-logistics.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>GARTNER is a registered trademark and service mark of Gartner, Inc. and/or its affiliates in the U.S. and internationally, MAGIC QUADRANT is a registered trademark of Gartner, Inc. and/or its affiliates and are used herein with permission. All rights reserved.<br><em>Gartner does not endorse any vendor, product or service depicted in its research publications, and does not advise technology users to select only those vendors with the highest ratings or other designation. Gartner research publications consist of the opinions of Gartner’s research organization and should not be construed as statements of fact. Gartner disclaims all warranties, expressed or implied, with respect to this research, including any warranties of merchantability or fitness for a particular purpose.</em></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/travel-transportation</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/magic-quadrant</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-network-for-logistics</category>
            <category>product/sap-transportation-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cloud-Based Visibility Equips Trading Partners to Counter Supply Chain Disruption]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/cloud-based-business-networks-equip-trading-partners</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/cloud-based-business-networks-equip-trading-partners</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Enterprises rely increasingly on cloud-based business networks to extend visibility, facilitate collaboration, and stay ahead of disruption.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17eccb1dbc9662324e6f79b18766a0335800c285f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17eccb1dbc9662324e6f79b18766a0335800c285f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_17eccb1dbc9662324e6f79b18766a0335800c285f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Cloud-Based Visibility Equips Trading Partners to Counter Supply Chain Disruption" src="./media_17eccb1dbc9662324e6f79b18766a0335800c285f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="cloud-based-visibility-equips-trading-partners-to-counter-supply-chain-disruption">Cloud-Based Visibility Equips Trading Partners to Counter Supply Chain Disruption</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>With geopolitical conflict and climate change roiling global shipping corridors from the <a href="https://www.arabnews.com/node/2463151/business-economy">Suez Canal</a> to <a href="https://www.reuters.com/business/panama-canal-does-not-plan-transit-restrictions-least-until-april-2024-02-07">Panama</a> and <a href="https://apnews.com/article/persian-gulf-oman-strait-hormuz-3a906e909be2ce63c87c1b208ed05baa">elsewhere</a>, enterprises rely increasingly on cloud-based business networks and artificial intelligence (AI) applications to extend visibility, facilitate collaboration, and ensure they stay one step ahead of the looming threat of disruption.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Meanwhile, as legislation to bolster transparency in supply chains <a href="https://www.bundesregierung.de/breg-en/service/archive/supply-chain-act-1872076">takes</a> <a href="https://minister.homeaffairs.gov.au/jasonwood/Pages/modern-slavery-act-delivers-transparency-in-supply-chains.aspx">hold</a> <a href="https://oag.ca.gov/SB657">around</a> <a href="https://laws.justice.gc.ca/eng/acts/F-10.6">the</a> <a href="https://www.consilium.europa.eu/en/press/press-releases/2023/12/14/corporate-sustainability-due-diligence-council-and-parliament-strike-deal-to-protect-environment-and-human-rights">world</a>, the digital platforms through which trading partners carry out interconnected operational processes have become indispensable for managing risk, advancing sustainability objectives, and verifying adherence to ethical business practices – even as volatility in international commerce gathers pace.</p>
  <p>After rebounding from several years of logjammed seaports, idled factories, and quarantined workers, many businesses find that though COVID-19 has receded, disruption stubbornly persists. Yet visibility across all aspects of the supply chain – from sourcing raw materials and managing logistics capacity to securing working capital solutions and managing dispersed physical assets – remains paramount in the quest to ensure business continuity, instill operational resilience, and deepen competitive advantage.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-business-network-powers-transparency-resiliency-and-sustainability">SAP Business Network powers transparency, resiliency, and sustainability</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-network.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>To help provide businesses with the 360-degree visibility and collaborative capabilities they require across complex trading relationships, SAP Business Network can connect people, processes, and systems across multiple enterprises to help digitize transactions, harness data-driven insights, and create transparent, resilient, and sustainable supply chains. Through <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-network/solutions.html#active_tab_item_1602592051931">SAP Business Network for Procurement</a>, trading partners can gain process efficiencies, improve supply assurance, and achieve business process and regulatory compliance by increasing operational transparency. With <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-network/solutions.html#active_tab_item_1602592257238">SAP Business Network Supply Chain Collaboration</a>, companies can achieve supply chain visibility by enabling plan-driven automation, optimizing capacity and inventory, and streamlining workflow. Aided by <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-network/solutions.html#active_tab_item_1602592296240">SAP Business Network for Logistics</a>, shippers and carriers can work together in unison, track and trace goods in transit, and achieve transparency throughout the supply chain by optimizing logistics processes, increasing on-time deliveries, and mitigating third-party risk. Relying on <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-network/solutions.html#active_tab_item_1660146110353">SAP Business Network Asset Collaboration</a>, owners, operators, and service providers can strengthen joint processes and the flow of shared information through a single, consistent version of asset master data to help streamline asset maintenance processes and reduce maintenance costs. With the benefit of <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-network/solutions.html#active_tab_item_1660146142567">SAP Business Network for Finance</a>, trading partners can enhance payment security, free up working capital through early-payment discounts, and leverage access to capital bound up in outstanding receivables.</p>
  <p>By linking together the routine business processes of trading partners, cloud-based networks establish the breadth of data necessary to apply predictive and generative AI applications to yield meaningful insights and outcomes. Through large language models and other forms of machine learning, cloud-based applications create new content with characteristics resembling that which precedes it. With every successive effort, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/spend-management/innovations.html#ai">generative AI</a> sharpens its ability to tailor desired content.</p>
  <p>As the world’s largest platform for business-to-business commerce, SAP Business Network can present an ideal setting for generative AI, in that it helps bring together an extremely large volume of trading partners across hundreds of millions of transactions representing US$5.3 trillion in commerce annually. Later this year, generative AI capabilities in SAP Business Network will be able to help detect errors and present automatic summaries when businesses create invoices. AI will also enable the network to help enrich catalog content and discovery posting responses for suppliers.</p>
  <p>SAP Business Network has accumulated significant structured content over many years to help generate broad operational insights for trading partners. When buyers, suppliers, carriers, and financing solution providers share operational data with each other in real time, the mutual value they create can be exponential rather than additive, enabling all participants in commerce to plan ahead with confidence, continuity, and enduring resilience.</p>
  <p>For further information on SAP Business Network and how we are equipping enterprises large and small with the digital tools needed to counter disruption, visit <a href="https://www.sap.com/businessnetwork">sap.com/businessnetwork</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Jörn Keller is executive vice president and chief product officer of SAP Business Network.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="stay-in-touch-and-follow-sap-news-on-linkedin">Stay in touch and follow SAP News on LinkedIn</h3>
        <p><em><a href="">Join us on LinkedIn</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/asset-management</category>
            <category>industry/travel-transportation</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-network-for-logistics</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Creating an Agile, Resilient, and Sustainable Logistics Network]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/creating-agile-resilient-sustainable-logistics-network</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/creating-agile-resilient-sustainable-logistics-network</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP's Till Dengel shares how industrial manufacturing businesses can drive an agile, resilient, and sustainable logistics network.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/travel-transportation</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-network-for-logistics</category>
            <category>product/sap-warehouse-robotics</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Named a Leader in the 2023 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Warehouse Management Systems]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/sap-a-leader-2023-gartner-magic-quadrant-wms</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/sap-a-leader-2023-gartner-magic-quadrant-wms</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is again a Leader in the Gartner Magic Quadrant for WMS, based on ability to execute and for the completeness of vision. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/magic-quadrant</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-network-for-logistics</category>
            <category>product/sap-extended-warehouse-management</category>
            <category>product/sap-transportation-management</category>
            <category>product/sap-warehouse-insights</category>
            <category>product/sap-warehouse-robotics</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>