<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/product/sap-information-collaboration-hub-for-life-sciences/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reflecting On a Year of Transformation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/reflecting-on-support-experience-transformation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/reflecting-on-support-experience-transformation</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP's Andreas Heckmann reflects on the support experience transformation of the past year, and how it will continue in 2023.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/application-lifecycle-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/built-in-support</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-solution-support-innovation</category>
            <category>news-tag/machine-learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/real-time-support</category>
            <category>product/sap-cloud-alm</category>
            <category>product/sap-information-collaboration-hub-for-life-sciences</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pharmaceutical Manufacturers Fight Fake Drugs with Intelligent Supply Chains]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/pharmaceutical-manufacturers-drug-supply-chains</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/pharmaceutical-manufacturers-drug-supply-chains</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Investing in intelligent supply chain solutions can enable resilience and prevent counterfeit drugs in the life sciences industry. Learn how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digitalization</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>industry/life-sciences</category>
            <category>product/sap-information-collaboration-hub-for-life-sciences</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-store</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Industry Innovation: Turning Supply Chains into Hot Spots for Meaningful Change]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/industry-innovation-supply-chains-meaningful-change</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/industry-innovation-supply-chains-meaningful-change</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The Customer Solution Support & Innovation organization at SAP works with various organizations to support and encourage industry innovation.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/banking</category>
            <category>news-tag/covid-19</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-solution-support-innovation</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>industry/life-sciences</category>
            <category>news-tag/research-development</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-advanced-track-and-trace-for-pharmaceuticals</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-information-collaboration-hub-for-life-sciences</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Take: New Technology Could All But Prevent Counterfeit Drugs from Reaching Consumers]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/01/the-take-counterfeit-drugs-technology-prevention</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/01/the-take-counterfeit-drugs-technology-prevention</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New technology like blockchain and track and trace can help prevent counterfeit drugs from reaching consumers. Get SAP's take.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>content-type/perspective</category>
            <category>industry/life-sciences</category>
            <category>product/sap-information-collaboration-hub-for-life-sciences</category>
            <category>news-tag/the-take</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[2021 Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award Finalists: Products and Technology]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/products-and-technology-finalists-hasso-plattner-founders-award-2021</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/products-and-technology-finalists-hasso-plattner-founders-award-2021</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Get to know the three Products and Technology finalists for the 2021 Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award, SAP's highest employee recognition.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_129285b67f76b890ac19d839e260195f38133f292.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_129285b67f76b890ac19d839e260195f38133f292.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_129285b67f76b890ac19d839e260195f38133f292.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="2021 Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award Finalists: Products and Technology" src="./media_129285b67f76b890ac19d839e260195f38133f292.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="hasso-plattner-founders-award-finalists-products-and-technology">2021 Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award Finalists: Products and Technology</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Nine teams across three categories are vying for this year’s Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award. Each category reflects a different type of breakthrough thinking, considering the various ways in which innovation drives SAP’s success.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Here, meet the finalists in the <strong>Products and Technology</strong> category.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>The Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award is the highest<br>employee recognition at SAP, awarded annually by the CEO<br>to an individual or a team.</p>
        <h2 id="finalist-greentoken-by-sap">Finalist: GreenToken by SAP</h2>
        <table>
          <thead>
            <tr>
              <th colspan="2">Promo</th>
            </tr>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td>
                <h3 id="learn-about-what-life-looks-like-at-sap">Learn about what life looks like at SAP</h3>
              </td>
              <td><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/careers/who-we-are/life.html">Learn more</a></strong></td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
        <p>Eighty percent of the world’s palm oil originates from Indonesia and Malaysia. While some of it is being sustainably sourced in sustainable fair-trade plantations and small holdings, much is also being harvested on recently deforested land. How can you tell one from the other?</p>
        <table>
          <thead>
            <tr>
              <th>Embed</th>
            </tr>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td>
                <p>
                  <picture>
                    <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_105dd24f6a7a30ed482a11a642c59bcd55b199697.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
                    <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_105dd24f6a7a30ed482a11a642c59bcd55b199697.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
                    <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_105dd24f6a7a30ed482a11a642c59bcd55b199697.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
                    <img loading="lazy" alt="GreenToken" src="./media_105dd24f6a7a30ed482a11a642c59bcd55b199697.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
                  </picture>
                </p>
                <p><a href="https://youtu.be/Dz2VDEBDAx8">GreenToken</a></p>
              </td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
        <p><em>Video produced by David Aguirre and Rana Hamzakadi</em></p>
        <p>The GreenToken by SAP solution was designed to address this issue by providing a new level of transparency into complex raw material supply chains.</p>
        <p>“In 2019 a group of SAP palm oil customers approached us with this very problem – they wanted a robust solution to maintain facts across the value chain from smallholder to end customer,” says GreenToken Co-Founder James Veale. “Traditional batch-based inventory systems with their simple rules don’t truly reflect the exact makeup of a raw material inventory, which may be a mix of sustainable and non-sustainable sources. At scale, we would be dealing with millions of batches.”</p>
        <p>GreenToken instead uses a digital twin token to represent a fixed and usually small amount of the raw material. Records are kept on a blockchain ledger, and as the material moves along the supply chain GreenToken passes the equivalent number of tokens that represent the volume of material moved, from one supply chain actor’s wallet to another. This creates a tracing history — an immutable chain of custody that adds complete supply chain transparency and makes the data trustworthy.</p>
        <p><strong>Transforming the World Economy</strong></p>
        <p>GreenToken’s elegant yet powerful design has found applications in many industries. The tokens can carry information on any kind of raw materials to help answer a variety of questions: “Are these food crops sustainably sourced? Has this cobalt been mined free of child labor? Is this plastic recycled with a high percentage coming from molecular recycling of plastic waste?”</p>
        <p>With over 77% of the world’s manufactured goods passing through an SAP system, GreenToken is receiving huge interest from SAP customers under increasing pressure from both legislation and their own customer base to prove that their raw material sourcing, processing, and supply chain practices are the best that they can be.</p>
        <p>“GreenToken is SAP’s answer to that,” says Nitin Jain, GreenToken co-founder. “We have found a truly innovative use for tokens on a blockchain ledger that gives transparency to these formerly opaque raw material supply chains. GreenToken’s purpose is to help the world transform to a sustainable and circular economy — and our innovation has made it available in the cloud using simple, frictionless browser-based interfaces.”</p>
        <p><strong>Finalist Fast Facts</strong></p>
        <ul>
          <li><strong>Submission Title</strong>: GreenToken by SAP</li>
          <li><strong>Team:</strong> Nitin Jain in Canada and James Veale in Australia, co-founders, with a global team of 18, including full-time employees and fellows spread across Asia-Pacific Japan, Europe, and North America regions</li>
          <li><strong>Number of employees:</strong> 20</li>
          <li><strong>Achievement:</strong> Developed an elegant yet powerful method to add complete supply chain transparency to previously opaque raw material supply chains using digital twin tokens on a blockchain ledger. The solution works for any raw material supply chain. The team is currently deploying the system in the U.S. and Europe to prove that plastic has a high degree of circular recycled content.</li>
          <li><strong>Impact:</strong> GreenToken allows SAP customers to not only measure and make claims on their current sustainable, ethical, and circular sourcing practices, but also use their procurement spending power to promote good supply chains over bad.</li>
        </ul>
        <h2 id="finalist-ecosilient">Finalist: Ecosilient</h2>
        <p>While optimizing resources and capacities is not exactly a new business challenge, B2B circular sharing platform Ecosilient aims to commodify demand, supply, and services, connecting organizations in a community to generate value more efficiently and sustainably with special focus on existing resources and capacities.</p>
        <table>
          <thead>
            <tr>
              <th>Embed</th>
            </tr>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td>
                <p>
                  <picture>
                    <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11211402536f520f8427a0ee83c63d86205e69ead.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
                    <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11211402536f520f8427a0ee83c63d86205e69ead.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
                    <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_11211402536f520f8427a0ee83c63d86205e69ead.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
                    <img loading="lazy" alt="Ecosilient" src="./media_11211402536f520f8427a0ee83c63d86205e69ead.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
                  </picture>
                </p>
                <p><a href="https://youtu.be/CMowD2YOGDY">Ecosilient</a></p>
              </td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
        <p><em>Video produced by David Aguirre and Rana Hamzakadi</em></p>
        <p>Ecosilient helps businesses leverage resources such as obsolete assets, surplus inventory, waste, and other byproducts into a circular economy. It creates a community layer based on enterprise resource planning (ERP) to enable this growing demand for businesses, stakeholders, and investors to make more responsible decisions that drive meaningful impact on critical issues.</p>
        <p>Ecosilient Founder Avital Ben-Natan says the team’s mission is to “decouple economic growth from natural extraction and corrosive business practices. It’s about creating a trust platform to discover and facilitate collaboration opportunities around shared values.”</p>
        <p>The goal is no less than to address interlinked problems like the climate crisis, social inequities, or broken supply chains. Ecosilient serves as a framework for evolving SAP’s core technologies, data, and its global ecosystem into an engine for a sustainable economy.</p>
        <p>Users will be able to work with SAP software as they are accustomed — sourcing materials, signing contracts, tracing their shipping, and managing their inventories. “But with Ecosilient,” Ben-Natan says, “there is this additional layer in our software that users can trust will guide them to make responsible choices — to do more and better with less.”</p>
        <p><strong>Leading the Sustainable Economy</strong></p>
        <p>Fostered within the SAP Intrapreneurs program, the idea of Ecosilient resonated with many people at SAP from the start and attracted like-minded employees willing to engage in their spare time. “Even though few of us have ever been in the same room, we’ve all become very close while building Ecosilient over the last one and a half years.”</p>
        <p>Ben-Natan says names the impact of climate change as his team’s motivation. “As parents, we feel responsible for the future of our kids and our communities. We have to answer the challenges that we face as a species, but also as a planet and as an economy, and find an appropriate response.”</p>
        <p>The team considers its solution as a natural evolution of what SAP stands for: to create order in chaos, to create opportunities and collaboration, to create a fair, responsible, and ultimately more efficient economy.</p>
        <p>But Ecosilient is also a way for SAP to innovate its own infrastructure and the way it operates as a company, as Ben-Natan stresses: “It’s about creating a fundamental direction for SAP to lead in the sustainable economy.”</p>
        <p><strong>Finalist Fast Facts</strong></p>
        <ul>
          <li><strong>Submission Title</strong>: Ecosilient, the B2B Circular Sharing Platform</li>
          <li><strong>Team:</strong> Avital Ben Natan, Umesh Shekar</li>
          <li><strong>Number of employees:</strong> More than 20, with engineers, designers, innovation specialists, and mentors that have contributed to the business model, design thinking, demo, MVP, and customer engagement, and with special thanks to New Ventures and Technologies, Services IMM, and SAP Experience Garage for platforming.</li>
          <li><strong>Achievement:</strong> Leveraged market research and data analysis to identify target industries and organizations for freight pooling; implemented a WIP MVP and a demo for a sustainable shipping network; started customer engagement and GTM with companies like Unilever, Bechtle, Steelcase, Cargill, and others.</li>
          <li><strong>Impact:</strong> Ecosilient helps companies increase resource efficiency while promoting a sustainable economy by engaging the ecosystem to create shared value.</li>
        </ul>
        <h2 id="finalist-sap-information-collaboration-hub-for-life-sciences">Finalist: SAP Information Collaboration Hub for Life Sciences</h2>
        <p>In recent years, the world has seen the issue of drug counterfeiting increase dramatically. In Africa alone, over 120,000 people die each year because they are being treated with fake malaria medication. It is estimated that currently over 50% of the drugs in Africa are counterfeit.</p>
        <table>
          <thead>
            <tr>
              <th>Embed</th>
            </tr>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td>
                <p>
                  <picture>
                    <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f7faef3f1072158912848af92b3b7caad8242c3c.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
                    <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f7faef3f1072158912848af92b3b7caad8242c3c.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
                    <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1f7faef3f1072158912848af92b3b7caad8242c3c.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
                    <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Information Collaboration Hub for Life Sciences" src="./media_1f7faef3f1072158912848af92b3b7caad8242c3c.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
                  </picture>
                </p>
                <p><a href="https://youtu.be/izPHfZP4CLE">SAP Information Collaboration Hub for Life Sciences</a></p>
              </td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
        <p><em>Video produced by David Aguirre and Rana Hamzakadi</em></p>
        <p>Enter SAP Information Collaboration Hub for Life Sciences: this industry network based on software-as-a-service (SaaS) helps SAP pharmaceutical customers share information on their pharmaceutical products with supply chain partners and government agencies to enable traceability and verification of individual product packs in these markets.</p>
        <p>“It was really a joint effort with plenty of input from SAP customers that inspired the info hub,” says Oliver Nuernberg, chief product owner, SAP Life Sciences. “They pointed out the need for a global network that would minimize the effort by connecting once while sharing data with many participants.”</p>
        <p>Running on SAP Business Technology Platform, the information hub leverages the platform’s integration services to exchange messages, SAP Blockchain Business Services to make data available for verification, and portal services. In 2021, new innovative capabilities enabling the automation of onboarding processes and self-onboarding of trading partners were delivered to enable customers to efficiently onboard hundreds of partners in parallel for new markets.</p>
        <p>The largest eight pharmaceutical manufacturers, and 14 of the top 20, are already using SAP Information Collaboration Hub for Life Sciences, including most of the COVID-19 vaccines manufacturers.</p>
        <p>Next, we plan to offer SAP Information Collaboration Hub for Life Sciences together with SAP Advanced Track and Trace for Pharmaceuticals to enable aid workers from organizations such as the Red Cross and Doctors Without Borders to verify, for example, COVID-19 vaccines that they receive on the spot to low- to middle-income countries.</p>
        <p>Initially, the team was made up of just a handful of SAP employees working out of Germany and Ireland. Today, there are more than 50 team members from the Customer Innovation &#x26; Maintenance organization, mainly located in India, who develop and operate the solution as well as help onboard customers and their business partners.</p>
        <p>Amba Bisht, senior developer for Engineering in Customer Innovation &#x26; Maintenance, says: “What’s so rewarding about working on this project is how it really brings the spirit of SAP — to make the world run better — to life, because by increasing security in the pharmaceutical supply chain and preventing counterfeit medication from reaching patients, SAP Information Collaboration Hub for Life Sciences may ultimately save lives.”</p>
        <p><strong>Finalist Fast Facts</strong></p>
        <ul>
          <li><strong>Submission Title</strong>: SAP Information Collaboration Hub for Life Sciences, Saving Lives One Serial Number at a Time</li>
          <li><strong>Team:</strong> Oliver Nuernberg, Martin Janssen, Dennis Keilbach, Vincent Varain, Sandeep Kumar Dikshit, Shashank Goyal, Amba Bisht, Anil Kumar Suresh, Geetha Ranjani G M, Athul Umesh</li>
          <li><strong>Number of employees:</strong> More than 50</li>
          <li><strong>Achievement</strong>: Global network with the eight largest pharmaceutical companies and 14 of the top 20, most COVID-19 vaccine manufactures, over 1,000 live trading partners. The hub currently hosts 2.2 billion product packs in the blockchain for verification in the U.S. market, manages tens of thousands of messages reported to government agencies, such as those in the EU, Russia, Brazil, and other markets, every day, all to prevent counterfeit products being introduced into the legitimate supply chain.</li>
          <li><strong>Impact:</strong> Increase patient safety by authenticating pharmaceutical products, thus avoiding counterfeit drugs reaching patients; increase sustainability by reducing drug wastage.</li>
        </ul>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>sap-award/hasso-plattner-founders-awards</category>
            <category>product/sap-green-token</category>
            <category>product/sap-information-collaboration-hub-for-life-sciences</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP and Boehringer Ingelheim Create Smart App Prototype to Track Counterfeit Pharmaceuticals]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/boehringer-ingelheim-smart-app-prototype-counterfeit-pharmaceuticals</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/boehringer-ingelheim-smart-app-prototype-counterfeit-pharmaceuticals</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A new smart app from SAP and Boehringer Ingelheim authenticates medicines in the fight against counterfeit pharmaceuticals. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16047e914d6a2f80ab2bcdd9b2b68ea5ecfdd18af.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16047e914d6a2f80ab2bcdd9b2b68ea5ecfdd18af.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_16047e914d6a2f80ab2bcdd9b2b68ea5ecfdd18af.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP and Boehringer Ingelheim Create Smart App Prototype to Track Counterfeit Pharmaceuticals" src="./media_16047e914d6a2f80ab2bcdd9b2b68ea5ecfdd18af.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-and-boehringer-ingelheim-create-smart-app-prototype-to-track-counterfeit-pharmaceuticals">SAP and Boehringer Ingelheim Create Smart App Prototype to Track Counterfeit Pharmaceuticals</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="solve-your-specific-life-sciences-needs-with-software-from-sap">Solve your specific life sciences needs with software from SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/life-sciences.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) is announcing a smart app designed to track, trace and authenticate prescription medicines in the United States. Developed in partnership with leading global pharmaceutical research company <a href="https://www.boehringer-ingelheim.us/">Boehringer Ingelheim</a>, the smart app will enable law enforcement officials to potentially detect illicit, counterfeit or unapproved Boehringer Ingelheim medicines being smuggled into the United States or sold illegally.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The smart app will allow U.S. law enforcement officials across the country to scan the 2D barcode on Boehringer Ingelheim-manufactured life-enhancing medications and authenticate them before the medicines reach patients.</p>
  <p>“The law enforcement smart app utilizes SAP’s scalable and secure blockchain solution for manufacturers to drastically improve the pharmaceutical supply chain from start to finish,” said SAP’s global GM for Consumer Industries, Matt Laukaitis. “As this app demonstrates, vertical industry expertise is a critical success factor in delivering innovations to protect patients and ensure access to authentic, life-enhancing medicines.”</p>
  <p>Passed into law in 2013, the U.S. Drug Supply Chain Security Act (DSCSA) aimed to boost the FDA’s ability to protect U.S. patients by developing a connected, digital system to trace prescription drugs throughout the country and identify counterfeit, stolen or contaminated medicine before it reached the hands of consumers.</p>
  <p>SAP’s smart app is a major step in achieving the vision of the DSCSA and is vital to protecting communities and patient safety. When counterfeit drugs are released into the supply chain, vulnerable patients and marginalized populations with limited access to safe, authentic and affordable medicines bear the brunt of the impact.</p>
  <p>“Patient safety is our top priority at our family-owned company, and unverified pharmaceuticals, especially amid a global pandemic, pose a significant threat to the safety and security of both patients and healthcare providers,” said Aaron Graham, Executive Director, Brand Safety &#x26; Security, Boehringer Ingelheim. “SAP’s blockchain-based solution allows our team to safeguard against illicit and unsafe medicines reaching the hands of those who need medicine the most.”</p>
  <p>This technology builds on SAP’s previous efforts to eliminate counterfeit products with SAP Information Collaboration Hub for Life Sciences, a blockchain-technology tool that allows users to authenticate pharmaceutical packaging as it moves between manufacturers, U.S. wholesalers and U.S. hospitals and pharmacies.</p>
  <p>To learn more, watch a <a href="https://event.on24.com/wcc/r/3355862/A2CD9C01627BDD6F71D4CAA6448EC638">webinar</a>.</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="http://news.sap.com/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP on Twitter at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Media Contact:</strong> Stacy Ries, +1 (484) 619-0411, <a href="mailto:stacy.ries@sap.com">stacy.ries@sap.com</a>, ET<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>Any statements contained in this document that are not historical facts are forward-looking statements as defined in the U.S. Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995. Words such as “anticipate,” “believe,” “estimate,” “expect,” “forecast,” “intend,” “may,” “plan,” “project,” “predict,” “should” and “will” and similar expressions as they relate to SAP are intended to identify such forward-looking statements. SAP undertakes no obligation to publicly update or revise any forward-looking statements. All forward-looking statements are subject to various risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results to differ materially from expectations. The factors that could affect SAP’s future financial results are discussed more fully in SAP’s filings with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (“SEC”), including SAP’s most recent Annual Report on Form 20-F filed with the SEC. Readers are cautioned not to place undue reliance on these forward-looking statements, which speak only as of their dates.<br>© 2021 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>industry/life-sciences</category>
            <category>product/sap-information-collaboration-hub-for-life-sciences</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Personalized Medicine Shouldn’t Be Cost Prohibitive: Life Science Business Networks Can Help]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/personalized-medicine-shouldnt-be-cost-prohibitive-life-science-business-networks</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/personalized-medicine-shouldnt-be-cost-prohibitive-life-science-business-networks</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[When professionals collaborate across the life science supply chain, personalized medicine becomes much more affordable. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/consumer-goods-cpg</category>
            <category>industry/life-sciences</category>
            <category>product/sap-information-collaboration-hub-for-life-sciences</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Completes Pharmaceutical Industry Pilot to Improve Supply Chain Authenticity]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/03/pharmaceutical-supply-chain-industry-pilot</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/03/pharmaceutical-supply-chain-industry-pilot</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[To establish trust in the pharmaceutical supply chain for indirect trade relationships, SAP has completed an industry-wide pilot.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16047e914d6a2f80ab2bcdd9b2b68ea5ecfdd18af.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16047e914d6a2f80ab2bcdd9b2b68ea5ecfdd18af.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_16047e914d6a2f80ab2bcdd9b2b68ea5ecfdd18af.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Completes Pharmaceutical Industry Pilot to Improve Supply Chain Authenticity" src="./media_16047e914d6a2f80ab2bcdd9b2b68ea5ecfdd18af.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-completes-pharmaceutical-industry-pilot-to-improve-supply-chain-authenticity">SAP Completes Pharmaceutical Industry Pilot to Improve Supply Chain Authenticity</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="improve-patient-outcomes-safety-and-quality-of-care-by-collaborating-across-the-digital-health-sciences-network">Improve patient outcomes, safety, and quality of care by collaborating across the digital health sciences network</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/life-sciences.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced the completion of an industry-wide pilot utilizing self-sovereign identity (SSI) credentials to establish trust in the pharmaceutical supply chain for indirect trade relationships.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The pilot is the first step toward establishing an industry-wide standard that will mitigate the risk of noncompliance for pharmaceutical companies.</p>
  <p>The U.S. Drug Supply Chain Security Act (<a href="https://www.fda.gov/drugs/drug-supply-chain-integrity/drug-supply-chain-security-act-dscsa">DSCSA</a>) requires stakeholders in the pharmaceutical supply chain to interact with other entities for product verification and tracing even when they do not have a direct business relationship. DSCSA also requires such interactions to be limited to authorized trading partners.</p>
  <p>One of the legal requirements of DSCSA is the verification of salable returns. This process is already established and supported by SAP Information Collaboration Hub for Life Sciences, which executes tens of thousands of verifications every month. In order to provide our customers with the best solution for compliance with verifying the identity and authorized trading status of partners, SAP chose an open, interoperable technology to validate all stakeholders in the pharmaceutical supply chain, including competitors.</p>
  <p>Together with SAP partner and wallet provider <a href="https://spherity.com/">Spherity GmbH</a>, verifiable credentials issuer <a href="https://legisym.com/">Legisym LLC</a>, and leading pharmaceutical manufacturers and U.S. wholesalers, as well as other serialization solution providers, SAP proved the ability of SSI to validate authorized trading partner status in indirect trade relationships as they occur during verification of product packs as required by U.S. legislation.</p>
  <p>“The inability to verify the identity and authorized trading partner status of companies requesting verification put us at risk for noncompliance” said Dave Mason, Novartis Americas Supply Chain Compliance and Serialization lead. “The use of verifiable credentials ensures that we can establish trust across the supply chain and that we comply to the letter of the law.”</p>
  <p>As early as May 2021, this functionality will be available to existing customers of the SAP Information Collaboration Hub for Life Sciences, to help ensure customers can achieve compliance quickly. To drive the utilization of SSI technology across the industry, SAP also plans to participate in the newly founded Open Credentialing Initiative (OCI).</p>
  <p>“Digital transformation is critical for the life sciences industry to be able to quickly and effectively address public health needs,” said Matt Laukaitis, SAP Consumer Industries global general manager. “This work is yet another example of SAP’s leadership with the life sciences ecosystem of partners and customers to address their industry-specific solution requirements. By establishing an efficient process for transmitting and verifying authorized trading partner status, the supply chain is more safe and secure.”</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="http://news.sap.com/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP on Twitter at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Media Contact:</strong> Stacy Ries, +1 (484) 619-0411, <a href="mailto:sap.contact@sap.com">stacy.ries@sap.com</a>, ET<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>Any statements contained in this document that are not historical facts are forward-looking statements as defined in the U.S. Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995. Words such as “anticipate,” “believe,” “estimate,” “expect,” “forecast,” “intend,” “may,” “plan,” “project,” “predict,” “should” and “will” and similar expressions as they relate to SAP are intended to identify such forward-looking statements. SAP undertakes no obligation to publicly update or revise any forward-looking statements. All forward-looking statements are subject to various risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results to differ materially from expectations. The factors that could affect SAP’s future financial results are discussed more fully in SAP’s filings with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (“SEC”), including SAP’s most recent Annual Report on Form 20-F filed with the SEC. Readers are cautioned not to place undue reliance on these forward-looking statements, which speak only as of their dates.<br>© 2021 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>industry/consumer-goods-cpg</category>
            <category>product/sap-information-collaboration-hub-for-life-sciences</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>