<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/sap-digital-commerce/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Revolution in Product Discovery with Zoovu Apps on SAP Store]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/revolution-in-product-discovery-zoovu-sap-store</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/revolution-in-product-discovery-zoovu-sap-store</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Zoovu humanizes product discovery, making products easier to find, evaluate, and buy by bringing context to your search. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-commerce</category>
            <category>news-tag/e-commerce</category>
            <category>product/sap-commerce-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-cpq</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-digital-commerce</category>
            <category>product/sap-sales-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-store</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Stratesys U-Verify: Intelligent Document Verification on SAP Store]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/06/stratesys-u-verify-intelligent-document-verification</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/06/stratesys-u-verify-intelligent-document-verification</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Available on SAP Store, Stratesys U-Verify for SAP Fieldglass validates compliance with encryption and security. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-digital-commerce</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-store</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Forter Trust Platform: On the Right Side of Digital Commerce]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/04/forter-trust-platform-digital-commerce</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/04/forter-trust-platform-digital-commerce</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[To combat fraud, the Forter Trust Platform recognizes shoppers through their data profile and authenticates them quickly and automatically.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1452c9c8db651a795c453d665f6511e78d518a805.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1452c9c8db651a795c453d665f6511e78d518a805.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1452c9c8db651a795c453d665f6511e78d518a805.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Forter Trust Platform: On the Right Side of Digital Commerce" src="./media_1452c9c8db651a795c453d665f6511e78d518a805.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="forter-trust-platform-on-the-right-side-of-digital-commerce">Forter Trust Platform: On the Right Side of Digital Commerce</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>If your organization has a stake in preventing fraud across your digital commerce operations, I’ll venture to say that you want Michael Reitblat and his team at Forter on your side.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As co-founder of the preeminent fraud-detection platform on the market – now available on <a href="https://store.sap.com/dcp/en/product/display-0000042467_live_v1/Forter%20Fraud%20Protection">SAP Store</a> – Reitblat told me that he has long experience in the “bad guy space,” building a successful career around staying ahead of bad actors. That means he’s the good guy for those making an honest living selling products and services online, and for buyers and shoppers making purchases digitally.</p>
  <p>Known as “The Trust Platform” for digital commerce, Forter doesn’t focus on keeping people out, rather on creating a seamless customer experience for trusted shoppers. How is this done? Machine learning and automated decisioning. Built upon a data set of billions of online identities, the Forter platform provides accurate decisions on whether the end shopper is who they say they are instantly. This ability to provide real-time decisions also streamlines merchant operations, eliminating any dependence on manual transaction reviews. That’s the key to understanding the value of this great app.</p>
  <p>The truth is that both online consumers and merchants are victimized by sophisticated, well-organized fraud networks, Reitblat explained, stealing and selling data in a chain of hard-to-detect transactions. To counteract that, merchants can inadvertently block shoppers who most need to purchase online because they fit the “wrong profile” – living in a country known for a high preponderance of fraudsters, for example. Someone might live a long distance from a physical retailer and be unable to buy essential items online, through no fault of their own. “We are here to give those buyers access, and that is a great source of pride,” he remarked. Further, if a consumer faces hurdles to online purchasing because of clumsy verification processes, they’ll just shop somewhere else. It is therefore crucial to eliminate false declines and reduce friction throughout the purchase journey.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-the-forter-trust-platform">Learn more about the Forter Trust Platform</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://store.sap.com/dcp/en/product/display-0000042467_live_v1/Forter%20Trust%20Platform%20for%20Digital%20Commerce">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="foiling-scams-through-a-circle-of-trust">Foiling Scams through a Circle of Trust</h2>
  <p>It’s somewhat ironic that the best way to thwart fraud is to operate in an environment of trust. In fact, trust among competitors is at the heart of Forter Fraud Protection. Criminals will target one type of company – a shoe manufacturer, for example – and, when detected, move on to exploit the next, giving them the advantage. “We reverse that asymmetry,” Reitblat said. “If you attack one of our customers, the others are immunized, thanks to an aggregated global network of data. They would never share their data with each other, but they are happy to do it through us.” Simply put, the Forter solution is built to recognize people through their data profile and authenticate them quickly and automatically.</p>
  <p>I asked Reitblat about credit card protection. When a consumer reports a fraudulent charge, he replied, the onus is on the retailer, who is left with the expense and is subject to fines or suspension by the credit card issuers if there are too many instances. I was also curious about how Forter stays in front of the fraudsters. Let’s just say that Reitblat, who grew up in Israel and was once a member of the intelligence community there, has his people. “Detecting security breaches, theft, the dark economy – it’s the same world,” he said. “We have an active research team staying on top of these constantly evolving threats.”</p>
  <h2 id="strength-in-numbers">Strength in Numbers</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="explore-all-that-sap-store-has-to-offer">Explore all that SAP Store has to offer</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="http://store.sap.com/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Reitblat co-founded Forter after working with a cybersecurity company that went through an acquisition – a crushing blow for him. Fortunately, he had reunited with an old high school friend from Jerusalem who also recognized that online commerce was about to take off. “In 2013, we still had to convince investors of the need for an authentication capability, and that it had to be fully automated or otherwise would require too many people to be scalable.” That resistance changed quickly, and today Forter is larger than many of its major customers, processing more than US$250 billion in transaction value per year and employing 500 professionals around the world. The solution is deployed in more than 30 countries.</p>
  <p>The <a href="http://news.sap.com/tags/covid-19">events of the past two years</a> have resulted in a burst of demand that Reitblat and his partner could not have foreseen. Besides the explosion in online shopping, purchasing behavior and customer demographics across industries changed. New retail features appeared, like curbside pickup, buy online/pick up in store (BOPIS), and contactless check-in and check-out in the hospitality industry. New online buyers included senior citizens, students, and those in advancing geographies who had never transacted online before. Additionally, with the sudden surge of orders to be delivered to alternate addresses – holiday gifts, for example, or people purchasing for family members – e-commerce systems had an extra challenge in verifying legitimacy. That process was less complex for Forter customers because its customers were already authenticated in the system.</p>
  <p>Forter Fraud Protection is tightly integrated with SAP Commerce Cloud. Laura Jorgens, director of Partnerships for Forter, acknowledged SAP partner <a href="https://netconomy.net/">Netconomy</a> for its “incredible support” in building out the integration. “Working with SAP and Netconomy feels like one ecosystem pulling together,” she said. “Hats off to the SAP partnership organization.” With the inclusion of Forter’s solution on SAP Store, she added, “SAP has become one of Forter’s most important partners.”</p>
  <p>Why not see for yourself how <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Tp3RHdk5Yic">Forter Trust Platform</a> works? The solution was just <a href="https://store.sap.com/dcp/en/news-blogs/blogs/celebrating-the-20th-year-of-sap-pinnacle-awards-and-partner-innovations-on-sap-store">named</a> an SAP Pinnacle Award finalist in the New App of the Year on SAP Store category. It’s available for download on <a href="https://store.sap.com/dcp/en/product/display-0000042467_live_v1/Forter%20Fraud%20Protection">SAP Store</a>. Or download the SAP and Forter <a href="https://l.forter.com/hubfs/forter-SAP-brochure.pdf">overview brochure</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Rajiv Nema is senior director of SAP Store Partner Solutions.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/financial-management</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/cybersecurity</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-commerce</category>
            <category>news-tag/e-commerce</category>
            <category>product/sap-commerce-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-digital-commerce</category>
            <category>sap-award/sap-pinnacle-awards</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-store</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[aconso Digital Personnel File: Automating HR Processes and Saving Forests]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/aconso-digital-personnel-file-automate-hr-save-forests</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/aconso-digital-personnel-file-automate-hr-save-forests</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Available on SAP Store, Digital Personnel File from aconso helps companies fully automate HR processes and documents management.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18fdd9d0f99016d560d122e285975d57cc0d9c212.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18fdd9d0f99016d560d122e285975d57cc0d9c212.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_18fdd9d0f99016d560d122e285975d57cc0d9c212.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="<em>aconso</em> Digital Personnel File: Automating HR Processes and Saving Forests" src="./media_18fdd9d0f99016d560d122e285975d57cc0d9c212.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="aconso-digital-personnel-file-automating-hr-processes-and-saving-forests"><em>aconso</em> Digital Personnel File: Automating HR Processes and Saving Forests</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Ulrich Jaenicke, co-founder and CEO of <em>aconso</em> AG, remembers well the meeting back in 2011 held by SAP for partners to announce the acquisition of SuccessFactors.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“It was a great moment,” he recalled, “because SuccessFactors – like us – was a cloud company. And unlike many others, we were already using web technologies. “After that, our company took off like a rocket.”</p>
  <p>Yet aconso had already made its mark in the human resources (HR) field with <a href="https://store.sap.com/en/product/display-0000015841_live_v1/Digital%20Personnel%20File">Digital Personnel File</a>, which is now available on SAP’s online marketplace, <a href="https://store.sap.com/en/">SAP Store</a>. From the beginning, he explained, aconso has been helping companies fully automate HR processes and documents management. Even as a startup, aconso established itself immediately, signing on customers like Lufthansa and a subsidiary of VW Group.</p>
  <p>All four founders hold the patent for Digital Personnel File and are now in charge of new product ideas and go-to-market strategies. They now comprise the aconso management board.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="browse-sap-store-now">Browse SAP Store now</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://store.sap.com/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="turning-the-page-on-paper-files">Turning the Page on Paper Files</h2>
  <p>Besides web technologies, the key to the product’s success was usability, taking advantage of “cover flow” – the ability to go through a file page by page electronically, in this case, on a PC. This was of course long before the era of scrolling on a smartphone. During the year or so of original product development, the team devised a way to transform pictures quickly and create a user-friendly, intuitive interface.</p>
  <p>Based in Munich, aconso has become the market leader for HR document management in Europe, now with <a href="https://store.sap.com/en/search/?sortCode=name-asc&#x26;query=:name-asc:publisher:aconso%20AG">four product offerings</a> on SAP Store. The spotlight app Digital Personnel File is a digital counterpart to the paper employee file, enabling HR staffers to retrieve electronic documents easily from the company’s SAP solutions through intelligent search and filing.</p>
  <p>Integrated with both the SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central and SAP ERP HCM solutions, the app digitizes document management, internal communication, and personnel data acquisition procedures, including scanning and logistics. The results of this end-to-end solution include big cost savings, big space savings, big time savings, faster processes – and much, much less paper. The counterpart of Digital Personnel File is the app <a href="https://store.sap.com/dcp/en/product/display-0000017444_live_v1/Document%20Creation">Document Creation</a>, enabling creation of contracts, certificates, and other HR documents.</p>
  <h2 id="helping-customers-pivot-fast-toward-more-climate-friendly-processes">Helping Customers Pivot Fast Toward More Climate-Friendly Processes</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="shop-aconsos-offerings-on-sap-store">Shop aconso's offerings on SAP Store</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://store.sap.com/en/search/?sortCode=name-asc&#x26;query=:name-asc:publisher:aconso%20AG">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>I asked Jaenicke how the company has fared during the challenges posed by the past year. “At first we were nervous about what would happen. But we are lucky guys, with most of our employees already working in home offices. Many of our customers had to make major adjustments to mobile working models. And one thing they learned very fast: you can’t handle paper.”</p>
  <p>Consequently, business has been booming for aconso as customers digitize HR processes, which, he remarked, “is one small step in saving our forests and reducing carbon footprint.”</p>
  <p>Next on the agenda for aconso is growing its presence in North America, where implementations already in place include Accenture, based in Chicago, and Bilfinger, based in Texas.</p>
  <p>The SAP Store team is providing excellent support in that regard, reported Silvia Bayerl, who is responsible for aconso’s partnership with SAP and works closely with SAP partner managers.</p>
  <p>“We are hopeful about going further transatlantic with SAP,” she remarked. “And we are exploring opportunities with hyperscalers that will enable us to meet special requirements in India and China for data storage within the country.”</p>
  <p>When it comes to saving forests, SAP is planting a tree for every purchase made on SAP Store, and we’re glad to do that on your behalf! Why not check out the spotlight app <a href="https://store.sap.com/en/product/display-0000015841_live_v1/Digital%20Personnel%20File">Digital Personnel File</a> now, and try it free?</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Anne Yi is general manager of SAP Store Partner Solutions at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-digital-commerce</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-store</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>