<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/core-topic/sustainable-business-operations/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Turning Agricultural Waste into Buildings]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/turning-agricultural-waste-into-buildings</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/turning-agricultural-waste-into-buildings</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Find out how a sustainable construction-material entrepreneur brought her idea to life by engaging local communities.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11ff1654bf1679391f4ffabdc421a48dedfe40db0.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11ff1654bf1679391f4ffabdc421a48dedfe40db0.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_11ff1654bf1679391f4ffabdc421a48dedfe40db0.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Workers bent over in a large agricultural field in southern India." src="./media_11ff1654bf1679391f4ffabdc421a48dedfe40db0.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1044">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="turning-agricultural-waste-into-buildings">Turning Agricultural Waste into Buildings</h1>
        <p>A sustainable construction-material entrepreneur brought her idea to life by engaging local communities.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>By Lauren Gibbons Paul</p>
  <p>Sometimes, just having a question is enough. That’s how Shriti Pandey, founder and CEO of Strawcture Eco, started a sustainable construction-materials company – despite having virtually no work experience.</p>
  <p>Back home for a 2016 fellowship in India after graduate school in New York, Pandey saw local farmers burning “stubble,” the waste that results from the unusable portion – often 50% of the total weight – of agricultural crops. Farmers burn that byproduct because they can’t make any money from it. Pandey’s business started with a question: What if we could turn that stubble into a material for sustainable construction?</p>
  <p>She had no experience in construction – or any kind of industry – only a degree in civil engineering. And she was a young woman entering an industry largely made up of older men. Pandey did have one advantage: She knew how to approach people and get their input and support for new ideas. This skill became very important when her small team had to engage with farmers to buy waste products from their crops. Barreling in from the outside and demanding a community do things differently, especially given language and cultural barriers, is a formula for failure, she says. Engaging in a meaningful, two-way interchange is the only way to do this work.</p>
  <p>This approach led to Strawcture Eco’s first product, a panel for building as sturdy as steel or concrete, but more affordable and sustainable – as well as some unexpected adventures, like managing the construction of a 75-bed rural COVID-19 hospital in just 45 days.</p>
  <p>The film <em>She Run the World</em> is part of SAP’s Roads to Regeneration series, produced in partnership with Hot Docs. SAP Insights spoke to Pandey about how community engagement has informed her business and career.</p>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b5d305a32c7b85791487ed0e662700a9f598ff71.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b5d305a32c7b85791487ed0e662700a9f598ff71.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1b5d305a32c7b85791487ed0e662700a9f598ff71.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="One of eight documentaries created by Hot Docs and produced by SAP. Part of the Roads to Regeneration compilation." src="./media_1b5d305a32c7b85791487ed0e662700a9f598ff71.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="319" height="179">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://d.dam.sap.com/m/aawW7zb/hls.m3u8">Roads to Regeneration - She Run The World</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>en-US</div>
      <div>English</div>
      <div><a href="https://d.dam.sap.com/o/s7Mct1x/SAP922411-en%5C%5C_us-English?rc=19">https://d.dam.sap.com/o/s7Mct1x/SAP922411-en\\_us-English?rc=19</a></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="sap-insights-what-was-your-core-idea-behind-strawcture-eco">SAP Insights: What was your core idea behind Strawcture Eco?</h2>
  <p><strong>Shriti Pandey:</strong> There's so much agricultural surplus residue – the byproduct of crop harvesting – especially in an agrarian country like India. While we're talking so much about climate change and resource waste, it seemed to me there were genuine renewable raw materials available that no one was using. We are literally burning waste, cutting trees, and then making materials in the factory that require so much fossil fuel. So the core question was, can this waste be converted into valuable products that reduce our reliance on fossil-based energy? That’s what I was obsessed about.</p>
  <h2 id="q-did-you-encounter-barriers-when-you-were-trying-to-break-into-the-construction-space-especially-as-a-young-woman">Q: Did you encounter barriers when you were trying to break into the construction space, especially as a young woman?</h2>
  <p>Pandey: I started Strawcture in 2018. I was 26. I had one year of experience working in New York, no prior work experience in India at all. So the idea was quite daunting to me. And I had no buddies to start the project with. It was not just about being young, but also because I was a solo founder.</p>
  <p>Until I started Strawcture, I thought there was no difference in the opportunities men and women get. I grew up as one of a set of triplets in a small town in India. I had the privilege of an upbringing where my parents were very capable of providing an education for my sister, brother, and me. They never told us what to do, which people think happens a lot in smaller towns and villages in India. I had complete freedom, which is why I thought I could even do this without questioning.</p>
  <p>It was only when I started my company that I realized that the world is not free of discrimination. I got exposed to a very male-dominated industry. Very early on after starting Strawcture, there was this government conference around green materials. As I stepped into that room, I vividly remember that it only had men in it, mostly in their 40s or older. And they all just looked at me, clearly thinking, “Who is she?” I felt for a second that I was in the wrong room. So I left. I asked somebody outside, “Is this the right room?” They said yes. So I went back in, and I didn’t know where to sit or who to talk to.</p>
  <p>It took me a while to get used to it. Before you can get other people to accept you, you also have to accept that you belong. So for me, that was the first step of the journey. Once I felt more confident, I started networking. Now, once they see me on stage as a speaker, there's a level of credibility, of substance. So people are more willing to approach me.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1071e3d8dcc85b3d1d0aabc48f450d2cb12891b35.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1071e3d8dcc85b3d1d0aabc48f450d2cb12891b35.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1071e3d8dcc85b3d1d0aabc48f450d2cb12891b35.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="In this school auditorium in Delhi, the walls, ceiling and stage flooring are made from recycled agricultural waste. Photo courtesy of Shriti Pandey." src="./media_1071e3d8dcc85b3d1d0aabc48f450d2cb12891b35.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="2160">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="q-its-only-five-years-later-but-these-days-are-you-seeing-more-participation-in-the-construction-industry-by-young-or-older-women">Q: It’s only five years later, but these days, are you seeing more participation in the construction industry by young or older women?</h2>
  <p><strong>Pandey:</strong> Yes, definitely. I see more women in these spaces as different stakeholders now, even a lot of women investors who are in the climate tech space.</p>
  <h2 id="q-what-happened-to-your-business-and-your-research-during-the-pandemic-shutdowns">Q: What happened to your business and your research during the pandemic shutdowns?</h2>
  <p><strong>Pandey:</strong> The lockdown happened in India in March 2020, and I had traveled from Delhi to my village for my mother's birthday. I ended up being there for a year. Our line of business is very tactile, very physical. If you don't meet people, they won’t understand, no one will buy. So everything came to a halt for three months.</p>
  <p>Then someone from the SELCO Foundation NGO approached us to build some COVID-19 hospitals. At that point, they could take the risk and let a new technology be tested in that scenario. So, we grabbed that opportunity. There were a lot of companies building COVID hospitals. We ended up building ours the fastest. We built a 75-bed, full COVID [treatment] hospital with 12 doctors in 45 days. The community immediately showed up needing medical services, which they previously had gone without.</p>
  <p>We built three more hospitals made from waste after that – our materials went to the walls and the ceilings. We also made all the furniture. The only thing we didn’t make other than medical equipment was the flooring. But we did everything else. And our materials were also used on the external facades of the building.</p>
  <h2 id="q-where-did-the-hospital-designs-and-plans-come-from-and-what-did-the-process-look-like">Q: Where did the hospital designs and plans come from? And what did the process look like?</h2>
  <p><strong>Pandey:</strong> The NGO gave us the plans and the patch of land in Masaurhi Block, Patna. They wanted to build where governmental services like healthcare and infrastructure were not present. So, this was not in the middle of the city, which made it more challenging. Being a civil engineer became helpful. We made all the structural drawings. We did everything – the plumbing, civil, electrical, which was not even our forte.</p>
  <p>Travel was a challenge. The police commissioner would only give our team permission to move outside of the village when the work was done, so we ended up living on-site for 45 days. I actually ended up living in the hospital itself as it was being built. I’ll never forget that.</p>
  <p>Because everything was locked down, we couldn’t bring in contractors or construction workers. I really learned about getting the community involved in these things. We went into the villages and announced, we've been told to make this hospital for your community. Help us find workers. The next day, almost half of the village showed up, like 100 people. Someone said I'm a carpenter, I'm an electrician, I'm a plumber. Everybody in the village ended up working on that project under our direction. This is during the month of June in India, which is like 48 degrees Celsius (118 degrees Fahrenheit).</p>
  <h2 id="q-you-were-under-30-years-old-at-that-time-and-you-built-a-hospital">Q: You were under 30 years old at that time, and you built a hospital!</h2>
  <p><strong>Pandey:</strong> I was 28. If it wasn’t during COVID-19, they wouldn’t have let me do it.</p>
  <h2 id="q-where-are-your-research-and-development-efforts-focused-these-days">Q: Where are your research and development efforts focused these days?</h2>
  <p><strong>Pandey:</strong> We are working a lot with biomimicry, a relatively new field where architects and product designers look to nature before they go into the lab. For example, how a bee would make its honeycomb. Those are some of the most geometrically stable structures. You can learn a lot from them to apply to making houses that are very earthquake-resistant.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_13ee708d2c78caf083b2fccdc9c3cff9914dfab25.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_13ee708d2c78caf083b2fccdc9c3cff9914dfab25.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_13ee708d2c78caf083b2fccdc9c3cff9914dfab25.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="A farmer works in a paddy field near Mysore in southern India. Photo courtesy of Shriti Pandey." src="./media_13ee708d2c78caf083b2fccdc9c3cff9914dfab25.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="2160">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p>That led to us creating these frame systems that are honeycomb in shape. There’s so much inspiration in nature, in terms of physics, science, and biology.</p>
  <p>We also launched a felt product that can be used for sound and thermal insulation. We were doing a project in Rajasthan, which is one of the hottest desert regions in the world, and the community asked, why do you use so much of the traditional glass wool insulation? Why not use animal-residue material like wool? Nothing is more insulating. That led us to look at the value chain of wool that is not sold for textile use and to a number of pastoralists in India who do sheep shearing, and then to us making 100% biodegradable felt.</p>
  <p>If we were not engaged with the community, we wouldn’t know how to even collect it.</p>
  <h2 id="q-in-the-film-you-talked-about-how-in-small-villages-nothing-goes-to-waste-what-did-you-learn-from-them">Q: In the film, you talked about how in small villages nothing goes to waste. What did you learn from them?</h2>
  <p><strong>Pandey:</strong> When I lived in a village for a year with a family that was living in a very low-cost, makeshift house, I witnessed that, whether it is their structures, the way they cook, the way they engage with each other in the community – they will not let anything go to waste. It's the perspective that when you don't have a lot, there's just no room to waste.</p>
  <p>And that made me realize that waste is only a waste if you waste it. It's a choice. We can look at it differently. Everything that's coming out of a factory, every construction site, demolition, and everything in our houses that we don't need any more is a possible resource for some added-value product. It’s a mind shift.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <h4 id="read-more-in-this-series">Read more in this series</h4>
  <div class="collection">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h6 id="editorial">Editorial</h6>
        <p><a href="/blogs/300-days-of-sun">300 Days of Sun: Communities Power Their Own Future</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>
        <h6 id="editorial-1">Editorial</h6>
        <p><a href="/blogs/a-case-for-carbon-accountability">A Case for Carbon Accountability</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>
        <h6 id="editorial-2">Editorial</h6>
        <p><a href="/blogs/restoring-peatlands">Restoring Peatlands, Nature’s Carbon Sponges</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>
        <h6 id="editorial-3">Editorial</h6>
        <p><a href="/blogs/road-to-regeneration-waste-to-life">Road to Regeneration: Waste to Life</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>
        <h6 id="editorial-4">Editorial</h6>
        <p><a href="/blogs/road-to-regeneration-beautiful-poison">Turning Toxic Coal Mine Waste into the Stuff of Art</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div><a href="/videos/roads-to-regeneration-series">Roads to Regeneration collection</a></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>sidebar</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>core-topic/sustainable-business-operations</category>
            <category>content-type/expert-opinions</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bridging the Sustainability Capability Gap]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/ext-bridging-the-sustainability-capability-gap</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/ext-bridging-the-sustainability-capability-gap</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn how businesses and government can come together to make more meaningful advances in sustainability.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>core-topic/sustainable-business-operations</category>
            <category>content-type/expert-opinions</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Accelerating the Transition to Clean Energy]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/ext-accelerating-the-transition-to-clean-energy</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/ext-accelerating-the-transition-to-clean-energy</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn what’s driving the transition to renewable energy across the globe and the necessary policy measures and tools used to get to net zero.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_136878ce38bf5d9b8daae1e4695b7b4adfa14c4cd.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_136878ce38bf5d9b8daae1e4695b7b4adfa14c4cd.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_136878ce38bf5d9b8daae1e4695b7b4adfa14c4cd.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="A row of wind turbines against a dark sky." src="./media_136878ce38bf5d9b8daae1e4695b7b4adfa14c4cd.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1044">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="accelerating-the-transition-to-clean-energy">Accelerating the Transition to Clean Energy</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>We are in the midst of a global energy crisis. But in our frantic efforts to fix the situation in the short term with fossil fuels, we can’t lose track of the long-term solution: a full energy transition in line with the United Nations sustainable development goals (Goal 7: <a href="https://unric.org/en/sdg-7/">Affordable and Clean Energy</a>).</p>
  <p>In fact, the current energy crisis might help accelerate the drastic changes needed to make the transition to clean energy. In this article, we’ll examine <strong>necessary policy measures</strong>, the available <strong>pathways to fully renewable energy systems</strong>, a <strong>possible road map to net zero</strong>, and the <strong>progress the global community has made so far</strong>.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14b20ac958df4ef29545f5c5468e7da0f4f7f5115.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14b20ac958df4ef29545f5c5468e7da0f4f7f5115.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_14b20ac958df4ef29545f5c5468e7da0f4f7f5115.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Image card for Envision Beyond chapter" src="./media_14b20ac958df4ef29545f5c5468e7da0f4f7f5115.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="2160">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="necessary-policy-measures">Necessary policy measures</h2>
  <p>The International Energy Agency (<a href="https://www.iea.org/about">IEA</a>) argues in its <em><a href="https://iea.blob.core.windows.net/assets/c282400e-00b0-4edf-9a8e-6f2ca6536ec8/WorldEnergyOutlook2022.pdf">World Energy Outlook 2022</a></em> that “faster clean energy transitions would have helped to moderate the impact of the crisis, and they represent the best way out of it.”</p>
  <p>This is an important point for framing any discussion about potential economic barriers to wide-scale implementation of renewable energies.</p>
  <p>The IEA report underscores that the current energy crisis promises to be a <strong>turning point for the transition to renewables</strong> based on <strong>stated policies</strong> and <strong>increased investment</strong> into clean energy by governments worldwide. Apart from the clear advantages for the environment and energy security, the economic case for the energy transition is getting stronger. According to the IEA, higher shares of renewable energy correlate with lower energy electricity prices.</p>
  <p>IEA’s Stated Policies Scenario (STEPS) predicts government investments in renewables will grow to more than $2 trillion by 2030, approximately 50% higher than today, according to the report. This scenario also foresees a peak or plateau for global fossil fuel demand within the next few years, which would be a singular turning point.</p>
  <p>The current energy crisis might help accelerate the drastic changes needed to make the transition to clean energy.</p>
  <h2 id="pathways-to-fully-renewable-energy-systems">Pathways to fully renewable energy systems</h2>
  <p>A combination of solar, wind, and limited nuclear power will be the primary drivers of the renewable energy transition.</p>
  <p>However, solar and wind energy fluctuate and are not universally available. Energy storage technologies like power-to-X (P2X) are a central component of fully renewable energy systems. P2X enables the production of various fuels, like green hydrogen, which can be transported to locations where renewable energy sources aren’t readily available. With this option for long-term storage and flexibility, strengthening the networking of electricity, heat, and mobility sectors is also possible.</p>
  <h2 id="the-p2x-principle">The P2X Principle</h2>
  <p>Power based on renewable energy (<strong>P</strong>) is converted into (<strong>2</strong>) another energy carrier (<strong>X</strong>) for long-term storage, such as power-to-gas (P2G).</p>
  <p>An <a href="https://hydrogencouncil.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/Hydrogen-Insights-2022-2.pdf">analysis</a> by McKinsey and Company and the Hydrogen Council notes that the race for green hydrogen has begun, even though production still needs to grow and supply chains have yet to be established. The report counts 680 large-scale project proposals worth a combined $240 billion, 10% of which have received a final investment decision.</p>
  <h2 id="a-road-map-to-net-zero">A road map to net zero</h2>
  <p>There is still a long way to go to reach our net-zero ambitions, as a closer look at the <a href="https://app.electricitymaps.com/map">Electricity Maps app</a> reveals.</p>
  <p>It’s all the more refreshing and inspiring, then, to read a recent <a href="https://ieeexplore.ieee.org/stamp/stamp.jsp?tp=&#x26;arnumber=9837910">study</a> from nearly 20 researchers and scientists around the world who developed a possible road map to net zero emissions by 2050.</p>
  <p>The route they outline goes far beyond the existing energy scenarios of the Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change reports. The interdisciplinary research team takes into consideration opportunities and challenges connected to grid congestion, energy storage, sector coupling, electrification of transport and industry by using P2X, and approaches to removing carbon dioxide from the atmosphere. Their conclusion is that a global 100% renewable energy system by 2050 is technically feasible <strong><em>and</em></strong> economically possible.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_188766238ed28aceda92d17ce991656f2f0b3a586.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_188766238ed28aceda92d17ce991656f2f0b3a586.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_188766238ed28aceda92d17ce991656f2f0b3a586.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Row of wind turbines bathed in sunlight." src="./media_188766238ed28aceda92d17ce991656f2f0b3a586.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="2160">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="progress-on-the-energy-transition">Progress on the energy transition</h2>
  <p>How far have we come on this journey?</p>
  <p>Renewable energies accounted for more than 80% of all new electricity capacity added in 2020, according to <a href="https://iea.blob.core.windows.net/assets/8b276fc2-c1ae-4a54-9681-eea1eb143d7f/TrackingSDG7TheEnergyProgressReport2022.pdf">Tracking SDG7: The Energy Progress Report 2022</a>. The report also states that IEA and International Renewable Energy Agency (IRENA) scenarios show that solar photovoltaic (PV) and wind will contribute the most growth in electricity production by 2030.</p>
  <p>To show the opportunities of the transition pathway for renewables, let’s look at the European energy market. According to a <a href="https://ember-climate.org/app/uploads/2022/10/E3G-EMBER-Briefing-More-renewables-less-inflation.pdf">status quo report</a> of energy think tanks E3G and Ember, wind and solar power accounted for 24% of the European Union’s energy mix from March through September 2022. Their contribution mitigated the effects of energy supply issues caused by unavailability of nuclear capacity and reduction in hydroelectricity generation during a period of drought. The year-on-year increase of 39 TWh, or 13%, comes at a time when the EU is <a href="https://www.consilium.europa.eu/en/press/press-releases/2022/10/04/repowereu-council-agrees-its-position/">stepping up its measures</a> to implement <a href="https://www.europarl.europa.eu/legislative-train/theme-industry-research-and-energy-itre/file-repower-eu-plan-legislative-proposals">the REPower EU proposal</a> to reduce its dependency on Russian gas.</p>
  <p>Aled Jones, director of the Global Sustainability Institute at Anglia Ruskin University, confirms that the tipping point for the shift to solar and wind as dominant technologies has already been reached in Europe. While the energy transition will cause job losses for roughly 3 million people, more than 12 million new jobs will be created as a result of this change <a href="https://www.weforum.org/agenda/2022/10/green-transition-decarbonization-myths-debunked/">by 2030</a>. This is an immense opportunity.</p>
  <h2 id="innovation-drivers">Innovation drivers</h2>
  <p>Business leaders should focus on the following three innovation areas to significantly accelerate the energy transition.</p>
  <h3 id="business-networks">1. Business networks</h3>
  <p>By leveraging business networks, key players and organizations can make full use of existing infrastructure and the latest technology innovations to accelerate their energy transition efforts.</p>
  <p><strong>Use case: CEO Alliance</strong></p>
  <p>Green hydrogen can play a significant role in creating a carbon-neutral future for energy-intensive industries such as building materials, chemicals, glass, nonferrous metals, paper, and steel. Leveraging business networks and organizations can help create an industrial-scale green hydrogen value chain. One example for cross-industry collaboration in this matter is the <a href="https://www.ceo-alliance.eu/about-the-alliance/">CEO Alliance</a>, an action tank of 14 top European companies. This industry business network aims to build up renewable energy production in Southern Europe to supply green hydrogen and ammonia to industrial hubs in Central and Northern Europe.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11df0c7360cc46dd7dc658153f285ebd57c0285ff.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11df0c7360cc46dd7dc658153f285ebd57c0285ff.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_11df0c7360cc46dd7dc658153f285ebd57c0285ff.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Close-up of blue molecules." src="./media_11df0c7360cc46dd7dc658153f285ebd57c0285ff.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="2160">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h3 id="decentralized-energy-systems">2. Decentralized energy systems</h3>
  <p>Future energy systems will be increasingly decentralized. Today's consumers are future producers, <a href="/resources/distributed-energy-resources-der-and-the-rise-of-the-prosumer">so-called prosumers</a>, who own rooftop solar panels, battery storage, and electric vehicle chargers. The goal is to make the interaction between energy supplier, grid, and prosumer seamless.</p>
  <p><strong>Use case: Integrating prosumers into the grid</strong></p>
  <p>Solar energy is an essential part of the energy transition. Integrating prosumers into the grid will make it possible to sell surplus solar energy to any local consumer, helping to decrease regional dependence on imported energy carriers. To do this, all stakeholders require digital systems and technologies that help collect data from sensors, analyze consumption profiles, and predict, simulate, and balance energy grids. Utility providers profit by integrating prosumers into the grid, because they can offer their smart metering hardware to new customers. An example for a community-centric software approach is <a href="https://www.exnaton.com/">Exnaton</a>’s energy community solution, which enables utility companies to track all relevant energy data and easily bill these energy exchanges.</p>
  <h3 id="digitalization">3. Digitalization</h3>
  <p>Digitalization is central to creating future intelligent and resilient energy systems. The energy transition will go hand in hand with digital transformation. In the future, energy service providers and information and communications technology companies will offer a range of services that go well beyond generating, transmitting, and distributing energy. We’ll see new business models, like energy as a service. IRENA identifies these additional services offerings in its <a href="https://www.irena.org/-/media/Files/IRENA/Agency/Publication/2020/Jul/IRENA_Energy-as-a-Service_2020.pdf">2020 innovation landscape brief</a> as energy advice, energy assets, and energy management.</p>
  <p><strong>Use case: Large real estate and infrastructure owners</strong></p>
  <p>Energy management affects more than utility providers, including large real estate and infrastructure like hotels, retail stores, and warehouses; airports; and train stations. Digitalization can help those stakeholders address challenges with energy efficiency and financial resilience. To better assess financial risks in real time, real estate and infrastructure owners must be able to forecast energy demand and simulate results from fluctuating energy prices. Future digital products and services will support these stakeholders’ net-zero goals by tracking energy assets and their overall energy mix. In addition, they can manage their green purchase agreements and calculate greenhouse gas emissions.</p>
  <p>From the tenant’s point of view, automated billing based on real consumption can provide an incentive to reduce energy use.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1be4eb268c135ce2c007666c3faefdf0e3f4343a9.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1be4eb268c135ce2c007666c3faefdf0e3f4343a9.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1be4eb268c135ce2c007666c3faefdf0e3f4343a9.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Row of blue solar panels in a line facing the sun." src="./media_1be4eb268c135ce2c007666c3faefdf0e3f4343a9.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="2160">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p>These are just some approaches to clean energy. There are many that will help us get to net zero. All will require political interventions by international organizations, technological innovation, regional initiatives, action from public and private companies, and a full commitment from each one of us.</p>
  <p>Business leaders must pursue innovative solutions to accelerate the transition to net zero. The need to use business networks and understand how decentralized energy systems and digitalization might be vital for resilient and sustainable intelligent enterprises.</p>
  <p>Regardless of which routes we might take, they will only be viable if we pursue them together – and if we act now. Especially when faced with current energy crises, there is no time to waste in our collective efforts to speed up the transition to renewable energy systems.</p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><strong>Snapshots</strong></p>
  <ul>
    <li>The Green Hydrogen <a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2023/10/f8639744-947e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Panel</a> features Klaus Schimmer, chief innovation architect of sustainability for SAP, in conversation with leaders from Fortescue Future Industries, E.ON, BMW, and BCG on making the transition to green hydrogen.</li>
    <li>Grace Galdos Arenas, global lead for the sustainability lab for SAP <a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2023/09/3e242cd4-917e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">interview</a>s Carsten Borchers, VP of global green gas projects for E.ON, about how business networks can help accelerate the transition to green energy.</li>
    <li>This episode of <em><a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2023/10/5854edd7-917e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Envision Beyond in 60 Seconds</a></em>, “Leading the Way for Clean Energy,” shares new insights on how to best use business networks to solidify sustainability efforts.</li>
  </ul>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div data-valign="middle">style</div>
      <div data-valign="middle">additional reading</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <h4 id="read-more-in-this-series">Read more in this series</h4>
  <div class="collection">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h6 id="editorial">Editorial</h6>
        <p><a href="/blogs/ext-envision-beyond-by-the-intelligent-enterprise-institute">Envision Beyond Curated Collection</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>
        <h6 id="editorial-1">Editorial</h6>
        <p><a href="/blogs/ext-accelerating-the-transition-to-clean-energy">Accelerating the Transition to Clean Energy</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>
        <h6 id="editorial-2">Editorial</h6>
        <p><a href="/blogs/ext-business-networks-the-only-path-forward">Business Networks: The Only Path Forward is Together</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>
        <h6 id="editorial-3">Editorial</h6>
        <p><a href="/blogs/ext-the-metaverse-a-new-space-for-business">The Metaverse: A New Space for Business</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>
        <h6 id="editorial-4">Editorial</h6>
        <p><a href="/blogs/ext-trust-in-an-age-of-mistrust">Trust in an Age of Mistrust</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>
        <h6 id="editorial-5">Editorial</h6>
        <p><a href="/blogs/ext-keys-to-ignite-the-generative-business-revolution">Keys to Ignite the Generative Business Revolution</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>
        <h6 id="editorial-6">Editorial</h6>
        <p><a href="/blogs/ext-generative-ai-for-business-process-excellence">Generative AI for the Renaissance of Business Process Excellence</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>sidebar</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>core-topic/sustainable-business-operations</category>
            <category>content-type/expert-opinions</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Currency of Customer Trust in Retail]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/the-currency-of-customer-trust-in-retail</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/the-currency-of-customer-trust-in-retail</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Building trustworthy customer experiences means sharing information and devoting resources to enhancing consumers’ trust.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>core-topic/sustainable-business-operations</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
            <category>content-type/business-case</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Business Value of Sustainability Is Here]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/the-business-value-of-sustainability-is-here</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/the-business-value-of-sustainability-is-here</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn why sustainable business practices are investments that pay, like R&D and customer relationships, from author Andrew Winston.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>core-topic/sustainable-business-operations</category>
            <category>content-type/business-case</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[300 Days of Sun: Communities Power Their Own Future]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/300-days-of-sun</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/300-days-of-sun</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Lebanon faces daunting economic and energy problems. A new documentary explores how citizens are looking to the sun for solutions.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>core-topic/sustainable-business-operations</category>
            <category>industry/oil-gas-energy</category>
            <category>industry/utilities</category>
            <category>content-type/expert-opinions</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Restoring Peatlands, Nature’s Carbon Sponges]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/restoring-peatlands</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/restoring-peatlands</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn from SAP about Germany’s efforts to reclaim critical wetlands that absorb carbon and protect habitats.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>core-topic/sustainable-business-operations</category>
            <category>content-type/expert-opinions</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Road to Regeneration: Turning Toxic Mine Waste into Art]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/road-to-regeneration-beautiful-poison</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/road-to-regeneration-beautiful-poison</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn how artists, citizens, business, and government are collaborating to restore waterways in Ohio in this Q&A from SAP Insights.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>core-topic/sustainable-business-operations</category>
            <category>industry/oil-gas-energy</category>
            <category>industry/chemicals</category>
            <category>content-type/expert-opinions</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Road to Regeneration: Waste to Life]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/road-to-regeneration-waste-to-life</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/road-to-regeneration-waste-to-life</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn how Rita Idehai helps Nigerian communities turn plastic waste into products, jobs, and revenue in this Q&A.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>core-topic/sustainable-business-operations</category>
            <category>industry/oil-gas-energy</category>
            <category>industry/chemicals</category>
            <category>content-type/expert-opinions</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Who's in Your Sustainability Department?]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/whos-in-your-sustainability-department</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/whos-in-your-sustainability-department</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Sustainability programs need effort from the whole company. Staffing your department right is a key step to achieving that company-wide support.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>core-topic/sustainable-business-operations</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>content-type/business-case</category>
            <category>stage/acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Future of Sustainable Operations]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/future-of-sustainable-operations</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/future-of-sustainable-operations</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[What if being sustainable didn’t require special effort? Here are some ways to make sustainability a no-brainer part of your operations.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10aabe055e588770b4ab0395597045b7b07bedf80.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10aabe055e588770b4ab0395597045b7b07bedf80.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_10aabe055e588770b4ab0395597045b7b07bedf80.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Farmer using tablet" src="./media_10aabe055e588770b4ab0395597045b7b07bedf80.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1044">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="the-future-of-sustainable-operations">The Future of Sustainable Operations</h1>
        <p>What if sustainability didn’t require special effort? Get ready to roll up your sleeves because we gathered some ways to make green part of your day-to-day operations.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Sustainability stops becoming an extra effort, an add-on, when you design it into your business processes. And sustainability doesn’t always have to be the only goal in mind – sometimes you can create sustainable processes just by doing them better. Three overall trends define the future of sustainable operations:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Digital doppelgängers to the rescue.</strong> Data is the invisible partner that every physical process needs. It improves performance through better analysis, of course, but it also doesn’t cost much or take up much room. That makes it greener, too.</li>
    <li><strong>The exponential bandwagon gets some new players.</strong> Moore’s Law isn’t just for PCs anymore. There are other technologies surfing Gordo’s wave of exponential increases in performance and decreases in cost that boost operations and greenness.</li>
    <li><strong>There’s a new way to make stuff in town.</strong> The essential components in the manufacturing process are getting a makeover. The bill of materials is expanding to improve performance and sustainability.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>You can learn more about how to make operations better (and greener) in the SAP Insights articles linked below.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="the-future-of-business-sustainability">The Future of Business Sustainability</h3>
        <p>How businesses are considering their impact on the planet at a strategic level.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="/resources/profitable-purpose-the-future-of-business-sustainability">Learn more</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_12abf6bc13bbdef3472473349755c641d3b190c06.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_12abf6bc13bbdef3472473349755c641d3b190c06.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_12abf6bc13bbdef3472473349755c641d3b190c06.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Solar panels" src="./media_12abf6bc13bbdef3472473349755c641d3b190c06.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="the-ghost-of-sustainable-business-operations">The ghost of sustainable business operations</h2>
  <p><strong>The emergence of digital twins.</strong> Digital twins – virtual replicas of physical objects – are helping operational leaders track and improve performance. Digital twins can identify ways to improve how a factory process works or when it’s time to fix a machine before it breaks down. Digitally enabling supply chains has the potential to create more efficient, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/integrated-business-planning/what-is-a-resilient-supply-chain.html">resilient</a>, and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/what-is-a-sustainable-supply-chain.html">sustainable</a> global trade. A digital twin could spot and solve many what-if scenarios to enable better decision-making for highly complex supply chains – if business partners are willing to share intelligence and data.</p>
  <p>Learn more in “<a href="/resources/how-digital-twins-are-driving-the-future-of-business">How Digital Twins Are Driving the Future of Business</a>.”</p>
  <p><strong>Charge it, then recharge it.</strong> Renewable energy is becoming competitive. To make it transformative, we also need to reinvent a technology that most of us take for granted: the battery. Scientists, industry players, and venture capitalists are approaching battery power with solutions ranging from carbon nanotubes to electric charges harnessed from compost piles. Still, many challenges remain in the quest to produce the cheap, renewable, zero-carbon batteries that the world craves.</p>
  <p>See what’s on tap at “<a href="/blogs/future-batteries-save-civilization">How Future Batteries Could Save Civilization</a>.”</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_170351e70eb3e63143ae596053999b5d533adc9d3.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_170351e70eb3e63143ae596053999b5d533adc9d3.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_170351e70eb3e63143ae596053999b5d533adc9d3.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Wind turbines" src="./media_170351e70eb3e63143ae596053999b5d533adc9d3.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="surf-turf-and-shimmer-the-new-ingredients-in-sustainable-production-processes">Surf, turf, and shimmer: The new ingredients in sustainable production processes</h2>
  <p><strong>Alternatives to conventional materials offer promise.</strong> Researchers and innovative companies are rethinking the materials that businesses use throughout their operations. Take plastics, for example. Promising experiments in developing durable but biodegradable alternatives to petroleum-based plastics involve citrus peels, lobster shells, and soybean oil by-products. Other projects are creating alternative materials that offer superior performance while avoiding harmful environmental side effects. Some experimental materials even help regenerate natural ecosystems.</p>
  <p>Check out “<a href="https://www.sap.com/insights/viewpoints/the-road-to-regeneration.html">The Road to Regeneration</a>" for a quick rundown of emerging plastic alternatives, textiles, construction materials, and other substances that meet industry needs while helping sustain the environment.</p>
  <p><strong>Advanced technologies are giving fashion a new look.</strong> The fashion industry has a sustainability problem. It’s on pace to generate 17.5 kilograms of waste for every citizen on Earth by 2030. Technology advances in everything, including sensors and fabrics, give the industry an opportunity to make a two-step change: less waste and more function. Among the innovations are clothes that will help us improve our performance and prevent injury on the job and those that change their appearance and function according to our requirements and desires.</p>
  <p>Check out what’s on the fashion tech runway at “<a href="/blogs/fashion-the-future-interface-between-mind-body-and-planet">Fashion: The Future Interface Between Mind, Body, and Planet</a>.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="the-circular-economy-goes-mainstream">The Circular Economy Goes Mainstream</h3>
        <p>How enterprises are taking sustainability to its ultimate goal: zero waste.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="/resources/the-circular-economy-goes-mainstream">Read it</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17a27c6517eb2e79db7a1efde7d7640039013e3d1.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17a27c6517eb2e79db7a1efde7d7640039013e3d1.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_17a27c6517eb2e79db7a1efde7d7640039013e3d1.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Woman holding child in garden" src="./media_17a27c6517eb2e79db7a1efde7d7640039013e3d1.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="reaping-the-harvest-of-more-sustainable-management">Reaping the harvest of more sustainable management</h2>
  <p><strong>Tech to preserve the natural world.</strong> Climate change, and the pollution and industrial expansion that exacerbate its risks, are leading to habitat loss and species extinction for the plants, animals, and other life forms that make Earth livable. Researchers are responding to the challenge with technologies designed to stem and reverse the damage, including satellite data that analyzes planetary health and sustainability and the planting of fast-growing trees that can remove high levels of metal from contaminated sewage.</p>
  <p>Read more in “<a href="/blogs/technology-for-biology-preserving-biodiversity">Technology for Biology: Preserving Biodiversity</a>.”</p>
  <p><strong>Table stakes.</strong> None of the world’s challenges exist in isolation, but the need to put food on the table – indeed, to feed the hungry – is unique in its impact on the entire global economy. By applying technology innovations, we could shrink the environmental burden of farming, improve crop diversity so that diets are more nutritious and agriculture is more sustainable, help farmers produce more food while increasing their profits, and make food distribution safer and more efficient. If you consider that the globe’s population continues to rise, it’s a big deal.</p>
  <p>Explore more in “<a href="/blogs/the-future-of-feeding-the-world">The Future of Feeding the World</a>.”</p>
  <p><strong>Calling out carbon.</strong> Researchers are finding intriguing ways to address elements of the climate crisis caused by carbon emissions – and providing signals of where future solutions may lie. Think: Fabric that collects solar energy so that your shirt can charge your phone. Generators that turn one drop of rainwater into energy that lights up 100 small LED bulbs. Electricity generated by the friction of elevator brakes. Using AI to spot model supply chains and find ways to cut carbon emissions.</p>
  <p>Read “<a href="/blogs/by-land-sea-and-air-emerging-technologies-to-tackle-climate-change">Emerging Technologies to Tackle Climate Change – By Land, Sea, and Air</a>" for a summary of the innovative approaches being used to pinpoint sources of excessive carbon emissions and mitigate them.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>core-topic/sustainable-business-operations</category>
            <category>content-type/trends-predictions</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Powering Up Your Business Processes]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/research/sustainability-a-business-process-power-up</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/research/sustainability-a-business-process-power-up</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Senior executives are linking sustainable business processes with revenue growth, improved efficiency, and lower risk. Read our findings]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1452f4e35e5e3f05d74e850e936410350499c00df.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1452f4e35e5e3f05d74e850e936410350499c00df.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1452f4e35e5e3f05d74e850e936410350499c00df.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Woman on escalator in the woods" src="./media_1452f4e35e5e3f05d74e850e936410350499c00df.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1044">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="powering-up-your-business-processes">Powering Up Your Business Processes</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>When we asked more than 11,000 senior executives from around the world about their priorities for revenue growth, operational efficiency, and risk management, they said they see a direct link between innovation and increasing revenues.</p>
  <p>They are exploiting that link by investing in new or more sustainable products and services along with improving customer experiences. Improving cost control and making operations more sustainable are their top strategies for bolstering operations. To battle risk, they are strengthening their supply chains, avoiding damage to their reputations, and protecting against cybersecurity attacks.</p>
  <p>These findings show how companies can remain competitive: by transforming business processes to support innovation and flexibility. Learn more about our findings.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c8e8d0c9c3147b1bc776ce3b05f2db0fe99b0e0b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c8e8d0c9c3147b1bc776ce3b05f2db0fe99b0e0b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1c8e8d0c9c3147b1bc776ce3b05f2db0fe99b0e0b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Picture of a PDF version of the content on this webpage." src="./media_1c8e8d0c9c3147b1bc776ce3b05f2db0fe99b0e0b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2744" height="1544">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p>Senior Executive Priorities</p>
  <p>Our survey shows that senior executives are transforming their businesses to be more sustainable, cost-effective, and flexible.</p>
  <p>Read the findings below, or download the PDF version of this report.</p>
  <p><a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2022/06/227db719-2f7e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Read the PDF</a></p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f4119f8e59a64a8630045d01616e586945d8efa2.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f4119f8e59a64a8630045d01616e586945d8efa2.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1f4119f8e59a64a8630045d01616e586945d8efa2.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Graph" src="./media_1f4119f8e59a64a8630045d01616e586945d8efa2.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="1080">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p>Revenue Growth Drivers</p>
  <p>Sustainability is a top revenue driver, and it lies at the core of some respondents’ growth strategies.</p>
  <p><sub>Click on image to view data</sub></p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14a266e9afbbaa4e0297eb49ec55e6dcbb5374fce.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14a266e9afbbaa4e0297eb49ec55e6dcbb5374fce.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_14a266e9afbbaa4e0297eb49ec55e6dcbb5374fce.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Graph" src="./media_14a266e9afbbaa4e0297eb49ec55e6dcbb5374fce.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="1080">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p>Efficiency Drivers</p>
  <p>Operating sustainably is important to gaining greater efficiency.</p>
  <p><sub>Click on image to view data</sub></p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d1d3adeaac59b5250897336a7e2298d43cb07fca.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d1d3adeaac59b5250897336a7e2298d43cb07fca.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1d1d3adeaac59b5250897336a7e2298d43cb07fca.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="graph" src="./media_1d1d3adeaac59b5250897336a7e2298d43cb07fca.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="1080">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p>Future Global Risks</p>
  <p>Leaders see future business risks stemming from a wide range of economic and social concerns, including climate change.</p>
  <p><sub>Click on image to view data</sub></p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d407ca3eca2cea955f7e649dc39e06f4b0a9605b.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d407ca3eca2cea955f7e649dc39e06f4b0a9605b.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1d407ca3eca2cea955f7e649dc39e06f4b0a9605b.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="graph" src="./media_1d407ca3eca2cea955f7e649dc39e06f4b0a9605b.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="1080">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p>Risk Reducers</p>
  <p>In the near term, businesses will be focused on reducing rooted in current threats.</p>
  <p><sub>Click on image to view data</sub></p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11870080f6f581b4ab276767ea63bcf4fd0c01f4c.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11870080f6f581b4ab276767ea63bcf4fd0c01f4c.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_11870080f6f581b4ab276767ea63bcf4fd0c01f4c.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="test" src="./media_11870080f6f581b4ab276767ea63bcf4fd0c01f4c.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="1080">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p>Process-Enabling Technologies</p>
  <p>Businesses are turning to technologies that help them improve processes that came under pressure during the pandemic.</p>
  <p><sub>Click on image to view data</sub></p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1eddcadba01600c9842ec81643d7a446ecae96f3a.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1eddcadba01600c9842ec81643d7a446ecae96f3a.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1eddcadba01600c9842ec81643d7a446ecae96f3a.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="graph" src="./media_1eddcadba01600c9842ec81643d7a446ecae96f3a.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="1080">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p>Critical Areas for Innovation</p>
  <p>Respondents see sustainability as an essential area for business innovation.</p>
  <p><sub>Click on image to view data</sub></p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_141aa18202298e305f5e5df855f0fcaae226f7ea2.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_141aa18202298e305f5e5df855f0fcaae226f7ea2.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_141aa18202298e305f5e5df855f0fcaae226f7ea2.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="graph" src="./media_141aa18202298e305f5e5df855f0fcaae226f7ea2.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="1080">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p>Competition and Profitability</p>
  <p>Successful business transformation is critical to companies’ long-term profitability and competitiveness.</p>
  <p><sub>Click on image to view data</sub></p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d1d3adeaac59b5250897336a7e2298d43cb07fca.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d1d3adeaac59b5250897336a7e2298d43cb07fca.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1d1d3adeaac59b5250897336a7e2298d43cb07fca.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="graph" src="./media_1d1d3adeaac59b5250897336a7e2298d43cb07fca.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="1080">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p>Needs for Process Change</p>
  <p>To improve their processes, businesses need to become more flexible, agile, and collaborative.</p>
  <p><sub>Click on image to view data</sub></p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1faf3528d40a91aaabfefe613ee2b28f9faf74ec5.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1faf3528d40a91aaabfefe613ee2b28f9faf74ec5.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1faf3528d40a91aaabfefe613ee2b28f9faf74ec5.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="graph" src="./media_1faf3528d40a91aaabfefe613ee2b28f9faf74ec5.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="1080">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p>Process Transformation Journey</p>
  <p>Many companies expect to still be in the earliest stages of business transformation in two years.</p>
  <p><sub>Click on image to view data</sub></p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a978273537a5cd47016ce478c2b373778ea70f07.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a978273537a5cd47016ce478c2b373778ea70f07.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1a978273537a5cd47016ce478c2b373778ea70f07.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Man sitting on a tree trunk in the woods" src="./media_1a978273537a5cd47016ce478c2b373778ea70f07.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2744" height="1544">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p>Read the analysis of our survey results: "Bridging the Gap Between Sustainability and Financial Metrics"</p>
  <p>Still think sustainability is a loss leader, a side project? Guess again. Survey respondents say they are embedding it into their business processes at the deepest levels, not because they have to, but because it gets results.</p>
  <p><a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2022/06/5e587926-307e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Read the report PDF</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>topic/business-transformation</category>
            <category>core-topic/sustainable-business-operations</category>
            <category>content-type/original-research</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[What Early Adopters Know About Sustainability and Profitability]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/what-early-adopters-know-technology-sustainability-profitability</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/what-early-adopters-know-technology-sustainability-profitability</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Working with early stage technologies requires an early adopters mindset, which can also help businesses become more sustainable and profitable.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>core-topic/sustainable-business-operations</category>
            <category>content-type/what-is</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Profitable Purpose: The Future of Business Sustainability]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/profitable-purpose-the-future-of-business-sustainability</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/profitable-purpose-the-future-of-business-sustainability</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[This set of SAP Insights articles shows how businesses around the globe are considering sustainability in their strategic calculations.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_149548eb47a30f35a1e4ed14edfc2d9c708c6f843.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_149548eb47a30f35a1e4ed14edfc2d9c708c6f843.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_149548eb47a30f35a1e4ed14edfc2d9c708c6f843.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Car driving on bridge across blue water" src="./media_149548eb47a30f35a1e4ed14edfc2d9c708c6f843.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1044">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="profitable-purpose-the-future-of-business-sustainability">Profitable Purpose: The Future of Business Sustainability</h1>
        <p>This set of SAP Insights articles shows how businesses around the globe are considering their impact on the planet in their strategic calculations.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Sustainability involves rethinking success by including the effects enterprises have on the planet in calculations about the costs of doing business and applying those insights to strategic decision-making.</p>
  <p>There are four overarching factors driving the future of sustainability:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Climate change:</strong> Concerns about the warming planet are causing organizations to rethink traditional practices. This starts with the use of natural resources, continues to the processes used to reshape them into products, and applies to the transportation, warehousing, and distribution choices companies make.</li>
    <li><strong>Resource scarcity:</strong> Natural resources are becoming harder to find and prices are less stable. Companies are compensating by finding ways to use less production materials and switching to alternatives.</li>
    <li><strong>Government regulations:</strong> New rules are appearing in Europe and elsewhere to encourage – and in some cases require – large companies to document their environmental impact and report their findings as part of their financial statements.</li>
    <li><strong>Advanced technologies:</strong> Making sustainability profitable means betting on new technologies. The Internet of Things, AI, autonomous vehicles, and data analytics will make processes cleaner and less costly.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>You can learn more about how businesses around the world are working to meet this potent stew of challenges in the SAP Insights articles linked below.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17e7672387aa702506044de86305de4480f728e83.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17e7672387aa702506044de86305de4480f728e83.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_17e7672387aa702506044de86305de4480f728e83.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="People are playing a jet ski in the sea. Aerial view" src="./media_17e7672387aa702506044de86305de4480f728e83.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1958" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p><strong>Start with stakeholders.</strong> While sustainable business practices may begin with reducing carbon emissions, the concept of sustainability has expanded to include fair labor practices and social inequities as consumers and workers press corporations to address their impact on the world. Leaders adopting a sustainability strategy are focusing on constant communication with shareholders, the media, customers, and other stakeholders about the efforts and what they mean to each group.</p>
  <p>Learn more in “<a href="/resources/sustainability-strategy-profits-follow-purpose">Sustainability as Strategy: When Profits Follow Purpose</a>.”</p>
  <p><strong>Profitable thinking.</strong> Most leaders calculating profits tend not to analyze their environmental and social costs. A significant minority, however, see that their fortunes are inevitably linked to those of the planet – and they are finding ways to make that link pay off, according to recent SAP Insights research.</p>
  <p>Read more about the survey findings in “<a href="/research/environmental-sustainability-affects-competitiveness">The Balance Sheet Blind Spot: How Sustainability Affects Competitiveness</a>.” Go deeper into the data to understand how regulatory compliance drives companies to invest in sustainability programs in “<a href="/research/sustainabilitys-role-in-business-performance">Sustainability’s Role in Business Performance</a>.” Learn about the views of leaders at midsize enterprises in “<a href="https://insights.sap.com/approaching-environmental-sustainability-a-view-from-midsize-companies/">Approaching Environmental Sustainability: A View from Midsize Companies</a>.”</p>
  <p><strong>Tech tools you can use.</strong> Sustainable business practices require changing the way we traditionally measure economic growth. Emerging technologies such as the Internet of Things, cloud, AI, autonomous vehicles, and data analytics are ready to support a shift in strategic thinking and action through such advances as inexpensive, iterative digital design processes; greater resource and supply chain transparency; and lower-cost logistics and recycling processes.</p>
  <p><strong>Sustainability case study in action.</strong> The global software company EPI-USE demonstrates how a business model can combine profits with purpose – in this case saving dwindling African elephant and rhinoceros populations. The company understood that customers are increasingly aware of the environmental and human costs of traditional ways of doing business, and employees are showing a powerful desire to work for companies that make a difference in the world. At the same time, the latest technologies create efficient – and profitable – methods of conserving resources and introducing more sustainable business models.</p>
  <p>Learn how they did it in “<a href="/resources/profit-from-purpose-elephants-on-the-balance-sheet">Profit from Purpose: Elephants on the Balance Sheet</a>.”</p>
</div>
<div>
  <h3 id="dive-beneath-the-buzzwords-to-find-profitable-steps-forward-for-manufacturers-from-sustainability-to-security-to-supply-chain">Dive beneath the buzzwords to find profitable steps forward for manufacturers, from sustainability to security to supply chain.</h3>
  <p><a href="/blogs/building-the-future-factory-a-special-report">Overview: Building the Future Factory</a></p>
  <p>Factory</p>
  <ul>
    <li><a href="/blogs/the-sustainable-factory-of-the-future">The Sustainable Factory of the Future</a></li>
    <li>“<a href="/resources/production-logistics-and-the-new-ot">Production Logistics and the New OT</a>”</li>
    <li>“<a href="/resources/how-industry-4-0-factories-can-still-embrace-the-past">Retrofitting: How Industry 4.0 Factories Can Still Embrace the Past</a>”</li>
    <li>“<a href="/blogs/twelve-security-issues-for-evolving-factories">12 Security Issues to Address as Your Factories Evolve</a>”</li>
  </ul>
  <p>The workforce</p>
  <ul>
    <li>“<a href="/resources/advanced-manufacturing-skills-workers-will-need">Advanced Manufacturing Skills Workers Will Need</a>”</li>
    <li>“<a href="/resources/hunting-for-advanced-manufacturing-talent-four-moves">Four Steps for Hunting for Advanced Manufacturing Talent</a>”</li>
  </ul>
  <p>The supply chain and business networks</p>
  <ul>
    <li>“<a href="/resources/contract-manufacturing-supply-chains-blind-spot">Contract Manufacturing: Supply Chains’ Blind Spot</a>”</li>
    <li>“<a href="/resources/supply-chain-innovation-whats-next">Supply Chain Innovation: What’s Next?</a>”</li>
    <li>“<a href="/blogs/landscape-view-into-value-chain-relationships">A Landscape View into Value Chain Relationships</a>”</li>
  </ul>
  <p>The full manufacturing lifecycle</p>
  <ul>
    <li>“<a href="/resources/circular-path-to-sustainability-for-manufacturers">A Circular Path to Sustainability for Manufacturers</a>”</li>
    <li><em><a href="/research/capacity-capture-a-new-approach-to-discovering-business-value">Capacity Capture: A New Approach to Discovering Business Value</a></em></li>
    <li>– SAP Insights Research</li>
  </ul>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>Style</div>
      <div>Additional Reading</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
<div>
  <p><strong>Creating new business standards.</strong> To create sustainability metrics that mesh with traditional financial reporting standards, companies are doing two things. First, they are repairing the damage they inflict on the planet. And second, they are measuring their success on both those efforts as compared to their own histories and standards demanded by regulators, investors, and society at large. The goal: a more integrated approach to reporting that gets companies to take their environmental and social impacts into account with every business decision.</p>
  <p>Learn about the ongoing efforts in “<a href="/resources/redefine-success-sustainability-reporting">The Quest to Redefine Business Success Through Sustainability</a>.”</p>
  <p><strong>Finding value in sustainability data.</strong> Data that ties a company’s financial performance to environmental sustainability is challenging to find. But executives who recognize that environmental sustainability has become material to their business explain that such data doesn’t have to be perfect to make a meaningful difference. According to an SAP Insights survey, these executives’ companies are <a href="/research/environmental-sustainability-affects-competitiveness">using this data to find business value – and report higher revenues than other companies do</a>.</p>
  <p>Read more in “<a href="/resources/sustainability-data-isnt-perfect-but-its-benefits-will-be">Sustainability Data Isn’t Perfect, but Its Benefits Will Be</a>.”</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e4196c8a2009a17481771df4d40261adadbeadf1.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e4196c8a2009a17481771df4d40261adadbeadf1.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1e4196c8a2009a17481771df4d40261adadbeadf1.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Person using tablet in greenhouse" src="./media_1e4196c8a2009a17481771df4d40261adadbeadf1.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p><strong>Showing customers how they do it.</strong> Today, some of the world’s biggest brands – from retail clothing chain H&#x26;M to coffee behemoth Starbucks – are embracing some of the highest sustainability standards. They’re also relying on a variety of approaches to back up their claims: from increasing visibility into supply chains, to receiving certification from well-known regulatory bodies, to savvy product design. These initiatives let companies do good and stand apart in crowded markets.</p>
  <p>Check out their stories in “<a href="/blogs/building-customer-trust-with-transparency">Seeing Is Believing: Building Customer Trust with Transparency</a>.”</p>
  <p><strong>Greener transport and logistics.</strong> With a call to run all businesses more sustainably, delivery and logistics are obvious paths to implement green measures. A variety of technologies used in combination – solar panels on refrigerated trucks, warehouses that run on renewable energy and use mobile devices (instead of paper) to manage bills of lading, real-time data and routing software to minimize fuel consumption on delivery routes – can make this part of the supply chain less carbon-intensive.</p>
  <p>Go along for the ride in “<a href="/resources/sustainable-logistics-on-the-move">Sustainable Logistics on the Move</a>.”</p>
  <p><strong>Putting theory into practice.</strong> Some companies are starting to view customer product returns as an opportunity to create great customer experiences, differentiate themselves from market rivals, and protect the planet. This new mindset, and the best practices needed to support it, include preventing returns (by helping customers know the precise specifications of the goods they are buying, to avoid misfits or surprises), and generating ROI from the goods that do come back (such as by selling “open box” items). These and other moves reduce wasted resources while improving business results.</p>
  <p>Read more in “<a href="/resources/business-of-returning-things">The Business of Returning Things</a>.”</p>
</div>
<div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="the-circular-economy-goes-mainstream">The Circular Economy Goes Mainstream</h3>
        <p>Read our guide for how to take sustainability to its ultimate goal: zero waste.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="/resources/the-circular-economy-goes-mainstream">Check it out</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>sidebar</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>core-topic/sustainable-business-operations</category>
            <category>content-type/what-is</category>
            <category>stage/acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sustainable Business Travel: Choosing the Greater Good]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/sustainable-business-travel-collective-choices-for-greater-good</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/sustainable-business-travel-collective-choices-for-greater-good</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Due to COVID-19, travel's carbon footprint has improved. But, can businesses support sustainable business travel as restrictions fade?]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15be4a9af17fc84631ec37cf74b7dc618f1bdb3a3.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15be4a9af17fc84631ec37cf74b7dc618f1bdb3a3.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_15be4a9af17fc84631ec37cf74b7dc618f1bdb3a3.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Packed suitcase open on bed" src="./media_15be4a9af17fc84631ec37cf74b7dc618f1bdb3a3.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1044">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="making-business-travel-sustainable">Making Business Travel Sustainable</h1>
        <p>The pandemic cut travel emissions. How can businesses include sustainability in their people’s itineraries?</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>According to a recent survey by the Boston Consulting Group, 70% of travelers expect to go back to their travel behavior from before the global pandemic. But there are good reasons not to bank on this.</p>
  <p>If there is a silver lining to the pandemic it would be all of us recognizing that it changed the way we work, live, and play. Companies had to shift gears over the last two years to not only survive, but to really thrive. And while they continue to adjust to the new business landscape realities, there is no doubt about the positive impacts and new areas of opportunity.</p>
  <p>Sustainability is one such area, as severely curtailed travel across the globe had a positive impact due to significantly decreased emissions.</p>
  <p>The most important impact of the pandemic wasn’t that we couldn’t travel anymore, but rather that we saw we could hold meetings by video conference with the same effect. Virtual meetings are here to stay, and will likely even grow, as technology continues to vastly improve. Aside from the productivity impact created by saving travel time, one cannot ignore the cost savings gained by replacing in-person meetings and events with virtual ones.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11d3647ab0f73942410697637fecf37925724ad03.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11d3647ab0f73942410697637fecf37925724ad03.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_11d3647ab0f73942410697637fecf37925724ad03.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Woman working from home" src="./media_11d3647ab0f73942410697637fecf37925724ad03.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p>Business travel doesn’t affect all companies equally. Consultants travel more than people in the manufacturing industry. There, <a href="/resources/circularity-creates-value-from-waste">reduction of plastic</a> plays a bigger role in sustainability than travel reductions. Still, with billions of dollars saved during the travel ban, companies are now taking a closer look at what is essential business travel and what is expendable.</p>
  <p>Although companies have long been aware of business travel’s huge carbon footprint, very little has been done to solve this issue. Travel was regarded as a necessity and therefore as acceptable pollution.</p>
  <p>Carbon dioxide emissions typically come to mind first when we think about the ecological footprint of business travel. But calculations can get very complex since there is more than just the transport to consider. Accommodations, meals, energy, and waste management all go into the equation.</p>
  <p>This raises the question of how future travel planning and booking systems must be designed if the goal is to support behavioral change and reduce the environmental costs of travel.</p>
  <h2 id="personal-choices-encouraged-by-corporate-education">Personal choices, encouraged by corporate education</h2>
  <p>Because achieving corporate sustainability often comes down to personal choices, it is vital to break down the topic of sustainable business travel into more understandable and hence obtainable goals. Only by measuring and showing the total emissions across all categories for an entire trip can companies educate employees on the impact of every action they take.</p>
  <p>In fact, many employees enjoy traveling in their daily work, even considering it a perk of their job. They are looking forward to returning to business travel as it was before the pandemic. This makes it even more important to educate employees on how their choices affect the overall ecological footprint of their company and, ultimately, the future of the planet. This should be less about making people feel guilty and more about highlighting ways to make their travel more sustainable.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="do-you-have-a-talent-for-sustainability">Do you have a talent for sustainability?</h3>
        <p>Learn why – and how – businesses are developing their sustainability skills.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="/research/does-your-business-have-a-talent-for-sustainability">Read the survey</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>It makes a difference whether we choose hotels built with LEED sustainability certification, use renewable energy, support recycling, use eco-friendly cleaning materials, drive electric or hybrid vehicles, or pick a vegan lunch instead of beef.</p>
  <p>Obviously, an airline could ban beef from its menu. But a company can hardly tell its employees not to order beef if it is offered. That remains a personal choice that an employer has no control over (and shouldn’t have, in fact). But, by providing information on the impact of meat farming on climate change companies may nudge employees into making more sustainable choices.</p>
  <p>To create awareness, corporate sustainability goals need to be defined and aligned with senior management for continuous support and measurement. Providing obtainable, comprehensible, drill-down reporting to employees is another keystone: basically, you have to know how you’re doing in order to know what you have to do.</p>
  <h2 id="the-business-trip-of-the-future-smooth-simplified-sustainable">The business trip of the future: Smooth, simplified, sustainable</h2>
  <p>Technology plays a big role both in providing transparency and changing behaviors. Transparency on sustainability goals and how the company plans to achieve them is vital if you want your employees to support you in your journey to become a sustainable enterprise. For example, they need to be educated that cutting down on connecting flights also reduces the number of flights per trip, thereby lowering emissions.</p>
  <p>While travel software already exists that triggers an alarm if you exceed your budget when booking a flight or train ride, that’s not yet the case when calculating your overall carbon travel footprint.</p>
  <p>In the future, before calculating the time and cost required to get you from New York to your meeting in Berlin, the system will take an additional step and ask whether this trip is necessary. Perhaps it can be avoided by making use of video conferencing rooms or co-working spaces nearby?</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sustainability-is-an-all-hands-effort">Sustainability is an all-hands effort</h3>
        <p>Here’s how to staff your sustainability department for company-wide success.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="/resources/whos-in-your-sustainability-department">Read the story</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Drawing the necessary information from calendar bookings, the system can make suggestions as to how you may travel. Different options such as train, car, or plane will be judged not just taking cost versus time or productivity into consideration. They will also be evaluated by sustainability criteria.</p>
  <p>If the system concludes that a flight needs to be booked in this case, it may suggest an offsetting catalog where you get to choose between planting trees or investing in climate initiatives, for example, to make the trip carbon neutral. The offsetting costs will be added to the overall travel cost. The trip becomes more expensive, the carbon footprint is compensated, and a new way of steering budgets becomes possible.</p>
  <p>While travel budget versus footprint budget is important, there are other developments to anticipate, with calendar-driven action becoming a keystone of future travel.</p>
  <p>We may no longer need to have our passport ready, but instead check in with <a href="/blogs/biometrics-sensing-healthy-society">biometrical</a> information. Smart hotel buildings will know about your reservation when you enter. Information about your exact lodgings and how to get there will be automatically copied to your calendar.</p>
  <p>So instead of waiting for your turn to check in at the reception you can just go to your room and unlock it with your smartwatch. Check-out will be handled the same way. We will also see a stronger <a href="https://insights.sap.com/mobility-as-a-service-future-business-travel/">individualization of travel</a>, as we may get used to arriving in a hotel room personalized for our needs from TV settings to a mini bar aligned with our lactose intolerance.</p>
  <p>Depending on the individual, the contactless hotel stay may seem like a scenario from either heaven or hell. A lot of travelers appreciate the human interaction when arriving at their destination. There is not a one-size-fits-all approach. The desired level of advantage (saving time) and the desired level of comfort (human contacts) are two needs that must be balanced.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e68c95b01897cb9069ce2610cf46de4b73b0d670.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e68c95b01897cb9069ce2610cf46de4b73b0d670.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1e68c95b01897cb9069ce2610cf46de4b73b0d670.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Woman using her smart watch in airport" src="./media_1e68c95b01897cb9069ce2610cf46de4b73b0d670.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="getting-everyone-on-board">Getting everyone on board</h2>
  <p>We must rethink the way we currently book our trips, starting with the respective event or meeting. This also means recognizing that our own travel behavior is shaped by an ecosystem of customers and partners – and vice versa. The more awareness created, the less likely it is we’ll be required to travel when there are other possibilities that provide the same business results.</p>
  <p>This is all the more important as companies will typically put the customer’s preferences first when faced with a customer’s insistence that an important meeting be held on-site. But making the carbon footprint savings transparent for a customer may even sway customers with a sustainability-focused brand away from the high carbon footprint option. That results in savings for both.</p>
  <p>Making non-tangible assets such as sustainability figures tangible and including them in company reports therefore also has a macro-economic impact.</p>
  <p>Once they know how good or bad their travel behavior is, companies can proactively aim for a green record by asking themselves questions such as: How many business trips from other companies did we initiate by requesting everyone to come to our company site? Or, when five people we invited to the meeting didn’t participate in person how much carbon emissions did we save?</p>
  <p>When carbon footprint savings become a tangible advantage, meeting decision-makers lose the incentive to insist on being on-site. That way, everyone achieves a “greener” record.</p>
  <p>We have to applaud and recognize the companies willing to draw a line in the sand and make a commitment to a publicly stated goal. Consulting firm Ernst and Young has set a goal to reduce their travel emissions by 35% by fiscal year 2025, compared to 2019 levels. Deloitte announced they would cut business travel emissions per employee in half. And <a href="https://news.sap.com/2021/03/sap-carbon-neutrality-goal-2023/">SAP aims to become carbon-neutral by 2023</a>.</p>
  <p>It is clear that companies are getting serious about sustainability, which includes establishing key roles to manage sustainability and continuous education of employees. By showing what we do as employers from a large corporate perspective we can also inspire our employees to work on their behaviors.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_145cb5e74f93768ab48d7891e8e408abe513180e5.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_145cb5e74f93768ab48d7891e8e408abe513180e5.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_145cb5e74f93768ab48d7891e8e408abe513180e5.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Green park" src="./media_145cb5e74f93768ab48d7891e8e408abe513180e5.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="sustaining-hearts-and-minds">Sustaining hearts and minds</h2>
  <p>We are in the midst of one of the greatest paradigm shifts the world has seen. And it will likely have more lasting impacts than any of us could have imagined. While business travel will likely gradually resume in 2022 and 2023, there are two significant changes that we’re seeing. Travel is being reimagined. And the traveler’s voice and sentiment are getting stronger.</p>
  <p>The pandemic has forced us to reevaluate almost everything in our lives. One of the outcomes is a global change in travel habits (both business and private). There is a consensus that we want to get back to travel, but only when we feel safe to do so.</p>
  <p>Instead of cleverly thought-out, but inflexible guidelines, employees want their health and safety to take precedence over their travel decisions. Employees are speaking out about this and that’s a major reason why companies will have to move forward on sustainable travel.</p>
  <p>For the past two years, time normally spent travelling was freed up for creative and innovative things instead of hanging around airports and train stations. Adding up all this waiting time, a frequent business traveler may spend weeks of their work year waiting on transport. That’s not to say you cannot have creative moments while waiting for your train. But smart usage of this time must lead to added value for the individual and/or their company.</p>
  <p>For some, that may mean getting sufficient sleep before hopping on an online meeting to start their workday. Others will be up at 4:00 a.m. to do yoga. Either is better than getting up at an ungodly hour to catch a flight.</p>
  <p>Sustainable business travel begins with treating your own brain and body as finite resources.</p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><strong><em>Editor’s note: Discover more about corporate sustainability in</em></strong></p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/insights/viewpoints/sustainable-logistics-on-the-move.html?url_id=text-glo-insights-text-cta">Sustainable Logistics on the Move</a></strong></li>
    <li><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/insights/viewpoints/by-land-sea-and-air-emerging-technologies-to-tackle-climate-change.html?url_id=text-glo-insights-text-cta">By Land, Sea, and Air: Emerging Technologies to Tackle Climate Change</a></strong></li>
    <li><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/insights/viewpoints/circular-economy-sustainable-profitability.html?url_id=text-glo-insights-text-cta">Circular Economy | Path to Sustainable Profitability</a></strong></li>
    <li><strong><a href="https://insights.sap.com/technology-for-preserving-biodiversity/?url_id=text-glo-insights-text-cta">Technology for Biodiversity Preservation</a></strong></li>
    <li><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/insights/viewpoints/blockchains-energy-crisis.html?url_id=text-glo-insights-text-cta">Blockchain’s Energy Crisis</a></strong></li>
    <li><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/insights/viewpoints/capturing-value.html?url_id=text-glo-insights-text-cta">Capturing Value | The Concept of Capacity Capture</a></strong></li>
  </ul>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div data-valign="middle">style</div>
      <div data-valign="middle">additional reading</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>core-topic/sustainable-business-operations</category>
            <category>industry/professional-services</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>content-type/what-is</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Smart Metering: Helping Customers Reduce Consumption]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/smart-metering-helping-customers-reduce-consumption</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/smart-metering-helping-customers-reduce-consumption</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Discover how smart meters, advanced metering infrastructure (AMI), and smart grids, give customers the data and support needed to reduce energy consumption.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_195e10339a1fc417336b3ee0b272a5b97956b1f70.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_195e10339a1fc417336b3ee0b272a5b97956b1f70.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_195e10339a1fc417336b3ee0b272a5b97956b1f70.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="smart meters gauging energy usage" src="./media_195e10339a1fc417336b3ee0b272a5b97956b1f70.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1044">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="smart-metering-helping-customers-reduce-consumption">Smart metering: Helping customers reduce consumption</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Global energy demand is on the rise – forecasted to increase almost 50% over the next three decades, according to the <a href="https://www.eia.gov/outlooks/ieo/">U.S. Energy Information Administration</a>. At the same time, extreme weather events are expected to continue, taxing the capabilities of an aging utilities infrastructure and unreliable energy grids. Consumer awareness about how and when to use energy is critical in order to optimize energy resources. Smart meters are at the heart of giving customers the information they need to reduce consumption, lower their bills, and support the environment.</p>
  <h2 id="what-is-a-smart-meter">What is a smart meter?</h2>
  <p>Smart meters are <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/what-is-iot.html">Internet of Things</a> (IoT) devices that attach to homes and businesses to track energy, water, and natural gas consumption. Whereas traditional meters only measure overall consumption, smart meters track exactly when and how much electricity – or water or gas – is used and transmit that information to utilities in near real time.</p>
  <p>Using <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/what-is-artificial-intelligence.html">artificial intelligence</a> (AI) and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/what-is-machine-learning.html">machine learning</a>, the data generated by smart meters can be parsed to determine how to lower operating costs, increase efficiency, and forecast demand. That ability to track usage, analyze it, and plan ahead could result in smart meters saving utility companies up to <a href="https://www.businessinsider.com/smart-meters-utilities-iot-energy-water?international=true&#x26;r=US&#x26;IR=T">US$157 billion by 2035</a>. Smart meters are also a gateway for consumers to become prosumers, allowing them to produce, store, and consume energy.</p>
  <p>Knowledge is power, and smart meter data benefits consumers by helping them:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Reduce energy consumption with detailed energy usage information that pinpoints energy-guzzling activities and appliances.</li>
    <li>Optimize energy usage by taking advantage of time-of-use tariffs and replacing outdated, power-hogging appliances with more energy-efficient ones.</li>
    <li>Manage their costs with notifications that alert them when their account hits a certain threshold or is higher than usual – to avoid an unexpectedly high bill at month end.</li>
  </ul>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div>With the ability to adapt and react to usage patterns and energy prices, [smart meters] could represent massive energy savings if applied to the broader population. Widespread implementation could contribute to a greener, more stable electric grid for everyone.</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div><a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/arielcohen/2020/08/31/get-smart-ai-and-the-energy-sector-revolution/?sh=5b70fe6b6044">Forbes</a></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="what-is-a-prosumer">What is a prosumer?</h2>
  <p>“Prosumer” is a <em>portmanteau</em> word combining “producer” and “consumer.” Energy prosumers typically remain connected to the central grid. However, they are also capable of producing and even storing energy – typically with photovoltaic solar panels and EV batteries. Depending on the amount of power generated, this energy can either be used to offset monthly bills or be sold back as surplus to utilities companies or other energy distribution services. This model may be applied to both residential and commercial prosumers, with a growing number of businesses plugging their solar panels and EV fleets into the grid.</p>
  <h2 id="smart-utilities-billing-supports-smart-engaged-customers">Smart utilities billing supports smart, engaged customers</h2>
  <p>With smart meters, power companies gain significant opportunities to improve the customer experience. Rather than relying on transactional communications around billing and payment, companies can use the data gathered from smart meters to drive communications that increase customer satisfaction, trust, and engagement.</p>
  <p>Companies can analyze this data and use it to send personalized recommendations to customers via text, e-mail, or as part of the billing process. For example, they can offer pool owners more efficient pool pumps, or encourage those with EVs to charge their vehicles when energy demands – and costs – are lower. This ability to personalize communications while helping customers save money and energy moves utilities from being seen as mere service providers to being valued energy partners. And at a time when there is rising competition in the energy sector, this opportunity to strengthen relationships with customers is paramount.</p>
  <p>Despite these benefits, smart meters haven’t quite come into their own yet. In the U.S., <a href="https://www.smart-energy.com/regional-news/north-america/75-of-us-households-have-smart-meters-report/">75% of homes</a> have smart meters, whereas about <a href="https://www.businessgreen.com/feature/4025086/getting-smart-meters-track-reach-half-britain-homes-businesses-2021">40% of UK</a> and <a href="https://www.smart-energy.com/industry-sectors/smart-meters/australia-new-directions-proposed-to-optimise-smart-meter-rollout/">fewer than 25%</a> of Australian households use them. As smart meter technology evolves, consumers will soon be able to set budgets and receive alerts via an app on their phone to let them know that they’ve left their stove on or have a water leak. They’ll also be able to integrate IoT devices such as smart thermostats or smart lighting into their home networks to better understand and manage their energy consumption. And with <a href="https://www.eia.gov/todayinenergy/detail.php?id=48396">renewable energy use growing</a>, consumers will be able to connect solar panels and batteries to the <a href="/resources/smart-grid-ai-in-energy-technologies">smart grid</a>, becoming prosumers. This will allow them to both store energy and sell excess power back to the grid – making them more active and engaged in the overall conversation around energy and the environment.</p>
  <h2 id="the-benefits-of-advanced-metering-infrastructure-ami">The benefits of advanced metering infrastructure (AMI)</h2>
  <p>AMI integrates smart meters, communication networks, and data management systems to provide two-way communications between utility providers and customers.</p>
  <p>The benefits of AMI include:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Increasing reliability and better managing outages by being able to pinpoint outage locations quickly and automatically alert utilities when the power comes back on</li>
    <li>Evaluating and managing energy consumption by providing accurate information about power usage and patterns that can be used to improve customer engagement</li>
    <li>Improving data quality and billing by providing accurate readings and alerting customers to usage anomalies as they happen rather than after the fact</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="smart-meters-and-ami-support-smart-grids">Smart meters and AMI support smart grids</h2>
  <p>Increasingly severe weather events have highlighted the weaknesses of existing power grids. And the global impact from flooding, forest fires, hurricanes, and heat is expected to continue to rise. As just one example, a recent McKinsey report on <a href="https://www.mckinsey.com/business-functions/sustainability/our-insights/climate-risk-and-response-physical-hazards-and-socioeconomic-impacts">climate risk and response</a> noted that in “Ho Chi Minh City, direct infrastructure asset damage from a 100-year flood could rise from about $200 to $300 million today, to $500 million to $1 billion in 2050.” That, coupled with <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/16/europes-energy-crisis-is-making-the-market-nervous-ahead-of-winter.html">rising energy prices</a>, calls for better overall energy management, which is where smart grids come into the picture.</p>
  <p>Smart grids, which integrate smart meters, renewable technologies, sensors, communications networks, and monitoring systems, allow utilities and their customers to exchange information and energy. This improves the grid’s reliability, quality, and efficiency, optimizing energy usage and catching and adjusting for small problems before they balloon into big issues.</p>
  <p>Smart grids also have self-healing, predictive capabilities. They can identify faults, isolate them, and react to them, reconfiguring energy flow around affected areas to protect the broader grid. They also can access weather and energy usage forecasts to adjust for upcoming situations. Using <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/cloud-analytics/what-is-predictive-analytics.html">predictive analytics</a>, they can also anticipate future maintenance and system management needs.</p>
  <h2 id="can-smart-metering-and-smart-grids-help-eliminate-overloads">Can smart metering and smart grids help eliminate overloads?</h2>
  <p>The short answer is “yes.” The connected, communicative nature of smart meters and smart grids allows for a much more nuanced response to everyday energy use, as well as to overloads and emergencies. Smart grids use edge computing, 5G, IoT, cloud, advanced streaming analytics, and AI to assess grid conditions in real time and rapidly adapt and respond to ever-changing demands. Customers can support overload management by reducing their consumption in response to current conditions.</p>
  <p>For example, they can respond to alerts and notifications via phone apps that advise them to:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Reduce their energy use or turn off non-essential appliances and devices in the face of impending brownouts or outages.</li>
    <li>Turn heating systems down in cold snaps and reduce AC usage in heat waves to decrease the surge in demand and lessen the risk of blackouts.</li>
    <li>Save money by charging EVs and running washing machines, dryers, dishwashers, or other appliances when their power company’s time-of-use tariffs are lower.</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="smart-meter-technologies-drive-greener-cleaner-smarter-energy-solutions">Smart meter technologies drive greener, cleaner, smarter, energy solutions</h2>
  <p>Energy solutions like smart metering and smart grids have many eco-friendly benefits including the reduction in diesel and gas consumption, as utilities would no longer need to dispatch meter readers in trucks.</p>
  <p>Smart meters can support:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>The integration of renewables into smart grids, reducing dependency on gas, nuclear, and coal-fired power</li>
    <li>Smart technology that can turn on and off heat pumps and other appliances to align usage with supply and demand without negatively impacting homeowners</li>
    <li>Encouraging consumers to use renewable energy when the supply is robust so that excess demand doesn’t need to be met by carbon-based energy sources</li>
    <li>Supporting local energy, which is cleaner energy – a decentralized smart grid will be able to connect microgrids where prosumers sell excess solar or wind energy back to utilities or even trade it with their neighbors</li>
    <li>Evolving smart cities. While cities only cover 2% of the Earth’s surface, <a href="https://unhabitat.org/topic/climate-change">UN research shows</a> that they account for more than 60% of greenhouse gas emissions and use 78% of the Earths’ energy</li>
  </ul>
  <p>But greener energy isn’t just about the power that gets used; it’s also about the energy that’s wasted – about two-thirds <a href="https://cleantechnica.com/2020/01/16/how-much-energy-does-the-us-consume-where-does-it-come-from-pew-research/">of all energy</a> in the U.S. annually. Smart meters can pinpoint energy wasted by not turning off lights or leaving devices on standby to help eliminate wastage. Because the cleanest energy is energy that isn’t used at all.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="explore-smart-metering-solutions">Explore Smart Metering solutions</h3>
        <p>Monitor, manage, and forecast energy consumption with analytics in real time.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/utilities.html#smart-metering">Learn more</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>core-topic/sustainable-business-operations</category>
            <category>industry/oil-gas-energy</category>
            <category>industry/utilities</category>
            <category>content-type/what-is</category>
            <category>content-type/use-case</category>
            <category>stage/acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Smart Grid: How AI is Powering Today’s Energy Technologies]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/smart-grid-ai-in-energy-technologies</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/smart-grid-ai-in-energy-technologies</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Discover how AI and Big Data analytics are powering smart grid solutions and modernizing energy technologies and customer service in the utilities sector.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10d6a8fe9ef30ae8bceecbee6d9c4632359c5f356.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10d6a8fe9ef30ae8bceecbee6d9c4632359c5f356.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_10d6a8fe9ef30ae8bceecbee6d9c4632359c5f356.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Wind turbines" src="./media_10d6a8fe9ef30ae8bceecbee6d9c4632359c5f356.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1044">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="the-smart-grid-how-ai-is-powering-todays-energy-technologies">The smart grid: How AI is powering today’s energy technologies</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Like oxygen, the power grid is essential to modern life but is not always top of mind – until problems occur. Today, aging grid infrastructure is taking a beating from severe weather events around the world, resulting in power outages that threaten health, safety, and economic activity. At the same time, a number of other factors are also putting pressure on century-old grids. The way that energy is produced is rapidly changing – more wind and solar, less coal and fossil fuel. This shift requires new processes and ways of managing. The “who” is also shifting, with energy now produced not only by the major energy companies, but also by a plethora of new competitors and prosumers (consumers who produce energy).</p>
  <p>And not only is the natural world changing fast, but the technological world is advancing at a gallop as well. Cloud-connected artificial intelligence (AI) technologies like machine learning, data analytics, and the Internet of Things (IoT) are driving the advancement of smart grids capable of managing far more complex power generation and distribution. These technologies herald significant opportunity for those in the complex energy ecosystem that are able to harness them.</p>
  <h2 id="what-is-a-prosumer">What is a prosumer?</h2>
  <p>Prosumer is a <em>portmanteau</em> word combining “producer” and “consumer.” Energy prosumers typically remain connected to the central grid. However, they are also capable of producing and even storing energy – typically with photovoltaic solar panels and EV batteries.</p>
  <p>Depending on the amount of power generated, this energy can either be used to offset monthly bills or be sold back as surplus to utilities companies or other energy distribution services. This model may be applied to both residential and commercial prosumers, with a growing number of businesses plugging their solar panels and EV fleets into the grid.</p>
  <h2 id="what-is-a-smart-grid">What is a smart grid?</h2>
  <p>A smart grid is a network that integrates energy distribution and digital communication technology in a two-way flow of electricity and data. This enables utility companies to optimize the generation, transmission, and distribution of electricity. And it also allows consumers to benefit from the stories all that data is telling – helping them to better understand the energy they use and even the energy they produce and store through things like solar panels and EV batteries.</p>
  <h2 id="what-is-the-difference-between-the-traditional-grid-and-a-smart-grid">What is the difference between the traditional grid and a smart grid?</h2>
  <p>The main difference between <a href="https://electricalacademia.com/electric-power/difference-traditional-power-grid-smart-grid/">traditional systems and smart grids</a> lies in the ability to exchange information in both directions across the network, from utility companies to consumers and vice versa. Some of the top features that differentiate smart grids include:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Technology:</strong> <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/what-is-artificial-intelligence.html">AI</a>, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/what-is-cloud-computing.html">cloud</a>, and digital technologies allow all the devices and assets within the grid to communicate, supporting better control and self-regulation.</li>
    <li><strong>Distribution:</strong> Energy generated by prosumers and other renewable energy sources – such as solar or wind – can be intermittent and uneven. Smart grid technologies help to coordinate, store, and distribute power from such sources into a steady and reliable stream.</li>
    <li><strong>Generation:</strong> <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/cloud-analytics/what-is-predictive-analytics.html">Predictive analytics</a> in smart systems means that high-demand strains can be forecasted and distributed to multiple plants and substations.</li>
    <li><strong>Sensors:</strong> <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/what-is-iot.html">IoT</a> sensors across the network can help detect risk early on, redistributing power to decrease outages and help balance loads without direct intervention by operators.</li>
    <li><strong>Self-repair and predictive maintenance:</strong> Sensors can also be used to detect mechanical problems and do simple troubleshooting and repairs, notifying technicians only when necessary – <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/apm/what-is-predictive-maintenance.html">before anything actually breaks down</a>.</li>
    <li><strong>Customer choice:</strong> More energy suppliers, cooperatives, and micro-generators can join the grid, allowing consumers to have more choice in how they receive energy.</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="applications-of-ai-in-smart-energy-solutions-the-utilities-sector-perspective">Applications of AI in smart energy solutions: The utilities sector perspective</h2>
  <p>Artificial Intelligence is the driving “intelligent agent” behind smart grids – evaluating the environment and taking actions to maximize a given goal. AI is fundamental to the integration of renewable energy, the stabilization of energy networks, and the reduction of financial risks associated with instability in the infrastructure.</p>
  <p>For instance, the self-learning, adaptability, and calculation capabilities of AI have significant potential to address the intermittent nature of renewable energy. An imbalance in peaks of production and consumption are often represented through “<a href="https://www.energy.gov/eere/articles/confronting-duck-curve-how-address-over-generation-solar-energy">the duck curve</a>” and can make these sources of energy difficult to control. The use of <a href="https://iopscience.iop.org/article/10.1088/1755-1315/510/2/022012/pdf#:~:text=Smart%20grid%20is%20a%20highly,series%20of%20value%2Dadded%20services.">AI in smart grids</a> will help address this challenge by rebalancing inequity between production and consumption loads.</p>
  <p>Smart grid technologies help to make utilities sector activities more transparent and competitive. Some of the applications of AI and machine learning in smart grids include:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Agility and resilience:</strong> When renewable energy is generated by new partners like cooperatives and prosumers, it is often intermittent and variable. Sensors and automation can be used to identify parts of the grid that are vulnerable and respond with automated rerouting – storing surplus energy during peak generation times and rerouting it during gaps in the flow.</li>
    <li><strong>More precise forecasting:</strong> The utilities sector faces widespread price variability due to changes in consumption. <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/cloud-analytics/what-is-predictive-analytics.html">Predictive analytics</a> models can be used to more reliably predict power loads and renewable energy generation. By combining data from advanced metering infrastructure (AMI) with AI, predictions are more accurate than traditional approaches.</li>
    <li><strong>More sophisticated outage alerts:</strong> The network of sensors, meters, and actuators in a smart grid can give a “<a href="https://www.smartgrid.gov/document/last_gasp_message_outage_notification_v30">last gasp</a>” short signal transmission, including time and date, to indicate a <a href="https://skyvisionsolutions.files.wordpress.com/2015/04/sgcc-outage-restoration-fact-sheet.pdf">loss in power</a> due to partial or complete outages. In addition, the predictive capabilities of AI and the real-time data of <a href="/resources/smart-metering-helping-customers-reduce-consumption">smart meters</a> can notify operators of outages right before they happen. These systems can even differentiate between individual, street, and zonal outages.</li>
    <li><strong>Optimized power yield:</strong> The use of AI-powered sensor networks in generation stages can also be used to optimize power output. In a similar way, solar energy also benefits from AI tools to increase productivity by predicting solar radiation.</li>
    <li><strong>Improved automated switching:</strong> The ability of AI tools to predict grid imbalances and to differentiate between a brief power interruption and a full-on outage will soon allow switching protocols to be automated. This will allow utility companies to reroute energy or isolate affected areas before severe damages occur or the outage expands to other areas. These tools are a line of defense that ensures the safety of the essential equipment used to isolate and repair faults.</li>
    <li><strong>More flexible demand-side management (DSM):</strong> Peaks in energy demand put utility companies under great strain. Using AI and smart meters in homes and offices can help with scheduling, planning, executing, and monitoring changes in energy demand to ensure that providers can meet them. Doing this can have a major impact on power usage, as shown by the U.S. <a href="https://www.ferc.gov/sites/default/files/2020-05/06-09-demand-response_1.pdf">Federal Energy Regulatory Commission</a>, which found that peak loads can be reduced by up to 150 GW through demand management. Similarly, the <a href="https://www.epri.com/research/products/1016987">Electric Power Research Institute (EPRI)</a> has estimated these smart tools could lead to a 175 GW reduction in summer energy peaks by 2030.</li>
    <li><strong>Improved security:</strong> <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/financial-management/what-is-cybersecurity.html">Cybersecurity</a> is a key concern for all business sectors. And the increasing number and complexity of <a href="https://www.energy.gov/articles/securing-americas-energy-infrastructure-cyber-threats">cyberattack</a> strategies presents a risk to both existing and new electrical grids. AI tools can help reduce this risk by detecting network attack features, malware, and intrusion and by providing network security protection for power systems. In addition, other technologies, like <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/what-is-blockchain.html">blockchain</a>, can provide transparent, tamper-proof, and secure systems that enable novel business solutions, especially when combined with smart contracts.</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="applications-of-ai-in-smart-energy-solutions-the-consumer-perspective">Applications of AI in smart energy solutions: The consumer perspective</h2>
  <p>Recent surveys from the <a href="https://www.ofgem.gov.uk/publications/consumer-survey-2020-update-consumer-engagement-energy">UK</a> and <a href="https://www.utilitydive.com/news/three-things-consumers-want-from-electricity-providers-1/520821/">U.S.</a> show less-than-great customer attitudes toward utility companies. With the rise in energy suppliers and prosumers, utilities companies will need to leverage smart solutions to help nurture better customer engagement and satisfaction. Below are some of the ways smart grid technologies can help to improve customer satisfaction:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Lower costs:</strong> AI-powered smart grid management and smart metering allow customers to get hourly assessments of their power usage – helping them to see not only when and where they use the most energy but offering personalized tips and suggestions for optimizing their typical daily routines to lower usage during peak times. It also helps prosumers manage energy production which can be sold back to the grid to reduce costs even further.</li>
    <li><strong>Improved sustainability and transparency:</strong> Smart grid data can help customers become more aware of where their energy is coming from, increasing their engagement and helping to <a href="https://www.utilitydive.com/news/ai-in-the-utility-industry/543876/">democratize the grid</a>. This can help to give them new <a href="https://www.nrel.gov/docs/fy11osti/50988.pdf">perspectives</a> on energy provision and the ability to choose more sustainable options.</li>
    <li><strong>Fewer outages:</strong> As mentioned, AI tools can help reduce the number of outages and mitigate their impact both for residential and commercial customers. This means an increase in security and confidence for consumers – especially as weather events and record temperatures bring fears of brownouts and other disruptions.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>Recently, a UK distribution system operator announced a pilot project to use smart meter data to help consumers improve energy management, optimize network loads, and reduce carbon emissions. The trial could save customers millions of pounds and potentially reduce millions of tons of greenhouse gas emissions from the UK’s annual carbon footprint. This is just one example of the potential benefits of smart grids for customers and the environment.</p>
  <h2 id="big-data-in-energy-why-it-matters">Big Data in energy: Why it matters</h2>
  <p>From the point of view of both customers and utilities companies alike, it’s not simply the <em>ability</em> of these technologies to gather and manage large and disparate amounts of <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/what-is-big-data.html">Big Data</a> that matters – it’s the ability to leverage and understand all that data and use it to optimize power usage and inform operations. Big Data is key to helping:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Better integrate renewable and alternative power in utilities companies by learning to predict and manage intermittence, and balance a myriad of small inputs from prosumer players.</li>
    <li>Protect consumers by anticipating outages and redirecting resources in a fraction of a second – rather than after everything has gone down.</li>
    <li>Save money for companies and consumers alike by digitally learning from past activities and using that intel to better manage and automate day-to-day activities.</li>
    <li>Provide fast, actionable insights that let utilities companies make confident and quick decisions in an increasingly competitive environment.</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="how-todays-utilities-industry-is-preparing-for-the-smart-grid-of-the-future">How today’s utilities industry is preparing for the smart grid of the future</h2>
  <p>There is no question that the future of energy is moving toward more decentralized, flexible, and sustainable power provision. But we are talking about a global industry that is over a century old – and often must rely upon infrastructures from nearly that long ago to serve billions of people and their rapidly changing demands.</p>
  <p>Other challenges include complex regulatory changes, the rise of prosumers, and new startups emerging in deregulated regions. Like any journey of business and <a href="/resources/what-is-digital-transformation">digital transformation</a>, the move to smarter grid management starts with a few cautious steps before breaking into a run. Utilities sector technologies are undoubtedly powering and enabling the evolution of this sector. However, for meaningful change to occur, utilities companies will need establish strong communication, customer engagement, and change management plans including:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Communicating a vision of the smart grid and aligning teams and stakeholders around it</li>
    <li>Strengthening consumer education about the changes and opportunities to come</li>
    <li>Providing win/win motivation for consumers, prosumers, and potential distribution partners</li>
    <li>Developing metrics to monitor progress in the implementation and effectiveness of smart grids</li>
    <li>Keeping the customer experience and customer retention in mind, given the additional competition and decentralization of a smart energy market</li>
  </ul>
  <p>The first step on the journey is to communicate with team leaders and subject specialists across your business, to break down silo walls and find the wealth of information often hidden within. Then, look at how you can implement smart technologies to drive your business forward.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="explore-smart-utilities-solutions">Explore smart utilities solutions</h3>
        <p>Transform the most important facets of your business, support energy transition.</p>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/utilities.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>core-topic/sustainable-business-operations</category>
            <category>industry/oil-gas-energy</category>
            <category>industry/utilities</category>
            <category>content-type/what-is</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Top Five Renewable Energy Challenges for the Utilities Industry]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/renewable-energy-challenges</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/renewable-energy-challenges</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Explore the top five renewable energy challenges for the energy sector – and how the utilities industry is meeting and beating them.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>core-topic/sustainable-business-operations</category>
            <category>industry/oil-gas-energy</category>
            <category>industry/chemicals</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>content-type/what-is</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Energy Transition: Utilities Take Center Stage]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/energy-transition</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/energy-transition</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn how clean energy transition and decarbonization are driving change in the energy and utilities sectors and leading toward a carbon-neutral future.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ee8c9b53a1a7ad387289bd543e597fb3a6da830e.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ee8c9b53a1a7ad387289bd543e597fb3a6da830e.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1ee8c9b53a1a7ad387289bd543e597fb3a6da830e.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Wind turbines on a hill" src="./media_1ee8c9b53a1a7ad387289bd543e597fb3a6da830e.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1044">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="energy-transition-utilities-take-center-stage">Energy transition: Utilities take center stage</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The <a href="https://data.worldbank.org/indicator/EG.ELC.ACCS.ZS">World Bank</a> tells us that the current global electrification rate is sitting at about 90% and has risen by over 15% in just 20 years. It is utility companies around the globe that are delivering that energy and – no strangers to disruption and change – they have been keeping our power flowing for well over a century. But as the post-pandemic dust begins to settle, key players in the utilities industry are taking a good look around and realizing that they’re operating in a very different landscape than ever before. If the energy sector wishes to meet its net-zero goals and still remain profitable, it will mean addressing new players and practices and responding to rapidly changing customer demands and behaviors.</p>
  <p>When it comes to clean energy transition, the world will be looking to the utilities sector for leadership and technological innovation as we collectively strive for decarbonization.</p>
  <h2 id="what-is-energy-transition">What is energy transition?</h2>
  <p>Energy transition refers to the shift from fossil-based systems of energy production and consumption – including oil, natural gas, and coal – to renewable energy sources such as wind and solar. The shift also encompasses the trend toward a connected network of distributed energy sources and away from traditionally centralized utilities and single sources of power.</p>
  <h2 id="decarbonization-and-the-economic-shift-toward-sustainable-energy">Decarbonization and the economic shift toward sustainable energy</h2>
  <p>In their extensive <a href="https://www.goldmansachs.com/insights/pages/gs-research/carbonomics-green-engine-of-economic-recovery-f/report.pdf">Carbonomics</a> report, Goldman Sachs notes that, in 2021, spending on renewable energy projects is predicted to surpass upstream oil and gas spending for the first time in history. Part of the reason these projects are so attractive is that the cost of delivering renewable energy is rapidly decreasing. A recent International Renewable Energy Agency (IRENA) <a href="https://www.irena.org/-/media/Files/IRENA/Agency/Publication/2020/Jun/IRENA_Power_Generation_Costs_2019.pdf">report</a> takes a look at the global weighted average levelized cost of electricity (LCOE) of renewable energy projects and finds that in the past 10 years “utility-scale solar photovoltaics (PV) fell 82%; concentrated solar power (CSP) by 47%; onshore wind by 39%; and offshore wind down more than 29%.”</p>
  <p>The report goes on to state that oil and gas spending is down more than 60% from 2014 and that the global oil reserve life (ratio of oil reserves to oil production) has also dropped significantly. In response to these trends, <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/arielcohen/2020/11/17/goldman-sachs-renewable-power-will-become-the-largest-area-of-spending-in-the-energy-industry-in-2021/?sh=4c2c2e4563eb">Forbes</a> tells us that in the past year “many private investment banks, including Deutsche Bank, Morgan Stanley MS, and Citi Bank, have also announced their strategies to reduce their exposure to the oil and gas sector. Additionally, big private equity firms are now increasingly putting their investments into decarbonization technologies.”</p>
  <p>At the moment, utilities companies find themselves in a time of increased investor appetite for renewables projects and continually lowering costs of related infrastructure and start-up costs.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sustainability-and-business-performance">Sustainability and business performance</h3>
        <p>Explore how sustainability is affecting competitiveness and profits.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="/research/environmental-sustainability-affects-competitiveness">Read the report</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="utility-scale-renewable-energy-sources-and-technologies">Utility-scale renewable energy sources and technologies</h2>
  <p>In the long-term quest to eliminate fossil fuel dependency, there are several arenas of human activity that will need to be decarbonized over time including transport, heavy industry, manufacturing, and the built environment. However, as the provider of energy to most of those other industries, the <a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/utilities.html">utilities sector</a> is on point for clean energy transition initiatives.</p>
  <h2 id="what-is-utility-scale">What is utility-scale?</h2>
  <p>We are seeing growing networks of smaller, more widely scattered energy generators and distributors, as well as greater overall demand for renewable energy sources like solar and wind.</p>
  <p>The term “utility-scale” serves as a yardstick by which we measure the capacity of all these resources. To be considered utility-scale, an energy system or network should be able to generate at least 10 megawatts or more – with reliability and consistency.</p>
  <p>Below are some of the most common renewable energy sources and the pros and cons their utility-scale implementation may present.</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Solar energy:</strong> Traditional solar modules use concentrating solar power (CSP) technologies and are limited due to their functional need for direct sunlight. However, the technologies around photovoltaic (PV) solar modules (that can use both direct and diffuse sunlight) have been advancing at a rapid pace. And their cost has been declining at an equally speedy rate, seeing the price of crystalline silicon PV modules drop by over <a href="https://www.irena.org/costs/Power-Generation-Costs/Solar-Power">80% since 2010</a>. When you factor in the $0.00 price of sunshine and the steadily lowering balance of system (BoS) costs, solar is becoming an increasingly profitable option within the utilities industry.</li>
    <li><strong>Hydropower:</strong> This is, of course, the backbone of energy production for many of the world’s largest utilities sector players. Hydroelectric power is clean, abundant, and pairs well with other renewable energy sources to fill intermittency gaps. Problem is: the building of utilities-grade dams involves engineering projects of epic cost and proportion. It also typically involves contentious land reclamation efforts and the potential for disasters of equally epic proportion if anything should ever fail or burst. In other words, if the infrastructure already exists, hydropower is great for the utilities industry. But if it doesn’t, it can be unfeasible to develop.</li>
    <li><strong>Wind energy:</strong> Since 2010, the cost of wind turbines has lowered significantly, with <a href="https://www.irena.org/costs/Power-Generation-Costs/Wind-Power">IRENA</a> predicting an ongoing drop in both set-up and O&#x26;M costs over the next 10 years. Additionally, improvements in turbine technology have led to larger rotor diameters and higher hub heights, meaning that more energy can be harvested from the same wind speeds and space allocation. Wind power projects often elicit complaints of noise and wildlife threat, but they can also result in homegrown profits for landowners so they are also seen as a good opportunity for regional economic growth. A major challenge for the utilities sector is the unreliability of wind. Due to its intermittency, wind power must either be stored in <a href="/blogs/future-batteries-save-civilization">high-capacity batteries</a> or paired with more reliable (often fossil-based) energy sources to sustain the grid during times of low generation. Nonetheless, the energy sector’s reliance on wind power has risen by about <a href="https://www.nationalgeographic.com/environment/article/wind-power">25% per year</a> for the past decade.</li>
    <li><strong>Geothermal energy:</strong> Where available, this can be a highly efficient source of energy due to its “always-on” nature. And compared to wind or solar farms, it has a relatively small geographic footprint. But from the point of view of the utilities sector, this power source is limited due to the price of establishing geothermal power infrastructures and the limited availability of these sources around the world. Furthermore, the constant circulation of hot water in and out of the ground can cause seismic disruptions and lead to earthquakes – especially as geothermal power sources tend to exist primarily in areas of already-high levels of seismic activity.</li>
    <li><strong>Bioenergy:</strong> Biomass is plentiful – often existing as a byproduct of other agricultural or production industries (corn husks, manure, landfill gas). But there is a bit of contention around biomass as a fuel source. The “carbon neutrality” of certain biofuels is achieved because the plants or trees involved – when alive – contributed sufficient oxygen production during their lifetimes to offset the CO2 generated by their eventual combustion. Many also question the assertion that forests are entirely renewable resources given that they can take up to a hundred years to regrow. For utilities companies in developing nations or largely rural areas, biomass options can be interesting, but when it comes to the urban power grids, the cost and complexity of biomass as a power source makes it challenging to implement on a large scale.</li>
    <li><strong>Tidal and wave energy:</strong> In areas of dense coastal population, there are utilities companies currently making headway with <a href="https://www.nsenergybusiness.com/features/tidal-energy-projects-2020/">tidal energy projects</a>. However, these energy technologies are still in their infancy. The potential benefit of tidal power is enormous and virtually limitless so it definitely represents an interesting area of exploration for the energy sector. But at the moment, there is still uncertainty over the long-term environmental impact of such projects. Furthermore, the technology is not yet streamlined enough to produce sufficient wattage to justify the enormous expense of initiating ocean energy projects.</li>
    <li><strong>Batteries:</strong> The challenge of many renewable energy sources is the fact that they can be unreliable and intermittent. Utility-scale batteries can enhance grid reliability to protect against unexpected demand or shortage. Battery integration can also allow power companies to gradually wean themselves off fossil fuels with minimal disruption. However, such industrial batteries are currently produced by only a few specialist manufacturers, and while they are definitely lowering in price, they are still expensive to purchase and maintain.</li>
    <li><strong>Smart, cloud-based technologies:</strong> The application of artificial intelligence (AI)-powered smart technologies and metering in utilities can improve efficiency, collect and analyze valuable data, minimize waste, and help to protect against (and anticipate) risk. Internet of Things (IoT) networks and connected systems can also help to automate and monetize prosumer and distributed power generation networks.</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="net-zero-emissions-goals-in-a-complex-utilities-market">Net-zero emissions goals in a complex utilities market</h2>
  <p>In the U.S., investor-owned utilities (IOUs) provide energy to <a href="https://www.eia.gov/todayinenergy/detail.php?id=40913">over 70%</a> of the population. But as <a href="https://www.greentechmedia.com/">Greentech Media</a> reminds us, they are under extreme pressure to “turn enough profit to retain their investors in a difficult, constrained, low-margin business.” As the utilities industry prepares for energy transformation, IOUs must address some old and familiar challenges, as well as some new factors that are affecting their sector.</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Natural and political disruptions:</strong> The <a href="https://wmo.int/topics/extreme-weather">World Meteorological Organization</a> tells us that weather-related disasters have increased five-fold in the past 50 years, making disaster and climate change preparedness a costly but necessary priority for the utilities sector. Also, as one of the most heavily <a href="http://www.perillon.com/blog/10-most-regulated-industries-in-the-us">regulated</a> of all industries (more so than even automobiles, banking, or air traffic), the utilities industry is especially vulnerable to global and regional political shifts, which can often add to the pressure to remain profitable.</li>
    <li><strong>Changing customer expectations and behaviors:</strong> Decarbonization, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/digitization-vs-digitalization.html">digitalization</a>, and decentralization are changing a century-old relationship between customers and energy providers. Demand response and smart meter technologies let utilities customers reduce their power consumption at peak times in return for lower, off-peak electricity. Improvements in energy storage capacity for electric vehicles (EV) and solar panel batteries also mean that customers can generate and distribute their own power – hence the rise of the “prosumer” (producer/consumer).</li>
    <li><strong>Less control over power sources and greater complexity within the grid:</strong> In one of the world’s most regulated industries, Texas stands out for having an unregulated power grid. As a result, many renewable energy players are flocking to the state, intent on disrupting the industry with clean energy startups. In fact, as <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/features/2021-03-08/tesla-is-plugging-a-secret-mega-battery-into-the-texas-grid">Bloomberg Green</a> informs us, Tesla has quietly been building a 100 megawatt storage battery near Houston and, in August 2021, filed with the Public Utility Commission of Texas to sell electricity on the retail market. With the growing availability and capacity of AI-powered digital technologies – and rapid advancement of battery technologies – it has become increasingly feasible for small-scale players to connect with millions of prosumers to create highly viable power storage and distribution stations. Further, the rise of prosumers alone can lead to hundreds of thousands of power generation and storage points being added to the grid, making it exponentially more complex for utilities companies to manage and operate.</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="sustainable-and-renewable-energy-change-is-the-only-way-forward">Sustainable and renewable energy: Change is the only way forward</h2>
  <p>In the 2020s, it’s no longer a matter of “if” we should transition to more sustainable energy sources, but “how” and “when.”</p>
  <p>Utilities companies are uniquely positioned with the scope, experience, and existing customer base to rethink their business models and begin a profitable journey toward net zero. Here are some examples of competitive strategies:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Lean into the DER and prosumer markets and build new partnerships.</strong> Based upon what we’re seeing around the world (and even in Texas), the digital technology and engineering capacity now exists for clean energy startups to begin to proliferate – scooping up both residential and industrial prosumers and becoming energy retailers and DER providers. For utilities companies, this can either shake out as a risk or an opportunity, depending upon their appetite for innovation and willingness to partner with new players in the market.</li>
    <li><strong>Invest in smart digital solutions and nurture data-driven business practices.</strong> In the energy sector of the future, it will be data that becomes an especially valuable commodity. Companies will achieve a competitive edge by leveraging <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/business-technology-platform.html">AI</a> and powerful <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/data-management.html">database</a> and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp.html">ERP</a> technologies to make sense of their data and to deliver actionable insights. From managing prosumers and multiple renewable energy sources to economical energy distribution and storage, utilities companies will increasingly rely on advanced analytics and data-driven practices to remain profitable and meet a rapidly shifting market and consumer base. The growth in smart technologies also has the potential to improve customers’ ability to self serve and personalize their services and usage.</li>
    <li><strong>Improve communication and customer experience strategies.</strong> The latest survey data from both the <a href="https://www.instituteofcustomerservice.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/ICS-UKCSI-Exec-Summary_July-21.pdf">UK</a> and <a href="https://www.smart-energy.com/industry-sectors/customer-services-management/customer-satisfaction-remains-stagnant-with-us-residential-water-utilities/">U.S.</a> shows unimpressive levels of consumer satisfaction and points to the fact that utilities companies may have some work to do on the customer relations front. Just as it’s a time of great change and upheaval for the energy sector, it’s also a time of confusion for consumers trying to figure out the best way to manage their power usage, what options are available to them as prosumers, and how to optimize the intel available from smart meter technologies. Energy providers need to partner with their own customers, just as they may need to partner with disruptive startups in order to best compete. Doing so, they can not only advertise and promote their brand but share information, increase communications relevance, and generally throw back the curtain on their ongoing plans for energy transition.</li>
  </ul>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div data-valign="middle">In the power and utilities sector, shifting business models, energy options, and the potential for new competitors to enter the market are creating an urgency to improve the relationship with customers.</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div data-valign="middle"><a href="https://www2.deloitte.com/content/dam/Deloitte/ca/Documents/energy-resources/ca-energy-and-resources-en-utilities-new-era-customer-choice-aoda.pdf">Deloitte 2021</a></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="digital-utilities-transformation-and-clean-energy-transition">Digital utilities transformation and clean energy transition</h2>
  <p>In his novel <em>The World Without Us</em>, Alan Weisman describes what would happen to the world around us if humans disappeared. The book gives an account of what would occur in New York City within hours of the power being shut off. The subways would be flooded and, almost immediately, the city’s infrastructures would begin to collapse like dominos. While an extreme example, this nonetheless reminds us of how much our survival depends upon reliable and accessible sources of power – and how over the past hundred years utility companies have created marvels of engineering and invention to fuel those needs.</p>
  <p>In the 2020s, this industry is under unprecedented pressure to innovate and reform, for the benefit of the earth and all of us on it. The good news: with this pressure comes tremendous opportunity to build on an impressive legacy and blaze the trail to a more sustainable future.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="utilities-solutions">Utilities solutions</h3>
        <p>Explore utilities management systems that support a sustainable future.</p>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/utilities.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>core-topic/sustainable-business-operations</category>
            <category>industry/oil-gas-energy</category>
            <category>industry/utilities</category>
            <category>content-type/what-is</category>
            <category>stage/acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Seeing Is Believing: Transparency Builds Customer Trust]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/building-customer-trust-with-transparency</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/building-customer-trust-with-transparency</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jul 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Transparency is an important part of building trust with customers, especially when it comes to ESG and sustainable business practices.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1588631a93738716a9fcff7d3666c006629759fd4.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1588631a93738716a9fcff7d3666c006629759fd4.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1588631a93738716a9fcff7d3666c006629759fd4.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Jeans hanging on a rack" src="./media_1588631a93738716a9fcff7d3666c006629759fd4.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1044">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="building-customer-trust-with-esg-transparency">Building customer trust with ESG transparency</h1>
        <p>Mere talk about ESG won’t win trust. Show it through transparency in product labeling, business practices and more.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>For nearly four years, Triarchy struggled to carve out a place for itself as a manufacturer of luxury designer jeans in a highly saturated marketplace. Adam Taubenfligel, who launched the California-based Triarchy in 2012 with his siblings Ania and Mark, describes an “uphill battle of just trying to get in front of people’s eyes.”</p>
  <p>That changed, however, the day Taubenfligel discovered the water-guzzling wastefulness of making jeans while visiting a denim production factory in China. It can take approximately 2,900 gallons of water to make one pair of traditional cotton jeans from crop to final product. That’s equivalent to nearly 11,000 one-liter bottles of water.</p>
  <p>Not content to be “just another irresponsibly consumptive denim brand,” Taubenfligel says he and his team completely overhauled the company into a luxury wholesaler committed to the highest standards of sustainability. This includes using eco-friendly materials like certified organic cotton, recycled cotton, hemp, and natural rubber, as well as adopting practices such as recycling any wastewater that is produced and limiting the use of chemicals in production.</p>
  <p>But these days, it’s not enough to simply adopt eco-friendly practices, especially if a company wants to gain a competitive edge. A flood of misleading marketing campaigns, unsubstantiated claims, and other acts of greenwashing have eroded customer trust. As a result, many customers now want to be able to verify that companies are doing what they say they are doing.</p>
  <p>To meet these demands, a growing number of companies are taking steps not only to adopt sustainable practices, but prove their veracity beyond a shadow of a doubt. If successful, the result is a trifecta of rewards: a cleaner planet, the public’s trust, and better business outcomes.</p>
  <p>Indeed, Triarchy’s shift wasn’t just to an environmentally friendly manufacturing process – it was a repositioning of its brand to stand apart from rivals. “We made the switch because we were horrified with what we saw in denim production,” says Taubenfligel. “But at the end of the day, it’s the smartest business decision we ever made.”</p>
  <p>Since then, Triarchy has increased revenue by 90% and its luxury denim products, ranging from lightweight button-down shirts to 70s-inspired wide leg jeans, can be purchased from some of today’s top retailers, including Shopbop, Revolve, and Nordstrom, as well as Triarchy’s Web site.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="holistic-steering-and-esg-reporting">Holistic Steering and ESG Reporting</h3>
        <p>Companies are putting holistic steering at the forefront of their strategy.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/sustainability/our-approach/reporting-and-policies.html">Learn more</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>To substantiate its sustainability claims, Triarchy makes its eco-friendly practices completely <a href="/resources/values-in-plain-sight-future-transparency-through-tech">transparent</a> to customers through its marketing. But Triarchy doesn’t presume that customers will automatically trust its word. To cement the bond of trust, Triarchy also has its practices validated by third-party sources.</p>
  <p>The term for this external stamp of approval is <em>ecolabeling</em>: the practice of using recognizable and reputable symbols to demonstrate that a company’s products and services are genuinely better for the environment than comparable products. To date, Triarchy’s ecolabels range in scope from PETA’s Approved Vegan to the Global Organic Textile Standard and Zero Discharge of Hazardous Chemicals.</p>
  <p>Triarchy is not the only company to discover the competitive advantage of transparency in building customer trust. Today, some of the world’s biggest brands – from retail clothing chain H&#x26;M to coffee behemoth Starbucks – are embracing some of the highest sustainability standards. And they’re relying on a variety of approaches to back up their claims: from increasing visibility into supply chains, to receiving certification from well-known regulatory bodies, to savvy product design. These initiatives are providing companies with an opportunity to not only do good but also stand apart in crowded markets.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a6271abb645f241b98a71bca19fee1b60dd7afd5.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a6271abb645f241b98a71bca19fee1b60dd7afd5.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1a6271abb645f241b98a71bca19fee1b60dd7afd5.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Woman in a store reading the label of a bottle for more information" src="./media_1a6271abb645f241b98a71bca19fee1b60dd7afd5.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="transparency-through-esg-labeling">Transparency through ESG labeling</h2>
  <p>Ecolabels date back as far as 1978, when the German government created the Blue Angel, a label awarded to companies whose products and services meet stringent environmental design standards. But what began as a stamp of approval has evolved into a strategy keenly adopted by businesses that want to both target much sought-after customers and establish a reputation as a responsible brand.</p>
  <p>Today, ecolabels from the Fairtrade Foundation, the Global Organic Textile Standard, USDA Organic, LEED, OEKO-TEX, and many more are fighting for white space on the packages of millions of products and services around the world. And not just the ones you find in patchouli-scented natural food stores.</p>
  <p>It’s easy to understand ecolabeling’s increasing popularity. According to an IBM Institute for Business Value <a href="https://cdn.nrf.com/sites/default/files/2020-01/Meet%202020%20consumers%20driving%20change_01_0.pdf">survey</a> conducted in association with the National Retail Foundation, 57% of consumers are willing to change their purchasing habits to help reduce negative environmental impact. And 71% of those who indicated that traceability is very important are willing to pay a premium for brands that provide it.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11f6cd0c8049a126d67f92b6408e27eeba5e590be.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11f6cd0c8049a126d67f92b6408e27eeba5e590be.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_11f6cd0c8049a126d67f92b6408e27eeba5e590be.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Young man working in a vegetable garden" src="./media_11f6cd0c8049a126d67f92b6408e27eeba5e590be.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="870" height="560">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="power-to-the-young-people">Power to the young people</h2>
  <p>These figures are only likely to rise as younger generations gain more buying power. An SAP Insights research <a href="https://www.sap.com/insights/social-impact-in-business.html">report</a> identified 20% of respondents as the Passionates – a group whose strong feelings about important global issues such as sustainability directly influence their purchasing and employment decisions. For instance, the Passionates care 18% more about sustainable sourcing, and 33% more about climate change, than other respondents. Primarily comprised of younger Millennials and Gen-Zers, Passionates will grow to become more dominant over time, making them an increasingly influential market force to reckon with.</p>
  <p>Together, these eco-conscious customer segments are giving brands good reason to clean up their acts. “In the last few years, customer demand for sustainable products has risen dramatically,” says Sandra Capponi, co-founder of Good On You, an Australian ethical ratings provider. “In fashion, the majority of people now say they are actively looking for sustainable brands, and they’re putting their money where their mouth is – spending more consciously than ever before.”</p>
  <p>Case in point: in early 2020, retail giant Walmart ran a signage campaign in a select group of stores, advertising the company’s investment in sustainable seafood. The result: a 25% <a href="https://www.seafoodsource.com/news/foodservice-retail/walmart-links-sustainability-initiative-to-higher-seafood-sales">improvement</a> in fresh seafood sales compared to the rest of Walmart’s U.S. stores.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b048fe99427a23890167aaafcd875df5cc014482.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b048fe99427a23890167aaafcd875df5cc014482.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1b048fe99427a23890167aaafcd875df5cc014482.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Farmer spraying his crops using a drone 289125" src="./media_1b048fe99427a23890167aaafcd875df5cc014482.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="2160">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="how-transparency-spurs-innovation">How transparency spurs innovation</h2>
  <p>Another business benefit of transparency is its power to spur innovation in sustainability techniques. Take Triarchy, for example. The company has eliminated using water to pre-wash jeans to give them a slightly bleached or lived-in look by instead taking air from the atmosphere and transforming it into ozone using specialized machinery. Particles of ozone then are released inside the washing machine, producing a vintage-style effect without the harmful use of chemicals such as bleach.</p>
  <p>Other innovations employed by Triarchy include laser technologies that distress and add details to denim without any toxic sprays, and e-flow technology, which uses non-toxic enzymes on the skin of nano bubbles. When these nano bubbles come into contact with the jeans, they burst and create an abrasion similar to stone washing, using only minimal amounts of water and producing very little waste.</p>
  <p>“The goal is to create a vintage-looking pair of jeans that appear as though they’ve been thrown into a vat of bleach but actually have been made using only a glass of water, instead of the hundreds of liters normally reserved for that process,” says Taubenfligel.</p>
  <h2 id="why-customers-dont-trust-brands-sustainability-claims">Why customers don’t trust brands’ sustainability claims</h2>
  <p>But for transparency to deliver a true competitive edge, companies must first gain buyers’ trust. That’s not always easy: only one out of five consumers say they would trust information given by a company itself regarding sustainability practices, according to an Ipsos Mori survey of 7,000 consumers for the <a href="https://changingmarkets.org/">Changing Markets Foundation</a>. Unfortunately, this mistrust is well-founded. According to a <a href="https://icpen.org/news/1147">review</a> by the International Consumer Protection Enforcement Network, as many as 40% of the sustainability claims made online could be misleading.</p>
  <p>Part of the problem is that third-party affirmations of sustainable practices come from a wide variety of sources, ranging from federal agencies to grassroots organizations. For example, there are ecolabels with the backing of governments, those that have been developed by companies, in collaborations with NGOs, by foundations, with various forms of non-profits, and those backed by private actors, says Graeme Auld, professor of comparative and global environmental politics and policy at Carleton University in Ottawa, Canada.</p>
  <p>And then there’s the all-too-common occurrence of <em>greenwashing</em>. “Brands are providing some very vague claims but these backfire because, eventually, people don’t see the company as authentic,” says Magali Delmas, author of <em>The Green Bundle: Pairing the Market with the Planet</em>. “They go too far claiming an environmental benefit that’s not really clear or substantiated – and that’s really a problem.”</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_126cc2747e2ea96731b9c68b6efe49a99f0ecb453.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_126cc2747e2ea96731b9c68b6efe49a99f0ecb453.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_126cc2747e2ea96731b9c68b6efe49a99f0ecb453.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Dandelion in the wind" src="./media_126cc2747e2ea96731b9c68b6efe49a99f0ecb453.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="your-values-in-plain-sight">Your Values in Plain Sight</h3>
        <p>The future is transparency through technology.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="/resources/values-in-plain-sight-future-transparency-through-tech">Learn more</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="strategies-for-sustainable-trust">Strategies for sustainable trust</h2>
  <p>The good news is brands are finding new and innovative ways to signal to an increasingly educated customer that they are doing good for the planet, and that their sustainability claims can be believed. Third-party auditing and rating systems are a good way to do this; they fill a vacuum created by a lack of universal standards for sustainability across industries.</p>
  <p>For instance, Triarchy relies on Green Story, a third-party platform, to conduct data-driven analyses of the company’s supply chain sustainability: information that is then published on Triarchy’s Web site using informative graphics. These metrics include how many kilometers of travel-related emissions the company has avoided, days of drinking water saved, hours of lightbulb energy conserved, and total square meters of pesticide-free farmland used to grow the cotton for Triarchy’s jeans.</p>
  <p>Although clients pay Green Story to have their practices reviewed, Taubenfligel says Green Story “vets all the sustainability practices we follow and then publishes this information independently. We don’t have the ability to access or edit these findings to make us look better as a company.”</p>
  <h2 id="the-challenges-that-remain">The challenges that remain</h2>
  <p>Yet there are still challenges companies must overcome if they wish to reap the business benefits of transparency. For starters, Delmas warns that the process of earning certification from well-respected agencies is often “a long one.” Even then, there’s no guarantee of winning over customers.</p>
  <p>“One of the biggest challenges is customer confusion,” says Charles Corbett, professor of operations management and sustainability at the Anderson School of Management, UCLA. “There are many labels with partly overlapping objectives and widely varying degrees of verification and stringency. Customers cannot possibly keep up; even individuals who are experts in sustainability have a hard time deciding how to interpret the variety of labels they see in the stores.”</p>
  <p>Luckily, organizations such as ISEAL Alliance are taking steps to create some order in the chaotic world of third-party verification, says Corbett. Comprised of more than 200 global organizations, the ISEAL Alliance has developed a set of principles for companies, governments, and NGOs to use as a framework for benchmarking sustainability efforts or internal audits.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1eabaca5877557bd9f83510eb077826f594438cb9.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1eabaca5877557bd9f83510eb077826f594438cb9.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1eabaca5877557bd9f83510eb077826f594438cb9.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Man entering office through glass door" src="./media_1eabaca5877557bd9f83510eb077826f594438cb9.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="make-trust-all-encompassing">Make trust all-encompassing</h2>
  <p>Done right, transparency is an important part of building trust with customers. But it’s important not to see it as a panacea. Brands can most effectively encourage sustainable purchases by “bundling” their sustainability transparency with five other key attributes: quality, status, health, money, and emotion, says Delmas. She offers the example of Tesla. The electric car manufacturer has built its success on performance, aesthetics, and acceleration, not just environmental impact.</p>
  <p>“Brands have to think about the environment <em>and</em> develop products that have superior quality,” says Delmas. “That’s how you gain a competitive advantage.”</p>
  <p>Clearly, however, transparency offers brands a big opportunity. Consumer demand for sustainability is high, and supply is low and often questionable. This means that companies that do it right will have a good chance of winning. The key is to tap into innovative technologies and business strategies that will not only sustain the planet – but also customers’ trust.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>core-topic/sustainable-business-operations</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
            <category>content-type/trends-predictions</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>stage/acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Preserving Biodiversity: Technology for Biology]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/technology-for-biology-preserving-biodiversity</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/technology-for-biology-preserving-biodiversity</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Applying technological innovation to conserving and restoring biodiversity can create a more environmentally and economically stable future.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>core-topic/sustainable-business-operations</category>
            <category>content-type/trends-predictions</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Emerging Technologies to Tackle Climate Change]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/by-land-sea-and-air-emerging-technologies-to-tackle-climate-change</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/by-land-sea-and-air-emerging-technologies-to-tackle-climate-change</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New technologies are helping fight climate change, cut carbon emissions, and mitigate damage to the planet.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>core-topic/sustainable-business-operations</category>
            <category>industry/engineering-construction-operations</category>
            <category>content-type/trends-predictions</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Capturing Value]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/research/capturing-value</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/research/capturing-value</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Capacity capture is a new way of doing business by which untapped resources and capabilities that are hiding in plain sight are utilized.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_19a1155be4e242a846f018a5e83ff0921ee4c97b1.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_19a1155be4e242a846f018a5e83ff0921ee4c97b1.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_19a1155be4e242a846f018a5e83ff0921ee4c97b1.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Abstract motion blurred view of a train" src="./media_19a1155be4e242a846f018a5e83ff0921ee4c97b1.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1044">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="capturing-circular-economy-value-in-waste-management">​Capturing Circular Economy Value in Waste Management</h1>
        <p>Rethinking the worth of everything – from underused and excess assets to waste products – can lead to sustainable innovations.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>We (or at least many of us) sure do love our beer. Globally, <a href="https://www.kirinholdings.co.jp/english/news/2019/1224_01.html">189 billion liters</a> (roughly 50 billion gallons) of suds are swilled every year. The problem is that beer comes with a by-product: spent grains that are left over after the brewing process. Some are sold to farmers for animal feed, but most are trashed. That’s a lot of landfill.</p>
  <p>But brewers are now finding new ways to both avoid this waste and put it to good use while making some money. One example is Scottish independent brewery BrewDog, which is now using its spent grains to <a href="https://www.beveragedaily.com/Article/2020/08/24/BrewDog-s-global-craft-beer-business-goes-carbon-negative">generate</a> energy for its brewery. It has also made <a href="https://www.beveragedaily.com/Article/2020/08/24/BrewDog-s-global-craft-beer-business-goes-carbon-negative">dog treats</a> from the spent grain that would otherwise be thrown away and will soon release Bad Beer Vodka, a spirit made – as the name implies – from the company’s subpar beer.</p>
  <p>Given the current climate crisis, literally nothing should go to waste. Environmental concerns dictate that we must use the resources we have to their utmost capacity and with minimal leftovers.</p>
  <p>Rethinking how we use and conserve resources is not just an environmental issue; it’s also tied to financial stability and business continuity, as we have learned all too well from COVID-19.</p>
  <p>During this period of economic uncertainty, businesses need to wring the most value from everything they do. That means not just finding better, more efficient ways to do what they already do but also discovering untapped resources and capabilities that are hiding in plain sight, such as the spent grains in a brewery. Identifying these “new” resources and ways of doing things doesn’t have to be a random accident; it can be a highly disciplined and repeatable practice. Called “capacity capture,” it is an emerging way of doing business that will help companies manage these challenges, become more efficient, minimize waste, improve competitiveness, and find new revenue streams.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="a-new-approach-to-capture-business-value">A new approach to capture business value</h3>
        <p>How do you assess, manage, incubate, or scale ideas? Start measuring them.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="/research/capacity-capture-a-new-approach-to-discovering-business-value">Learn more</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Reframing waste as a potential asset is part of adapting to expectations across the board, says Andrew Winston of Winston Eco-Strategy. Waste is beginning to look just… wrong. “I think increasingly your investors, your communities, your employees are just less and less impressed with a company that doesn’t operate more efficiently and use its resources better,” Winston says.</p>
  <p><a href="/research/capacity-capture-a-new-approach-to-discovering-business-value">Capacity capture</a> – the utilization of assets and resources that were considered waste or weren’t used completely – is a key element of the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/sustainability/what-is-circular-economy.html">circular economy</a>, a model in which one enterprise’s waste becomes another’s inputs for production. But even companies that recognize the necessity of this change have difficulty understanding how to implement capacity capture. That’s because capacity capture is a philosophy and a new approach to business. It takes creativity and a willingness to take risks and challenge assumptions. Businesses will need to reconsider fundamental assumptions about what they are and how they work.</p>
  <p>Capacity capture is about finding ways to reframe underused resources as assets with real value – whether it’s for your company or someone else’s.</p>
  <p>Apart from the fact that the environment is in real trouble – the planet is literally on fire, that birds are dropping from the sky, and we’re eating plastic with every meal – disposing of waste is getting too expensive. “I see a growing interest for a company to convert waste into resources,” says Rémy Le Moigne, managing director of Paris-based consultancy Gate C. “For a lot of companies, especially, for example, chemical companies, the cost to get rid of spent chemicals is sometimes very high, and they’re looking for solutions to reduce this cost, and one of the possible solutions is to convert waste into resources.”</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a96d8bc6d9b4fcbfedb3d860ae82f066737f9085.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a96d8bc6d9b4fcbfedb3d860ae82f066737f9085.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1a96d8bc6d9b4fcbfedb3d860ae82f066737f9085.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Person operating machine" src="./media_1a96d8bc6d9b4fcbfedb3d860ae82f066737f9085.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="capacity-capture-questions-assumptions">Capacity capture questions assumptions</h2>
  <p>The new trifecta of price, quality, and now values is driving consumers’ brand loyalty and purchasing decisions. Values have become less of an afterthought and more of a crucial ​​distinction.</p>
  <p>Winston believes there’s just been more awareness of waste in recent years. “Companies increasingly have to prove their value to society, their role in society, that they’re taking care of resources effectively,” he says.</p>
  <p>But the pandemic, along with other challenges facing companies today like the environment and increasing costs, has offered an opportunity to embark on a new way of thinking. Companies need to look for ideas that may not make sense in the context of how things have been done before. That includes ingrained assumptions about how the value of assets impact capacity.</p>
  <p>Capacity capture is about stretching organizational thinking by exploring untapped resources across three categories: Physical assets are the tangible objects and places that an organization holds. Digital assets include network infrastructure, data, and software. And human assets refer to people – their behaviors, roles, and skills.</p>
  <p>The capacity capture mindset looks at each of these assets with fresh eyes to find ways that value can be realized. This approach examines each untapped resource – no matter which category it falls in – to consider whether it is unwanted, excess, or underused.</p>
  <p>Prospective resources can be evaluated by considering how they could be reused by another part of an organization, either by themselves or combined with other resources; how a resource can be used as much as possible; and when and how selling, recycling, and donating make sense.</p>
  <p>Capacity capture looks at the value of assets in these categories and finds ways they can be exploited. For example, in some countries, fast food chain McDonald’s utilizes its used <a href="https://www.cnn.com/2020/01/30/business/neutral-fuels-dubai/index.html">cooking</a> oil as biofuel for delivery trucks, and one restaurant donated some as a replacement for liquid plastic for 3D printing.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ccc446d906098c6cadcee53af166c809e3cce294.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ccc446d906098c6cadcee53af166c809e3cce294.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1ccc446d906098c6cadcee53af166c809e3cce294.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Machine 3D printing something" src="./media_1ccc446d906098c6cadcee53af166c809e3cce294.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="three-types-of-untapped-resources-questions-for-exploration">Three types of untapped resources: Questions for exploration</h2>
  <p><strong>The capacity capture approach focuses on three asset categories – physical, digital, and human – and asks whether they are unwanted, excess, or underused.</strong></p>
  <p><strong>Unwanted assets</strong> are created or accumulated as a by-product of another process. <strong>Excess assets</strong> are produced or gathered intentionally; they become surplus either because there are too many of them or because the process that created them is no longer in use. <strong>Underused assets</strong> are created intentionally; they’re in use but not to their full potential.</p>
  <p>The following examples look at different assets through the capacity capture lens:</p>
  <h3 id="physical-assets-tangible-objects-such-as-facilities-heavy-equipment-and-office-supplies">1. Physical assets (tangible objects, such as facilities, heavy equipment, and office supplies)</h3>
  <p><strong>Unwanted:</strong> What is created unintentionally as a side effect and then discarded?</p>
  <p><em>Example:</em> UK's Wensleydale Creamery works with a nearby bioenergy plant to convert whey waste into home heating energy.</p>
  <p><strong>Excess:</strong> What is produced intentionally but becomes surplus?</p>
  <p><em>Example:</em> Several European utility companies are working with Nissan and Mitsubishi to develop a means for electric car owners to sell energy stored in their vehicles’ batteries.</p>
  <p><strong>Underused:</strong> What kinds of existing assets are not used to their full potential?</p>
  <p><em>Example:</em> Coca-Cola transports vaccines using empty spaces in its refrigeration trucks.</p>
  <h3 id="digital-assets-network-infrastructure-software-data-and-metadata-and-bandwidth">2. Digital assets (network infrastructure, software, data and metadata, and bandwidth)</h3>
  <p><strong>Unwanted:</strong> What is collected incidentally and rarely used or analyzed?</p>
  <p><em>Example:</em> UnitedHealth Group spinoff Optum repurposes aggregated data and provides pharmaceutical companies an analysis of how their products are being used.</p>
  <p><strong>Excess:</strong> What is developed or gathered intentionally but rarely used?</p>
  <p><em>Example:</em> LED bulbs can be programmed to transmit data through visible light communication or Li-Fi networks.</p>
  <p><strong>Underused:</strong> What kinds of existing storage and channels are not used to their full potential?</p>
  <p><em>Example:</em> Amazon rented out excess computing infrastructure capacity, creating Amazon Web Services.</p>
  <h3 id="human-assets-people-and-their-behaviors-roles-and-skills">3. Human assets (people and their behaviors, roles, and skills)</h3>
  <p><strong>Unwanted</strong>: Where are people or their behaviors seen as undesirable?</p>
  <p><em>Example:</em> Mobile phones at business events were once considered rude. Now companies encourage employees to promote brands on their smartphone social media accounts.</p>
  <p><strong>Excess:</strong> Where do you gather people or encourage behaviors but then not use them fully?</p>
  <p><em>Example:</em> A company that <a href="/resources/how-to-keep-baby-boomers-an-essential-talent-resource">invites retired employees</a> to use their experience and institutional knowledge as coaches.</p>
  <p><strong>Underused:</strong> How can you tap into unrecognized skills and capabilities?</p>
  <p><em>Example:</em> The Hilton Worldwide hotel chain keeps records of employee skills, giving the company fast access to people with certain knowledge (such as language fluency) when needed.</p>
  <p>Even some assets that have been conventionally thought of as valuable are being challenged. For example, with the rising population of remote workers, the value of real estate is being questioned. Companies like Shopify and REI Co-op are going mostly remote; REI is even selling its recently built <a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/business/2020/08/12/rei-seattle-headquarters-commercial-real-estate/">headquarters</a>. Now companies must ask if such assets are really driving the value of business and if they can do business better without them.</p>
  <h2 id="technology-makes-it-easier">Technology makes it easier</h2>
  <p>A capacity capture approach involves identifying an asset or activity and then figuring out how it might be valuable to somebody, somewhere. That could mean, for example, looking to other industries for opportunities. The car company Renault is investigating repurposing batteries that can no longer supply the huge energy demands of its electric cars for less demanding uses, such as <a href="https://easyelectriclife.groupe.renault.com/en/outlook/technology/the-circular-economy-of-the-electric-vehicle-battery/">storage</a> for wind or solar power.</p>
  <p>But finding the right match or use for an untapped asset, particularly outside a company’s own industry, is not an easy task. The main hurdles, says Le Moigne, are usually the risk and investment required. Companies generally prefer to direct investment capital to new production. “When you start such a project, you don’t know what the result will be,” he says. “Companies are not sure they will find a solution, and they’re not sure how expensive the solution will be.”</p>
  <p>But that’s changing.</p>
  <p>Technology platforms increasingly make finding new partnerships and assessing market potential quicker, less risky, and less expensive. Cloud service providers make it straightforward to spin up the back end of a new business venture, for example. Drop-shipping and warehousing services ease access to logistics services. Intermediaries like <a href="https://materialconnexion.com/">Material ConneXion</a> make available a collection of raw and manufactured materials to companies that could use them, while online networks like Upwork and LinkedIn provide a parallel service for peoples’ talents. Together, these and other communication channels and transactional networks connect supply with previously inaccessible demand across industries and physical distance. They lower the bar for trying out a new business model or working with partners in other industries, making the capacity capture opportunities easier to explore.</p>
  <p>Another example is one of Le Moigne’s clients, <a href="https://sourcing.inex-circular.com/">iNex</a>, a startup in Paris that acts as a matchmaker for companies with industrial waste and companies that could use it. “In the past, the waste was valuable, but finding a company that needed it and wanted it was terribly difficult and expensive,” says Le Moigne.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_130d65982a0d25363239cc789f2698e3ee20b746c.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_130d65982a0d25363239cc789f2698e3ee20b746c.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_130d65982a0d25363239cc789f2698e3ee20b746c.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Two people analyzing data" src="./media_130d65982a0d25363239cc789f2698e3ee20b746c.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2007" height="1493">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="the-case-for-a-chief-capacity-officer">The case for a chief capacity officer</h2>
  <p>The essential work of capacity capture may never happen unless companies make it someone’s job. A chief capacity officer would be in charge of uncovering where value is being lost or is untapped. The role would be to look outside a company’s core competencies, to look at different ways to use fallow assets, and to try to find those with the most potential.</p>
  <p>But this position and its team would need people who can think in truly unexpected and unconventional ways, who can come up with ideas that are, on the surface, almost ridiculous. They would need to be able to look outside a company’s core competencies to spot those unwanted, excess, and underused resources and explore potential for value outside the usual channels. Not everyone has the ability to think like this, so assembling the right team may require counterintuitive choices.</p>
  <p>In fact, a company that develops the expertise in capacity capture can take its capability further by turning the activities into a line of business, helping other companies create their capacity capture mindsets and projects.</p>
  <h2 id="how-to-encourage-the-capacity-capture-mindset">How to encourage the capacity capture mindset</h2>
  <p>During the initial stages of the COVID-19 pandemic, companies and manufacturers that suddenly found their production lines and employees idle came up with ways to contribute to the overwhelming need for PPE. Distilleries made hand sanitizer, clothing factories made medical gowns, and camping outfitters made masks. Other pivots in response to the new normal include office workers, event planners, and entertainers doing business online. Restaurants and shops expanded outdoors into parks and streets. Some of these changes have been temporary, but others have revealed entirely new audiences and ways of working.</p>
  <p>How can we build this way of thinking into everyday business strategy and planning? Here are three moves:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Continuously identify untapped resources.</strong> Use the physical, digital, and human categories to stretch your team’s thinking. Keep an ongoing resources list and invite many people to contribute from all parts of your organization.</li>
    <li><strong>Regularly explore potential opportunities.</strong> As part of your strategic planning, ask a diverse group to explore the untapped resources list and generate possibilities for capturing value both inside and outside your organization (see “<a href="#prompts-for-capacity-capture-idea-generation">Prompts for capacity capture idea generation</a>”).</li>
    <li><strong>Reach for the unexpected.</strong> As you analyze the list of resources, suspend disbelief and convention. Look for the seemingly ridiculous ideas – true innovation often feels uncomfortable at first.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>This mindset can lead to opportunities when you look hard enough – beermaker BrewDog and its canine treats is one example. Retailer Ikea is another. Its stores are globally consistent – big and flat – and the company has committed to creating as much energy as it uses. So far it has installed 900,000 solar panels on its stores’ roofs. The British Wensleydale Creamery converts its waste from cheesemaking into <a href="https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2019/jun/15/wensleydale-cheese-waste-heat-4000-homes-biogas">biogas for home heating</a>. And the grandparent of circular economic activity, the industrial park in <a href="http://www.symbiosis.dk/en/">Kalundborg, Denmark</a>, famously hosts 13 companies that exchange materials like sludge, steam, and fly ash in a cyclical harvest of waste into inputs and energy.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f093469d64181fe9145ba45be18d30fc40dc7335.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f093469d64181fe9145ba45be18d30fc40dc7335.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1f093469d64181fe9145ba45be18d30fc40dc7335.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Close-up of memory board" src="./media_1f093469d64181fe9145ba45be18d30fc40dc7335.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="prompts-for-capacity-capture-idea-generation">Prompts for capacity capture idea generation</h2>
  <p><strong>Consider unwanted, excess, and underused materials as assets in the following categories. For each identified resource, ask the following questions to generate potential value:</strong></p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Reuse:</strong> How could it benefit another part of your organization?</li>
    <li><strong>Extend and combine:</strong> What other things could you do with this resource, alone or combined with another resource?</li>
    <li><strong>Spin off:</strong> What could you do with this resource if you removed it from its current context to stand alone?</li>
    <li><strong>Maximize:</strong> How could you create and use even more of this resource?</li>
    <li><strong>Sell:</strong> Under what circumstances might someone else value this resource enough to buy it from your organization?</li>
    <li><strong>Recycle:</strong> How could another organization use this resource when you’re done with it?</li>
    <li><strong>Donate:</strong> Could you create non-monetary value and save the cost of disposal by giving this resource away?</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="thinking-flexibly-for-the-future">Thinking flexibly for the future</h2>
  <p>Like Renault, companies that are nimble and successful at capacity capture often are doing it outside their given industry. In fact, the very idea of industries is becoming less relevant. The competitive companies of the future will be operating in several industries, cross-pollinating ideas and innovations. When Renault sells its old batteries outside the automotive industry, is it still a vehicle manufacturer? Or a renewable energy and utility company? Or all of the above?</p>
  <p>The challenges facing companies today – including climate change, shrinking resources, and of course, the pandemic – have also offered an opportunity to embark on a new way of thinking. Flexible exploration of resources and business models is proving critical to connecting with new markets and sustaining organizations through disruptive change. What are your organization’s equivalents of spent grains, flat roof space, or used batteries? Capacity capture offers a way to broaden your thinking about what’s possible, reduce your organization’s footprint, and uncover the value that’s hiding in plain sight.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>core-topic/sustainable-business-operations</category>
            <category>industry/consumer-goods-cpg</category>
            <category>content-type/original-research</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Future Batteries Could Save Civilization]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/future-batteries-save-civilization</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/future-batteries-save-civilization</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Batteries able to store power at grid scale can help reduce reliance on fossil fuels. Read how innovation at the atomic level leads the way.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_180cb63c65513b67fe0cbefd1eeb6ad1039edeb68.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_180cb63c65513b67fe0cbefd1eeb6ad1039edeb68.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_180cb63c65513b67fe0cbefd1eeb6ad1039edeb68.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Close-up of battery panel" src="./media_180cb63c65513b67fe0cbefd1eeb6ad1039edeb68.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="522">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="how-future-batteries-could-save-civilization">How Future Batteries Could Save Civilization</h1>
        <p>Innovations in materials, chemicals and engineering will yield next-gen batteries that support renewable energy efforts.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10063118369659b1fbe9b62dd577b1e6b7ddc424f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10063118369659b1fbe9b62dd577b1e6b7ddc424f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_10063118369659b1fbe9b62dd577b1e6b7ddc424f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_10063118369659b1fbe9b62dd577b1e6b7ddc424f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="319" height="179">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://d.dam.sap.com/m/tjMjc1R/hls.m3u8">SAP Digital Futures: How Future Batteries Could Save Civilization</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The future of humanity may well depend on our ability to move away from our dirty and dwindling supply of fossil fuels as fast as possible. To steer ourselves and our planet in the right direction, we have to find another way to feed our civilization’s need for a reliable supply of energy.</p>
  <p>Nuclear power may well be part of the solution for the near term, but the need to manage depleted radioactive fuel for centuries makes nuclear energy as environmentally problematic as the fossil fuels it replaces. At best, we should only consider it a bridge to more sustainable forms of power.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="want-a-quick-overview">Want a quick overview?</h3>
        <p>Learn how next-gen batteries will redefine our approach to renewable energy.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2022/10/a65cb9ff-477e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Read story</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Fortunately for the human race, renewable energy is finally becoming competitive. To make it truly transformative, though, we also need to reinvent a technology most of us take for granted: the battery.</p>
  <p>Scientists, industry players in industries ranging from utilities and energy to automotive, and venture capitalists are investing billions in a quest to quench our unending demand for electric power for everything from the gadgets in our pockets to the vehicles on our roads. There are a number of impressive advances underway involving things as far apart as carbon nanotubes to electric charges harnessed from compost piles. But there remain many challenges to mass-produce the cheap, renewable, zero-carbon batteries the world craves.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_124e72c598e3b96995b88bcd19941de1ac67e8076.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_124e72c598e3b96995b88bcd19941de1ac67e8076.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_124e72c598e3b96995b88bcd19941de1ac67e8076.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_124e72c598e3b96995b88bcd19941de1ac67e8076.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="746" height="560">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="saving-power-for-later">Saving power for later</h2>
  <p>Utility companies are responsible for delivering power at all hours, under all conditions. That’s the central challenge in building a grid powered by renewable energy: you can’t generate wind power on a still day or solar power on a cloudy one, and you can’t tweak the weather to boost power production during times of peak demand. To ensure we continue to have abundant, consistent electricity in a post-fossil fuel age, we need grid-scale ways to store hydroelectric, solar, and wind power for later use and move it to where it’s needed.</p>
  <p>The most common rechargeable batteries in use today are lithium ion (Li-ion). Li-ion batteries can pack a lot of energy into a small, lightweight package that charges quickly, retains a charge for a long time, and can be recharged many times before wearing out. The <a href="https://www.nobelprize.org/prizes/chemistry/2019/press-release/">2019 Nobel Prize for Chemistry</a> recognized three scientists who developed the technology in the 1970s that now powers millions of smartphones and other gadgets. They are even being used to store energy in <a href="https://www.scientificamerican.com/article/utility-scale-energy-storage-will-enable-a-renewable-grid/">the power grid</a>. Yet the challenge of replacing conventional energy sources like oil and gas with batteries is one reason battery research and development attracted <a href="https://www.power-eng.com/2020/01/22/lithium-ion-startups-attract-lions-share-of-energy-storage-venture-capital-in-2019/">nearly US$2 billion</a> in venture capital in 2019.</p>
  <p>The next generation of energy storage seems to be on the verge of breaking out. Keep an eye on these technologies currently in development:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Batteries made of graphene – a one-atom-thick layer of graphite that conducts energy faster and more efficiently than any other material on earth. Graphene batteries charge and discharge dozens of times faster than standard Li-ion batteries, can be charged to full in less time, and store an enormous amount of power for their size. At least one company is working to produce graphene batteries for use in electric cars to give the vehicles a driving range of up to <a href="https://www.pocket-lint.com/gadgets/news/130380-future-batteries-coming-soon-charge-in-seconds-last-months-and-power-over-the-air">500 miles</a> on one charge.</li>
    <li>A battery made from cheap, plentiful sodium needs to be much bigger than an Li-ion battery to hold the same charge. That makes sodium batteries impractical for portable devices but ideal for homes, office buildings, or the grid itself. In fact, an Australian company plans to implement <a href="https://www.greencarcongress.com/2020/04/20200423-faradion.html">sodium-ion batteries</a> for energy storage this year.</li>
    <li>A <a href="https://www.frontiersin.org/articles/10.3389/fenrg.2019.00123/full">lithium-sulfur</a> (Li-S) battery could store two to three times as much power in the same space as an Li-ion battery, or the same amount of power in half to one-third the size. So far, though, Li-S batteries don’t last long, so researchers say there is still a long way to go for a commercial version.</li>
    <li>Lithium combined with air could store twice as much power as an Li-ion battery of the same size (or the same amount of power in a battery half the size). Like Li-S batteries, though, <a href="https://phys.org/news/2019-10-lithium-air-batteries-flight.html">Li-air batteries</a> have a longevity problem that researchers are still working to solve.</li>
    <li>Solid-state batteries developed by Toyota scientists can completely charge or discharge in just eight minutes and, because they do not contain liquid as other batteries do, should continue working in temperatures from boiling to well below freezing. The company has said it expects to begin mass production of <a href="https://www.autonews.com/shift/solid-state-batteries-show-promise">solid-state batteries</a> around 2025.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>Other possibilities at early stages of development include batteries made with a <a href="https://www.batterypoweronline.com/news/stanford-team-develops-fireproof-solid-state-electrolyte/">fire-retardant solid polymer</a>; batteries that are 3D-printed from <a href="https://www.greencarcongress.com/2019/09/20190904-prieto.html">copper foam</a>; lightweight, long-lasting, miniaturized, <a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41929-019-0310-y">solid-oxide fuel cells</a>; and <a href="https://www.pocket-lint.com/gadgets/news/130380-future-batteries-coming-soon-charge-in-seconds-last-months-and-power-over-the-air">gold nanowires</a> that can be recharged 200,000 times with no loss of capacity. Scientists also have figured out that they can use the waste products in compost to generate power in “<a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41598-020-61038-7">microbial fuel cells</a>.”</p>
  <p>Researchers in the UK have even used nanogenerators to build a phone that charges its own batteries using <a href="https://www.pocket-lint.com/gadgets/news/130380-future-batteries-coming-soon-charge-in-seconds-last-months-and-power-over-the-air">ambient sound</a> – including the voice of the person talking into the phone. And in a development that could redefine how we think about energy storage, the Massachusetts Institute of Technology is working with Italian sports car manufacturer Lamborghini to build an electric “supercar” that doesn’t even have a battery in the conventional sense – because it can store energy in its body panels, which are made of lightweight <a href="https://www.cnn.com/2019/11/05/cars/lamborghini-supercar-electric-supercapacitor/index.html">carbon nanotubes</a>.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1065fb398f07ff7b70c9cd15cef9166ead9c7e932.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1065fb398f07ff7b70c9cd15cef9166ead9c7e932.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1065fb398f07ff7b70c9cd15cef9166ead9c7e932.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Images of batteries on screen" src="./media_1065fb398f07ff7b70c9cd15cef9166ead9c7e932.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1958" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="getting-charged-up-about-batteries-potential">Getting charged up about batteries’ potential</h2>
  <p>Businesses and governments alike are finally recognizing the potential of being able to store power at grid scale and investing accordingly. Automotive manufacturers are setting up divisions to leverage their existing investments in electric cars into energy storage solutions for the residential and commercial market. Airplane manufacturers are experimenting with lightweight, battery-driven propulsion systems. Governments worldwide are rolling out subsidies to encourage cost-saving, industry-disrupting battery innovations. For example, a South Australia project that, in 2017, built the world’s biggest Li-ion battery installation to store wind energy power using technology from Elon Musk’s Tesla and French renewable energy company Neoen announced in late 2019 that it was expanding from 100 to <a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2019-11-19/sa-big-battery-set-to-get-even-bigger/11716784">150 megawatts</a>.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="the-circular-economy-gets-rolling">The Circular Economy Gets Rolling</h3>
        <p>Learn how circularity is building more profitable and sustainable companies.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="/resources/circular-economy-sustainable-profitability">Read story</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The battery revolution isn’t merely about charging your phone just once a week or driving your electric car 1,000 miles without plugging in. It’s about enabling a society-wide transformation with massive ramifications. Developing better ways to store energy will create new job opportunities, not just at battery manufacturers but across the economy as we retool and build out an infrastructure that relies on renewable energy sources. Less expensive, more environmentally friendly sources of power will play a vital role in the growth of circular business models that recapture and reuse resources. The power grid will have the decentralized reserves of power it needs to remain resilient even as it increases its reliance on renewable sources.</p>
  <p><a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2019/12/04/climate/climate-change-acceleration.html">Scientists say</a> the effects of human-made climate change are accelerating as we near a tipping point that tumbles us into an extremely unpleasant future – so we need to make the transition to a sustainable, post-fossil fuel world as quickly as possible. By allowing us to use power more efficiently and store it more effectively, the next generation of batteries will do more than just help smooth the inevitable turbulence of that societal shift. The energy storage systems we develop today may actually contain the future of civilization.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>core-topic/sustainable-business-operations</category>
            <category>content-type/trends-predictions</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Profit from Purpose: Elephants on the Balance Sheet]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/profit-from-purpose-elephants-on-the-balance-sheet</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/profit-from-purpose-elephants-on-the-balance-sheet</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[There's value in creating new growth models based on purpose. Global software company EPI-USE adds saving elephants from poachers into its business success.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1084088c245ea53fcf331590cae17ad011eb55e89.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1084088c245ea53fcf331590cae17ad011eb55e89.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1084088c245ea53fcf331590cae17ad011eb55e89.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Herd of elephants walking in Amboseli National Park" src="./media_1084088c245ea53fcf331590cae17ad011eb55e89.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="522">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="profit-from-purpose-elephants-on-the-balance-sheet">Profit from Purpose: Elephants on the Balance Sheet</h1>
        <p>One company’s efforts to save elephants from poachers shows the value in creating new growth models based on purpose.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>When a group of computer science professors at South Africa’s University of Pretoria started global software integrator EPI-USE in 1982, all they wanted to do was generate funding for their department by providing IT services. They did that and then some, employing more than 3,000 people in over 30 countries to date, according to EPI-USE associate partner David Allen.</p>
  <p>But company leaders weren’t satisfied. They wanted to hit the magic US$1 billion mark in revenues. To get there, they created a novel strategy: reorganize the business model around saving Africa’s dwindling elephant and rhino populations. In other words, they used purpose as a powerful motivator to drive profits.</p>
  <p>“Our wild elephant population has dropped from millions to less than half a million in the last 100 years, and South Africa’s rhinos, which represent some of the last viable wild populations in the world, are down to just a few thousand,” says Allen. “The thought that in just a few years we might not see them anymore was a powerful thing.”</p>
  <p>Other people might resign themselves to the relentless loss of wildlife or try to soothe their feelings of despair and powerlessness by writing a check. Not the leaders of EPI-USE. They took it on as a personal challenge.</p>
  <p>Africa as a whole loses four elephants an hour to poachers, and South Africa alone loses five rhinos a day. Company leaders weren’t going to let that continue happening to <em>their</em> wildlife on <em>their</em> continent. They knew that taking action would boost their profile, motivate their employees, and inspire their customers – and they knew they had the expertise and resources to make a concrete, significant difference.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_13c5242aea911193dd6c51cf5850c06db6027522f.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_13c5242aea911193dd6c51cf5850c06db6027522f.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_13c5242aea911193dd6c51cf5850c06db6027522f.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Close up of the eye of an elephant" src="./media_13c5242aea911193dd6c51cf5850c06db6027522f.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p>They understood what many other organizations are now beginning to understand: customers are increasingly aware of the environmental and human costs of traditional ways of doing business, and employees are showing a powerful desire to work for companies that make a difference in the world. At the same time, the latest technologies create efficient – and profitable – methods of conserving resources and introducing more sustainable business models. As a result, purpose is no longer a siloed PR exercise. Instead, it’s something to embed into operations as a driver of growth.</p>
  <p>So the company created an umbrella organization called Group Elephant and split itself into three parts under that umbrella. The first part is the organization’s for-profit business, comprising 11 enterprise resource planning (ERP) software, testing, engineering, and services companies.</p>
  <p>The second part is also known as ERP – for Elephants, Rhinos &#x26; People. It’s a nonprofit that runs conservation and poverty-fighting initiatives. Initiatives include an app that Allen created, ERP Air Force, which repurposes the company’s existing systems, including drones and satellite tracking tags, to monitor the whereabouts and well-being of elephants and rhinos in real time. There’s also a project that returns land privatized by the apartheid government to the communities that once owned it and then works with those communities to develop ecotourism preserves where elephants and rhinos can live safely while attracting tourist dollars.</p>
  <p>The final part is a private investment firm that funds like-minded “for good” initiatives until they can become self-sustaining and supports communities building ecotourism preserves by helping them manage their assets and the development process.</p>
  <h2 id="values-fuel-growth">Values fuel growth</h2>
  <p>Group Elephant’s for-profit businesses support the nonprofit by contributing 1% of their global revenues, free infrastructure support, and as many hours of volunteer time as employees want to give. Employees can also suggest ideas for new nonprofit projects – or turn an idea that originated on the nonprofit side into a revenue-generating product or service, as Allen has done.</p>
  <p>“I started out thinking that if one of our solutions can run a massive petroleum factory, there’s no reason it can’t run a nontraditional, conservation-related project,” he says. “Then I realized that if I was using it to track elephants, there was no reason we couldn’t use it to track valuable animals elsewhere, like racing stables, commercial game ranches, and livestock farms. So we’re going to introduce that and create a whole new for-profit market.”</p>
  <p>The company keeps its purpose front and center by reminding everyone, from top executives to interns, that their daily tasks create the revenue for the ERP project. It’s a powerful motivator – and not just for employees. The project has enticed customers to hire Group Elephant to set up and help run their own conservation initiatives.</p>
  <p>“The best way to grow your business is to get people to buy into your business, and one powerful way to do that is to get them to want to participate in your business for more than just financial gain,” Allen explains. “Our initiatives to save animals and create economic alternatives so people don’t need to poach them fascinate customers by showing them creative new uses of technology. They open new markets by inspiring new offerings for our customers. And they improve our retention and sales by giving employees a sense of purpose.”</p>
  <p>In a typical year, Group Elephant conducts 7,500 hours of elephant monitoring and moves 130 elephants and 30 rhinos from places where they were endangered by humans to wildlife preserves and other safe locations, according to Allen. It also collars some of these animals for ongoing monitoring and funds reconstructive surgery for rhinos injured by poaching attempts. Allen adds that the company has also helped turn 17,000 acres of community-owned land from low-income uses to high-income ecotourism. It leases the land from the community and involves residents in building, running, and providing services to ecolodges, where tourists can visit to see animals roaming safe and free.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c70f50e49a4710af071a6f499c67bf3b3a9e90b1.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c70f50e49a4710af071a6f499c67bf3b3a9e90b1.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1c70f50e49a4710af071a6f499c67bf3b3a9e90b1.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Female worker walks with elephant in a conservation area." src="./media_1c70f50e49a4710af071a6f499c67bf3b3a9e90b1.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="reaching-a-tipping-point">Reaching a tipping point</h2>
  <p>There have always been small businesses driven by faith, politics, or some other sense of purpose, but their patrons tended to be willing to pay more for less attractive or functional products for the sake of supporting a cause. Combining purpose with profit at scale seemed impossible, at least not without buyer sacrifice. More recently, however, a confluence of trends has shifted the conversation.</p>
  <p>In the 1970s, governments began passing regulations to better protect consumers and the environment. This inspired individuals and groups to leverage these regulations to push for the common good, leading to a flood of lawsuits in the 1980s about everything from pharmaceuticals to consumer goods.</p>
  <p>Companies began to realize that they needed to become more invested in their impact on people and the planet. They took small steps at first. In the 1990s, corporate social responsibility (CSR) programs started to become common. They tended to be low-cost, high-PR activities, such as support for local schools or participation in company-wide days of service, with little connection to business strategy.</p>
  <p>But even these small efforts, dismissed by most executives as marketing, showed business benefits. Customers and employees began paying attention to and distinguishing between companies that merely did well and those that did good. And they started giving more loyalty to companies that paid more than lip service to purpose.</p>
  <p>Today, organizations are starting to think about their business goals in the context of global parameters for sustainability. For example, more than 700 companies worldwide with a collective market capitalization of more than $10 trillion have <a href="https://sciencebasedtargets.org/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/SBTi-Progress-Report-2019-FINAL-v1.2.pdf">committed</a> to meeting targets for reducing their greenhouse gas emissions and proving that climate awareness and profitability can go hand in hand.</p>
  <p>It’s not that companies can’t grow without purpose. They can, and they do. It’s that purpose seems to create greater opportunities for growth as well as greater mindshare among customers.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17a3d1ae0803ac4aa530ea17721b6e4ac7217c57a.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17a3d1ae0803ac4aa530ea17721b6e4ac7217c57a.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_17a3d1ae0803ac4aa530ea17721b6e4ac7217c57a.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Lady Justice - holding the scale of justice" src="./media_17a3d1ae0803ac4aa530ea17721b6e4ac7217c57a.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p>Researchers at the Center for Sustainable Business at New York University’s Stern School of Business recently <a href="https://sustainability.hapres.com/UpLoad/PdfFile/JSR_1204.pdf">reported</a> that “sustainability-marketed” consumer packaged goods (CPG) are outperforming equivalent conventional products. They calculated that the market share of products with sustainability messaging on their packaging grew from 14% in 2013 to 17% in 2018, and that these products accounted for approximately half the growth in overall CPG sales in that time. What’s more, they found that products with third-party certification of sustainability on the packaging significantly outperformed products with sustainability messaging but no third-party certification.</p>
  <p>Businesses are also finding value in creating new growth models based on purpose. This may mean creating better products that also happen to be more sustainable, like the Adidas x Parley <a href="https://www.adidas.com/us/parley">line</a> of high-performance running shoes and sportswear made from recycled plastic waste recovered from coastlines and beaches.</p>
  <p>It may also mean cutting costs by demanding that partners take less resource-intensive approaches to manufacturing, packaging, and shipping.</p>
  <p>Decades of research indicate that motivated employees are more productive, more satisfied with their work, and more likely to remain at their jobs. Companies with purpose have an additional tool by which to motivate them. In fact, international market research firm Atomik Research has found that employees who are happiest in their current jobs <a href="https://cdn.wrike.com/ebook/2019_US_Happiness_Index_Compensation.pdf">say</a> “meaningful work” is the reason why.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sustainability-questions-and-answers">21+ Sustainability Questions and Answers</h3>
        <p>Questions about embedding sustainability into your operations? We have answers.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="/blogs/future-of-corporate-environmental-sustainability">Learn more</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Finally, investors are beginning to take an interest in the potential of companies that have the long-term literal health of the market in mind. In the United States alone, socially responsible investing hit $12 trillion in assets in 2018, a 38% increase from 2016, according to The Forum for Sustainable and Responsible Investment (US SIF), which <a href="https://www.ussif.org/store_product.asp?prodid=40">surveys</a> socially responsible investing trends every two years. Worldwide, global sustainable investment assets reached $30.7 trillion, a 34% increase in two years.</p>
  <p>Investors are ensuring that their money yields return by exerting their influence at the board level. Half of the Standard &#x26; Poor’s (S&#x26;P) 500 companies now <a href="https://www.mdpi.com/2071-1050/11/12/3421/pdf">link</a> top executives’ compensation to CSR goals. Companies that adopt this “CSR contracting” see their value <a href="https://www.bu.edu/questrom-magazine/spring-2019/flammer-csr-ceo-pay/">increase</a> 3% in the ensuing five years, reduce their greenhouse gas emissions by 9%, and are more likely to invest in research and development (R&#x26;D) for innovative green technologies.</p>
  <p>In short, businesses are confronting an uncomfortable truth: They can’t serve markets if consumers in those markets are at risk. United Nations (UN) Secretary-General António Guterres <a href="https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2019/oct/03/climate-action-un-antonio-guterres">warned</a> in October 2019, “Science tells us that on our current path, we face at least 3C of global heating by the end of the century. I will not be there, but my granddaughters will. I refuse to be an accomplice in the destruction of their one and only home.” Meanwhile, the UN Office for the Coordination of Humanitarian Affairs <a href="https://reliefweb.int/report/world/global-humanitarian-overview-2020-enarfrzh">says</a> that in 2020, nearly 168 million people – one of every 45 people in the world – will need humanitarian help and protection, and if current trends in conflict, disease, and natural disaster continue, that number could top 200 million within two years. The need for enlightened self-interest has never been greater.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14f9af450b2b5d385cd4f132707a09973b5a43601.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14f9af450b2b5d385cd4f132707a09973b5a43601.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_14f9af450b2b5d385cd4f132707a09973b5a43601.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Businessman using virtual visual screen with smart phone" src="./media_14f9af450b2b5d385cd4f132707a09973b5a43601.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="measuring-the-path-to-purpose">Measuring the path to purpose</h2>
  <p>It’s difficult to identify the key components of a purposeful organization because as of now, there’s no centralized or consistent movement across companies or industries to support purpose. One move in that direction could be the World Economic Forum’s proposed <a href="http://www3.weforum.org/docs/WEF_IBC_ESG_Metrics_Discussion_Paper.pdf">framework</a> for businesses to assess their long‑term sustainability, which melds traditional financial metrics with other criteria, such as environmental, social, and governance (ESG) considerations, gender equity, fair compensation, and supply chain transparency. The proposal includes four “pillars” of metrics – principles of governance, planet, people, and prosperity – as well as core metrics and disclosures in areas ranging from the consumption of fresh water in water-stressed areas to the risk of child labor or slavery in a company’s supply chain.</p>
  <p>Until the world adopts a global standard, though, we need to look for other markers to indicate progress toward purpose. One broad indicator is technology-driven transparency throughout the product lifecycle. Digital tools that increase transparency in the value chain make it easier to track and trace internal operations and those of supplier networks to discover where components of different products are coming from and who’s making and handling them. This allows companies to assure stakeholders that, for example, products are made without additives or that the people at various points in the supply chain are paid fairly or that materials are being sourced sustainably.</p>
  <p>Any company can integrate making a difference into business strategy and leverage technology to create new, purpose-driven business models, measure efforts, and demonstrate results.</p>
  <p>Walmart, for example, issues an annual ESG report detailing its progress in reducing waste, lowering greenhouse gas emissions, creating jobs, and evaluating suppliers against a detailed sustainability scorecard.</p>
  <p>This is in line with the broader trend toward <a href="https://integratedreporting.org/">integrated reporting,</a> which links a company’s value creation over time with both financial and non-financial indicators. It’s also reflected in the rise of <a href="https://www.bcorporation.net/">Certified B Corporations,</a> which embed purpose into their bylaws alongside fiduciary responsibilities. For these companies, doing the right thing is simply part of the daily work of running a company.</p>
  <p>Another indicator of purpose is a move toward sustainable and circular design, which reduces waste and pollution by making it easy to upgrade, refurbish, and recycle products. For example, automaker Renault is redesigning its cars to be more easily taken apart. This supports a thriving market for certified rebuilt or second-hand Renault parts while keeping recyclable materials like copper, aluminum, and textiles out of landfills.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_106474a472144f30c20b8e80f7784d41cf85d3c13.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_106474a472144f30c20b8e80f7784d41cf85d3c13.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_106474a472144f30c20b8e80f7784d41cf85d3c13.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Close-up of an elephant trunk." src="./media_106474a472144f30c20b8e80f7784d41cf85d3c13.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="digital-on-purpose">Digital on purpose</h2>
  <p>Customers, employees, and investors are demanding profitable purpose. Digital transformation is enabling it. By reducing the expense and broadening the possibilities for acting in a responsible manner, digitalization is helping companies find a path to profitable purpose. Here are some ways to do it:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Digitalization enables companies to collect and present data, including non-financial data about social and environmental impact, to show customers and investors how they’re working to bring about positive change.</li>
    <li>Data also marks progress in the pursuit of purposeful goals.</li>
    <li>Digitalization helps companies work more effectively at scale for higher performance with less waste.</li>
    <li>Sensors, analytics, and other Internet of Things tools give organizations low-cost eyes and ears to monitor purpose-focused compliance in their value chains and communicate with people and devices for fast adaptation in changing environments.</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="the-purpose-of-purpose">The purpose of purpose</h2>
  <p>Purpose isn’t limited to specific industries, demographics, or product lines. Any company can integrate making a difference into business strategy and leverage technology to create new purpose-driven business models, measure efforts, and demonstrate results. It also doesn’t have to be as flashy as a new business model. The right planning and the right technology can bring sustainable improvements to fundamental business processes like procurement or sales – efforts that can fuel a greater purpose as much as a new product or service can. It also should not be viewed as charitable giving. Purpose is about finding new core business value while solving global challenges.</p>
  <p>What matters is your company’s ability to demonstrate that it’s actively working to create new solutions to old problems, like the poverty and lack of opportunity that drive people to poach Africa’s precious pachyderms. In the process, your pursuit of purpose will earn you not just revenues but also respect and loyalty from stakeholders of all kinds.</p>
  <p>For EPI-USE’s Allen, the elephants and rhinos are symbolic of a new definition of business success, one that makes going to the office each morning that much easier. “It definitely keeps up our enthusiasm and energy as we chase that $1 billion revenue goal,” Allen says. “I’m happier working with people I like and respect and who have a real sense of social responsibility, and I can tell that our clients feel the same. But also, for an hour every day, I can be on the phone with a ranger who tells me how my elephants are doing, and I can open up my app to see where they are, using the technology I work with the rest of my day. And that’s just plain old nice.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="explore-esg-reporting">Explore ESG reporting</h3>
        <p>Learn how companies are using data to manage their sustainability efforts.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/sustainability/social-responsibility.html">Learn more</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>core-topic/sustainable-business-operations</category>
            <category>content-type/business-case</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Blockchain’s Energy Crisis]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/blockchains-energy-crisis</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/blockchains-energy-crisis</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Blockchain is an energy hog, but companies can reduce blockchain power consumption with renewable sources, energy-efficient equipment, and AI.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1be1a3fa484376fc5f6f1cd26157ffc1dcfad6842.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1be1a3fa484376fc5f6f1cd26157ffc1dcfad6842.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1be1a3fa484376fc5f6f1cd26157ffc1dcfad6842.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Futuristic-looking server room" src="./media_1be1a3fa484376fc5f6f1cd26157ffc1dcfad6842.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1044">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="blockchains-energy-crisis">Blockchain’s Energy Crisis</h1>
        <p>Bitcoin mining uses as much electricity as a medium-sized country. But there are some easy ways to change blockchain power consumption.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>History gives us a great lens for viewing blockchain’s appetite for energy: Remember the <a href="https://www.britannica.com/topic/oil-crisis">oil crises</a> of 1973 and 1979? Though much of the industrialized West and Japan felt the shock, gasoline was in such short supply in the United States that the federal government <a href="https://www.history.com/this-day-in-history/nixon-signs-national-speed-limit-into-law">cut</a> the national speed limit to conserve it and drivers <a href="https://qz.com/1824804/coronavirus-could-lead-america-to-pass-its-biggest-climate-bill-ever/">lined up</a> for hours to fill their tanks at sky-high prices.</p>
  <p>The blow to industrial economies was profound, but it also encouraged positive changes in energy usage, from limits on lighted advertising signs to greater fuel cleanliness and efficiency requirements for cars.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="want-a-quick-overview">Want a quick overview?</h3>
        <p>Learn how blockchain is transforming to be a force for sustainability.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2022/10/02a2b8ff-477e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Access the brief</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Something similar may be happening today as people realize that technology is a power hog. Data centers and transmission networks account for about 1.5% of global energy consumption, according to the <a href="https://www.iea.org/energy-system/buildings/data-centres-and-data-transmission-networks">International Energy Agency</a> (IEA). Technology companies have become more efficient at meeting the demand for computing power and connectivity while using relatively less electricity. But as demand continues to rise, especially from the use of mobile networks, electricity usage and carbon emissions will also increase unless they are able to make additional improvements. By 2021, modest efficiency gains from data networks would still result in a 10% increase in electricity usage compared to 2018, generating around 9.9 million additional tons of carbon emissions. That’s the equivalent of driving <a href="https://www.epa.gov/energy/greenhouse-gas-equivalencies-calculator">1.9 million passenger vehicles</a> for a year.</p>
  <p>Whether we are able to avoid a crisis like the energy shocks of the 1970s will depend on technology companies’ ability to increase supplies of electricity from renewable sources, deploy energy-efficient equipment, and use <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/what-is-artificial-intelligence.html">artificial intelligence (AI)</a> to manage energy usage as the IEA recommends.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_185578f3393e8c1a4384acb02a4fb6739de334a21.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_185578f3393e8c1a4384acb02a4fb6739de334a21.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_185578f3393e8c1a4384acb02a4fb6739de334a21.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Motion-blurred abstract people walking to the airport terminal" src="./media_185578f3393e8c1a4384acb02a4fb6739de334a21.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="a-shocking-level-of-energy-consumption">A shocking level of energy consumption</h2>
  <p>One now well-publicized example of technology’s power problem is <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/what-is-blockchain.html">blockchain</a>. Blockchain’s use of intensive cryptographic computations to verify the existence and validity of transactions first attracted attention as the basis of cryptocurrencies like bitcoin. But now all kinds of industries are considering it as a solution to challenges of authentication, identity, and trust.</p>
  <p>There’s one big problem, though: it’s the energy consumption equivalent of Grandma’s gas-guzzling 1973 Ford LTD.</p>
  <p>What makes a blockchain work is the consensus of all the computers on its network that every transaction on the blockchain is true. The competition between computers to arrive at that consensus by solving cryptographic puzzles is known as <a href="https://www.investopedia.com/terms/b/bitcoin-mining.asp">mining</a>. And mining uses powerful, purpose-built computer chips and software, plus a reliable Internet connection and air conditioning to keep CPUs cool as they churn away 24×7 at complex calculations. All of that consumes <a href="https://digiconomist.net/bitcoin-energy-consumption">an enormous amount of electricity</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>How much energy does blockchain use?</strong></p>
  <p>So much that if miners were a country, they would rank 41st in energy consumption, almost as much as Austria.</p>
  <p>So much that mining generates as many carbon <a href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2019/06/190613104533.htm">the city of Las Vegas or Hamburg</a>.</p>
  <p>So much that a single Bitcoin transaction consumes as much energy as 100,000 Visa transactions.</p>
  <p>So much that cryptocurrency miners are setting up server farms in places with inexpensive electricity, like Iceland (which has ample geothermal power), <a href="https://www.iea.org/commentaries/bitcoin-energy-use-mined-the-gap">rural China</a> (which has underused hydroelectric power plants), and small-town America, putting a burden on their electrical infrastructure.</p>
  <p>Indeed, one upstate New York town attracted so much mining activity that it briefly <a href="https://www.wamc.org/post/plattsburgh-ends-cryptocurrency-moratorium">imposed</a> a moratorium on new mining operations to stop them from literally using up the town’s electricity supply.</p>
  <p>Some argue that estimates of blockchain’s power consumption are <a href="https://www.ccn.com/bitcoin-mining-key-stat-exposes-ridiculous-energy-consumption-fud/">overblown</a>, but even if that’s true, it’s still far from energy efficient. In fact, it poses an awkward conundrum: this technology was invented to make transactions more efficient is itself profoundly wasteful.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b687bbae1f39367377000b5d9e0a727b83efbf20.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b687bbae1f39367377000b5d9e0a727b83efbf20.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1b687bbae1f39367377000b5d9e0a727b83efbf20.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Multiple smokestacks emitting pollution." src="./media_1b687bbae1f39367377000b5d9e0a727b83efbf20.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="why-taking-risks-on-new-tech-pays-off">Why Taking Risks on New Tech Pays Off</h3>
        <p>Find out what early technology adopters have learned about sustainability.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="/resources/what-early-adopters-know-technology-sustainability-profitability">Read story</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="current-thinking-about-solutions">Current thinking about solutions</h2>
  <p>The problem may already be in the process of solving itself. First, there is the never-ending march forward in chip speed and efficiency, which delivers more compute power using less electrical power. Specialization helps, too. For example, Intel has filed a <a href="https://www.investopedia.com/news/intel-applies-patent-crypto-mining-chip/">patent</a> for a system-on-a-chip specifically optimized to use less space and energy for mining, joining similar initiatives from Samsung, Nvidia, and AMD as well as a proprietary chip from Bitmain, the world’s largest Bitcoin miner.</p>
  <p>At the same time, the evolving blockchain industry is looking at less power-ravenous approaches to authenticating transactions. The original approach, <a href="https://www.ledger.com/academy/blockchain/what-is-proof-of-work">proof of work</a>, expends massive amounts of energy as miners compete to demonstrate that each transaction can be trusted.</p>
  <p>Another alternative is <a href="https://finance.yahoo.com/news/does-proof-authority-algorithm-090006261.html">proof of authority</a>, which relies on a small but diverse number of known validators on a blockchain network who are rewarded for their work with transaction fees that aren’t related to the type or value of the transaction. Rules would be established to govern who becomes a validator and how they validate transactions.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1cae76f4c078676fba5aaccea334552e033963819.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1cae76f4c078676fba5aaccea334552e033963819.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1cae76f4c078676fba5aaccea334552e033963819.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Solar panels in an urban center on a sunny day." src="./media_1cae76f4c078676fba5aaccea334552e033963819.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p>Even if none of these alternatives pan out, it’s still possible that blockchain’s impact on carbon emissions will drastically decline over time. The mining computers that calculate and maintain blockchains can be located anywhere in the world, but because of their prodigious use of electricity, they’re increasingly set up where the cheapest power is available.</p>
  <p>That could well drive energy production to be more widely distributed and decentralized, from hydroelectric plants on remote rivers to acres of solar panels in deserts. And that, in turn, could spur investment in new renewable energy sources and power storage for an abundance of cleaner, less expensive electricity.</p>
  <p>On top of all this, blockchain could also make the <a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC6891730/">power grid</a> itself smarter, more efficient, and greener. Once we can generate low-carbon energy at scale, with devices enabled for the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/what-is-iot.html">Internet of Things</a> measuring production and demand in real time, we’ll be able to use blockchain to make sure power gets from where it’s produced to where it’s needed without human supervision. And that will further ensure that blockchain (and technology in general) becomes a high-efficiency engine for our economy instead of contributing to a global environmental crash and burn.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>core-topic/sustainable-business-operations</category>
            <category>content-type/trends-predictions</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Future of Feeding the World]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/the-future-of-feeding-the-world</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/the-future-of-feeding-the-world</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Digital transformations in the global food ecosystem are here to stay. Read about the potential of technology in agriculture.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>core-topic/sustainable-business-operations</category>
            <category>content-type/trends-predictions</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Capacity Capture: A New Approach to Discovering Business Value]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/research/capacity-capture-a-new-approach-to-discovering-business-value</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/research/capacity-capture-a-new-approach-to-discovering-business-value</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Untapped value is hiding in plain sight throughout every organization. The key is knowing where and how to find it.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17054abb901ef1c7e765318e7ca9e4b7c5d6442de.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17054abb901ef1c7e765318e7ca9e4b7c5d6442de.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_17054abb901ef1c7e765318e7ca9e4b7c5d6442de.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Graphic of a woman head with pie chart" src="./media_17054abb901ef1c7e765318e7ca9e4b7c5d6442de.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1044">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="capacity-capture-a-new-approach-to-discovering-business-value">Capacity Capture: A New Approach to Discovering Business Value</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Untapped value is hiding in plain sight throughout every organization. The key is knowing how to find it.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><strong>The rooftop of a big-box store is:</strong></p>
  <ol>
    <li>A flat expanse of hundreds of square feet exposed to the weather</li>
    <li>A great, if not perfect, way to protect what’s inside from that weather</li>
    <li>A power source for the building, and maybe for the neighbors, too</li>
  </ol>
  <p>If you’re the Ingka Group, which owns IKEA, the answer is “all of the above.” As part of its commitment to use only renewable energy by 2020, the Ingka Group installed 900,000 solar modules on the roofs of IKEA stores and warehouses around the world, turning what would otherwise be vacant space into a literal powerhouse. These solar installations generated 155 GWh of electricity in 2018, enough to supply nearly 5% of IKEA’s global energy needs. In fact, according to Karol Gobczyński, the Ingka Group’s head of climate and energy, some locations are generating enough solar power to sell some back to the local electrical grid.</p>
  <p>What holds companies back from coming up with breakthroughs like this in a systematic, repeatable way?</p>
  <p>A failure of perspective.</p>
  <p>Methodologies like Six Sigma and technologies like sharing platforms and AI-driven analytics are powerful tools to uncover new opportunities, but they are held back by outdated thinking. If they weren’t, digital transformations wouldn’t fail up to 80% of the time, and they’d meet or exceed expectations more than just 5% of the time. To be truly transformative – in other words, to get more than just incremental returns on investment – companies need to combine technology with a new way of thinking about what value is and where to find it.</p>
  <p>Massive value is lying fallow in excess resources, like unused real estate, over-purchased software, and employees who aren’t being used to their full potential (people themselves are never excess). It’s concealed in underused resources, like vehicles that are on the road only a few hours a day, computing cycles that whir away pointlessly at night, and employees with untapped skills. It’s hiding in things that, according to current wisdom, have no value whatsoever, like production waste, “<a href="https://www.computerworld.com/article/3070475/5-things-you-need-to-know-about-data-exhaust.html">data exhaust</a>,” and people who move on to other employers.</p>
  <p>But waiting for the hidden value in these resources to reveal itself practically guarantees that it will remain unseen. Companies need to adopt a new mindset for systematically seeking out resources so they can extract more value from existing investments and encourage the development of potential new products, services, and business models. In other words, they need a capacity capture mindset.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10df3ef19246ff30e16f4790161c7b2adfea6c866.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10df3ef19246ff30e16f4790161c7b2adfea6c866.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_10df3ef19246ff30e16f4790161c7b2adfea6c866.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="White pencil draws dotted lines over an abstract purple cube pattern." src="./media_10df3ef19246ff30e16f4790161c7b2adfea6c866.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="broadening-the-search-for-value">Broadening the search for value</h2>
  <p>The traditional business approach assumes that resources are too specialized to be reused or deployed in new ways. The capacity capture mindset, on the other hand, starts with the assumption that resources are ubiquitous and infinite, because anything can be a resource, and any resource has capacity for value beyond its primary or original purpose.</p>
  <p>Capacity capture is about actively identifying resources that are underused, wasted, or discarded and coming up with ways to recapture, use, sell, or otherwise monetize them. Consider how much money real estate companies invest in building and maintaining parking lots in office parks, even though the parking spaces sit empty for 12 or more hours a day. In Europe, a technology platform that lets long-haul truck drivers reserve those spots overnight has created a new income stream for the office parks. At the same time, it gives drivers safer places to sleep than highway shoulders and on-ramps, which protects the drivers, their cargo, and everyone else on the road.</p>
  <p>Capacity capture allows organizations to discover new areas of innovation that end up delivering bigger benefits than just resource efficiency. Imagine a factory that actively looks for ways to generate more heat during production because it can make more money by selling or repurposing that heat than it can save by minimizing it. In the Danish town of Kalundborg, for example, <a href="https://we-economy.net/case-stories/kalundborg-symbiosis.html">13 different companies in the local industrial park</a> use an elaborate system of pipelines to exchange materials and energy. Sludge, steam, and fly ash that are waste for some become valuable input for others, lowering the cost of energy and raw materials for everyone while reducing the amount and expense of waste disposal.</p>
  <p>Using the capacity capture mindset, companies can also find ways to make their products more effective by capturing and using what would otherwise be considered waste. For example, MIT and Stanford scientists have invented a way to expand the capacity of rechargeable batteries by warming them while they’re first charging. A battery manufacturer could theoretically do this by capturing waste heat from the manufacturing process and then selling these higher-capacity batteries at a premium. Kohler, the tile company, is already doing something along these lines by <a href="https://www.greenbiz.com/article/how-kohler-turned-production-waste-new-tile-line">repurposing waste</a> from its tile manufacturing process, including broken tiles, cast iron slag, and leftover glazes, and using them to create a new line of designer tile.</p>
  <p>The capacity capture mindset also encourages a deeper examination of experience as a resource. Just look at the Dutch city of Rotterdam, home to Europe’s largest industrial port and, like most of the Netherlands, below sea level. Rotterdam has tapped its underused wealth of institutional expertise in preventing and managing flooding to launch a <a href="https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2017/06/15/world/europe/climate-change-rotterdam.html">consulting business</a>. In guiding other coastal cities on how to cope with rising sea waters and worsening storms in the face of climate change, the city collects extra funding for the city budget, which in turn supports further innovations in flood-resistant urban renewal.</p>
  <h2 id="defining-the-search-grid-body">Defining the search grid body</h2>
  <p>The first step to capturing capacity is to understand what capacity is and where it might be found.</p>
  <h3 id="types-of-assets">Types of assets</h3>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Physical assets</strong> are tangible objects of any kind, from facilities and heavy equipment to lighting and office supplies.</li>
    <li><strong>Digital assets</strong> include network infrastructure, software, data and metadata, and bandwidth.</li>
    <li><strong>Human assets</strong> are people and their behaviors.</li>
  </ul>
  <h3 id="areas-of-untapped-capacity">Areas of untapped capacity</h3>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Unwanted assets</strong> are assets that are created or accumulated unintentionally or incidentally as a side effect or byproduct of another process.</li>
    <li><strong>Excess assets</strong> are produced or gathered intentionally but become surplus either because there are too many of them or because the process that produced or gathered them is no longer in use.</li>
    <li><strong>Underused assets</strong> are created intentionally and are in use but not to their full potential.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>The following framework gives examples of these asset types and capacities and the questions a company might ask itself to discover them:</p>
  <div class="table">
    <div>
      <div>Asset Type</div>
      <div>Unwanted</div>
      <div>Excess</div>
      <div>Underused</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>Physical</div>
      <div>What is created unintentionally as a side effect and then discarded? Examples include trash, offcuts, steam, and heat.</div>
      <div>What is produced intentionally but becomes surplus? Examples include products, energy, and materials.</div>
      <div>What kinds of existing assets go unused? Examples include space, vehicles, and equipment.</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>Digital</div>
      <div>What is collected incidentally and rarely used or analyzed? Examples include sensor readings, metadata, and data exhaust.</div>
      <div>What is developed or gathered intentionally but rarely used? Examples include software functionality, infrastructure, and legacy data.</div>
      <div>What kinds of existing storage and channels go unused? Examples include computing cycles, bandwidth, and repositories.</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>Human</div>
      <div>Where are people or their behaviors seen as undesirable? Examples include former employees and prohibited behaviors.</div>
      <div>Where do you gather people or encourage behaviors but then not use them fully? Examples include job roles, training, and passion.</div>
      <div>How can you tap into unrecognized skills and capabilities? Examples include surveying employees for unused skills, matching personal goals with needed capabilities, and partnering employees with others.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The boundaries between these different types of assets can be porous. For example, some physical assets also have characteristics of digital assets, as with autonomous vehicles. Some digital assets, such as servers and storage media, may be thought of as physical assets. What’s more, physical and digital assets often enhance human assets, a convergence that will accelerate as technologies evolve.</p>
  <p>As a result, many assets will overlap several categories, and the process of considering where they might fit can generate further possibilities.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_138fbbaff6bf4f7733bb57de5587e8ce9f5947c9d.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_138fbbaff6bf4f7733bb57de5587e8ce9f5947c9d.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_138fbbaff6bf4f7733bb57de5587e8ce9f5947c9d.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Illustration of an ice cream cone with a network of pipes running in the background." src="./media_138fbbaff6bf4f7733bb57de5587e8ce9f5947c9d.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="categories-of-capacity-capture-in-action">Categories of capacity capture in action</h2>
  <p>Each square of the capacity capture grid represents myriad possibilities for finding or creating more value. The following examples describe just a few opportunities that companies in a range of industries have uncovered.</p>
  <h3 id="physical-assets">Physical assets</h3>
  <p><strong>Unwanted.</strong> The UK’s <a href="https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2019/jun/15/wensleydale-cheese-waste-heat-4000-homes-biogas">Wensleydale Creamery</a> works with a nearby bioenergy plant to turn the waste whey from its world-famous cheese into enough renewable biogas to heat 4,000 homes in the Yorkshire Dales. The bioenergy plant, which also processes leftovers from a nearby ice cream factory, pumps the natural gas from food waste back into the gas grid. What remains becomes fertilizer for local farmland.</p>
  <p><strong>Excess.</strong> Several European utility companies are working with automakers Nissan and Mitsubishi to develop services that let people sell the <a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-electric-vehicles-charging-grid-analy/european-power-firms-aim-to-harness-electric-car-batteries-idUSKCN1PF0IT">energy stored in their electric vehicle</a> (EV) batteries back to the grid. Today, the return on the extra juice is limited, but as batteries continue their Moore’s Law-like improvement in cost and power, people who charge their EV batteries during off-peak times and sell power back to the grid during peak times could end up charging their cars for free – or even making a profit.</p>
  <p><strong>Underused.</strong> As early as 2012, Coca-Cola began partnering with pharmaceutical companies to deliver vaccines in developing countries using the existing <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/skollworldforum/2013/04/08/soda-pop-and-vaccines-leveraging-consumer-supply-chains-to-promote-public-health-and-economic-uplift/">refrigerated trucks and supply chain know-how</a> that have made its products available around the world. By fitting medical perishables into the empty space in trucks that deliver soft drinks, the company reduced vaccine delivery times and increased the number of people getting vaccinated while boosting its brand reputation.</p>
  <h3 id="digital-assets">Digital assets</h3>
  <p><strong>Unwanted.</strong> Companies of all types are offering data they collect that is incidental to their primary business models to other organizations who mine it for value. For example, health insurer UnitedHealth Group provides aggregated data from its claim forms to drug companies seeking insight into how their products are being used. This secondary income stream has been so successful that the resulting spinoff, Optum, has been more <a href="https://www.healthcarefinancenews.com/news/secret-weapon-unitedhealths-optum-business-laying-waste-old-notions-about-how-payers-make-money">profitable and faster-growing</a> than UnitedHealth itself.</p>
  <p><strong>Excess.</strong> As more streetlights are fitted with LED bulbs to reduce costs and save energy, it turns out that they can do more than their centuries-old roles of guiding travelers and making pedestrians safer. Visible light communication, or <a href="https://www.networkworld.com/article/3214670/how-wi-fi-could-get-a-boost-from-li-fi.html">Li-Fi</a>, transmits data by switching individual LED bulbs on and off at nanosecond speeds, much faster than the human eye can detect, so that the lights can still do their primary jobs while transmitting data at rates <a href="https://www.lifi-centre.com/about-li-fi/applications/">1,000 times faster</a> than traditional Wi-Fi over short distances.</p>
  <p><strong>Underused.</strong> Amazon famously created a significant new business model, Amazon Web Services, by renting out unused capacity on its flexible computing infrastructure. It’s now captured that capacity for a second time by creating a <a href="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSEC2/latest/UserGuide/ri-market-general.html">marketplace</a> where it charges a 12% service fee to customers who are reselling their reserved but unused cloud instances.</p>
  <h3 id="human-assets">Human assets</h3>
  <p>When we talk about unwanted or excess human assets, we’re talking about roles, skills, and behaviors, not the people themselves. All people are valuable; indeed, they’re the only constant resource companies have, and digital and physical resources have no value without them. People can change their value throughout their lives through ongoing learning and development. It’s time to jettison the idea that someone stops being valuable when the workplace changes and instead quantify their value based on what they’re capable of doing and what they’re willing to do to keep pace with change.</p>
  <p><strong>Unwanted.</strong> Just a few years ago, employees could be disciplined or even fired for using their smartphone at a corporate event. At best, it was considered rude, and at worst, it was viewed as a potential breach of company security. Today, organizations actively encourage employees to brandish their phones to promote conference panels and other events on social media in real time.</p>
  <p><strong>Excess.</strong> Many companies make decisions about whether to lay off high-salary employees to cut costs by looking at their roles in isolation, without considering how those employees enhance the value of the people they work for and with. Finding a way to capture and quantify the value of an employee’s contribution to the organization will encourage companies to consider whether letting someone go will cost the company more than it saves. Similarly, companies can reduce retirement-driven brain drain by inviting retiring employees to become “business angels” who coach new teams. They could even partner with similar companies in a consortium that captures the untapped value of people who just missed being hired by sharing these candidates with and recommending them to each other.</p>
  <p><strong>Underused.</strong> The Hilton Worldwide hotel chain keeps a record of every employee’s specific skills, such as language ability and local connections, even if those skills aren’t immediately relevant or used in the employee’s current role. That gives the company fast access to internal people when they are most needed. For example, if the company plans to open a hotel in a new location it can easily search for an employee who is a native speaker of the language and has connections in that market.</p>
</div>
<div>
  <h3 id="dive-beneath-the-buzzwords">Dive beneath the buzzwords</h3>
  <p>Find profitable steps forward for manufacturers, from sustainability to security to supply chain.</p>
  <p><a href="/blogs/building-the-future-factory-a-special-report">Overview: Building the Future Factory</a></p>
  <p>Factory</p>
  <ul>
    <li><a href="/blogs/the-sustainable-factory-of-the-future">The Sustainable Factory of the Future</a></li>
    <li><a href="/resources/profitable-purpose-the-future-of-business-sustainability">Profitable Purpose: The Future of Business Sustainability</a></li>
    <li><a href="/resources/production-logistics-and-the-new-ot">Production Logistics and the New OT</a></li>
    <li><a href="/resources/how-industry-4-0-factories-can-still-embrace-the-past">Retrofitting: How Industry 4.0 Factories Can Still Embrace the Past</a></li>
    <li><a href="/blogs/twelve-security-issues-for-evolving-factories">12 Security Issues to Address as Your Factories Evolve</a></li>
  </ul>
  <p>The workforce</p>
  <ul>
    <li><a href="/resources/advanced-manufacturing-skills-workers-will-need">Advanced Manufacturing Skills Workers Will Need</a></li>
    <li><a href="/resources/hunting-for-advanced-manufacturing-talent-four-moves">Four Steps for Hunting for Advanced Manufacturing Talent</a></li>
  </ul>
  <p>The supply chain and business networks</p>
  <ul>
    <li><a href="/resources/contract-manufacturing-supply-chains-blind-spot">Contract Manufacturing: Supply Chains’ Blind Spot</a></li>
    <li><a href="/resources/supply-chain-innovation-whats-next">Supply Chain Innovation: What’s Next?</a></li>
    <li><a href="/blogs/landscape-view-into-value-chain-relationships">A Landscape View into Value Chain Relationships</a></li>
  </ul>
  <p>The full manufacturing lifecycle</p>
  <ul>
    <li><a href="/resources/circular-path-to-sustainability-for-manufacturers">A Circular Path to Sustainability for Manufacturers</a></li>
  </ul>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>Style</div>
      <div>Additional Reading</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
<div>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18d2a75433f02b28e108c016068e09d640bc47e99.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18d2a75433f02b28e108c016068e09d640bc47e99.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_18d2a75433f02b28e108c016068e09d640bc47e99.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Illustration of a couple harnessing energy from a storm cloud." src="./media_18d2a75433f02b28e108c016068e09d640bc47e99.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="identifying-capacity">Identifying capacity</h2>
  <p>Capacity capture begins with a deliberate focus on expanding your thinking about where you might find value beyond increasing efficiency and reducing waste, as well as suspending any disbelief about what constitutes a resource or how resources can or should be used. As you use the above grid to identify possible resources, ask other people in your organization, in every department and at every level, to do the same. Insight can come from anyone, and the people who are closest to the resources are the ones most likely to recognize the value in them.</p>
  <p>Once you’ve developed a list of potential resources, don’t get bogged down in trying to evaluate them all at once or even in groups. Focus on each one with the presumption that it’s inherently valuable and that your job is to determine its value.</p>
  <p>As you assess each potential resource, consider how you might extract the value:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Reuse.</strong> How could it benefit another part of your organization? Extend and combine. What other things could you do with this resource, alone or combined with another resource?</li>
    <li><strong>Spin off.</strong> What could you do with this resource if you removed it from its current context to stand alone?</li>
    <li><strong>Maximize.</strong> How could you create and use even more of this resource?</li>
    <li><strong>Sell.</strong> Under what circumstances might someone else value this resource enough to buy it from your organization?</li>
    <li><strong>Recycle.</strong> How could another organization use this resource when you’re done with it?</li>
    <li><strong>Donate.</strong> Could you create nonmonetary value, and save the cost of disposal, by giving this resource away?</li>
  </ul>
  <p>It isn’t as odd as it may seem to take this approach to human assets as well as physical or digital assets. Your company already knows how to reuse people’s skills by shifting them to other departments and maximize them by providing more training. It could just as easily spin off a group of especially unconventional thinkers into a skunkworks or “donate them” by encouraging them to share their skills with volunteer organizations.</p>
  <p>This process is intended to generate ideas through rapid iteration and participation from a variety of people across the organization. There are no wrong answers, only creative possibilities.</p>
  <p>As with other transformations, it makes sense to begin experimenting with capacity capture in one small, distinct area as a proof of concept. Setting up new business models – especially outside of a company’s existing industry – used to be a huge hurdle, but emerging technologies and technology-enabled platforms (think Airbnb, Lyft, and Spotify) make it more affordable to experiment and test the market. A small-scale, iterative approach that keeps the cost of entry low lets you continually spin up new opportunities instead of passing on something promising because you lack the visibility and depth of understanding about its potential.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e1aaf8639385b658f7b16e12aba276c35c5f2b5a.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e1aaf8639385b658f7b16e12aba276c35c5f2b5a.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1e1aaf8639385b658f7b16e12aba276c35c5f2b5a.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Illustration of a person peering into a telescope and seeing something valuable on the other side." src="./media_1e1aaf8639385b658f7b16e12aba276c35c5f2b5a.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="capacity-capture-as-strategic-imperative">Capacity capture as strategic imperative</h2>
  <p>It’s critical to note that while technology enables capacity capture, the concept isn’t technology driven. Rather, it’s a mindset of looking for opportunities, like selling data gathered through tracking or creating platforms that connect customers with each other, and then choosing tools based on the opportunities that arise.</p>
  <p>Another key aspect of the capacity capture mindset is that you aren’t trapped (or protected) by your existing business model or industry. If your explorations uncover a newfound opportunity that you don’t want to ignore but also don’t want to make your primary focus, you may decide to pursue it through a joint venture with an existing partner, a company you wouldn’t ordinarily have a reason to do business with, or even a competitor.</p>
  <p>As business shifts to a capacity mindset, it could make sense to carve out a top management role – maybe even a chief capacity officer position – with ultimate responsibility for identifying capacity throughout the organization and driving innovative projects to capture it for business benefit.</p>
  <p>This role would require a knowledge of where end-to-end processes are and what they need, credibility with colleagues across functions, and the ability to think creatively. A business leader with established ideas about the <em>right</em> way to run an organization may not be as good a fit for the role as someone with talent and enthusiasm for spotting unused or overlooked resources in their own, and other, departments.</p>
  <p>A company fortunate to have multiple people with the necessary skills may decide to create a capacity capture team. An organization that develops expertise in capacity capture may even develop or spin off a consultancy that helps other businesses shift their own thinking around resources, as the city of Rotterdam did with its water containment knowledge. That is itself an opportunity to capture underused human capacity.</p>
  <p>Researchers at the Global Footprint network say the human race now consumes renewable resources at <a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/we-just-used-up-all-of-earth-s-resources-for-the-year-and-it-s-only-july">almost twice the rate</a> the earth can replenish them. Capacity capture provides an alternative to working within the limitations of what we perceive as our available resources. It lets us question our perceptions – and therefore our limitations – about what we have to work with in the first place.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div data-valign="middle">Featured Artist <a href="http://www.kata-illustration.com/">Kotryna Zukauskaite</a></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/business-transformation</category>
            <category>core-topic/sustainable-business-operations</category>
            <category>industry/consumer-goods-cpg</category>
            <category>content-type/original-research</category>
            <category>stage/acquisition</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>