<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/sap-csr/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA["Source from Ukraine" Initiative: The S Stands for Solidarity]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/source-from-ukraine-initiative-s-for-solidarity</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/source-from-ukraine-initiative-s-for-solidarity</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The "Source from Ukraine" initiative aims to activate procurement spend to support Ukrainian suppliers in rebuilding their businesses.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/csr</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/ukraine</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP's “Source from Ukraine” Initiative Boosts Business and Social Responsibility]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/source-from-ukraine-initiative-boosts-business-social-responsibility</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/source-from-ukraine-initiative-boosts-business-social-responsibility</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The "Source from Ukraine" initiative aims to activate procurement spend to support Ukrainian suppliers in rebuilding their businesses.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1be90b8393bfeb6a3a3bdc9a317fa62a7be1e9acb.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1be90b8393bfeb6a3a3bdc9a317fa62a7be1e9acb.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1be90b8393bfeb6a3a3bdc9a317fa62a7be1e9acb.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP’s “Source from Ukraine” Initiative Boosts Business and Social Responsibility" src="./media_1be90b8393bfeb6a3a3bdc9a317fa62a7be1e9acb.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="saps-source-from-ukraine-initiative-boosts-business-and-social-responsibility">SAP’s “Source from Ukraine” Initiative Boosts Business and Social Responsibility</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>SAP’s “Source from Ukraine” initiative, launched in March 2023, has a clear goal: to increase spend with Ukrainian companies while also generating business benefits for SAP. This shows SAP’s deep understanding of social responsibility as an integral part of its commitment to a sustainable future.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The initiative aims to activate <a href="/topics/procurement">procurement</a> spend as a means to support Ukrainian suppliers in rebuilding their businesses. Beyond sourcing for quality goods and services, SAP has a focus on integrating ESG (environmental, social, and governance) principles into decision-making as is standard with its procurement policy.</p>
  <p>It highlights SAP’s commitment not only to sourcing products from Ukraine, but also to promoting social change.</p>
  <h2 id="built-in-sustainability">Built-In Sustainability</h2>
  <p>In implementing the initiative to attract more suppliers from Ukraine, SAP initially focused on the IT sector and conducted a rigorous selection process. So far, suppliers, including industry leaders like Softserve, Unicsoft, and Luxoft, have been selected. SAP’s commitment extends beyond services to include product areas, where notable Ukrainian companies producing innovative environmentally sustainable products have been discovered.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-is-powering-equitable-access-to-economic-opportunity-education-and-employment-and-the-circular-economy">SAP is powering equitable access to economic opportunity, education and employment, and the circular economy</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/our-values/csr.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>At SAP Spend Connect Live in Vienna, Austria, held in October 2023, Ukrainian manufacturers Rekava, Mol’far Tea, and Releaf Paper showcased their sustainable and innovative products. Rekava, for example, specializes in producing biodegradable candles made from recycled coffee grounds, while Mol’far focuses on minimalism and ethical environmental practices in tea production. Releaf Paper is the world’s first manufacturer of paper made from fallen leaves, promoting sustainable products such as paper bags. By supporting these unique Ukrainian companies, SAP is not only contributing to the economic reconstruction of the country, but also sustainability efforts.</p>
  <p>One of SAP’s tier one suppliers, ABC Premium, has taken an important step by offering Rekava candles within its purchasing catalog, available to SAP employees on the SAP Ariba Buying solution.</p>
  <h2 id="strong-alliances-for-reconstruction">Strong Alliances for Reconstruction</h2>
  <p>At the outset of the project, the NGO Impact Ukraine helped SAP connect with Ukrainian suppliers. It focuses on microfinance, procurement, and recruitment from Ukraine. The collaboration is facilitated by the voluntary engagement of professionals from the technology, healthcare, and finance sectors. With Impact Ukraine’s support, SAP and other organizations can further advance their goals regarding procurement from Ukraine.</p>
  <p>SAP’s commitment to promoting innovation, sustainability, and economic growth through partnerships with Ukrainian companies not only fulfills its aspirations for procurement with purpose, but also contributes to making the world a better place.</p>
  <h2 id="helping-the-world-run-better">Helping the World Run Better</h2>
  <p>The “Source from Ukraine” initiative builds on global efforts to integrate social enterprises and diverse suppliers into SAP purchasing opportunities. Beyond SAP’s own internal purchasing efforts, the SAP Corporate Social Responsibility (SAP CSR) team is also investing in social and sustainable procurement ecosystems alongside public, private, and social sector partners like the European Commission, Deloitte, World Economic Forum’s Global Alliance for Social Entrepreneurship, and Social Enterprise World Forum’s People and Planet First verification.</p>
  <p>Consider that US$5.3 trillion in annual commerce is transacted on <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-network.html">SAP Business Network</a>. If we can help create a small shift in procurement spend to organizations prioritizing people and planet like Releaf Paper, we could collectively increase investment in sustainable development in a way that is not possible through corporate philanthropy alone. To join our efforts, please e-mail: <a href="mailto:csr-global@sap.com?subject=Please%20Share%20More%20Collective%20Social%20Procurement%20Investments%20and%20How%20to%20Get%20Involved">csr-global@sap.com</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Elena Parker is chief revenue officer for Intelligent Spend and Business Network, MEE, at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-sap-news-delivered-to-your-inbox-once-a-week">Get the latest SAP news delivered to your inbox once a week</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/nl/sap-news-center-newsletter/index.html">Sign up today</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/csr</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/ukraine</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP CSR's eBook Celebrates a Year of Global Impact]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/sap-csr-ebook-celebrates-global-impact</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/sap-csr-ebook-celebrates-global-impact</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The impact of SAP CSR in 2023 is a testament to the power of collective action and shared vision. Read to find out how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1aa60aead41f035043e44cbfe1f53c8c65e859485.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1aa60aead41f035043e44cbfe1f53c8c65e859485.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1aa60aead41f035043e44cbfe1f53c8c65e859485.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP CSR’s eBook Celebrates a Year of Global Impact" src="./media_1aa60aead41f035043e44cbfe1f53c8c65e859485.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-csrs-ebook-celebrates-a-year-of-global-impact">SAP CSR’s eBook Celebrates a Year of Global Impact</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Reflecting on the past year, one event stands out vividly in my memory: the Social Enterprises World Forum (SEWF) in Amsterdam, the Netherlands. For those unfamiliar, imagine a global assembly where more than 1,500 entrepreneurs from 82 countries dedicated to societal and environmental missions come together. These enterprises prioritize people and the planet, reinvesting their profits to advance their respective causes. Witnessing the energy and innovation in Amsterdam was a powerful reminder of why SAP has emphasized social entrepreneurship for the second consecutive year.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>It makes me proud to think about the 676 SAP colleagues who, in 2023, participated in our pro bono consulting programs, offering their expertise to these visionary social entrepreneurs. As in previous years, this collaboration has proven mutually beneficial, with 74% of our employees reporting a positive, lasting impact on their careers. Furthermore, 96% of the supported organizations and 77% of their beneficiaries have seen significant improvements. These numbers speak volumes about the shared value of our engagement.</p>
  <p>But the 2023 SEWF wasn’t just a personal highlight; it marked the beginning of another significant milestone. We announced our investment in the <strong>Social Enterprise People and Planet First Verification</strong> with Good Market and SEWF. This initiative aims to set a global standard for recognizing organizations prioritizing social and environmental impacts. Social enterprises can now also identify themselves on SAP Business Network, the world’s largest B2B commerce platform. This breakthrough can make it easier for these businesses to explore new business-to-business opportunities while also helping SAP customers achieve their goals of being more environmentally and socially responsible. Saying it’s a win-win situation is a bit cliché, but in this case it’s actually true.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-is-powering-equitable-access-to-economic-opportunity-education-and-employment-and-the-circular-economy">SAP is powering equitable access to economic opportunity, education and employment, and the circular economy</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/our-values/csr.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Working with SEWF shows how much we believe in working together and driving towards collective impact. I’ve said it before and I’ll say it again: we can’t do this by ourselves. Working with others is the key to driving the kind of systemic change our world needs. This idea is a big part of what we stand for at SAP, and is at the heart of our corporate social responsibility (<a href="/topics/csr">CSR</a>) strategy.</p>
  <p>This idea of working together really comes to life in our collaboration with <strong>UNICEF and Generation Unlimited</strong>. In 2023 – the fourth year of our partnership – we set out to make a real difference by not just developing the skills of young people but also finding jobs in the SAP ecosystem. Launching the SAP Educate to Employ program is a big step in that direction. Helping 25 young people get jobs with SAP in each of our pilot countries – Nigeria, Kenya, South Africa, and the Philippines – might not sound like a lot, but it’s a huge deal for each of those young people. For them, it’s a gateway to a sustainable livelihood, offering them not just gainful employment but a chance to build a career, achieve financial stability, and make meaningful contributions to their communities and the broader world. It’s about unlocking their potential and enabling them to participate in the digital and green economy. By the end of the year, we saw amazing results. While more than 2,500 had already passed the aptitude test, over 1,000 young people in Africa finished our “Boost Your Career with SAP Skills” course and more than 500 got through the first big part of their training.</p>
  <p>But, what’s a year recap without some high-level numbers? Let’s dive into some impressive <strong>numbers from 2023</strong>. More than 20,000 of our SAP colleagues volunteered over 140,000 hours. Our initiatives reached over 2.8 million young people – almost half girls – and supported over 41,000 teachers. Our partner network reached 1 billion people in over 140 countries. These stats are just the tip of the iceberg, showing our big reach and impact together with our partners.</p>
  <p>Building on this, our signature partnerships with Africa Code Week, Meet and Code, and Latin Code Week have always been at the heart of our achievements. As we handed over these initiatives in 2023, we took a moment to reflect and evaluate Africa Code Week and Latin Code Week outcomes more deeply. For instance, by empowering 14.6 million participants with the education, knowledge, and ICT skills needed to participate in the digital future, <strong>Africa Code Week</strong> has increased the likelihood that beneficiaries will realize higher earnings during their working lives. Common Good Marketplace estimates that Africa Code Week catalyzed up to US$1 billion in social value for program participants between 2015 and 2022 based on future increased income.</p>
  <p>As we close the chapter on 2023 and look ahead, the journey we’ve embarked upon at SAP CSR is a testament to the power of collective action and shared vision. The stories, numbers, and outcomes shared in our eBook reflect our commitment to making a meaningful difference. <a href="https://d.dam.sap.com/a/Gnggenc/SAP%20CSR%20in%20Review%202023.pdf?rc=10">Read the full eBook.</a></p>
  <p>Thank you to everyone who has been a part of this journey. Your passion, dedication, and commitment are what drive us forward.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Alexandra van der Ploeg is global head of Corporate Social Responsibility at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="follow-sap-news-on-linkedin-to-stay-up-to-date">Follow SAP News on LinkedIn to stay up-to-date</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news">Connect with us</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>non-sap-event/africa-code week</category>
            <category>news-tag/csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/generation-unlimited</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/social-entrepreneurship</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The State of Computer Science in the U.S.]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/the-state-of-computer-science-in-the-us</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/the-state-of-computer-science-in-the-us</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Shaina Glass from the Computer Science Teachers Association gives an interview about the state of computer science education in the country.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[COP28 Spotlights Youth in Combatting Climate Change]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/cop28-spotlights-youth-in-combatting-climate-change</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/cop28-spotlights-youth-in-combatting-climate-change</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP has four-pronged approach to empower youth against climate change, spotlighted at the RewirED Summit during COP28. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/climate-change</category>
            <category>non-sap-event/cop28</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP at COP28: Navigating Climate Change Together]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/sap-at-cop28-navigating-climate-change-together</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/sap-at-cop28-navigating-climate-change-together</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Read to learn more about SAP's innovations and youth-focused initiatives aimed to transform climate action at COP28.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d07c04d3ed1e6ad051b5a3361ceab103e7b331db.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d07c04d3ed1e6ad051b5a3361ceab103e7b331db.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1d07c04d3ed1e6ad051b5a3361ceab103e7b331db.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP at COP28: Navigating Climate Change Together" src="./media_1d07c04d3ed1e6ad051b5a3361ceab103e7b331db.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-at-cop28-navigating-climate-change-together">SAP at COP28: Navigating Climate Change Together</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>The world is watching as tens of thousands of leaders gather for the 28<sup>th</sup> UN Climate Change Conference (<a href="/topics/cop28">COP28</a>) at Expo City in Dubai, UAE, from November 30 to December 12. The primary goal is to negotiate agreements that will limit global warming to 1.5 degrees Celsius.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The conference participants face complex challenges as they strive to turn these aspirations into concrete action. Amidst the vibrant backdrop of Dubai, the objective stands tall: to ensure that all nations, particularly the less affluent, aren’t disproportionately burdened in pursuing a sustainable world. Yet, can these ambitious goals truly be achieved?</p>
  <p>The UN Climate Change Conference is a platform for governments to collaborate on creating policies against rising global temperatures and confronting the consequences of climate change. Over the years, these gatherings have shown progress, but many say they are too slow in creating tangible results. Recent assessments suggest a potential warming of 3 degrees Celsius, highlighting the urgent need for collective action to achieve the crucial 1.5-degree target.</p>
  <p>COP28 aims to be more than just another meeting; it seeks to serve as a significant moment where the international community reflects on and evaluates the progress made since the 2015 Paris Agreement. Above all, it represents a critical self-assessment, examining what actions are required to bridge the gap by 2030.</p>
  <h2 id="sap-promotes-sustainable-innovation-making-progress-together">SAP Promotes Sustainable Innovation: Making Progress Together</h2>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="truly-sustainable-businesses-gain-a-competitive-advantage">Truly Sustainable Businesses Gain a Competitive Advantage</h3>
        <p><em><a href="/2023/11/sap-sustainability-research-study-wave-3">Read the feature</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP is participating in COP28 and advocating for ambitious policy action and the adoption of technology for corporate sustainability management. Through the active participation of CEO and Member of the Executive Board of SAP SE Christian Klein, SAP Chief Marketing &#x26; Solutions Officer and Member of the Executive Board of SAP SE Julia White, and Chief Sustainability and Commercial Officer Sophia Mendelsohn, SAP showcases its critical role in advancing sustainability. SAP underscores its commitment to climate action by engaging in nearly 70 initiatives during COP28 on various fronts like carbon accounting, climate justice, and the circular economy.</p>
  <p>Businesses of every stripe are reshaping their processes and how they operate to not only adjust to increasing regulation but to thrive in an era demanding zero emissions. “SAP’s customers generate 87% of the world’s global commerce, about US$46 trillion. That puts us in a unique position in which we play a critical role in the global economic ecosystem,” says Mendelsohn. “SAP can help 87% of total global commerce organize its supply chain, transportation, and financial data in a way that enables a circular and net zero economy.”</p>
  <p>A <a href="https://www.sap.com/insights/research/to-profit-from-sustainability-be-resolute.html">recent study</a> conducted by SAP revealed a significant advantage for businesses that proactively incorporate sustainability into their strategies, surpassing those that merely respond to external pressures. SAP’s solutions can help by streamlining data collection, enabling comprehensive analysis, sharing standardized data, and seamlessly integrating sustainability measures into core business processes. This transparency and integration can empower businesses to effectively navigate regulatory landscapes and make well-informed, sustainable decisions across their entire value chain.</p>
  <p>SAP’s advocacy of managing carbon, fostering collaborative supply chain ecosystems, and supporting local initiatives in combating climate change and societal challenges exemplifies its strategic priorities driving this significant global shift towards sustainability. This underscores the urgency for all companies, regardless of size or industry, to prioritize sustainability. Climate change poses an unparalleled challenge that necessitates collective effort – a challenge no single entity can tackle alone.</p>
  <p>That’s why SAP is working with a broad set of partners for sustainability. Alicia Lenze, global marketing head of Sustainability Marketing at SAP, says, “Collaborating with our global sustainability ecosystem is essential to our customer success. We work with partners of all kinds – institutional, strategic, consulting, and technology – to achieve our sustainability goals together. We actively engage with institutional partners such as The World Business Council for Sustainable Development <a href="https://www.wbcsd.org">(WBCSD)</a>, The International Chamber of Commerce (<a href="https://iccwbo.org/">ICC</a>), and We Mean Business <a href="https://www.wemeanbusinesscoalition.org/">(WMB)</a> to demonstrate how we are helping companies take concrete actions to tackle climate change.”</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="record-report-and-act-on-your-sustainability-goals-with-sap">Record, report, and act on your sustainability goals with SAP</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/sustainability.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP also strives to be a trusted sustainability partner to governments, international organizations, and civil society. By fostering meaningful relationships, SAP drives climate action through technology and advocates for effective climate policies and youth inclusion in a just transition. COP28 is an opportunity for governments to implement a balanced approach to addressing climate challenges, combining mitigation and adaptation with crucial technological support. “I’m hopeful for an ambitious and impactful set of outcomes, which will send a strong signal to all stakeholders, including businesses, that we need to act with urgency and scale to meet the goals of the Paris Agreement for our people and planet,” says Pete Selfridge, head of Global Government Affairs at SAP.</p>
  <h2 id="empowering-change-through-education-and-youth-action">Empowering Change Through Education and Youth Action</h2>
  <p><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/innovation/next-gen-innovation-platform/university-alliances.html">SAP University Alliances</a> is teaming up with Abu Dhabi University to host a special Academic Community Conference. Dr. Karina Edmonds, senior vice president and global head of SAP Academies and University Alliances, will lead the talks, focusing on the critical mix of education, sustainability, and technology. This partnership aims to teach the next generation of leaders, equipping them to navigate and work in our changing world. “Engaging academia and youth in SAP’s sustainability efforts is paramount. We are very proud to team up with our academic partners and innovation ecosystem during COP28 to facilitate dialogue around the power of emerging technologies in addressing climate change and its impact,” says Edmonds.</p>
  <p>SAP also focuses on climate justice initiatives, particularly empowering youth through events like the Green Rising Showcase and Youth to the Table’s COP28 Collaborator Roundtable, highlighting the significance of youthful involvement in shaping a sustainable and equitable future. The private sector plays a big role in climate justice by bringing people together, speaking up, teaching new skills, and giving resources. Projects like <a href="https://www.generationunlimited.org/documents/green-rising-concept-note">Green Rising</a> aim to involve 10 million young people in climate action. Ensuring youth representation in decision-making forums is vital for inclusive policies.</p>
  <p>Climate justice is a critical element in addressing the challenges posed by climate change on a global scale. It emphasizes the need to tackle the uneven effects it has on various regions and populations, particularly those that are more susceptible. Projections suggest that by 2050, approximately 1.2 billion individuals could face displacement due to climate-related disasters, underlining the pressing need for action. These forecasts also indicate heightened health risks for nearly all of the world’s 2 billion children, potentially resulting in a 20% increase in malnutrition cases. Among the most affected are young people whose futures might encounter disruptions amidst these unfolding crises.</p>
  <p>COP28 marks an important moment for global action on climate change. It represents an opportunity for collective effort, emphasizing the need for collaboration and a shared commitment to addressing this critical issue. SAP’s engagement goes beyond mere attendance – it entails spearheading initiatives toward a sustainable future, encouraging collective responsibility, innovation, and progress.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Claudia Cortes is part of Global Sustainability Communications at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-sap-news-delivered-to-your-inbox-once-a-week">Get the latest SAP news delivered to your inbox once a week</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/nl/sap-news-center-newsletter/index.html">Sign up now</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>non-sap-event/cop28</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-university-alliances</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Take Small Steps and Create Big Impact Through Volunteering]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/small-steps-big-impact-volunteering-maggie-ramaiah</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/small-steps-big-impact-volunteering-maggie-ramaiah</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Enabling others to make their mark creates lasting impact. SAP employee Maggie Ramaiah integrates CSR activities to build that mindset.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/leadership</category>
            <category>news-tag/pro-bono-for-economic-equity</category>
            <category>news-tag/purpose</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-employee-profile</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[From Mentorship to Female Empowerment: Learnings from Our Partnership with the Global Give Back Circle]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/global-give-back-circle-mentorship-female-empowerment</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/global-give-back-circle-mentorship-female-empowerment</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Through work with the Global Give Back Circle, SAP supports vulnerable girls in Kenya, recognizing that education promotes economic growth.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Empowering Africa's Future: Bridging the Teacher Gap through Digital Education and Upskilling]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/teacher-gap-africa-world-teachers-day-2023</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/teacher-gap-africa-world-teachers-day-2023</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[For World Teachers' Day 2023, SAP shines a spotlight on Africa Code Week and the importance of honoring all educators. Read more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>non-sap-event/africa-code week</category>
            <category>news-tag/life-at-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/un-sdgs</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Gears Up for UNGA 78]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/sap-unga-78</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/sap-unga-78</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn how SAP is preparing for UNGA 78, which signifies the midpoint toward the 2030 target for implementing the UN SDGs.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/life-at-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-at-unga</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-educate-to-employ</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Empowering Anthems: A Playlist for International Youth Day]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/international-youth-day-2023-anthems</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/international-youth-day-2023-anthems</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[For International Youth Day 2023, get the playlist you need to inspire us all to work better together to protect people and planet.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/redefining-youth</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Transform Your Career and the World Around You Through Volunteering]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/transform-career-world-through-volunteer-pro-bono-work</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/transform-career-world-through-volunteer-pro-bono-work</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP employees are transforming the world through their volunteer and pro bono consulting work. Learn more about their efforts.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_151aa28cc4c3b93ece1704e100b04d40a6cf71ac9.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_151aa28cc4c3b93ece1704e100b04d40a6cf71ac9.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_151aa28cc4c3b93ece1704e100b04d40a6cf71ac9.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Transform Your Career and the World Around You Through Volunteering" src="./media_151aa28cc4c3b93ece1704e100b04d40a6cf71ac9.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="transform-your-career-and-the-world-around-you-through-volunteering">Transform Your Career and the World Around You Through Volunteering</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-csr-at-sap">Learn more about CSR at SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/our-values/csr.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>If you were given the opportunity to help others, build your professional skills, gain confidence, and feel more energized in your life and career, would you take it? SAP has dedicated over <a href="https://www.sap.com/dmc/exp/2017_03_46558/enUS/impact/">a decade to exactly that</a>: creating volunteer and pro bono consulting programs that not only help the world run better and improve people’s lives, but also benefit employees, their teams, and the company as well.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Karen Vergara, from the Global Learning Services Enablement Program Management for SAP Concur, is an alumni participant from several SAP-driven pro bono consulting programs, as well as a mentor, trainer, and SAP Corporate Social Responsibility (SAP CSR) fellow.</p>
  <p>Vergara always knew she wanted to help other people become successful and has taken that passion, along with the development of her own professional skills, to a new level. She began her career in education, but found that while she was making a difference, she wanted to do more. She leveraged her educational foundation to move into various roles at Microsoft, Accenture, and most recently SAP, earning a higher salary that allowed her to donate more to the causes she was passionate about but offered her less time for traditional, hands-on volunteering. Vergara decided to seek out opportunities within her professional role to make an impact in new ways.</p>
  <p>What started as a way to get involved soon turned into so much more. With each experience, Vergara gained more than she expected.</p>
  <p>“I’ve found that I’ve taken away as much as I’ve given, maybe sometimes even more,” she says. Volunteering, particularly skills-based volunteer experiences, provided her with the ability to do good and to keep learning and growing both personally and professionally at the same time.</p>
  <p>From helping students find success to changing her career and making an impact through volunteerism and pro bono consulting as a part of the SAP community, Vergara’s journey is showing no signs of slowing down. Over the past six months, she has been working on a fellowship with the SAP CSR team to position every type of volunteering offered at SAP, particularly pro bono engagements, as an opportunity for learning, career, and leadership development.</p>
  <p>“If you are already volunteering, it is a just a bonus and a way to think more intentionally about your professional development,” Vergara shares. “You can do good and learn, taking skills away from it and gaining experience that will help you in your own career.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-more-stories-and-coverage-about-csr-efforts-at-sap">Read more stories and coverage about CSR efforts at SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/topics/sap-csr">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In fact, Vergara has taken this one step further, becoming a leader and champion for employee volunteering. She shared one anecdote from an SAP employee who was looking to gain specific experience to advance to a new role. Vergara pointed them to skills-based volunteering, and when it came time for the interview for the new role, the employee was able to share examples of the experience they gained through participation in these kinds of activities – experience that they otherwise would not have had – putting them in a better position to obtain the new role.</p>
  <p>Thanks to Vergara’s work during her fellowship, as well as her own lived experiences as a corporate volunteer and pro bono consultant, she has demonstrated that utilizing skills and concepts through volunteering and pro bono consulting <em>is</em> career development.</p>
  <p>Through volunteering in any capacity, there is always an opportunity to explore career interests and find a path forward utilizing the right opportunities. CSR activities represent an alternative form of experiential learning; it benefits every professional, whether employee or manager, to consider how they can be incorporated into our professional development plans and goal setting. Vergara’s work has highlighted that intentional and well thought-out engagement in these types of offerings can lead to the acquisition of new skills and chances to practice skills someone may have learned in an academic setting. It also provides an opportunity to learn from others, share one’s own skills, and build a network.</p>
  <p>Everyone who participates in CSR activities stands to gain from the work that Vergara has done in defining how volunteering contributes to career growth beyond social impact. When thinking about volunteerism, often what comes to mind is doing good, serving others, giving back to our communities, and making a positive social and environmental impact. Beyond these more obvious benefits, there are powerful takeaways for the volunteer as well. Traditional activities are a fantastic way to build community with others who are like-minded and share common interests. Skills-based volunteering and pro bono consulting offers an opportunity to build a professional network, while practicing skills such as collaboration, creative problem-solving, and inclusive leadership behaviors. Like Vergara, many employees seek fulfillment beyond their day-to-day roles. Her story is one example of taking the initiative to make a societal impact and gaining so much more. She has found community in her career, opportunities to lead, and a renewed commitment to continue helping the world run better and improving people’s lives.</p>
  <p><strong>Join Us</strong></p>
  <p>With a <a href="https://www.sap.com/dmc/exp/2017_03_46558/enUS/impact/">decade of success</a> engaging employees like Karen Vergara, SAP, together with EY, MovingWorlds, TRANSFORM, and Unilever, continue to partner on the TRANSFORM Support Hub, connecting employees everywhere to social entrepreneurs anywhere through pro bono consulting, coaching, and more. If you feel inspired to build your skills as well as a more sustainable world, we invite you to <a href="https://movingworlds.org/transform/corporates">join us</a>!</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/moments-of-service</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Youth Skills Development: The Path of Education to Employability]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/world-youth-skills-day-2023-education-to-employability</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/world-youth-skills-day-2023-education-to-employability</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Youth skills development brings a brighter future and prosperity. For World Youth Skills Day 2023, learn what SAP and partners doing to help.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1adc8edbcf4a007b333a5f2d3be5417c37c1e13fa.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1adc8edbcf4a007b333a5f2d3be5417c37c1e13fa.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1adc8edbcf4a007b333a5f2d3be5417c37c1e13fa.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Youth Skills Development: The Path of Education to Employability" src="./media_1adc8edbcf4a007b333a5f2d3be5417c37c1e13fa.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="youth-skills-development-the-path-of-education-to-employability">Youth Skills Development: The Path of Education to Employability</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-saps-efforts-around-building-future-skills">Learn more about SAP's efforts around building future skills</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/our-values/csr.html#build">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>As we approach World Youth Skills Day 2023 on July 15, the strategic importance of equipping young people with the skills they need for employment, decent work, and entrepreneurship is crucial. This year’s theme, “<a href="https://www.un.org/en/observances/world-youth-skills-day">Skilling Teachers, Trainers, and Youth for a Transformative Future</a>,” underscores the vital role played by educators in providing young people with the necessary skills to enter the labor market and actively engage in their communities.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Reflecting the hurdles that youth and businesses are grappling with, recent statistics from the International Labour Organization reveal concerning figures. For example, a <a href="https://www.ilo.org/wcmsp5/groups/public/---dgreports/---dcomm/---publ/documents/publication/wcms_853321.pdf">quarter of the global youth population</a> is not in education, employment, or training, and a staggering <a href="https://ilostat.ilo.org/258-million-workers-in-the-world-are-over-educated-for-their-jobs/">935 million workers worldwide have jobs that do not match their educational level</a>. Furthermore, employers are struggling to find workers with the necessary skill set for the job.</p>
  <p>World Youth Skills Day serves as a reminder of the current challenges faced by youth globally and shines a spotlight on actionable steps to create better livelihoods and improve skills alignment for employers. As technological advancements and shifting market dynamics demand agile and adaptable skill sets, it is imperative to empower young people to navigate these changes effectively.</p>
  <p>To add another layer, it is vital to highlight that corporations, businesses, and non-profit organizations also have a crucial role in building future skills and creating employment opportunities.</p>
  <p>In recognizing this, SAP has partnered with UNICEF to support Generation Unlimited (GenU) on two initiatives. The first is the GenU signature program, Youth Agency Marketplace (YOMA), which aims to reach more than 500,000 young people with opportunities for foundational and digital skills.</p>
  <p>The second initiative is the pilot of the <a href="/2022/09/sap-unicef-global-youth-employment-coalition">SAP Educate to Employ</a> program, which will enable more than 100 young people with the essential skills, knowledge, attitudes, and values required to drive employment, innovation, and entrepreneurship — helping to ensure equal opportunities for all.</p>
  <p>Already initiated in the Philippines, Nigeria, Kenya, and South Africa, SAP Educate to Employ is built on the Organisation for Economic Cooperation and Development (OECD) Learning Framework 2030, which enables young people to develop the skills and knowledge necessary to meet the demands of the present and future workforce.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-more-stories-and-coverage-about-csr-efforts-at-sap">Read more stories and coverage about CSR efforts at SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/topics/sap-csr">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Micro-credential programs form a vital component of the initiative, focusing on socio-emotional skills like emotional intelligence, problem-solving, and critical thinking. These programs are accessible to young individuals with a high school education, vocational training, or a university degree. The curriculum also encompasses employability skills, technology in the workplace, business foundation knowledge, SAP foundational knowledge, and SAP skills certification.</p>
  <p>Upon achieving their SAP certification, participants will have opportunities to secure various IT internship roles in departments such as consulting, development, analysis, and support within the SAP ecosystem. Recognizing that some information and communications technology (ICT) roles may face displacement in the next three to five years, the program emphasizes continuous learning and growth to support sustainable employment.</p>
  <p>Through SAP Educate to Employ, SAP is committed to providing equitable education and job opportunities for underrepresented individuals, including minorities from diverse ethnic backgrounds, women, differently abled individuals, the underprivileged, and the disadvantaged.</p>
  <p>By participating in programs like SAP Educate to Employ, businesses gain access to certified and diversified talent while uplifting their livelihoods. Additionally, they can help bridge the demand and supply gap for SAP skills and accelerate digital transformation within their respective countries through a digitally skilled workforce.</p>
  <p>On World Youth Skills Day 2023, it is crucial to acknowledge the immense potential of young people as catalysts for positive change. By making a firm commitment to equipping them with the essential skills, values, knowledge, and attitudes, we can work together to shape a brighter future, leaving no young person behind. After all, skills and education can help society overcome any difficult situation.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Eugene Ho is global CSR director for Future Skills at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-educate-to-employ</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fostering Refugee Inclusion: Lessons Learned from Social Entrepreneurs]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/supporting-refugees-sap-csr</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/supporting-refugees-sap-csr</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[When it comes to supporting refugees, social entrepreneurs are among those who can play a vital role in fostering inclusion.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ea9a5a56c75ee44ca639d30f89e1d7b48c0ac813.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ea9a5a56c75ee44ca639d30f89e1d7b48c0ac813.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1ea9a5a56c75ee44ca639d30f89e1d7b48c0ac813.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Fostering Refugee Inclusion: Lessons Learned from Social Entrepreneurs" src="./media_1ea9a5a56c75ee44ca639d30f89e1d7b48c0ac813.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="fostering-refugee-inclusion-lessons-learned-from-social-entrepreneurs">Fostering Refugee Inclusion: Lessons Learned from Social Entrepreneurs</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>SAP recently marked two significant events: World Refugee Day on June 20 and the United Nations (UN) Micro-, Small, and Medium-Sized Enterprise Day on June 27.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>To underscore the vital role of partnerships in creating a global environment where refugees are fully integrated and valued members of society, we hosted a webinar, “Hope, Inclusion, Action: Building Opportunity for Refugees.” (<a href="https://broadcast.sap.com/replay/230628NSQ_sapcsr">Watch a replay here</a>.) Joining me were two remarkable social entrepreneurs, Innocent Tshilombo, co-founder of <a href="https://kakumaventures.com/">Kakuma Ventures</a>, and Mozamel Aman, co-founder and CEO of <a href="https://startsteps.org/en">StartSteps</a> and founder of <a href="https://www.startupistan.org/">Startupistan</a>.</p>
  <p>In 2022, the number of forcibly displaced people for the first time exceeded <a href="https://www.unhcr.org/refugee-statistics/">100 million</a> due to war, violence, and persecution. Unfortunately, this number is expected to rise even further given the current global challenges, such as conflicts, political tensions, and climate change.</p>
  <p>These social entrepreneurs are among many who are playing a role in supporting refugees to integrate into their new environment by finding meaningful work and education opportunities. After an hour with Tshilombo and Aman, I felt privileged to hear their personal narratives and gain valuable insights into navigating challenges with authenticity and vulnerability.</p>
  <p>To provide some context: Tshilombo, an entrepreneur and humanitarian professional, has spearheaded educational, business, and humanitarian initiatives in the Kakuma refugee camp in Kenya. As the co-founder of Kakuma Ventures, a renowned social enterprise, Tshilombo aims to enhance the well-being of refugees and host communities by leveraging digital services and opportunities through energy and internet access for education, trades, and employment. Meanwhile, Aman is deeply passionate about the intersection of technology, entrepreneurship, and social impact. Through his involvement in various startup organizations, Aman has developed a unique perspective on problem-solving. He firmly believes that privilege comes with great responsibility, forming the foundation of sustainable social ventures.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-csr-at-sap">Learn more about CSR at SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/our-values/csr.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="the-transformative-power-of-social-entrepreneurship">The Transformative Power of Social Entrepreneurship</h2>
  <p>Despite operating in challenging environments with limited resources, these founders did not seek traditional employment for stability and security. Instead, they cultivated their own skills and forged ahead, building their social businesses in the face of adversity while remaining driven.</p>
  <p>The Kakuma Camp hosts approximately 200,000 refugees, and Germany, where Aman operates, is home to around <a href="https://www.unhcr.org/refugee-statistics/">2 million refugees</a>. One might assume that scaling their ventures should be a top priority from the get-go. However, both entrepreneurs emphasized the significance of starting small and witnessing the impact created. By demonstrating success, they gradually gained access to additional resources, facilitating further growth.</p>
  <p>This reminded me of a powerful notion: systemic change doesn’t necessarily require focusing on the big picture; it can begin by positively impacting one individual at a time. Through this approach, social enterprises have the opportunity to learn, adapt, and secure the resources needed to expand their efforts over time.</p>
  <h2 id="partnerships-are-crucial-to-overcoming-challenges">Partnerships Are Crucial to Overcoming Challenges</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-more-stories-and-coverage-about-csr-efforts-at-sap">Read more stories and coverage about CSR efforts at SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/topics/sap-csr">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Many corporations have strict criteria and predefined standards that often hinder the inclusion of individuals from diverse backgrounds. However, more companies have started to recognize the potential in these individuals and consider them as potential employees. This realization has led to the development of tailored programs in collaboration with companies. However, there is a challenge in Germany, for example, where many open positions exist. Still, the skills companies require are often too specific or need to be adequately addressed in generic training programs. It is, therefore, essential to work with employers and partners to design and develop programs that meet their specific needs.</p>
  <p>These entrepreneurs have managed to navigate this barrier by forging strategic alliances and fostering a mindset shift among potential hiring partners. By showcasing the skills and potential of their participants, they have successfully broken down these barriers and opened doors to new opportunities.</p>
  <h2 id="sustainability-and-scalability-make-the-world-run-better">Sustainability and Scalability Make the World Run Better</h2>
  <p>Both Tshilombo and Aman’s experiences highlight the importance of sustainability and scalability in social enterprises. While charitable and nonprofit organizations undoubtedly play a crucial role, integrating a business model offers long-term viability. Social enterprises create a continuous cycle of positive impact by generating profits and reinvesting them into sustainable projects. This approach supports self-sufficiency and allows for scalability, replication, and the ability to address specific community needs effectively.</p>
  <p>At SAP, we are dedicated to accelerating social enterprises and take great pride in providing continuous pro bono consulting support to organizations like these. The recent discussion held in commemoration of World Refugee Day and SME Day underscores a powerful message: when we work together, we have the ability to create a transformative ecosystem that empowers purpose-driven enterprises and positively impacts the lives of individuals in need.</p>
  <p>Recognizing the importance of creating economic opportunities and education for refugees and migrants, SAP has established robust partnerships that began several years ago. One notable program is <a href="https://digitalskillsfortoday.org/">Digital Skills for Today</a> in the Middle East, which aims to equip young refugees with the necessary skills to pursue employment opportunities in the IT sector. Additionally, SAP collaborates with the <a href="https://www.uopeople.edu/">University of the People</a>, offering free scholarships to refugees seeking bachelor’s and master’s degrees. The nonprofit tuition-free American accredited online university has an impressive enrollment of more than 120,000 students from 200 countries, including 16,500 refugees.</p>
  <p>If you are a social enterprise in need of our support or an experienced professional who can offer skilled expertise, join us on the <a href="https://movingworlds.org/transform">TRANSFORM Support Hub</a>.</p>
  <p>Together, we can create change and be changed.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Alexandra van der Ploeg is head of <a href="/topics/sap-csr">Corporate Social Responsibility at SAP</a>.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/social-entrepreneurship</category>
            <category>non-sap-event/world-refugee-day</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Breaking Barriers Through Education: SAP's Partnership with University of the People]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/breaking-barriers-through-education-sap-university-of-the-people</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/breaking-barriers-through-education-sap-university-of-the-people</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP has partnered with University of the People, helping provide global access to higher education. Read the stories of two refugee students.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning-for-life</category>
            <category>news-tag/purpose</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
            <category>news-tag/ukraine</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Showing Up in the World Through Pro Bono Consulting]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/showing-up-through-pro-bono-consulting</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/showing-up-through-pro-bono-consulting</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Product Engineering and SAP CSR joined forces to leverage pro bono consulting to develop the next generation of SAP engineering leaders.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/purpose</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Saving Lives in the Turkish Earthquake Zone]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/saving-lives-in-the-turkish-earthquake-zone</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/saving-lives-in-the-turkish-earthquake-zone</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP employee Sebastian Hodapp and the volunteer search and rescue organization @fire rescued trapped victims after the earthquake in Türkiye.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-employee-profile</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP CSR Launches Third Edition of eBook, Celebrating a Year of Global Impact]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/sap-csr-launches-ebook-third-edition</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/sap-csr-launches-ebook-third-edition</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Corporate Social Responsibility (SAP CSR) launched the third edition of its annual eBook, "Helping the World Run Better – Together."]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-social-sabbatical</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Power of Change Activists: SAP x ChangemakerXchange]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/01/power-of-change-activists-changemakerxchange</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/01/power-of-change-activists-changemakerxchange</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP supported a North America-focused gender and climate action summit with ChangemakerXchange. Read to learn more about the event.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/climate-action</category>
            <category>news-tag/csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/gender-equality</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Power of Partnerships to Unlock the Social Economy]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/01/unlock-the-social-economy-catalyst-2030</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/01/unlock-the-social-economy-catalyst-2030</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Every organization and sector has a role in unlocking the social economy. The Catalyst Business Commitment aims to build its ecosystem.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>non-sap-event/wef-davos</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Social Sabbatical: Resiliency and Impact in Action]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/sap-social-sabbatical-resiliency-and-impact-in-action</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/sap-social-sabbatical-resiliency-and-impact-in-action</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Pro bono consulting programs like SAP Social Sabbatical build immense impact for employees, social sector partners, and SAP overall.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/purpose</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-social-sabbatical</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Act Now, Together, Through Pro Bono Consulting]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/together-act-now-pro-bono-consulting</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/together-act-now-pro-bono-consulting</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Together Act Now was the theme for the 2022 UN International Volunteer Day. Learn how SAP employees participate.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/life-at-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-social-sabbatical</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
            <category>news-tag/un-sdgs</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fostering Diversity and Inclusion Through Immersive Pro Bono Consulting]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/immersive-pro-bono-consulting-fostering-diversity-inclusion</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/immersive-pro-bono-consulting-fostering-diversity-inclusion</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Pro bono consulting programs like the SAP Social Sabbatical foster diversity and cultivate an inclusive mindset for participants. Learn how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17c7e0cc1436024ff2536a47add3bf4d172041915.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17c7e0cc1436024ff2536a47add3bf4d172041915.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_17c7e0cc1436024ff2536a47add3bf4d172041915.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Fostering Diversity and Inclusion Through Immersive Pro Bono Consulting" src="./media_17c7e0cc1436024ff2536a47add3bf4d172041915.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="fostering-diversity-and-inclusion-through-immersive-pro-bono-consulting">Fostering Diversity and Inclusion Through Immersive Pro Bono Consulting</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Global Diversity Awareness Month is a time to reflect and honor diversity in all its facets – nationality, race, sex, gender, country of origin, and language, just to name a few.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>This is celebrated each year in October; however, at SAP, diversity is something we honor throughout the year. Within our 110,000+ strong company, we have employees from all over the world, with many of our teams working from multiple locations together to reinvent how the world runs as a network of intelligent, sustainable enterprises. Through global teamwork, employees are exposed to different cultures, diverse ways of thinking, and building skills that grow empathy and resiliency. Not only is diversity and inclusion good for employees, but it is also good for business.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-how-sap-is-powering-equitable-access">Learn how SAP is powering equitable access</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/our-values/csr.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="diversity-in-action-through-pro-bono-consulting">Diversity in Action through Pro Bono Consulting</h2>
  <p>As a global organization with employees representing more than 150 nationalities, we are constantly seeking various ways to incorporate diversity and inclusion proactively, both within our workplace and in the markets we serve.</p>
  <p>One of the ways SAP has prioritized a diversity mindset for employees over the past decade is through <a href="https://www.sap.com/socialsabbatical">SAP Social Sabbatical</a>. In this program, SAP employees from around the world can share their skills, knowledge, and professional expertise with innovative non-profit organizations and social enterprises in emerging markets to help them solve their business challenges. The program has been run in over 52 countries with participants representing 64 different nationalities. This highlights our commitment to bring together different perspectives, amplifying the power of diversity of thought and experience, which creates positive impact for both the organizations and participating SAP employees.</p>
  <p>Meera Shenoy, founder of SAP Social Sabbatical host client <a href="https://www.youth4jobs.org/">Youth4Jobs</a>, shared how her organization benefited from the team’s diversity of professional experience: “The volunteers came from three different countries, and each had a different specialty. They quickly adopted our passion for inclusion and became part of the larger Youth4Jobs family, understanding our challenges and transformational work. They also gave us a peek into the amazing SAP processes in several areas. For example, the team shared the SAP neurodiversity training with us, and we got to learn the techniques that a corporation like SAP uses for neurodiversity inclusion in the workplace.”</p>
  <p>When diversity is incorporated through pro bono consulting programs like SAP Social Sabbatical, organizations are able to tap into the varied perspectives and approaches that each individual employee brings to the <a href="https://www2.deloitte.com/us/en/insights/focus/human-capital-trends/2014/hc-trends-2014-diversity-to-inclusion.html">workplace</a>. Research shows that diversified teams can lead to an increase in innovation, improve problem-solving, and boost decision-making. This can heighten performance by <a href="https://diversity-inclusion-speakers.com/news/tips-and-tricks/benefits-diversity-inclusion-workplace-statistics/#:~:text=%E2%80%9CRacially%20diverse%20teams%20report%20a,key%20factor%20in%20any%20workplace.">at least 35%</a>, which not only accelerates innovation within SAP but also helps the host client organization anticipate and fulfill the needs of diverse customers.</p>
  <h2 id="the-employee-advantage">The Employee Advantage</h2>
  <p>For employee participants, we know that the pro bono consulting benefits include skill development, networking opportunities, gaining new perspectives, and cultural immersion, among others. For example, a participant from India stated, “It gives you a whole new perspective that we don’t get in our day-to-day work.”</p>
  <p>From a recent <a href="https://www.sap.com/dmc/exp/2017_03_46558/enUS/impact/">long-term impact study</a> that we conducted in partnership with impact measurement social enterprise <a href="https://60decibels.com/">60 Decibels</a>, 88% of SAP employees who have participated in SAP Social Sabbatical reported that the program benefited them personally. Additionally, 86% of employees said their ability collaborate with global and diverse colleagues improved by their participation.</p>
  <p>“It allowed me to dive into a new world for weeks. You gain experience you have never had before. It brings you to a new level culture-wise, and you meet many talented people from SAP across the world,” said one participant from Germany.</p>
  <p>Another employee commented, “In my personal life, I am more aware of differences in people and better at understanding peoples’ challenges. These differences go beyond age, gender, geography and race but also diversity of thought, upbringing, values and perspectives. Understanding these differences is key to solving problems and empowering others.”</p>
  <h2 id="focusing-on-sustainable-long-term-impact">Focusing on Sustainable Long-Term Impact</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="explore-what-sap-is-doing-to-accelerate-social-businesses">Explore what SAP is doing to accelerate social businesses</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/our-values/csr.html#accelerate">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In addition to the diversity benefits for participants and social sector partners, the long-term impacts have gone beyond the SAP Social Sabbatical program. These principles of diversity as a building block of the program have supported the evolution of new initiatives that address social challenges and build equity, while leveraging pro bono consulting as a tool. In learning from our success over the past 10 years, we developed the Pro Bono for Economic Equity program in North America, which was launched in 2021 in partnership with <a href="https://www.pyxeraglobal.org/">PYXERA Global</a>, as part of SAP’s overall response to the social justice movement with an aim to foster economic equity for Black-owned business and social enterprises.</p>
  <p>The program allows SAP employees to leverage their professional skills and expertise as pro bono volunteer consultants for under-resourced businesses and social enterprises and help them address systemic and business challenges. Within the first year, the program expanded internationally to the UK, Brazil, and South Africa. Based on the success of the program, we have extended the cohorts to have a focus on Indigenous-owned businesses in Canada. <a href="/2022/05/pro-bono-for-economic-equity-impact">Learn more about the program here</a>.</p>
  <h2 id="cultivating-an-inclusive-mindset">Cultivating an Inclusive Mindset</h2>
  <p>At SAP, diversity and inclusion are not simply goals to strive for; they are strategic components of our corporate culture that fuel innovation and help us turn our purpose to action.</p>
  <p>We recognize that continuously bolstering the diversity, equity, and inclusion mindset is crucial when it comes to shaping the next generation of leaders in our company. Not only will this support employee engagement today, but it means that they will build a more inclusive environment when it comes to how they work in teams, how they hire, and how they engage colleagues who are different from them, now and into the future.</p>
  <p>For more information about SAP Social Sabbatical, visit <a href="https://www.sap.com/socialsabbatical">sap.com/socialsabbatical</a> and to learn about how SAP is empowering Black- and Indigenous-owned businesses and social enterprises, read <a href="/topics/pro-bono-for-economic-equity">more stories about the Pro Bono Economic Equity program here</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Hemang Desai is global program director for SAP Corporate Social Responsibility.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/life-at-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-social-sabbatical</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Community Holiday Shopping Guide: Ideas to Excite, Inspire, and Make an Impact]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/holiday-gift-guide-shopping-ideas-sap-community</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/holiday-gift-guide-shopping-ideas-sap-community</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Review our new holiday gift guide, a one-stop resource for all your shopping needs this holiday season, and all throughout the year.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/purpose</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
            <category>news-tag/social-enterprise</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Lasting Impact of SAP’s Early College High School Program]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/impact-of-sap-early-college-high-school-program</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/impact-of-sap-early-college-high-school-program</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A survey from SAP and Digital Promise reveals the lasting impact of Early College High School program participants in pursuing STEM.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/education</category>
            <category>industry/higher-education-research</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Named Best Corporate Steward by U.S. Chamber of Commerce Foundation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/sap-named-best-corporate-steward</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/sap-named-best-corporate-steward</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP has been named Best Corporate Steward by U.S. Chamber of Commerce Foundation for its commitment to a more inclusive, sustainable economy.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_158bc723afdf76ef6718b04ea6166dfa5dfcfab7a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_158bc723afdf76ef6718b04ea6166dfa5dfcfab7a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_158bc723afdf76ef6718b04ea6166dfa5dfcfab7a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Named Best Corporate Steward by U.S. Chamber of Commerce Foundation" src="./media_158bc723afdf76ef6718b04ea6166dfa5dfcfab7a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-named-best-corporate-steward-by-us-chamber-of-commerce-foundation">SAP Named Best Corporate Steward by U.S. Chamber of Commerce Foundation</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>The U.S. Chamber of Commerce Foundation named SAP “Best Corporate Steward: Large Business” at the 23rd annual Citizens Awards in Washington D.C. The recognition is given to the company that best demonstrates itself as a “responsive and responsible member of society, whose overall values, operational practices, and decision-making exemplify shared value.”</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1675116b99aa002c87c7da6d2f5648b6307bbba33.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1675116b99aa002c87c7da6d2f5648b6307bbba33.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1675116b99aa002c87c7da6d2f5648b6307bbba33.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_1675116b99aa002c87c7da6d2f5648b6307bbba33.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2252" height="2552">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p><em>SAP’s Jennifer Beason, Carmen Krueger, Jim Sullivan, Robin Manherz, Kevin Richards</em></p>
  <p>It was accepted on behalf of SAP by Global Chief Operating Officer Robin Manherz.</p>
  <p>SAP technology helps companies embed sustainability into core business processes, which, combined with an industry-leading social responsibility strategy, is delivering global solutions to unlock a more inclusive and sustainable economy.</p>
  <p>Manherz shared that this award means a lot to her personally and to the company. “This is such a tremendous and important honor for me to represent SAP tonight,” she said. “From the planes in the sky to the electricity on the grid, we run most of the world with our technology. We take that responsibility very seriously and look forward to working with you today and every day to make sure we are living up to our purpose.”</p>
  <p><a href="https://www.uschamberfoundation.org/citizens-awards/2022-winners">Meet all the Citizens Awards winners here</a>.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-how-the-sap-csr-team-is-working-toward-ensuring-an-inclusive-recovery-and-equal-opportunities-for-all">Learn more about how the SAP CSR team is working toward ensuring an inclusive recovery and equal opportunities for all</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/our-values/csr.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="helping-the-world-run-better-together">Helping the World Run Better, Together</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-what-life-looks-like-at-sap">Learn more about what life looks like at SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/careers/who-we-are.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP’s mission is to help every business become a sustainable, intelligent enterprise. In practice, that means we create solutions to manage the most mission-critical business operations, like finance, human resources, and manufacturing, that, at the same time, address some of the most profound economic, social, and environmental challenges of our time.</p>
  <p>For example, SAP Cloud for Sustainable Enterprises helps companies manage their carbon footprint and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/responsible-design-and-production.html">reduce material waste</a>. In addition to the <a href="https://www.sap.com/sustainability.html">sustainability</a> portfolio, SAP is investing in supply chain transparency through SAP Ariba and SAP Business Network to promote human rights, circularity, and socially responsible procurement standards. With more than $3 trillion traded across SAP Business Network, SAP has an opportunity to help companies shift procurement spend from traditional trading partners to companies like <a href="https://www.forthebluedot.com/">Blue Dot Way</a>, <a href="https://auticon.com/">Auticon</a>, and <a href="https://televerde.com/">Televerde</a>. Procuring quality goods and services from organizations like these increases investment in economic equity, social impact, and environmental sustainability in a way that cannot be done through corporate philanthropy alone.</p>
  <p>“SAP’s vision to help the world run better and improve people’s lives is evident through its investments and innovative technology to make a profound impact on the most vulnerable populations,” said Marc DeCourcey, senior vice president of the U.S. Chamber of Commerce Foundation. “Their purpose-driven culture serves as a model for companies around the world.”</p>
  <p>As DeCourcey affirms, technology by itself is not the answer. That is why SAP is also investing in equitable access to economic opportunity, education, and employment, as well as a green, circular economy.</p>
  <p>“As a company, we have an unwavering commitment to innovation and to the communities around the U.S. and the world where we operate,” shared Lloyd Adams, president of SAP North America. “This award belongs to our employees, customers, and partners who have committed to sustainable and equitable business practices that focus on supporting people and protecting the planet.”</p>
  <p>These values are embedded throughout the leadership culture at SAP, along with the way we engage and develop future talent. Adams, for example, personally champions the Autism at Work program and spearheads SAP North America’s Emerging Talent Advisory Board. In the past year alone, Adams and the North America leadership team engaged 30 next-generation leaders in the <a href="https://drive.google.com/file/d/1i4u5GiU8qCAwrssBcdVvQS51J1Q2Nbbs/view">Acceleration Collective</a>, a virtual pro bono consulting initiative, solving strategic business challenges for B2B social enterprises tackling issues of plastics and waste, inclusion, and responsible supply chains. And there are plans to continue embracing experiential learning through pro bono across North America in the future.</p>
  <p>In 2021, SAP Corporate Social Responsibility programs and partnerships trained more than 119,000 teachers, educated 3.5 million youth, 50% of whom were girls, and impacted more than 8.3 million lives. More than 20,000 employees globally engage in skills-based volunteerism through SAP, representing a $20 million in-kind contribution to impact organizations through pro bono consulting in the last decade.</p>
  <p>Looking ahead, SAP has reinforced its partnership with <a href="https://www.unicef.org/partnerships/sap-unicef-genu-help-young-people-gain-skills-for-employment">UNICEF</a> and Generation Unlimited, announcing the <a href="/2022/09/sap-unicef-global-youth-employment-coalition">SAP Educate to Employ initiative</a>, a program that supports learning-to-earning pathways in the digital and green economies for youth in need. Additionally, to help combat the global refugee crisis, SAP is fulfilling associate and bachelor’s degree scholarships with <a href="https://www.uopeople.edu/about/worldwide-recognition/press-releases/sap-providing-50-scholarships-for-ukrainian-refugees-at-uopeople/">University of the People</a>, the first nonprofit, tuition-free, American-accredited online university dedicated to providing global access to higher education.</p>
  <p>Based on SAP’s own success engaging employees and partners, SAP — together with EY, MovingWorlds, TRANSFORM, and Unilever — partnered to launch the <a href="https://movingworlds.org/transform/social-enterprises?utm_source=sap&#x26;utm_medium=email&#x26;utm_campaign=transformlaunch_0422">TRANSFORM Support Hub</a>, helping employees everywhere connect to social enterprises anywhere, through pro bono consulting, coaching, and more. The open, online platform is a place where new and existing partners can come together to expedite world-changing solutions. If you share our commitment to building a more sustainable world, we hope you will <a href="https://movingworlds.org/transform/corporates">join us</a>!</p>
  <p>To learn more about SAP and its purpose in action, visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/csr">www.sap.com/csr</a> and follow us on social media using @SAP4Good.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/life-at-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Organizations Measure the Real Impact of Social Enterprise Programs]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/measure-real-impact-of-social-enterprise-programs</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/measure-real-impact-of-social-enterprise-programs</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Social enterprise programs that educate and train disadvantaged people to address challenges are a force for positive change. Learn how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/circular-economy</category>
            <category>news-tag/climate-change</category>
            <category>news-tag/csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>news-tag/entrepreneurship</category>
            <category>news-tag/esg</category>
            <category>news-tag/pyxera-global</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-social-sabbatical</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The "S" in ESG: A Business Imperative]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/esg-business-imperative</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/esg-business-imperative</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The "S" in a company's ESG (environmental, social, and governance) investment strategy is now a business imperative. Learn why.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-social-sabbatical</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Skill Immersion Lab: Year Two Results of Virtual Reality in the Classroom]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/the-skill-immersion-lab-year-two-results-vr-classroom</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/the-skill-immersion-lab-year-two-results-vr-classroom</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[As technology plays- an increasing role in education, learn more about the success of VR in the Skill Immersion Lab from SAP and JFFLabs.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/education</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Why the Skills Mismatch Is a Global Challenge]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/09/skills-mismatch-global-challenge</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/09/skills-mismatch-global-challenge</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The skills mismatch is largely attributed to under-education. Learn more about what SAP is doing through programs and partnerships to help.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/generation-unlimited</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/un-sdgs</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>