<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/product/sap-successfactors-employee-central/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Modernizing Benefits Enrollment to Boost Employee Satisfaction and Retention]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/modernizing-benefits-enrollment-boost-employee-satisfaction-retention</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/modernizing-benefits-enrollment-boost-employee-satisfaction-retention</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central Global Benefits empowers employees to take control of their benefits with an intuitive, guided experience.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1330c66286be6108050da7ab27c52e68fc719102b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1330c66286be6108050da7ab27c52e68fc719102b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1330c66286be6108050da7ab27c52e68fc719102b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Modernizing Benefits Enrollment to Boost Employee Satisfaction and Retention" src="./media_1330c66286be6108050da7ab27c52e68fc719102b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="modernizing-benefits-enrollment-to-boost-employee-satisfaction-and-retention">Modernizing Benefits Enrollment to Boost Employee Satisfaction and Retention</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Employee satisfaction is driven by more than paychecks and perks – it’s also about everyday work experiences. One often-overlooked aspect that can significantly impact how employees feel about their workplace is the benefits enrollment experience.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>A confusing benefits enrollment experience is a significant source of frustration for many employees and can leave them feeling uncertain about their benefits elections. The majority of employees struggle to understand their benefits options and navigate through the enrollment process.</p>
  <p>As a result, many employees choose to simply roll over their previous year’s elections rather than review and update their choices to ensure they are getting the most out of their benefits. This often leads to missed opportunities to take advantage of lower-cost options or benefits that are a better fit for them and their family and can even lead to increased attrition of top talent.</p>
  <p>With <a href="/2024/04/sap-successfactors-first-half-2024-release">the first half 2024 release</a>, updates to the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/employee-central-hris/features.html#benefits?url_id=ctabutton-us-hcm-EC-freetrial">SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central Global Benefits</a> solution can enable you to empower your employees to take control of their benefits with an intuitive guided enrollment experience.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="extend-your-benefits-capabilities-with-sap-successfactors">Extend your benefits capabilities with SAP SuccessFactors</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/employee-central-hris/features.html#benefits">Learn how</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="making-benefits-enrollment-more-seamless-simple-and-intuitive">Making Benefits Enrollment More Seamless, Simple, and Intuitive</h2>
  <p>The new benefits enrollment experience in <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/employee-central-hris/features.html#benefits?url_id=ctabutton-us-hcm-EC-freetrial">SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central Global Benefits</a> introduces a process-driven approach to benefits enrollment that helps simplify and streamline the activity. Available for insurance, savings plans, and pension benefit types, this new enrollment experience can enable employees to make better, more informed benefits choices without the unnecessary hurdles.</p>
  <p>Here are some key highlights:</p>
  <h3 id="guided-enrollment">Guided Enrollment</h3>
  <p>A step-by-step progression flow guides employees through the process, working to simplify navigation and helping them complete benefits enrollment. Real-time benefits eligibility updates help employees continually understand the choices and options available by presenting them with all the benefits for which they are eligible to enroll.</p>
  <h3 id="personalized-user-experience">Personalized User Experience</h3>
  <p>Customizable text and instructions enable a tailored enrollment experience aligned with organizational policies.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c17ad14f21e83c7450704c1afdf399c3a412c660.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c17ad14f21e83c7450704c1afdf399c3a412c660.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1c17ad14f21e83c7450704c1afdf399c3a412c660.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Screenshot of benefits enrollment welcome page in SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central Global Benefits" src="./media_1c17ad14f21e83c7450704c1afdf399c3a412c660.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="580">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>Benefits enrollment welcome page. Click to enlarge.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="flexible-framework">Flexible Framework</h3>
  <p>Benefits admins can now have more flexibility in designing the enrollment experience to meet their organization’s needs with a new framework that helps support the capture of life insurance guaranteed issue amounts, customizable terms and conditions, and enhanced localization capabilities.</p>
  <h3 id="anytime-anywhere-access">Anytime, Anywhere Access</h3>
  <p>Available on both desktop and the SAP SuccessFactors Mobile app, employees can complete benefits enrollment from any location using a mobile-friendly platform that helps ensure a seamless experience across devices.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c77980d26be6e40ac83dd9b643d8a7c3585a72b5.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c77980d26be6e40ac83dd9b643d8a7c3585a72b5.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1c77980d26be6e40ac83dd9b643d8a7c3585a72b5.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Screenshots of benefits enrollment on mobile device and desktop" src="./media_1c77980d26be6e40ac83dd9b643d8a7c3585a72b5.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="452">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>Benefits enrollment on a mobile device or desktop. Click to enlarge.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="employee-educational-resources">Employee Educational Resources</h3>
  <p>Simplified on-screen access to additional resources and information helps employees better understand their benefits and can promote more informed decision-making throughout the enrollment process.</p>
  <p>Side-by-side benefit plan comparisons of costs and plan details help employees assess their plan options and select the best-fit plan. Localizable instructional text on each page helps ensure that the benefits and enrollment processes are well understood. Additionally, flexible options for defining contribution amounts within the IRS limits can make it easier for employees to make decisions regarding savings plans and pension elections.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a34b6a531c49ffa414de06cd26af9eae0983046c.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a34b6a531c49ffa414de06cd26af9eae0983046c.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1a34b6a531c49ffa414de06cd26af9eae0983046c.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Screenshot showing flexible options for defining HSA contribution amount" src="./media_1a34b6a531c49ffa414de06cd26af9eae0983046c.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="601">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>Flexible options for defining HSA contribution amount. Click to enlarge.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="consolidated-benefits-enrollment-process">Consolidated Benefits Enrollment Process</h3>
  <p>Employees can complete all benefits-related tasks including reviewing and updating dependents, completing health declarations, enrolling in benefits, managing beneficiaries, and more through a single consolidated process, helping to improve employee engagement and satisfaction.</p>
  <p><a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2024/03/72d228c0-b77e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html?url_id=ctabutton-us-hcm-benefits-demo">Watch the demo</a> to learn more about the new enrollment experience in SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central Global Benefits.</p>
  <p>To learn about all the other innovations in the SAP SuccessFactors first half 2024 release, read the <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2024/04/300e8c6d-b77e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">release highlights brochure</a> and watch the <a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2024/04/8c907f14-b77e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">1H 2024 release highlights video</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Nicole Ramirez is senior director of Product Marketing at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-employee-central</category>
            <category>news-tag/ux</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP SuccessFactors First Half 2024 Release: Make Every Employee a Success Story]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-successfactors-first-half-2024-release</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-successfactors-first-half-2024-release</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[To help take HR to the next level, the SAP SuccessFactors first half 2024 release delivers more than 250 features and enhancements.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_115cc4b7786cb688433caf45dec5bf248f041afdb.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_115cc4b7786cb688433caf45dec5bf248f041afdb.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_115cc4b7786cb688433caf45dec5bf248f041afdb.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP SuccessFactors First Half 2024 Release: Make Every Employee a Success Story" src="./media_115cc4b7786cb688433caf45dec5bf248f041afdb.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-successfactors-first-half-2024-release-make-every-employee-a-success-story">SAP SuccessFactors First Half 2024 Release: Make Every Employee a Success Story</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Success can take many forms. It’s achieving AI-driven results faster and smarter. It’s unlocking more meaningful and aspirational career development experiences. It’s empowering employees and managers through simple HR-related tasks in the flow of work, freeing up more productive time across the organization.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>And for you and your business, you can tell all those success stories – and more – with the SAP SuccessFactors HCM suite and our first half 2024 release.</p>
  <p>As your organization and employees begin to embrace AI, <a href="/topics/human-resources">HR</a> has the opportunity to drive new levels of employee productivity, engagement, and growth. SAP SuccessFactors HCM can give you everything you need – the global foundation, skills framework, people-first experiences, and purpose-built AI capabilities – to help take HR to the next level. With the SAP SuccessFactors first half 2024 release, we are delivering more than 250 innovative features and enhancements.</p>
  <h2 id="sap-business-ai">SAP Business AI</h2>
  <p>In 1H 2024, we are thrilled to introduce more than 25 new AI capabilities to enable better employee experiences and new levels of productivity.</p>
  <p>Among these capabilities include the ability for applicants to provide skills during the application process. This can enable recruiters to see a skills compatibility for each applicant based on matching the applicant’s skills and the job requisition, helping improve applicant screening and time to hire. Furthermore, personalization in SAP SuccessFactors Opportunity Marketplace is enhanced with new AI-driven recommendation categories, “Ignite Your Role” and “Reach Your Aspirations.” These guided experiences can enable employees to proactively take steps to reach their development goals.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e755ea739e2394a3bec10a53f644e2d9cd718123.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e755ea739e2394a3bec10a53f644e2d9cd718123.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1e755ea739e2394a3bec10a53f644e2d9cd718123.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Screenshot of the assisted screening and skills match capabilities" src="./media_1e755ea739e2394a3bec10a53f644e2d9cd718123.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="803" height="521">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>Assisted screening and skills match available in 1H 2024 release. Click to enlarge.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Generative AI continues to be embedded across the SAP SuccessFactors HCM suite, including new capabilities to help employees create ready-made performance and development goals and AI-assisted writing to help improve the quality, clarity, and conciseness of writing across a variety of areas within SAP SuccessFactors solutions.</p>
  <p>Further, with this release, insights based on an employee’s compensation and job history are available to help support managers in having effective and well-informed compensation discussions.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="the-ai-copilot-that-truly-understands-your-business">The AI copilot that truly understands your business</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/ai-assistant.html">Meet Joule</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>We have also added more than 15 new <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/ai-assistant.html">Joule</a> capabilities in this release to help both managers and employees get work done in a conversational way, such as creating or changing a position, creating spot awards, clocking in and out, and viewing pay statements as well as time capabilities like requesting time off, checking leave balances, and syncing holidays to Outlook calendars while managers can review and approve time off. Further, employees can now clock in and out using Joule, Microsoft Teams, or the SAP SuccessFactors Mobile app.</p>
  <h2 id="sap-successfactors-employee-central">SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central</h2>
  <p>We are excited to unveil two new people profile experiences – the profile preview and the spotlight view. The profile preview can provide a snapshot of key areas of the employee profile, including job, manager, location, and contact details, to quickly view and connect with others. Additionally, the spotlight view can showcase employee skills and competencies, mentoring and target roles, and other relevant personal and organizational information.</p>
  <p>We are also introducing a new org chart experience with a refreshed look and feel. Available on desktop and mobile, users can explore their organizational structure with improved expand and collapse capabilities, which helps provide full accessibility to an employee’s profile preview, with an option to open the new spotlight view.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b181ba5a94a8b936ff644a1c243245079ecbbab4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b181ba5a94a8b936ff644a1c243245079ecbbab4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1b181ba5a94a8b936ff644a1c243245079ecbbab4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Screenshot of the new org chart experience" src="./media_1b181ba5a94a8b936ff644a1c243245079ecbbab4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="576">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>The new org chart experience. Click to enlarge.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Customers can now automatically process new hires from SAP SuccessFactors Recruiting and SAP SuccessFactors Onboarding into SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central. This capability helps further reduce the time to hire, which is especially important with mass, seasonal, and high-volume hiring.</p>
  <h2 id="sap-successfactors-employee-central-global-benefits">SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central Global Benefits</h2>
  <p>With this release, we are pleased to introduce a new benefits enrollment experience for insurance, savings, and pension benefit types. Available on both desktop and mobile, the guided experience for benefits elections can give employees increased convenience with improved navigation and increased confidence with side-by-side plan comparisons and embedded instructional text. Additionally, employees can update dependent information and manage beneficiaries directly from the benefits enrollment process, which helps further streamline the enrollment experience.</p>
  <h2 id="sap-successfactors-time-tracking">SAP SuccessFactors Time Tracking</h2>
  <p>We are thrilled to share the launch of a new time sheet experience that integrates the latest version of My Timesheet in SAP S/4HANA with SAP SuccessFactors. Employees can now record time for payroll, as well as against activities and cost objects, from a single time sheet across applications. This helps organizations leverage real-time connectivity between HR and finance operations to keep track of employee activity and labor costs and to pay employees accurately and on time.</p>
  <p>Additionally, a new monthly calendar view for time sheets can give employees and managers a complete picture of recorded time over a month. Users can drill down into specific days and submit or approve time for pay periods beyond a week, such as biweekly or monthly.</p>
  <p>For managers, a new time approval center helps simplify approvals with a centralized dashboard highlighting anomalies for swift resolution. Managers can monitor team working hours effectively, helping to ensure accurate and timely payroll processing.</p>
  <h2 id="sap-successfactors-onboarding">SAP SuccessFactors Onboarding</h2>
  <p>With enhancements to the onboarding journey experience, new hires can now use the new Your Onboarding Checklist page to reference and complete all tasks – onboarding data collection, compliance tasks, additional onboarding tasks, and exploring the onboarding guide – from one place with a single view. Available for new hires, rehires, internal hires, and employees with global assignments, this improved experience can save time for onboarding participants while helping to ensure productivity from the start.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e12cd49909a64b18778552665ee0147fcacdc707.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e12cd49909a64b18778552665ee0147fcacdc707.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1e12cd49909a64b18778552665ee0147fcacdc707.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Screenshot of the new onboarding journey experience" src="./media_1e12cd49909a64b18778552665ee0147fcacdc707.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="576">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>The new onboarding journey experience. Click to enlarge.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>And that’s only a fraction of all the innovations we’re bringing to customers in 1H 2024. There’s much more in the release, including new and exciting updates in:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Generative AI and Joule capabilities</li>
    <li>SAP SuccessFactors Opportunity Marketplace</li>
    <li>SAP SuccessFactors Compensation</li>
    <li>SAP SuccessFactors Succession &#x26; Development</li>
    <li>SAP SuccessFactors Incentive Management</li>
    <li>SAP SuccessFactors Work Zone</li>
  </ul>
  <p>Read the <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2024/04/300e8c6d-b77e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">SAP SuccessFactors first half 2024 release highlights brochure</a> and watch the <a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2024/04/8c907f14-b77e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">1H 2024 release highlights video</a> to find out more.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Bianka Woelke is group vice president of Application Product Management at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-employee-central</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors-hcm-suite</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-onboarding</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-opportunity-marketplace</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-recruiting</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Convista Harmonizes Workplace Culture with SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central and SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/convista-harmonizes-workplace-culture-with-sap-successfactors</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/convista-harmonizes-workplace-culture-with-sap-successfactors</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Convista's people culture and respected brand built on trust and transparency is supported by SAP S/4HANA Cloud and SAP SuccessFactors.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11a18052b07fa380b0a184821d2508dc2d57d515a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11a18052b07fa380b0a184821d2508dc2d57d515a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_11a18052b07fa380b0a184821d2508dc2d57d515a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Convista Harmonizes Workplace Culture with SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central and SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition" src="./media_11a18052b07fa380b0a184821d2508dc2d57d515a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="convista-harmonizes-workplace-culture-with-sap-successfactors-employee-central-and-sap-s4hana-cloud-public-edition">Convista Harmonizes Workplace Culture with SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central and SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>In a merger between two well-matched organizations, cultural integration can be the key to successfully transforming into a single high-performing entity ready to take on new opportunities. Notably, more than a few high-profile mergers have failed due to cultural incompatibility. Add a third organization into the merger and the cultural complexities increase exponentially. But some multi-organization mergers do successfully navigate these challenges and reap the transformational benefits.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="https://www.convista.com/en/">Convista</a>, a consultancy and SAP partner based in Cologne, Germany, emerged stronger and better positioned to serve its clients following a <a href="https://www.convista.com/en/news/axxiome-health-and-enowa-become-part-of-the-new-convista/">recent merger</a> that brought together three former consultancies: Axxiome Health, ConVista Consulting, and enowa. With 25 years of experience delivering transformation projects to its clients, Convista used that expertise in its own rebranding to present its capabilities to clients and employees: a vibrant people culture as well as a respected and trusted brand supported by <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/s4hana.html">SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition</a> for ERP and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/employee-central-hris/features.html">SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central</a> for core HR.</p>
  <p>“Trust and transparency are common values that we share at Convista,” declares Convista CEO Martin Hinz. “Combined with a dynamic team spirit and passion, it’s what we bring to our clients every day.”</p>
  <p>With a workforce of around 1,200 employees, Convista has made a name for itself through its dedication and expertise providing end-to-end solutions to clients throughout the world with a presence in Germany, Austria, Switzerland, Poland, Spain, Brazil, Israel, and further locations across the globe. It supports client projects primarily in four sectors: insurance, industry, healthcare, and energy/utilities. In recent years, Convista has twice been awarded SAP <a href="https://www.convista.com/en/news/for-the-second-time-in-a-row-sap-partner-of-the-year-award-in-the-financial-services-sector/">Partner of the Year</a> in the Financial Services sector.</p>
  <p>“At Convista you meet everyone on the same level, independent of your skill level or where you are in your career,” says Stefanie Weber, project lead of People and Culture – HR Systems, Convista. “Also, when we’re working with customers, we try to approach them at eye level, which makes quite a good working environment. The implementation of SAP SuccessFactors came as a natural extension to our brand and our culture.”</p>
  <h2 id="the-challenges-of-data-siloed-in-three-systems">The Challenges of Data Siloed in Three Systems</h2>
  <p>Weber says one of the reasons she joined Convista in 2012 while studying business at university was the high priority its leaders place on trust and transparency, values that permeate the entire organization and empower employees in their work and career development. “Trust is one of our main values,” she underscores. “Also, the trust that people are willing to do their best to get motivated and move the company ahead.”</p>
  <p>Convista grew quickly both organically and as a result of mergers with other consultancies. In 2019, IT service provider Axxiome Health joined the ConVista Group to deepen the organization’s expertise in the health insurance sector. In 2021, enowa joined the group, infusing its knowledge of industries and insurance. With the mergers complete, the incipient organization became <a href="https://www.convista.com/en/news/axxiome-health-and-enowa-become-part-of-the-new-convista/">the new Convista</a> on January 1, 2023.</p>
  <p>Though team members were highly motivated to collaborate from the start, Convista’s vision for itself as a modern organization was held back in both its daily work for projects and internal services. Using disparate tools based on older technology and a patchwork of third-party solutions that lacked integration proved to be inefficient and unsuitable as a basis for decision-making.</p>
  <p>“Whenever we wanted to have a report, even something as simple as a headcount, we always had to go into three different systems, collect the data, and report on that,” Weber recalls. “It’s just one of the many examples of why we really urgently needed one IT platform.”</p>
  <h2 id="project-one-achieves-milestone-integration">Project ONE Achieves Milestone Integration</h2>
  <p>To build a strong foundation for future growth, Convista embarked on “Project ONE” with the goal to have one digital platform flexible and powerful enough for the entire organization. For this, it chose SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition and SAP SuccessFactors solutions with self-service capabilities for employees to log time-off.</p>
  <p>Overall, implementing SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central with SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition can result in streamlined HR processes; end-to-end integration with seamless connectivity between HR and finance functions for accurate and up-to-date employee data across the organization; greater transparency of data for analytics and reporting on workforce trends, costs, and profitability to enable better strategic planning and resource allocation; and compliance with regulatory requirements and data security.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-successfactors-solutions-can-fuel-the-success-of-every-individual-and-drive-org-agility-at-scale">SAP SuccessFactors solutions can fuel the success of every individual and drive org agility at scale</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm.html">Learn how</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Among the key advantages is the ability for employees to access their own HR-related information, such as personal details and time-off balances. This self-service capability helps empower employees, improve transparency, and enhance the overall employee experience.</p>
  <p>Convista’s project team decided for a phased approach to the implementation by first introducing the SAP solutions in Poland and later in Germany, Austria, and Switzerland – with SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition planned to launch in the German-speaking countries during the course of 2024. To optimize success, the project team used the combined best practices of Convista and SAP and hosted regular meetings that provided clear communication to steer the project. “We were always aligned on the requirements of the other teams,” says Weber, who managed the HR workstream. “We all knew the main goal of the implementation. This was helpful for everyone on the project.”</p>
  <p>In-house experts from Convista certified on SAP SuccessFactors solutions contributed valuable knowledge for the implementation. Consultants from SAP Services and Support successfully integrated the cost center replication from SAP S/4HANA Cloud to SAP SuccessFactors and the workforce replication from SAP SuccessFactors to SAP S/4HANA Cloud, and delivered a detailed administration guide on the integration setup for Convista. Additionally, they provided an overview, the architecture guidance, and the navigation through major hurdles in performing the configuration to set up identity access governence (IAG), identity provisioning service (IPS), and identity authentication services (IAS). The SAP Early Adopter Care program supported Convista for the master data integration (MDI) during the implementation and helped to solve all roadblocks efficiently.</p>
  <p>On January 1, 2023, Convista’s 80-person team in Poland was the first to go live with the new SAP solutions. “It was really a great experience for them and quite an advancement,” says Weber, citing the benefits of the new solutions that provide optimizations and intuitive workflows. The project took a pivotal turn on January 1, 2024, with the launch of SAP SuccessFactors solutions for Convista’s 800 employees in the German-speaking countries.</p>
  <p>“The biggest milestone was to have [SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition and SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central] speaking with each other,” says Weber, who emphasizes how valuable it is for the team “to have an end-to-end process within one platform.” With an integrated IT platform in place, she says that it is no longer necessary to do workflows, authorizations, or any other processes in other systems.</p>
  <p>The seamless synchronization of data by using a common data model for SAP business applications helps reduce the need for manual data entry and redundant processes. This means, for example, employee data that is maintained in SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central is available in real-time in SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition; while master data, like cost center data, flows seamlessly from SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition to SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central. Eliminating data silos enables the HR and finance teams to work with consistent, accurate data for all-important employment decisions and legal reporting obligations.</p>
  <p>Now Convista’s team is unified in its brand, values, spirit – and employee data.</p>
  <h2 id="more-transparency-and-intuitive-workflows-are-just-the-beginning">More Transparency and Intuitive Workflows Are Just the Beginning</h2>
  <p>Feedback has been overwhelmingly positive, according to Weber, with employees speaking favorably about the improved transparency and workflows. “The first thing I heard from everyone was, well, this is simple and intuitive. They were so happy about it,” she says. “They are big fans of the mobile application. They find it very transparent and easy to use.”</p>
  <p>For some colleagues, the new solution lets them view their own data for the first time. “When we went live, everyone was viewing their profile,” says Weber. “This was also quite new that you are able to see what data is maintained for your person, your address, but also job information – to view it and have this transparency. People like this very much and also the ability to have the self-services in SAP SuccessFactors.”</p>
  <p>To strengthen communication between HR and employees, Convista will bring more people processes onto the new digital platform. In fact, the team very recently implemented the SAP SuccessFactors Performance &#x26; Goals solution for annual employee appraisals, goal setting, and project feedback. “It’s just the beginning,” Weber says. “There’s still a lot of work ahead of us.”</p>
  <p>Hinz says, “We have been careful to preserve our workplace culture during the transformation. Now that we are rebranded as one organization, we are seeing the benefits of that early effort. With SAP, we now have the digital platform to build people-centered processes that advance our vision as a unified, high-performing organization serving our clients.”</p>
  <p>Find out more about <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/solutions.html?url_id=ctabutton-us-hcm-convista">SAP SuccessFactors solutions</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Jacqueline Prause is a journalist at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-sap-news-delivered-to-your-inbox-once-a-week">Get the latest SAP news delivered to your inbox once a week</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/nl/sap-news-center-newsletter/index.html">Sign up today</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-employee-central</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Eastman Energizes HR Reporting to Deliver One-Stop Insights to Leaders]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/eastman-hr-reporting-deliver-insights-to-leaders</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/eastman-hr-reporting-deliver-insights-to-leaders</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Eastman accelerated HR reporting for improved efficiency and insights using story reports in SAP SuccessFactors People Analytics. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>topic/data-analytics</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-preferred-success</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-employee-central</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-people-analytics</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-recruiting</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central Grows to 6,000 Customers]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/sap-successfactors-employee-central-6000-customers</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/sap-successfactors-employee-central-6000-customers</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is thrilled to announce more than 6,000 organizations have chosen SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central to elevate their core HR operations.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1dfaa5052208192ed8d56df80f5f16592b8c93bf7.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1dfaa5052208192ed8d56df80f5f16592b8c93bf7.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1dfaa5052208192ed8d56df80f5f16592b8c93bf7.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central Grows to 6,000 Customers" src="./media_1dfaa5052208192ed8d56df80f5f16592b8c93bf7.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-successfactors-employee-central-grows-to-6000-customers">SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central Grows to 6,000 Customers</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Today, SAP is thrilled to announce more than 6,000 organizations have chosen SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central, our cloud HRIS software, to help elevate their core HR operations. This milestone demonstrates strong momentum in the SAP SuccessFactors community, which includes leaders and business users that are driving strategies that put people at the center of business.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>People and culture are increasingly becoming some of the most critical aspects of an organization. It’s what attracts new talent to join and keeps current employees growing and developing. Whether that’s scaling up, diving into a new market segment, or pivoting to meet changing customer demands, having the right people in the right roles determines success.</p>
  <p>From midsize organizations to large enterprises, having a single view of employees across all countries is a differentiator. It’s no longer about just maintaining a system of record. It’s <em>the</em> foundation to manage the total workforce – from setting organizational goals to establishing the talent intelligence that’s needed to build a workforce that is agile and adaptable.</p>
  <p>Organizations of all sizes, industries, and regions use SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central to help improve experiences for managers and employees, automate compliance for more than 100 locales, manage benefits and absence management, and standardize processes across multiple locations. Here’s what some of our customers are saying:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>“SAP SuccessFactors is our people backbone. It provides the common processes, systems, and data that let us create engaging people experiences at scale.” – <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/customer-stories/nestle.html#:~:text=Nestl%C3%A9&#x27;s%20journey%20with%20SAP%20began,to%20workforce%20and%20talent%20management.">Giancarlo Pala, head of IT HR / Nestlé S.A.</a></li>
    <li>“With the SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central solution, the company now has a single HR and payroll system providing a single source of truth, instant access to employee data, automated approval workflows, and enhanced reporting – available on the go, anytime, anywhere.” – <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/customer-stories/emirates-fast-food-company.html">Binay Moktan, senior HR director, Emirates Fast Food Company LLC</a></li>
    <li>“The SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central solution, branded at Woodbridge as Teammate Central, supports the company’s core HR processes and provides teammates with intuitive, fast access to HR self-services. The solution’s localization capabilities support Woodbridge’s operations at 50 locations in more than 10 countries, while its position management feature helps smooth the plant acquisition process.” – <a href="https://www.sap.com/asset/dynamic/2022/11/e4f78c1e-4f7e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Peter Martin, vice president, Total Rewards, The Woodbridge Group</a></li>
    <li>“Using SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central, we have mitigated the need for manual monthly and quarterly data input efforts from our local HR teams and can now automatically generate reports whenever required with access to global workforce data.” – <a href="https://www.sap.com/asset/dynamic/2023/07/b65d2def-827e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Jing Yin, global HR strategy manager, OMRON Corporation</a></li>
  </ul>
  <p>Additional organizations, including <a href="/2023/09/versuni-hxm-cloud-erp-strong-data-foundation">Versuni</a>, <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/customer-stories/roehm.html">Röhm</a>, <a href="https://www.sap.com/asset/dynamic/2023/04/7a53dae4-6c7e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Purolator</a>, <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2022/01/88cc7a19-117e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Taylor’s Education Group</a>, and many more, have chosen SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central to help manage their workforce.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="streamline-core-hr-processes-with-cloud-hris-software-from-sap-successfactors">Streamline core HR processes with cloud HRIS software from SAP SuccessFactors</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/employee-central-hris.html">Discover how</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="continued-improvements-to-enhance-the-employee-experience">Continued Improvements to Enhance the Employee Experience</h2>
  <p>Since SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central was introduced over a decade ago, we have continued to adapt and innovate to help our customers meet the changing expectations of their employees and the rising demands from HR to deliver greater insights and data.</p>
  <p>Customers using SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central can have access to:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>A single foundation for HR, with consistent and standardized HR processes for over 200 countries and territories around the globe</li>
    <li>A proactive approach to worldwide regulatory compliance with localization delivered and maintained for more than 100 locales</li>
    <li>Self-service functionality to help support automation, improve data quality, and elevate HR service delivery with efficient, real-time processes</li>
    <li>A consumer-grade user experience with live insights to help make data-driven decisions</li>
  </ul>
  <p>The newest innovations in the <a href="/2023/10/sap-successfactors-second-half-2023-release">2H 2023 release</a> include:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Simplified self-services allow employees and managers to make updates directly from the SAP SuccessFactors home page. For example, employees can quickly update their chosen name and personal pronouns, while managers can initiate a transfer, promotion, location change, and more</li>
  </ul>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_13adf4267e650d0083629bd18a1e43de019fe85d1.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_13adf4267e650d0083629bd18a1e43de019fe85d1.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_13adf4267e650d0083629bd18a1e43de019fe85d1.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_13adf4267e650d0083629bd18a1e43de019fe85d1.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="576">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>Click to enlarge.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Self-service actions are integrated into the flow of work, including within Microsoft Teams, SAP SuccessFactors Work Zone, and Joule, SAP’s AI-powered copilot. With use cases across the SAP SuccessFactors Human Experience Management (HXM) Suite, such as the ability to clock in and out and to view pay statements from within Microsoft Teams, employees can quickly complete their most critical HR tasks without switching applications.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1586494fbb4371898380235e9a5d919f3e4e587f8.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1586494fbb4371898380235e9a5d919f3e4e587f8.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1586494fbb4371898380235e9a5d919f3e4e587f8.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Screenshot of SAP SuccessFactors task in Microsoft Teams" src="./media_1586494fbb4371898380235e9a5d919f3e4e587f8.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="576">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>Click to enlarge.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Learn more about the latest <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/innovations.html">SAP SuccessFactors product innovations</a> and visit the <a href="https://www.sap.com/events/successconnect/virtual.html?campaigncode=CRM-YI23-HXM-2055448&#x26;source=text-glo-SAPNews">SuccessConnect Virtual</a> event site for a replay of the keynote, expert sessions, and other on-demand content.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Maryann Abbajay is chief revenue officer at SAP SuccessFactors.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-employee-central</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Leveraging SAP SuccessFactors Solutions: Five Ways User Experience Drives DEI&B Success]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/five-ways-sap-successfactors-ux-drives-deib</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/five-ways-sap-successfactors-ux-drives-deib</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP SuccessFactor's focus on UX helps businesses advance DEI&B by offering an interface that can address employee needs in the flow of work.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-employee-central</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-learning</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-performance-goals</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-workforce-analytics</category>
            <category>news-tag/ux</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Customers Realize the Power of Connected Cloud HR and ERP]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/sap-customers-realize-power-of-connected-cloud-hr-erp</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/sap-customers-realize-power-of-connected-cloud-hr-erp</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP customers connect SAP SuccessFactors solutions for HR with SAP S/4HANA Cloud to improve end-to-end business processes and experiences.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_12c8a896617a0e516f610561e9bf9c127d0a779ff.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_12c8a896617a0e516f610561e9bf9c127d0a779ff.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_12c8a896617a0e516f610561e9bf9c127d0a779ff.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Customers Realize the Power of Connected Cloud HR and ERP" src="./media_12c8a896617a0e516f610561e9bf9c127d0a779ff.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-customers-realize-the-power-of-connected-cloud-hr-and-erp">SAP Customers Realize the Power of Connected Cloud HR and ERP</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>SAP customers are unlocking strategic value across the organization by using a single cloud platform to connect HR, run on <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm.html?campaigncode=CRM-YI23-HXM-2053446&#x26;source=text-glo-SAPNews">SAP SuccessFactors</a> solutions, with finance and other business operations that use <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/s4hana.html?campaigncode=crm-ya22-int-1517075&#x26;source=ppc-de-google_ads-search-71700000111912410-58700008464076060-s4hana_s4fin-x-&#x26;dfa=1&#x26;gclid=EAIaIQobChMImKnKw_7tgQMV94ZoCR1j7QLcEAAYASAAEgJPEfD_BwE&#x26;gclsrc=aw.ds?campaigncode=CRM-YI23-HXM-2053446&#x26;source=text-glo-SAPNews">SAP S/4HANA Cloud</a>. In various industries, large and midsized organizations alike are discovering the power of having a common people and skills data model that is used across the entire organization. The combined effectiveness of SAP SuccessFactors solutions and SAP S/4HANA Cloud is moving leading brands to new levels of strategic insight and organizational agility.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>With this integrated approach, real-time people data from the SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central solution is automatically consumed by SAP S/4HANA Cloud and other SAP cloud applications. This “single source of truth” helps to improve end-to-end business processes, experiences, and insights for the organization. Learn more in this SAP Community <a href="https://blogs.sap.com/2023/08/07/sap-successfactors-and-sap-s-4hana-cloud-public-edition-supercharge-your-hr-and-erp-investments-now-on-demand/?campaigncode=CRM-YI23-HXM-2053446&#x26;source=text-glo-SAPNews">blog</a>.</p>
  <p>Maryann Abbajay, chief revenue officer at SAP SuccessFactors, spoke with some of these customers at <a href="https://www.sap.com/events/successconnect/virtual.html?campaigncode=CRM-YI23-HXM-2055448&#x26;source=text-glo-SAPNews?campaigncode=CRM-YI23-HXM-2053446&#x26;source=text-glo-SAPNews">SuccessConnect</a> to find out how they are leveraging the combined power of SAP SuccessFactors solutions and SAP S/4HANA Cloud to overcome business challenges and grow their organizations with people at the center of business. “These organizations show how HR and finance come together to enable business transformation while keeping employee experience at the center,” she underscored.</p>
  <h2 id="pandora-becomes-a-future-ready-organization">Pandora Becomes a Future-Ready Organization</h2>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="catch-up-on-this-years-event-with-successconnect-virtual-on-demand">Catch up on this year’s event with SuccessConnect Virtual on-demand</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/events/successconnect/virtual.html?campaigncode=CRM-YI23-HXM-2055448&#x26;source=text-glo-SAPNews?campaigncode=CRM-YI23-HXM-2053446&#x26;source=ctabutton-glo-SAPNews">Watch now</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Connecting people in the moments that matter is at the heart of <a href="https://us.pandora.net/">Pandora</a>, the world’s largest jewelry brand. Based in Copenhagen, Denmark, Pandora employs 32,000 people worldwide. With 6,500 points of sale, including 2,500 concept stores, Pandora depends on the experience of its brick-and-mortar stores, which account for the majority of its sales.</p>
  <p>Three years ago, Pandora began its transformation from an analog retailer to a future-ready organization. It set out to strengthen and harmonize the global HR system landscape with an implementation of SAP SuccessFactors solutions to gain efficiency in how the company hires, manages, and develops employees worldwide, thus replacing a multitude of local applications.</p>
  <p>“We used the SAP SuccessFactors portfolio as a driver of transformation,” said Mihael Šutalo, vice president of People Technology, Pandora. “This is transforming the experience. The future integration of SAP S/4HANA Cloud with SAP SuccessFactors solutions will give us a tremendous opportunity to manage our workforce and manage our revenue model in a completely different way.”</p>
  <h2 id="bt-group-connects-people-for-good">BT Group Connects People for Good</h2>
  <p><a href="https://www.bt.com/about">BT Group</a>, the world’s oldest telecommunications company, recently modernized its HR information systems to provide a digital colleague experience for its 100,000 employees working in 44 countries. “In 2021, we started what we call our I-Connect program,” said Elaine Bergin, director of Colleague Experience and Delivery, BT Group. The program name highlights BT Group’s purpose: “We connect for good.”</p>
  <p>The new colleague experience, launched in 2022, now uses the SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central solution, reporting and analytics, and the full suite of talent and learning management solutions to support the organization’s big focus on skills. BT Group also uses SAP SuccessFactors and SAP Fieldglass solutions to manage a contingent workforce of 60,000 additional employees.</p>
  <p>Bergin said, “Through our SAP SuccessFactors journey, we’re in a great place with a single master source of truth on our colleague and contingent workforce data – and our organizational hierarchy.”</p>
  <h2 id="brightspeed-manages-rapid-growth-and-contingent-workforce">Brightspeed Manages Rapid Growth and Contingent Workforce</h2>
  <p><a href="https://www.brightspeedplans.com/about">Brightspeed</a> is a telecommunications company that provides affordable, quality internet in rural areas of the U.S. Since it started in 2022 with 30 permanent employees, Brightspeed has grown exponentially through acquisition. Today, it has 4,200 employees using SAP solutions and a sizable contingent workforce. To manage growth, Brightspeed implemented SAP SuccessFactors solutions, SAP Fieldglass solutions, and SAP S/4HANA Cloud.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="predict-manage-and-create-a-future-ready-workforce-with-sap-successfactors">Predict, manage, and create a future-ready workforce with SAP SuccessFactors</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm.html?campaigncode=CRM-YI23-HXM-2053446&#x26;source=text-glo-SAPNews">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Greg Williams, director of Human Resources Information Systems, Brightspeed, summarized the value of an integrated approach for the organization: “Finance is up and running on SAP S/4HANA and with SAP Fieldglass solutions. We import that data into SAP SuccessFactors Learning, so our contractors can train on compliance and technical training. The SAP S/4HANA data is integrated into <a href="https://api.sap.com/package/SuccessFactorsEmployeeCentralwithThirdPartyTimeVendorWorkForceSoftwareWFS/overview">WFS</a>, which is our time system. We capture millions of dollars of project costs. Those are sent back to SAP S/4HANA on a pay-for-period basis.”</p>
  <h2 id="versuni-gains-agility-with-hxm-and-connected-cloud-erp">Versuni Gains Agility with HXM and Connected Cloud ERP</h2>
  <p><a href="https://www.versuni.com/">Versuni</a>, formerly known as Philipps Domestic Appliances, is a consumer products company with the purpose to help people turn their houses into homes. It took the unique opportunity of reinventing itself as an independent company to transform its entire technology landscape. To succeed in a dynamic, consumer marketplace, it had to adopt best-of-suite applications that power advanced, digital-first consumer goods organizations.</p>
  <p>By connecting SAP S/4HANA Cloud to SAP SuccessFactors solutions, Versuni has achieved three key benefits: a seamless user journey based on a single source of truth across the entire landscape; increased visibility achieved from the integration with other systems, especially finance; and improved reporting, which is leading to better decision-making. Lokesh Rastogi, IT platform leader for Finance and HR at Versuni, summarized: “It’s one source of truth, one system, and one number.”</p>
  <h2 id="nestlé-creates-engaging-people-experiences-at-scale">Nestlé Creates Engaging People Experiences at Scale</h2>
  <p><a href="https://www.nestle.com/">Nestlé</a>, one of the world’s largest food and beverage companies, is using RISE with SAP to help advance its digital transformation. With 275,000 employees in 188 countries, Nestlé focused on the modernization of its HR systems. SAP SuccessFactors solutions now enable it to standardize and automate HR processes and provide a personalized employee experience from recruitment to retirement. Nestlé plans to continue its journey to migrate its entire business operations to <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/s4hana-private-edition.html">SAP S/4HANA Cloud</a> with finance and procurement already live. To learn more, watch this <a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2023/09/5c433416-8d7e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html?campaigncode=CRM-YI23-HXM-2053446&#x26;source=text-glo-SAPNews">video</a>.</p>
  <p>Giancarlo Pala, head of IT/HR, Nestlé S.A., said, “SAP SuccessFactors is our people backbone. It provides the common processes, systems, and data that let us create engaging people experiences at scale.”</p>
  <h2 id="accelerating-business-performance">Accelerating Business Performance</h2>
  <p>SAP customers are experiencing firsthand the value of having HR and finance connected on a single cloud platform to help improve speed, accuracy, and insights. This integration can extend beyond the data to connect business processes and employee experiences across all business areas. To find out more about the benefits of connected cloud HR and ERP, watch <a href="https://www.sap.com/events/successconnect/virtual.html?campaigncode=CRM-YI23-HXM-2055448&#x26;source=text-glo-SAPNews?campaigncode=CRM-YI23-HXM-2053446&#x26;source=ctabutton-glo-SAPNews">SuccessConnect Virtual</a> on demand.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="follow-sap-news-on-linkedin">Follow SAP News on LinkedIn</h3>
        <p><em><a href="">Connect with us</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fieldglass</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-employee-central</category>
            <category>sap-event/successconnect</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Three Highlights from SuccessConnect 2023]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/three-highlights-from-successconnect-2023</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/three-highlights-from-successconnect-2023</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SuccessConnect 2023 celebrated the HR community, discussed what AI means for the future of work, and shared ideas. Here are the highlights.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_19ceecf9802c64707f3aee1c60f9ef5908b6cd90d.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_19ceecf9802c64707f3aee1c60f9ef5908b6cd90d.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_19ceecf9802c64707f3aee1c60f9ef5908b6cd90d.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Three Highlights from SuccessConnect 2023" src="./media_19ceecf9802c64707f3aee1c60f9ef5908b6cd90d.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="three-highlights-from-successconnect-2023">Three Highlights from SuccessConnect 2023</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Thousands of attendees came to Las Vegas, Nevada, to celebrate the HR community, discuss what artificial intelligence (AI) means for the future of work, and share new ideas for how to ignite the potential within every workforce and business.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Indeed, from the mainstage keynote and breakout sessions to networking with customers and partners, AI was at the center of every conversation. If you weren’t able to attend this year’s event, you can catch the latest product announcements and select content now available <a href="https://go3.events.sap.com/successconnect/virtual/2023/reg/flow/sap/sc23/catalog/page/catalog?tab.sessionplanned=1692641568884001cZ9d">on demand</a>.</p>
  <p>Here are three takeaways from this year’s SuccessConnect.</p>
  <h2 id="the-time-is-now-to-adopt-ai">The Time Is Now to Adopt AI</h2>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="igniting-workforce-potential-with-the-new-sap-successfactors-ai-innovations">Igniting Workforce Potential with the New SAP SuccessFactors AI Innovations</h3>
        <p><em><a href="/2023/10/new-sap-successfactors-ai-innovations-successconnect">Read keynote coverage</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As the pace of technological innovation continues to accelerate, organizations face an incredible opportunity to explore new ways to get work done – ways that take engagement and productivity to new heights for everyone at work. Special guest <a href="https://go3.events.sap.com/successconnect/virtual/2023/reg/flow/sap/sc23/catalog/page/catalog/session/1695684941523001eAp3">Josh Bersin</a>, global industry analyst and CEO of The Josh Bersin Company, discussed the urgent need for companies to get on board with AI, emphasizing how AI can help keep companies ahead of the curve by transforming the employee experience. Bersin also shared ways to increase everyone’s knowledge and confidence when it comes to adopting AI, as well as the real economic benefits organizations can achieve based on early case studies.</p>
  <p>In addition, Julia White, member of the Executive Board of SAP SE and chief marketing and solutions officer, shared what AI means for businesses today and <a href="https://go3.events.sap.com/successconnect/virtual/2023/reg/flow/sap/sc23/catalog/page/catalog/session/1695684941478001eFQ4">how SAP is embedding AI into its cloud HR solutions</a>. She talked about the latest addition to SAP Business AI, <a href="/2023/09/joule-new-generative-ai-assistant">Joule</a> – a natural-language, generative AI copilot designed to help improve the experiences of everyone at work by making it easy for users to find information, get answers to questions, navigate processes, and complete tasks related to HR as well as finance, supply chain, and customer relationship management. She emphasized how Joule, with its AI-powered insight and assistance, can help organizations unlock new levels of performance, productivity, and efficiency.</p>
  <h2 id="talent-intelligence-is-key-to-closing-skills-gaps">Talent Intelligence Is Key to Closing Skills Gaps</h2>
  <p>The power of talent intelligence has far-reaching implications for how organizations can more accurately and efficiently evaluate talent across all levels and address skills gaps. During the event, there was a lot of buzz around the general availability of the <a href="/2023/10/skills-based-organization-talent-intelligence-hub">talent intelligence hub</a>, an AI-powered skills framework that’s built into the foundation of <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/solutions.html?campaigncode=CRM-YI23-HXM-2055448&#x26;source=text-glo-SAPNews">SAP SuccessFactors Human Experience Management (HXM) Suite</a>. Now organizations can have the power and simplicity of a single skills model to fuel everything from recruiting and onboarding to learning and development, as well as performance and succession.</p>
  <p>Sam Passman, vice president, Product Management at SAP SuccessFactors, provided a comprehensive overview of the <a href="https://go3.events.sap.com/successconnect/virtual/2023/reg/flow/sap/sc23/catalog/page/catalog/session/1695684941379001elme">talent intelligence hub</a>, including how organizations can better understand and leverage the skills of their workforce. “An organization that is not focused on skills is going to be left behind,” he said. “Customers often struggle with having visibility into their full skills picture and having employee profile data integrated throughout talent management processes. The talent intelligence hub is how we are making sure our customers can match the right people, doing the right work, at the right time – truly helping them become skills-based organizations.”</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="put-your-people-at-the-center-of-everything-with-sap-successfactors">Put your people at the center of everything with SAP SuccessFactors</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In addition, Tim Gregory, managing director of HR Innovation and Workforce Technology at <a href="https://go3.events.sap.com/successconnect/virtual/2023/reg/flow/sap/sc23/catalog/page/catalog/session/1695684941731001exmK">Delta Air Lines</a>, shared how the company is using SAP SuccessFactors solutions, including the talent intelligence hub, to create personalized career development plans for employees based not only on the skills most important to Delta but also each individual’s capabilities, strengths, and aspirations.</p>
  <p>Other sessions provided tips for becoming a skills-based organization and focused on <a href="https://go3.events.sap.com/successconnect/virtual/2023/reg/flow/sap/sc23/catalog/page/catalog/session/1693098679964001yjIr">how to get ready for the talent intelligence hub</a> and use it to help guide actions across all areas of talent management and development. And, of course, a live demonstration brought the talent intelligence hub to life as part of the <a href="https://go3.events.sap.com/successconnect/virtual/2023/reg/flow/sap/sc23/catalog/page/catalog/session/1692366446499001bBgm">SuccessConnect keynote</a>.</p>
  <h2 id="a-powerful-cloud-foundation-drives-true-hr-transformation">A Powerful Cloud Foundation Drives True HR Transformation</h2>
  <p>Having a cloud-based HR foundation is key for achieving true HR transformation – the kind of transformation that makes data-driven insights, smarter decision-making, automation, and a positive employee experience a reality. At the event, Mihael Sutalo, vice president, People Technology at <a href="https://go3.events.sap.com/successconnect/virtual/2023/reg/flow/sap/sc23/catalog/page/catalog/session/1695672921270001Czuo">Pandora</a>, the world’s leading jewelry brand, shared how the company is digitalizing HR and adopting new technologies to create amazing employee experiences as a unified, global company. “We wanted to scale to future-proof the company, and we believe strongly in the power of the cloud,” he said. He explained how Pandora has successfully moved from a fragmented HR landscape to SAP SuccessFactors HXM Suite, improving the company’s ability to attract and retain top talent.</p>
  <p>Avery Williams, manager of HR Operations Strategy at <a href="https://go3.events.sap.com/successconnect/virtual/2023/reg/flow/sap/sc23/catalog/page/catalog/session/1693098680331001ybtw">Starbucks Corporation</a>, also discussed how the company modernized its core HR technology, service delivery, and employee and partner experience by migrating 250,000 employees and partners from the legacy, on-premise SAP ERP Human Capital Management solution to a new cloud-based platform with <a href="https://go3.events.sap.com/successconnect/virtual/2023/reg/flow/sap/sc23/catalog/page/catalog/session/1695684941222001ejfa">SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central</a>.</p>
  <p>In addition, Todd Asevedo, GVP, chief expert, SAP, shared a host of best practices for how customers can minimize risk and disruption as they <a href="https://go3.events.sap.com/successconnect/virtual/2023/reg/flow/sap/sc23/catalog/page/catalog/session/1693098680290001ycKR">make the move</a> from SAP ERP HCM to the cloud. He also outlined the various deployment options to help organizations understand the transition paths available for a smooth migration.</p>
  <p>Couldn’t attend the in-person event? You can get the best of SuccessConnect wherever you are! Be sure to access the <a href="https://go3.events.sap.com/successconnect/virtual/2023/reg/flow/sap/sc23/catalog/page/catalog?tab.sessionplanned=1692641568884001cZ9d&#x26;search.sessiontype=sessionType_keynote">keynotes</a>, <a href="https://go3.events.sap.com/successconnect/virtual/2023/reg/flow/sap/sc23/catalog/page/catalog?tab.sessionplanned=1692641568884001cZ9d&#x26;search.sessiontype=1693097660680001RkSd&#x26;search.sessiontype=1695686379399001hUNT">customer success stories</a>, and <a href="https://go3.events.sap.com/successconnect/virtual/2023/reg/flow/sap/sc23/catalog/page/catalog?tab.sessionplanned=1692641568884001cZ9d&#x26;search.sessiontype=1679388717208002sub4">expert sessions</a>, including road maps, product demos, and more, all available <a href="https://go3.events.sap.com/successconnect/virtual/2023/reg/flow/sap/sc23/catalog/page/catalog?tab.sessionplanned=1692641568884001cZ9d">on demand</a>. Plus, don’t forget to sign up to stay informed about the <a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/nl/successconnect/index.html">SuccessConnect event in 2024</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Lara Albert is global vice president of Solution Marketing for SAP SuccessFactors.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-sap-news-delivered-right-to-your-inbox">Get the latest SAP news delivered right to your inbox</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/nl/sap-news-center-newsletter/index.html">Sign up now</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-employee-central</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
            <category>sap-event/successconnect</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Versuni Gains Agility with HXM and Connected Cloud ERP as Strong Data Foundation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/versuni-hxm-cloud-erp-strong-data-foundation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/versuni-hxm-cloud-erp-strong-data-foundation</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Versuni achieved a successful HR transformation in 10 months, deploying SAP SuccessFactors solutions in a greenfield implementation.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>industry/consumer-goods-cpg</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>sap-award/sap-innovation-awards</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-employee-central</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-learning</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-work-zone</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Standard Chartered Gains Agility with Total Workforce Management]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/standard-chartered-total-workforce-solution</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/standard-chartered-total-workforce-solution</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Standard Chartered uses total workforce management with SAP SuccessFactors and SAP Fieldglass for one view of permanent and external workers.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/banking</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/external-workforce-management</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fieldglass</category>
            <category>sap-award/sap-innovation-awards</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-employee-central</category>
            <category>news-tag/total-workforce-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP SuccessFactors First Half 2023 Release: Skill-Centric Innovation to Build Your Future-Ready Workforce]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/sap-successfactors-first-half-2023-release</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/sap-successfactors-first-half-2023-release</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With the SAP SuccessFactors first half 2023 release, we continue to deliver on our promise to help build future-ready workforces. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/future-of-work</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-employee-central</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-opportunity-marketplace</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-work-zone</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[tesa Bonds Employees with an Innovative Digital HR Transformation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/tesa-bonds-employees-hr-transformation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/tesa-bonds-employees-hr-transformation</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[tesa chose SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central to build a single, harmonized global HR system to manage employee and company data worldwide.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-employee-central</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Milliken & Company Transforms HR in the Cloud]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/01/milliken-company-transforms-hr-cloud</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/01/milliken-company-transforms-hr-cloud</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Milliken & Company leveraged cloud HR solutions to create a sustainable workforce. Read to learn more about its transformation.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>topic/data-analytics</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-employee-central</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-recruiting</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Measuring the Carbon Footprint of Employees Can Help You Make More Informed and Strategic Business Decisions]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/measuring-employee-carbon-footprint-business-decisions</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/measuring-employee-carbon-footprint-business-decisions</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Executives can make informed decisions when considering the social and actual carbon footprint of employees in planning. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/experience-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/people-sustainability</category>
            <category>news-tag/qualtrics</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-product-footprint-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-employee-central</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-people-analytics</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-workforce-analytics</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central Surpasses 5,000 Customers]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/09/sap-successfactors-employee-central-customers-5000</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/09/sap-successfactors-employee-central-customers-5000</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[More than 5,000 SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central customers are building more sustainable workforces and changing work for good.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/people-sustainability</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-employee-central</category>
            <category>sap-event/successconnect</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The New Organizational Chart: Structuring the Workforce of Tomorrow]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/ingentis-workforce-of-tomorrow</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/ingentis-workforce-of-tomorrow</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP partner Ingentis used SAP BTP to build Ingentis org.manager, an add-on application to SAP SuccessFactors to stay on top of HR data.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-partneredge</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-partneredge-build</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-employee-central</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How SAP SuccessFactors Innovation Can Help You Tackle Your Toughest Challenges]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/sap-successfactors-innovation-tackle-2022-hr-trends</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/sap-successfactors-innovation-tackle-2022-hr-trends</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Take on 2022 HR trends like hybrid work, diversity and inclusion, well-being, and the race for talent with SAP Successfactors solutions.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-technologies</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/mental-health-well-being</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-employee-central</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-opportunity-marketplace</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-performance-goals</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-recruiting</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-work-zone</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Banking On a People-Centric Digital Transformation for Continued Success]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/banco-atlantida-people-centric-digital-transformation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/banco-atlantida-people-centric-digital-transformation</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[During COVID-19, Banco Atlántida digitally transformed so customers could continue to complete their financial activities uninterrupted.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/banking</category>
            <category>news-tag/covid-19</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-employee-central</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Vaccine Portlet: The Key to a Confident Return to the Workplace in an Ongoing Pandemic]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/vaccine-portlet-key-to-return-to-workplace-in-ongoing-pandemic</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/vaccine-portlet-key-to-return-to-workplace-in-ongoing-pandemic</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The health and vaccine tracking portlet in SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central can help businesses ensure employee health and safety.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1499e4043e2ec12a14a471f15c12bc19e9be2b663.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1499e4043e2ec12a14a471f15c12bc19e9be2b663.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1499e4043e2ec12a14a471f15c12bc19e9be2b663.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Vaccine Portlet: The Key to a Confident Return to the Workplace in an Ongoing Pandemic" src="./media_1499e4043e2ec12a14a471f15c12bc19e9be2b663.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="vaccine-portlet-the-key-to-a-confident-return-to-the-workplace-in-an-ongoing-pandemic">Vaccine Portlet: The Key to a Confident Return to the Workplace in an Ongoing Pandemic</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>With every new variant, a triumphant return to the office and a fully staffed operation gets pushed back further and further. And HR leaders are exhausted, facing a slew of questions that never seem to go away, including:</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <ul>
    <li>Can the business accommodate teams requiring physical space to get work done?</li>
    <li>How can leaders help accelerate the transition to having their staff back in proximity to them?</li>
    <li>Are there any state, local, federal, and customer pandemic policies that should be considered?</li>
    <li>Will the workforce respond to the transition well enough to build a cohesive culture and strong morale?</li>
    <li>How can employees come back with the peace of mind that they and their families will remain safe, regardless of vaccination status?</li>
  </ul>
  <p>These matters unquestionably impact how businesses drive enduring changes to operating models, adapt mindsets to meet safety measures, and ensure inclusive environments that support productivity. But when left unanswered, undue anxiety and stress emerge across the workforce – driving hesitancy of on-site work, increasing employee turnover and burnout, and making attracting new talent unnecessarily tricky.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-tracking-vaccination-data-with-sap-successfactors-employee-central">Learn more about tracking vaccination data with SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/06/80473e7e-e47d-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="building-assurance-and-trust-with-technology">Building Assurance and Trust with Technology</h2>
  <p>Just like technology was a critical enabler of a successful work-from-home transition, it can produce the insight and visibility to define and communicate policies and their rationale. And for employees, information – such as overall health and vaccine status – can boost their confidence when stepping foot into the workplace again.</p>
  <p>After talking to our customers about their workforce challenges throughout the <a href="/covid-19">pandemic</a>, SAP introduced the <a href="https://www.sap.com/programs/covid-vaccinations.html?video=c6d81ed9-f97d-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b">health and vaccine tracking portlet</a> as a free upgrade option for the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/employee-central-hris.html">SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central</a> solution that is also accessible through the <a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/oth/sapsuccessfactors-mobile-app/index.html">SAP SuccessFactors Mobile</a> app.</p>
  <p>SAP is not positioned to offer legal advice on vaccine mandates, health guidelines, and state, local, and federal requirements. But we are distinctively qualified to build a mobile-friendly portlet that collects data from our cloud-based human resource information system (HRIS) solution to help monitor and track employee health and vaccine status and inform decision-making.</p>
  <p>For example, employees can provide <a href="https://blogs.sap.com/2021/10/13/attaching-covid-vaccine-card-to-health-and-vaccine-portlet/">proof of vaccination status</a> by uploading a copy of their vaccine cards or exemption documents with their desktops and mobile devices. Plus, by checking the verification field in their profile and following related workflows and notifications, they can help ensure the HRIS solution records their status accurately.</p>
  <p>HR organizations can extend the employee vaccination feature to the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/employee-onboarding.html">SAP SuccessFactors Onboarding</a> solution. They can customize vaccine data collection for new hires and existing employees to better monitor and make decisions that safeguard the health and safety of the workforce according to local and federal requirements.</p>
  <p>Other areas of the business can also address unique demands and processes by personalizing the standardized content delivered through the health and vaccine tracking portlet. The portlet’s home page can be reconfigured to include links to national and local agencies, regional vaccine trackers, corporate policies, and organizational information.</p>
  <p>Analytics embedded in the HRIS solution can also be used in the portlet to assess health risks securely and confidentially. A report story dashboard provides actionable data to designated executives and managers – such as employees in need of vaccination and the percentage of vaccinated employees based on, for example, department, division, and cost center.</p>
  <h2 id="sharing-data-to-help-ensure-business-wide-health">Sharing Data to Help Ensure Business-Wide Health</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="put-employees-at-the-heart-of-everything-you-do-with-sap-successfactors">Put employees at the heart of everything you do with SAP SuccessFactors</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/employee-central-hris.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The health and vaccination data collected with the portlet can help automate compliance verification. This capability can help meet the requirements of organizations that conduct government work, operate in countries or industries with strict mandates, or have internal vaccination policies for existing employees and new hires.</p>
  <p>Automation of the validation processes is particularly important as vaccine-related obligations evolve rapidly and differ for every organization based on the type of business, location, and the emergence of new variants and health recommendations. Organizations can quickly report who is fully or partially vaccinated, has intentions to start the process, or chooses to decline due to health reasons or personal objections.</p>
  <p>Businesses can further extend their use of the health and vaccine tracking portlet to include their legal and compliance teams in planning a physical workplace reopening. They can work together to address organizational and individual employee concerns with expertise in immediate corporate needs, local and federal policies, and long-term growth strategies.</p>
  <h2 id="calming-fears-and-moving-forward">Calming Fears and Moving Forward</h2>
  <p>While the desire for returning on-site work remains mixed, clear COVID-19 protocols and interventions can alleviate a considerable portion of employees’ stress. But following generic guidance is not enough to calm fears.</p>
  <p>With the health and vaccine tracking portlet in SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central, businesses can be better equipped to care for the health and safety of employees and their families through specific COVID-19 practices. They can now understand their workforce’s health status in real time to identify opportunities and risks and plan a strategy that keeps people protected and productive.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Rinky Karthik is principal HR cloud architect for Cloud Architecture Advisory at SAP.</em><br><em>Mark Baker is head of Human Experience Management (HXM) Services Strategy at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/covid-19</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-employee-central</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-onboarding</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Prince's Trust Empowers Employees to Transform the Lives of Young People]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/the-princes-trust-empowers-employees-young-people</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/the-princes-trust-empowers-employees-young-people</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[At UK youth charity The Prince’s Trust, SAP SuccessFactors software supports cut costs, improved HR efficiency, and delighted employees.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_185d938a6f72a6a485347ec22797b91e2c2a98728.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_185d938a6f72a6a485347ec22797b91e2c2a98728.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_185d938a6f72a6a485347ec22797b91e2c2a98728.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="The Prince’s Trust Empowers Employees to Transform the Lives of Young People" src="./media_185d938a6f72a6a485347ec22797b91e2c2a98728.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="the-princes-trust-empowers-employees-to-transform-the-lives-of-young-people">The Prince’s Trust Empowers Employees to Transform the Lives of Young People</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="video-empowering-employees-to-help-disadvantaged-young-people-in-the-uk">Video: Empowering Employees to Help Disadvantaged Young People in the UK</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2021/11/d05b39df-057e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>As a leading youth charity in the UK, The Prince’s Trust helps young people get into jobs, education, and training. <a href="https://www.princes-trust.org.uk/">The Trust</a> offers free courses, grants, and mentoring opportunities to inspire those aged 11 to 30 to build their confidence, gain new skills, and change their lives for the better. Founded by HRH The Prince of Wales in 1976, the Trust has helped more than 1 million young people to date.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“Our employees and volunteers are incredibly passionate about helping young people reach their full potential,” said Kimberley Cleland, director of People and Learning at The Prince’s Trust. “Our job in HR is to nurture that drive and enthusiasm, and equip staff with the tools that will help them support young people.”</p>
  <p>To enable employees to work as efficiently and effectively as possible, the Trust wanted to provide the very best working experience. By moving to cloud-based <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm.html">SAP SuccessFactors solutions</a>, the Trust transformed its HR function, delivering intuitive employee self-services, supported by a modern, digital platform. Employees are delighted with the convenience and simplicity of self-service HR, while the Trust has cut costs and improved HR efficiency.</p>
  <p>Today, the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/employee-central-hris.html">SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central solution</a> serves as the master record for all employee data, including training information, and for Disclosure and Barring Service (DBS) checks. DBS checks are carried out by a UK government agency to establish a person’s criminal record history, helping employers to make safer recruitment decisions to prevent unsuitable people from working with vulnerable groups. The Prince’s Trust built custom portals in SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central to manage employees’ DBS check status. Automatic alerts are triggered when DBS checks near their expiration date, enabling managers to apply for new checks in a timely manner.</p>
  <p>In addition, the move to SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central is enabling further HR benefits. For example, The Prince’s Trust can respond rapidly to requests from funding partners for information, helping to secure much-needed donations. Similarly, centralized recruiting processes have helped the Trust to make smarter hiring decisions across the organization and reduce reliance on external agencies, freeing up precious resources to invest in youth services.</p>
  <p>The SAP SuccessFactors solutions also underpin the Trust’s new employee development strategy, which is designed to equip staff with the competencies they need to support young people, such as mentoring and conflict resolution skills. Using the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/corporate-lms.html">SAP SuccessFactors Learning solution</a>, employees now have access to a central catalog of digital training programs, and the HR team can track course completion, helping to ensure that all employees undertake mandatory and career-progression training.</p>
  <p>With integrated, automated processes covering the entire employee life cycle, SAP SuccessFactors solutions have laid the foundation for efficient, user-friendly HR operations.</p>
  <p>Kimberley Cleland concludes, “With the SAP SuccessFactors solutions, everyone at The Prince’s Trust has all the information they need at their fingertips. Ultimately, this helps us get the right people with the right skills out in the field to provide life-changing support to help young people realize their potential.”</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Top image via The Prince’s Trust.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-employee-central</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-learning</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Business Imperative for Localized HR Systems]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/06/business-imperative-localized-hr-systems</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/06/business-imperative-localized-hr-systems</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Change is constant, especially today. Read to learn how SAP technology can help streamline and simplify localized HR efforts.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14c495a05fbfd40f2dfdcb9e0e752f87ece5687a5.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14c495a05fbfd40f2dfdcb9e0e752f87ece5687a5.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_14c495a05fbfd40f2dfdcb9e0e752f87ece5687a5.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="The Business Imperative for Localized HR Systems" src="./media_14c495a05fbfd40f2dfdcb9e0e752f87ece5687a5.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="the-business-imperative-for-localized-hr-systems">The Business Imperative for Localized HR Systems</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Things are changing faster than ever – it’s so obvious that it almost isn’t worth saying any more. Some changes are pretty great, like curbside pick-up for instance. Others are not so great, like learning to wear a mask when out in public. Navigating change is tough – for individuals, for government agencies, and for businesses. But when the changes are legal mandates imposed on businesses, it doesn’t matter if meeting the requirements is simple and straightforward or incredibly complex and arcane – businesses have to step up and prove compliance. If they can’t, they face a host of negative consequences like fines or hits to brand reputation.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Even before the <a href="http://news.sap.com/covid-19">pandemic</a>, we were seeing a rise in the number of government regulations around the world and a rise in the pace of changes to regulations. Throw in the uncertainty of the pandemic and pretty much every organization in nearly every country is looking at new rules for managing workforce health and safety. As the situation evolves and more data comes in about what works and what doesn’t, those rules are in continual flux.</p>
  <p>The good news is that this is a problem that technology can streamline and simplify, as long as the tech provider fully understands and embraces the scope and complexity of the problem. The other good news is that SAP has nearly 50 years of experience in solving the world’s most complex problems and <a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/dg/global-hr-payroll-regulatory-compliance/index.html">SAP SuccessFactors Human Experience Management Suite</a> works to provide embedded automated support for managing regulatory changes in more than 100 countries.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="streamline-core-processes-for-hr-with-sap-solutions">Streamline core processes for HR with SAP solutions</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/employee-central-hris.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="what-types-of-regulations"><strong>What Types of Regulations?</strong></h2>
  <p>Right now, we’re seeing rapid change in three main categories of regulation:</p>
  <p><strong>Employee Health and Safety</strong> Many industries, such as manufacturing, mining, and energy production, have long had robust health and safety programs designed to keep plant and field workers safe and productive. In the wake of the pandemic, those existing programs need to be extended to include office workers at corporate headquarters, while other ‘less hazardous’ industries such banking or retail suddenly find that they need far more robust workforce safety training and tracking.</p>
  <p><strong>Data Privacy and Security</strong><br>When the EU passed the General Data Privacy Rule in 2016, the rest of the world had no choice but to take notice, and many other countries also passed legislation outlining how personal information needed to be managed and used – or not. For employers, this has had a massive impact on how they manage personally identifiable information (PII) of their employees. They must appropriately manage and secure the data, obtain explicit consent from employees to store or process their data, and handle change audits and data purges in a manner that meets local laws.</p>
  <p><strong>Corporate Malfeasance</strong><br>After the 2008 global recession caused by unexamined banking processes, governments across the world have instituted financial transparency and reporting regulations designed to prevent financial instability.</p>
  <h2 id="how-can-hr-technology-help-manage-regulatory-compliance"><strong>How Can HR Technology Help Manage Regulatory Compliance?</strong></h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="experience-wins-with-sap-successfactors-hxm-suite">Experience wins with SAP SuccessFactors HXM Suite</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm/hxm-suite.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>HR technology can help streamline and optimize compliance by digitizing and automating compliance management, enabling monitoring of workforce qualifications, and offering learning solutions to bring workers up to speed. It also needs to provide embedded support that goes beyond mere translation and initial configuration. For an HR solution to be fully globalized, it needs to provide not only basic translation to local languages, but also the ability to display local currencies and local formatting for fields like name and address. In addition, it needs to provide ongoing updates for regulations, proactively pushing them forward so systems stay up-to-date.</p>
  <h2 id="the-sap-successfactors-difference"><strong>The SAP SuccessFactors Difference</strong></h2>
  <p><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm/core-hr-payroll.html">SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central and SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central Payroll</a> customers in over 100 countries are supported by more than 200 in-country product managers who analyze local legal requirements and prioritize software adaptations to support regulatory changes. More than 300 product developers are responsible for implementing statutory and legal changes into SAP SuccessFactors solutions. These changes are automatically shared, working to simplify and streamline the compliance process.</p>
  <p>For a deeper dive into the power of SAP’s localized HCM software, read the full report, <em><a href="https://www.sap.com/registration/protected/default-overlay.html?gated_asset_path=%2F%2Fwww.sap.com%2Fdocuments%2F2021%2F05%2Fb08304d0-e27d-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.rc.html&#x26;pdf-asset=b08304d0-e27d-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b&#x26;page=1">Fulfill Regulatory Requirements with a Localized Human Capital Management Approach</a></em>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Barbara Ocain is global executive advisor at SAP SuccessFactors.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/compliance</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-employee-central</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Realizing a People-Centered Future of Work Through the Intelligent Enterprise]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/06/people-centered-future-of-work-intelligent-enterprise-hxm</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/06/people-centered-future-of-work-intelligent-enterprise-hxm</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A people-centered future of work requires a strong tech backbone across the enterprise, end to end. Learn how SAP technology helps.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/future-of-work</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-employee-central</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Microsoft Moves HR to the Cloud with SAP SuccessFactors]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/06/sap-successfactors-at-microsoft-hr-cloud</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/06/sap-successfactors-at-microsoft-hr-cloud</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Microsoft has been on a journey to transform its people strategy. Learn more about SAP SuccessFactors at Microsoft.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10721d47f45f641339803a1b91af08b8c6a41dad7.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10721d47f45f641339803a1b91af08b8c6a41dad7.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_10721d47f45f641339803a1b91af08b8c6a41dad7.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Microsoft Moves HR to the Cloud with SAP SuccessFactors" src="./media_10721d47f45f641339803a1b91af08b8c6a41dad7.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="microsoft-moves-hr-to-the-cloud-with-sap-successfactors">Microsoft Moves HR to the Cloud with SAP SuccessFactors</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="explore-the-hr-track-at-sapphire-now">Explore the HR track at SAPPHIRE NOW</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://reg.sapevents.sap.com/flow/sap/sapphirenow2021/portal/page/track-hr">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Microsoft has successfully completed the implementation of <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/employee-central-hris.html">SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central</a> for its 140,000 employees in 109 countries. For the first time, Microsoft now has all of its employees on a single human resources (HR) platform, which runs on Microsoft Azure.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Microsoft has been on a journey to transform its people strategy in order to better understand the behaviors, pain points and motivations of its employees, and attract skilled, curious, and passionate talent.</p>
  <p>After decades of running its HR operations on the on-premise SAP ERP Human Capital Management solution and multiple homegrown applications, the company needed a cloud platform that could deliver on its mobile-first, cloud-first philosophy and provide a foundation for future transformations. It selected <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm.html">SAP SuccessFactors Human Experience Management (HXM) Suite</a> for the global and local reach that it provides in both data and regulatory needs and an open platform that can easily be integrated with other solutions in its larger ecosystem.</p>
  <p>With many Microsoft employees continuing to work remotely or in a <a href="https://blogs.microsoft.com/blog/2021/03/22/the-philosophy-and-practice-of-our-hybrid-workplace/">hybrid model</a>, it is even more important today that it has the technology to connect a distributed workforce, encourage collaboration, and keep employees engaged and inspired. Since implementing SAP SuccessFactors HXM Suite, including <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm/products.html#active_tab=item_1602592257238">SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central</a>, Microsoft can provide a consistent employee experience for its entire global workforce – regardless of location or role. SAP SuccessFactors solutions will serve as the foundation for the innovations Microsoft is developing to manage the changes and impacts of the hybrid workplace</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="create-a-more-flexible-engaged-workforce-and-a-more-resilient-business">Create a more flexible, engaged workforce and a more resilient business</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Since migrating to cloud-based HXM solutions from SAP, Microsoft has increased the quality of data in its HR system, thus increasing the efficiencies in payroll and other critical processes. It also has the ability to extend and create delightful experiences for their employees. With solutions including <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/employee-onboarding.html">SAP SuccessFactors Onboarding</a>, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/corporate-lms.html">SAP SuccessFactors Learning</a>, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/succession-development.html">SAP SuccessFactors Succession &#x26; Development</a>, and now <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/employee-central-hris.html">SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central</a>, the company has also simplified and unified its HR processes and can access data faster. Not only has this improved visibility into the workforce, it has elevated HR’s ability to provide timely, accurate insights in real time.</p>
  <p>“As we continue Microsoft’s HR transformation journey, it’s been critical to have a cloud platform that can adapt and grow with our needs, especially as the needs of the workforce change,” said Rajamma Krishnamurthy, senior director of HR Technology, Microsoft. “In fact, we completed the implementation of SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central in more than 90 countries in a completely virtual environment due to the global <a href="/covid-19">pandemic</a> by adopting an agile approach. Moving forward, SAP will continue to be a critical partner in helping use data to design engaging, inclusive experiences for all of our global employees.”</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Angelique Slagle is head of SAP SuccessFactors for North America.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/future-of-work</category>
            <category>news-tag/microsoft</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-employee-central</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Announces New Enhancements to Human Experience Management Solutions to Bring Workers Back to the Office]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/new-hxm-enhancements-workers-back-to-the-office</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/new-hxm-enhancements-workers-back-to-the-office</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 19 Apr 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New HXM innovations from SAP help bring employees back to the office and allow organizations to better support, connect, and empower them.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-employee-central</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-learning</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-performance-goals</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[RHI Magnesita Heats Up HR Transformation with SAP SuccessFactors Solutions]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/rhi-magnesita-hr-transformation-sap-successfactors</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/rhi-magnesita-hr-transformation-sap-successfactors</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[RHI Magnesita implemented SAP SuccessFactors to deliver the employee experience, support its workplace culture and transform HR processes.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-preferred-success</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-employee-central</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-recruiting</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[FC Bayern Implements SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central to Improve Digital HR Capabilities]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/fc-bayern-sap-successfactors-employee-central</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/fc-bayern-sap-successfactors-employee-central</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP SuccessFactors at FC Bayern is helping standardize and optimize core HR processes and improve the experience for 1,000+ employees.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17221bbf506e9a85143673ed151423bc1bd1e1fd2.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17221bbf506e9a85143673ed151423bc1bd1e1fd2.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_17221bbf506e9a85143673ed151423bc1bd1e1fd2.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="FC Bayern Implements SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central to Improve Digital HR Capabilities" src="./media_17221bbf506e9a85143673ed151423bc1bd1e1fd2.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="fc-bayern-implements-sap-successfactors-employee-central-to-improve-digital-hr-capabilities">FC Bayern Implements SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central to Improve Digital HR Capabilities</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>MUNICH</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced that FC Bayern, Germany’s most winning football club, has successfully implemented the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/employee-central-hris.html?btp=74873987-7925-4fc0-8240-97dea52648e4">SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central</a> solution to standardize and optimize its core human resource (HR) processes and improve the experience for its 1,000+ employees.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>By leveraging the <a href="https://www.sap.com/services/implementation/preconfigured-industry-solutions.html">SAP Model Company</a> service for accelerated solution deployment, FC Bayern benefitted from ready-to-use, preconfigured processes and best practices.</p>
  <p>Part of <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm/human-experience.html">SAP SuccessFactors Human Experience Management Suite</a>, SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central is a cloud-based human resource information system that organizations use to manage global workforces with all core HR functions.</p>
  <p>With the implementation of SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central, FC Bayern has moved from spreadsheets and manual processes to a fully integrated platform. This allows for consistent and digital HR processes and will unify data across recruiting, onboarding and performance management in the future. In addition, reports can be generated easily and efficiently for optimized workforce planning and analytics.</p>
  <p>“The SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central solution enables FC Bayern’s HR team to do what it does best — focus on strategic, value-added HR rather than transactional processes,” FC Bayern Executive Vice Chairman Jan-Christian Dreesen said. “Before implementing the solution, we worked with legacy, time-consuming processes. The integration has enabled us not only to digitalize our processes but also to innovate and redesign them. By creating a more efficient environment, our HR team can prioritize on delivering the best employee experience possible.”</p>
  <p>SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central includes self-service options to help increase employee engagement at FC Bayern. The <a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/oth/sapsuccessfactors-mobile-app/index.html">SAP SuccessFactors Mobile</a> app provides all employees — including players, coaches, managers and office employees — with a modern, intuitive mobile experience. They can access their personal data and update their employee profiles as well as enter, approve and record absences such as vacations — all tasks that previously required them to reach out to HR for approval.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-successfactors-shift-from-transactional-hcm-to-end-to-end-experiences">SAP SuccessFactors: Shift from transactional HCM to end-to-end experiences</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="hear-how-fc-bayern-employees-have-shaped-the-clubs-story-for-decades-of-success">Hear how FC Bayern employees have shaped the club’s story for decades of success:</h3>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18a9729a6cec4a11cb227a043055cf075e7ff7cd4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18a9729a6cec4a11cb227a043055cf075e7ff7cd4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_18a9729a6cec4a11cb227a043055cf075e7ff7cd4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="FC Bayern: Success is built on many shoulders" src="./media_18a9729a6cec4a11cb227a043055cf075e7ff7cd4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://youtu.be/DytM11OKogA">FC Bayern: Success is built on many shoulders</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“With the implementation of SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central, we are happy to open a new chapter in the long-standing partnership between FC Bayern and SAP,” said Andreas Jung, FC Bayern Executive Board member.</p>
  <p>“Since 2014, SAP has been an official platinum partner of FC Bayern, working together to innovative solutions that help the club reach its sports and business goals,” said Thomas Saueressig, member of the SAP Executive Board, Product Engineering. “The go-live of SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central extends this partnership to human experience management, enabling the sports club to further accelerate its growth and remain competitive at all times, both on and off the field.”</p>
  <p>For more information, visit the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm.html">HR and People Engagement area of SAP.com</a> and the <a href="/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP on Twitter at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Media Contacts:</strong> Dana Rösiger, +49 6227 7 63900, <a href="mailto:dana.roesiger@sap.com">dana.roesiger@sap.com</a>, CET<br>Samantha Yerks, +1 (914) 918-6087, <a href="mailto:samantha.yerks@sap.com">samantha.yerks@sap.com</a>, ET<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>Any statements contained in this document that are not historical facts are forward-looking statements as defined in the U.S. Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995. Words such as “anticipate,” “believe,” “estimate,” “expect,” “forecast,” “intend,” “may,” “plan,” “project,” “predict,” “should” and “will” and similar expressions as they relate to SAP are intended to identify such forward-looking statements. SAP undertakes no obligation to publicly update or revise any forward-looking statements. All forward-looking statements are subject to various risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results to differ materially from expectations. The factors that could affect SAP’s future financial results are discussed more fully in SAP’s filings with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (“SEC”), including SAP’s most recent Annual Report on Form 20-F filed with the SEC. Readers are cautioned not to place undue reliance on these forward-looking statements, which speak only as of their dates.<br>© 2021 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-news</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-sponsorships</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-sports</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-employee-central</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>