<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/topic/sustainability/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Data-Driven Decision-Making with Connected Financial and Carbon Information]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/data-driven-connected-financial-carbon-information</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/data-driven-connected-financial-carbon-information</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Beyond environmental responsibility, merging carbon and financial data unlocks additional advantages. Learn about them.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-accounting</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP's New AI Innovations and Partnerships Deliver Real-World Results]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/ai-innovations-partnerships-sap-sapphire</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/ai-innovations-partnerships-sap-sapphire</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Explore the AI capabilities and ecosystem innovations presented at SAP Sapphire in 2024, all aimed at delivering real-world results.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>news-topic/financial-management</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/abap-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/accenture</category>
            <category>news-tag/ai-ethics</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/aws</category>
            <category>news-tag/bcg</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Putting Sustainability at the Heart of ERP]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sustainability-erp-sap-business-ai-sap-sapphire</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sustainability-erp-sap-business-ai-sap-sapphire</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP’s ERP-centric, cloud-based, AI-enabled approach is redefining how companies manage sustainability. Learn how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_19f549b1c60b71d253752564f5659b7cd5b69ae91.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_19f549b1c60b71d253752564f5659b7cd5b69ae91.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_19f549b1c60b71d253752564f5659b7cd5b69ae91.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Putting Sustainability at the Heart of ERP" src="./media_19f549b1c60b71d253752564f5659b7cd5b69ae91.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="putting-sustainability-at-the-heart-of-erp">Putting Sustainability at the Heart of ERP</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Sustainability has evolved from a boardroom buzzword to a critical driver of business success and strategic differentiation. To thrive, companies are going to need to understand how to operate in a modern, low-carbon, circular economy. SAP solutions will support them by embedding sustainability into every aspect of their operations.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-sapphire-taking-business-to-the-next-level-in-the-era-of-ai">SAP Sapphire: Taking Business to the Next Level in the Era of AI</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/events/sapphire/news-guide.html">Read the news guide</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>At our customer flagship event, <a href="/topics/sap-sapphire">SAP Sapphire</a>, we’re discussing how we support customers with their biggest challenges, looking at future trends, and unveiling the latest product innovations.</p>
  <p>This makes the event the perfect opportunity to highlight how we are redefining the way companies manage sustainability through our ERP-centric, cloud-based, AI-enabled approach.</p>
  <h2 id="erp-centric">ERP-Centric</h2>
  <p>For true business model transformation, sustainability needs to be at the core of how companies operate. At SAP, we integrate sustainability data into cloud ERP business processes, which helps companies connect financial and non-financial information and thus treat carbon like money. This makes all decisions financially <em>and</em> environmentally sound while enabling customers to record real impacts and report audit-ready environmental, social, and governance (ESG) metrics seamlessly.</p>
  <h2 id="cloud-based">Cloud-Based</h2>
  <p>Instant access to fast-evolving innovations is only possible through the cloud. Our modern cloud-based solutions ensure that businesses can quickly adopt new functionality and stay ahead in a rapidly changing environment.</p>
  <h2 id="ai-enabled">AI-Enabled</h2>
  <p>Business AI is revolutionizing the way we approach sustainability. At SAP, AI takes complex sustainability tasks reliant on sustainability data and ERP data and makes them automated and auditable. It enables companies to improve operational efficiency, foster greater transparency around supply chain emissions, design and plan more effectively, and automate time-consuming tasks. SAP Business AI is built on the data and processes that run the business world, including sustainability related information from both inside and outside the company’s walls, making our solutions smarter, faster, and more effective.</p>
  <p>With SAP Business AI, we support our customers’ efforts to optimize for sustainable impact. This year at SAP Sapphire, we are thrilled to announce two new AI-driven sustainability use cases:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Emission Factor Mapping with AI:</strong> Available in SAP Sustainability Footprint Management, this feature enhances the accuracy and speed of carbon footprint calculations through automated, intelligent suggestions. By reducing the manual effort involved in mapping emission factors, businesses can achieve more precise measurements and make informed decisions faster.</li>
    <li><strong>ESG Report Generation with AI:</strong> This capability allows for the automatic generation of ESG reports based on the data within SAP Sustainability Control Tower. This not only streamlines the reporting process but also helps ensure that the data is reliable and actionable, providing a clear picture of a company’s sustainability performance.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>Our comprehensive approach to carbon management is becoming a reality as we introduce new sustainability tracking, monitoring, and reporting features within the SAP cloud ERP portfolio as well as a new solution that will help customers manage sustainability commitments and comply with global regulations.</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Advanced Carbon Calculator Engine:</strong> This powerful tool featured in SAP Sustainability Control Tower and SAP Sustainability Footprint Management integrates ERP data from SAP S/4HANA Cloud and other sources and embeds results back into business processes for informed decision-making. As such, it allows customers to meet Greenhouse Gas Protocol reporting standards, offering advanced, granular calculations of both product and corporate carbon footprints.</li>
    <li><strong>SAP Green Ledger</strong> will be released at the end of 2024. The solution will help customers connect their emissions data and financial data, allowing customers to easily understand the correlation between emissions and finances, model sustainable business scenarios, and then act with decisions that are both financially and environmentally sound.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>At SAP, we believe that the future of business is inextricably linked to sustainability. This is why sustainability is a key pillar of our growth strategy. Businesses must recognize that sustainable practices are not just ethical choices, but strategic financial decisions that drive innovation, reduce costs, and mitigate risks.</p>
  <p>Moreover, sustainable transformation opens up significant economic opportunities. By transforming their operations around sustainability, businesses can create a modern, low-carbon, circular economy that benefits both the environment and their bottom line, enhancing overall resilience.</p>
  <p>This transformation aligns business success with global sustainability goals, paving the way for a more sustainable, valuable, and prosperous future.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Sophia Mendelsohn is chief sustainability and commercial officer at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-news-and-coverage-from-sap-sapphire-in-2024">Get the latest news and coverage from SAP Sapphire in 2024</h3>
        <p><em><a href="/topics/sap-sapphire">Read more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-footprint-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Infuses Business AI Throughout Its Enterprise Cloud Portfolio and Partners with Cutting-Edge AI Leaders to Bring Out Customers’ Best]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-sapphire-news-business-ai-enterprise-cloud-portfolio-cutting-edge-partnerships</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-sapphire-news-business-ai-enterprise-cloud-portfolio-cutting-edge-partnerships</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New SAP Business AI innovations and collaborations with partners are igniting ingenuity. Read the news from SAP Sapphire Orlando in 2024.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18ff27978e1178b1dce994986e74f4cc1f6087f26.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18ff27978e1178b1dce994986e74f4cc1f6087f26.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_18ff27978e1178b1dce994986e74f4cc1f6087f26.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Infuses Business AI Throughout Its Enterprise Cloud Portfolio and Partners with Cutting-Edge AI Leaders to Bring Out Customers’ Best" src="./media_18ff27978e1178b1dce994986e74f4cc1f6087f26.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-infuses-business-ai-throughout-its-enterprise-cloud-portfolio-and-partners-with-cutting-edge-ai-leaders-to-bring-out-customers-best">SAP Infuses Business AI Throughout Its Enterprise Cloud Portfolio and Partners with Cutting-Edge AI Leaders to Bring Out Customers’ Best</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>SAP Business AI Innovations and Collaborations with Partners including Google Cloud, Meta, Microsoft, Mistral AI and NVIDIA Ignite Ingenuity</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <table>
          <thead>
            <tr>
              <th>Text Large</th>
            </tr>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td><strong><em>ORLANDO</em></strong> — At its annual SAP Sapphire conference, SAP unveiled generative AI innovations and partnerships that showcase how the company is taking business to the next level in the era of AI.</td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="taking-business-to-the-next-level-in-the-era-of-ai">Taking Business to the Next Level in the Era of AI</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/events/sapphire/news-guide.html">Read the news guide</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>By infusing Business AI across an enterprise cloud portfolio that powers the world’s most mission-critical processes and partnering with companies pushing the edge of what’s possible with AI, SAP is igniting a new wave of insight and ingenuity in global business.</p>
  <p>“The Business AI innovations we’re announcing at SAP Sapphire in 2024 will redefine the way businesses run,” says Christian Klein, CEO and member of the Executive Board of SAP SE. “Today’s AI announcements and partnerships build on our commitment to deliver revolutionary technology that drives real-world results, helping customers unleash the agility and ingenuity they need to succeed in today’s fast-moving business landscape.”</p>
  <h2 id="ai-that-means-business">AI That Means Business</h2>
  <p>As SAP embeds Business AI across its enterprise solutions, it puts rich insights at users’ fingertips, empowering them to deliver better outcomes and elevate the creative problem-solving humans do best. Examples include AI-generated reports in SAP SuccessFactors solutions that give people managers responsibly sourced insights for compensation-related discussions as well as forecasting capabilities in SAP Sales Cloud solutions that predict combinations of salespeople and products most likely to drive sales. Meanwhile, the SAP Business Technology Platform is adding large language models from Amazon Web Services, Meta and Mistral AI to its generative AI hub. This capability in the SAP AI Core infrastructure makes it easier to build generative AI use cases for SAP applications.</p>
  <p>SAP’s generative AI copilot Joule, which quickly sorts and contextualizes data from multiple systems to advance automation and improve decision-making, is expanding throughout the company’s solution portfolio. Joule launched in <a href="/2023/09/joule-new-generative-ai-assistant">SAP SuccessFactors solutions last fall</a> and is now embedded into SAP S/4HANA Cloud solutions and others including SAP Build and SAP Integration Suite. Further expansion by year-end will include SAP Ariba and SAP Analytics Cloud solutions. At Sapphire, SAP also announced <a href="/">plans to further broaden Joule’s scope</a> by integrating it with Microsoft Copilot to surface even richer insights. This deep, bi-directional integration gives users a unified experience built right into the flow of work, enabling seamless access to information from interactions with business applications in SAP and Microsoft 365.</p>
  <p>Reflecting Business AI’s increasing importance, SAP is redoubling its commitment to the principles of relevant, reliable, and responsible AI it pioneered. At Sapphire, SAP is adopting the 10 guiding principles of the UNESCO Recommendation on the Ethics of Artificial Intelligence, which aim to ensure that AI technologies are developed and used in ways that respect human rights, promote fairness and contribute to sustainable development.</p>
  <h2 id="partnerships-that-scale-innovation">Partnerships That Scale Innovation</h2>
  <p>SAP is partnering with best-in-class technology leaders to push the limits of what generative AI can do at an enterprise level. In addition to our expanded collaborations with <a href="/2024/05/aws-sap-generative-ai-new-innovation">AWS</a> and Microsoft, partnerships with Google Cloud, Meta, Mistral AI and NVIDIA ensure SAP can harness the power of AI-ready technology to innovate at speed and deliver richer real-world results.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Google Cloud</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP and Google Cloud are expanding their partnership, using Business AI to help enterprises better predict and mitigate supply-chain risks to minimize disruptions and maintain optimal inventory levels. The companies will integrate Joule and the SAP Integrated Business Planning for Supply Chain solution with Google Cloud’s Gemini models AI assistant and Google Cloud Cortex Framework’s data foundation.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Meta</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP will leverage Meta Llama 3 to generate scripts that render highly customized analytics applications in SAP Analytics Cloud. Meta’s next-generation AI model excels at language nuances and contextual understanding, making it an ideal candidate for translating enterprise business requirements into tangible outcomes.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Mistral AI</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP will also add <a href="/">new large language models from Mistral AI</a>, a global company headquartered in Paris specializing in generative AI, to the generative AI hub capability in SAP AI Core.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>NVIDIA</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP and NVIDIA Corporation advance a <a href="https://blogs.nvidia.com/blog/sap-sapphire-ai-omniverse/">cross-product partnership</a> to embed cutting-edge technologies into enterprise-ready business applications:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>As SAP trains Joule to serve as an AI assistant for the RISE with SAP solution implementations, NVIDIA’s state-of-the-art AI models sift through SAP consulting assets to provide relevant and precise answers to implementation-related questions;</li>
    <li>As SAP embeds Joule in the ABAP Cloud model to generate ABAP code for SAP developers, NVIDIA’s accelerated infrastructure will run, scale, and manage SAP’s generative AI model for ABAP code generation;</li>
    <li>As SAP infuses generative AI into the SAP Intelligent Product Recommendation solution, NVIDIA Omniverse Cloud APIs enable the simulation of complex manufacturing products and configurations as industrial digital twins.</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="cloud-technology-that-drives-agility-and-sustainability">Cloud Technology That Drives Agility and Sustainability</h2>
  <p>Business success in the era of AI means being in the cloud. SAP is making the move easier than ever with initiatives that help customers find partners with the expertise needed for complex SAP S/4HANA Cloud transformations. Further cloud innovations at SAP Sapphire include features that help the world’s organizations measure, manage and execute their sustainability strategies. SAP Sustainability Control Tower and SAP Sustainability Footprint Management solutions now track carbon footprints at scale and help businesses meet regulatory standards.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><a href="https://www.sap.com/events/sapphire/news-guide.html">Learn more in the 2024 SAP Sapphire News Guide</a>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Visit the <a href="/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-news-and-coverage-from-sap-sapphire-in-2024">Get the latest news and coverage from SAP Sapphire in 2024</h3>
        <p><em><a href="/topics/sap-sapphire">Read more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>About SAP</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As a global leader in enterprise applications and business AI, SAP (NYSE:SAP) stands at the nexus of business and technology. For over 50 years, organizations have trusted SAP to bring out their best by uniting business-critical operations spanning finance, procurement, HR, supply chain, and customer experience. For more information, visit <a href="http://www.sap.com">www.sap.com</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Note to editors:</strong><br>To preview and download broadcast-standard stock footage and press photos digitally, please visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/photos">www.sap.com/photos</a>. On this platform, you can find high resolution material for your media channels.</p>
  <p><strong>For customers interested in learning more about SAP products:</strong><br>Global Customer Center: +49 180 534-34-24<br>United States Only: 1 (800) 872-1SAP (1-800-872-1727)</p>
  <p><strong>For more information, press only:</strong><br>Joellen Perry, +1 (650) 445-6780, <a href="mailto:joellen.perry@sap.com">joellen.perry@sap.com</a> PT<br>Marcus Winkler, +49 6227-767497, <a href="mailto:marcus.winkler@sap.com">marcus.winkler@sap.com</a> CET<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>This document contains forward-looking statements, which are predictions, projections, or other statements about future events. These statements are based on current expectations, forecasts, and assumptions that are subject to risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results and outcomes to materially differ. Additional information regarding these risks and uncertainties may be found in our filings with the Securities and Exchange Commission, including but not limited to the risk factors section of SAP’s 2023 Annual Report on Form 20-F.<br>© 2024 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.<br>Please consider our <a href="https://www.sap.com/corporate/en/legal/privacy.html">privacy policy</a>. If you receive this press release in your e-mail and you wish to unsubscribe to our mailing list please contact <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a> and write Unsubscribe in the subject line.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/abap-cloud</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-sales-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-footprint-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA["Source from Ukraine" Initiative: The S Stands for Solidarity]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/source-from-ukraine-initiative-s-for-solidarity</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/source-from-ukraine-initiative-s-for-solidarity</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The "Source from Ukraine" initiative aims to activate procurement spend to support Ukrainian suppliers in rebuilding their businesses.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/csr</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/ukraine</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP's “Source from Ukraine” Initiative Boosts Business and Social Responsibility]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/source-from-ukraine-initiative-boosts-business-social-responsibility</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/source-from-ukraine-initiative-boosts-business-social-responsibility</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The "Source from Ukraine" initiative aims to activate procurement spend to support Ukrainian suppliers in rebuilding their businesses.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1be90b8393bfeb6a3a3bdc9a317fa62a7be1e9acb.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1be90b8393bfeb6a3a3bdc9a317fa62a7be1e9acb.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1be90b8393bfeb6a3a3bdc9a317fa62a7be1e9acb.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP’s “Source from Ukraine” Initiative Boosts Business and Social Responsibility" src="./media_1be90b8393bfeb6a3a3bdc9a317fa62a7be1e9acb.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="saps-source-from-ukraine-initiative-boosts-business-and-social-responsibility">SAP’s “Source from Ukraine” Initiative Boosts Business and Social Responsibility</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>SAP’s “Source from Ukraine” initiative, launched in March 2023, has a clear goal: to increase spend with Ukrainian companies while also generating business benefits for SAP. This shows SAP’s deep understanding of social responsibility as an integral part of its commitment to a sustainable future.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The initiative aims to activate <a href="/topics/procurement">procurement</a> spend as a means to support Ukrainian suppliers in rebuilding their businesses. Beyond sourcing for quality goods and services, SAP has a focus on integrating ESG (environmental, social, and governance) principles into decision-making as is standard with its procurement policy.</p>
  <p>It highlights SAP’s commitment not only to sourcing products from Ukraine, but also to promoting social change.</p>
  <h2 id="built-in-sustainability">Built-In Sustainability</h2>
  <p>In implementing the initiative to attract more suppliers from Ukraine, SAP initially focused on the IT sector and conducted a rigorous selection process. So far, suppliers, including industry leaders like Softserve, Unicsoft, and Luxoft, have been selected. SAP’s commitment extends beyond services to include product areas, where notable Ukrainian companies producing innovative environmentally sustainable products have been discovered.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-is-powering-equitable-access-to-economic-opportunity-education-and-employment-and-the-circular-economy">SAP is powering equitable access to economic opportunity, education and employment, and the circular economy</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/our-values/csr.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>At SAP Spend Connect Live in Vienna, Austria, held in October 2023, Ukrainian manufacturers Rekava, Mol’far Tea, and Releaf Paper showcased their sustainable and innovative products. Rekava, for example, specializes in producing biodegradable candles made from recycled coffee grounds, while Mol’far focuses on minimalism and ethical environmental practices in tea production. Releaf Paper is the world’s first manufacturer of paper made from fallen leaves, promoting sustainable products such as paper bags. By supporting these unique Ukrainian companies, SAP is not only contributing to the economic reconstruction of the country, but also sustainability efforts.</p>
  <p>One of SAP’s tier one suppliers, ABC Premium, has taken an important step by offering Rekava candles within its purchasing catalog, available to SAP employees on the SAP Ariba Buying solution.</p>
  <h2 id="strong-alliances-for-reconstruction">Strong Alliances for Reconstruction</h2>
  <p>At the outset of the project, the NGO Impact Ukraine helped SAP connect with Ukrainian suppliers. It focuses on microfinance, procurement, and recruitment from Ukraine. The collaboration is facilitated by the voluntary engagement of professionals from the technology, healthcare, and finance sectors. With Impact Ukraine’s support, SAP and other organizations can further advance their goals regarding procurement from Ukraine.</p>
  <p>SAP’s commitment to promoting innovation, sustainability, and economic growth through partnerships with Ukrainian companies not only fulfills its aspirations for procurement with purpose, but also contributes to making the world a better place.</p>
  <h2 id="helping-the-world-run-better">Helping the World Run Better</h2>
  <p>The “Source from Ukraine” initiative builds on global efforts to integrate social enterprises and diverse suppliers into SAP purchasing opportunities. Beyond SAP’s own internal purchasing efforts, the SAP Corporate Social Responsibility (SAP CSR) team is also investing in social and sustainable procurement ecosystems alongside public, private, and social sector partners like the European Commission, Deloitte, World Economic Forum’s Global Alliance for Social Entrepreneurship, and Social Enterprise World Forum’s People and Planet First verification.</p>
  <p>Consider that US$5.3 trillion in annual commerce is transacted on <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-network.html">SAP Business Network</a>. If we can help create a small shift in procurement spend to organizations prioritizing people and planet like Releaf Paper, we could collectively increase investment in sustainable development in a way that is not possible through corporate philanthropy alone. To join our efforts, please e-mail: <a href="mailto:csr-global@sap.com?subject=Please%20Share%20More%20Collective%20Social%20Procurement%20Investments%20and%20How%20to%20Get%20Involved">csr-global@sap.com</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Elena Parker is chief revenue officer for Intelligent Spend and Business Network, MEE, at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-sap-news-delivered-to-your-inbox-once-a-week">Get the latest SAP news delivered to your inbox once a week</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/nl/sap-news-center-newsletter/index.html">Sign up today</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/csr</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/ukraine</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Power of the Consumer]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/the-power-of-the-consumer</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/the-power-of-the-consumer</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Retailers have experienced a notable shift in consumer behavior towards more sustainable products and conscious consumption. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c74888da6a92ef0c940cec39419b20613ae1ce55.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c74888da6a92ef0c940cec39419b20613ae1ce55.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1c74888da6a92ef0c940cec39419b20613ae1ce55.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="The Power of the Consumer" src="./media_1c74888da6a92ef0c940cec39419b20613ae1ce55.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="the-power-of-the-consumer">The Power of the Consumer</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Over recent years, retailers have experienced a notable shift in consumer behavior towards more sustainable products and conscious consumption. Consumers have driven this shift with their increased awareness of environmental issues, ethical concerns, and desire to support products which are eco-friendly, ethically sourced, and produced under fair labor conditions.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Companies that prioritize <a href="/topics/sustainability">sustainability</a> in their operations, such as using recycled materials, reducing carbon emissions, or supporting social causes, are gaining popularity among consumers. But those consumers demand proof of these values and product promises at the point of sale.</p>
  <p>“The rise of sustainability isn’t just a movement; it is a shift in consumer consciousness,” said Dania Fayyaz, SAP North America sustainability program manager. “Today’s consumers are redefining their purchasing patterns, opting for products and brands that align with their values, and driving a demand for eco-conscious practices and ethical sourcing.” In her conversations with retailers that visited SAP’s booth at NRF 2024, the world’s largest retail fair, she saw a high interest in sustainability solutions.</p>
  <h2 id="consumers--and-markets--demand-visibility">Consumers – and Markets – Demand Visibility</h2>
  <p>When the EU Deforestation Regulation (EUDR) comes into effect for large enterprises later this year all products sold in the EU containing palm oil, cocoa, soy, rubber, cattle/leather, coffee, wood, and their derivatives will need proof that their harvest didn’t contribute to deforestation. Non-compliance will result in potential fines of up to 4% of companies’ EU annual turnover. To help businesses simplify this complex task, the SAP Green Token solution can track the geolocation of where raw materials are harvested and automate the creation of due diligence statements (DDS). The solution can also help improve visibility for consumers on where the raw material for their clothing was sourced and offer information on potential reuse and recycling.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="record-report-and-act-with-sap-sustainability-solutions">Record, report, and act with SAP Sustainability solutions</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/sustainability.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Take the example of a cotton shirt made from 50% certified recycled materials. Cotton can be sourced from multiple farms or recycling services and taken to a cotton mill where it’s spun into thread and later fabric. It becomes impossible to distinguish the different cotton elements – conventional versus recycled cotton – once they are co-mingled and the manufacturer loses insight into the sustainability attributes of the raw materials. That’s why it’s important to have a sophisticated tracking solution in place. “SAP Green Token can enhance transparency for bulk-traded, co-mingled raw materials by digitally storing sustainability attributes on tokens that traverse the supply chain,” said Fayyaz.</p>
  <p>In addition to making conscious decisions on raw materials and products, consumers can also consider circular economy models. “I’m really intrigued by the idea of revitalizing clothing items,” said Fayyaz. “Imagine being able to exchange a well-loved jacket you’ve had for years and receive credit in return. And the jacket might find a new owner who will genuinely appreciate it.” The SAP Recommerce solution enables that scenario, helping brands and retailers take back, manage, and resell secondhand inventory to help accelerate the shift from linear to circular business models. On an even larger scale, SAP Green Ledger is SAP’s vision to make transactional carbon accounting a reality. It can enable organizations to track carbon like they do cash, with every financial transaction having a corresponding carbon entry. “This is incredibly desirable because we will see taxes for carbon imposed in the future, and decision-makers will want insights into which processes are utilizing the most carbon,” Fayyaz said.</p>
  <h2 id="the-future-of-retail--a-retailers-view">The Future of Retail – A Retailer’s View</h2>
  <p>At a recent SAP event, Christoph Werner, CEO at German retailer dm-drogerie markt, shared his view on the future of retail and his insights on what customers want – and therefore what will shape the way retailers have to engage to drive business.</p>
  <p>For Werner, individualization of the shopping experience and any transaction will play a major role. Therefore, retailers will have to focus on the individual shopper, not on clusters of shoppers like in the past. Hyper-personalizing the customer experience will improve loyalty; the value for the customer will not only be the price, but increasingly the overall service and experience. This will change the concept of promotions. Werner is convinced that retailers will benefit from giving added benefits and delighting the customer, rather than pushing products into the market based on reduced prices. “Bring home flowers every now and then, but keep it special,” Werner said.</p>
  <p>To no surprise, AI will be the foundation for personalized shopping experiences. “AI has benefits and downsides and today it remains to be seen where it will take us,” Werner stated. Overall, retailers see AI as an opportunity, with the technology completing repeatable tasks, freeing up employees for more value-adding tasks, and empowering individuals to make a difference. As retail stores often face staffing challenges, this can empower people in sales and marketing teams instead of replacing them. From Werner’s perspective, an AI-empowered workplace will attract new employees.</p>
  <p><a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2024/04/d2065341-b97e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Learn more about dm-drogerie markt and its path to excellence with SAP.</a></p>
  <h2 id="a-glance-into-the-crystal-ball">A Glance into the Crystal Ball</h2>
  <p>At the same time, low-price online platforms continue to attract consumers with their affordable and wide range of products. They offer competitive prices on trendy clothing and accessories using economies of scale and direct-to-consumer models. Despite concerns about their environmental and ethical practices, these platforms remain popular among price-conscious consumers. However, there is growing awareness of the environmental and social impacts of fast fashion and low-price models. As a result, consumers are becoming increasingly discerning in their purchasing decisions, prioritizing quality, longevity, and sustainability over cheap prices and fast fashion trends.</p>
  <p>“Overall, the consumer landscape is evolving, with a growing emphasis on sustainability, conscious consumption, and ethical practices,” said Sven Denecken, chief marketing and solutions officer for SAP Industries &#x26; CX. “Companies that can adapt to these changing preferences and demonstrate a commitment to environmental and social responsibility are likely to thrive in the long term.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-us-to-get-all-the-updates-on-company-news-stories-and-coverage">Connect with us to get all the updates on company news, stories, and coverage</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news">Follow SAP News on LinkedIn</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/circular-economy</category>
            <category>news-tag/green-ledger</category>
            <category>news-tag/nrf</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
            <category>product/sap-green-token</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-sustainability-solutions</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[CP Foods Selects SAP Solutions for Cloud Sustainability]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/cp-foods-selects-sap-solutions-for-cloud-sustainability</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/cp-foods-selects-sap-solutions-for-cloud-sustainability</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[CP Foods has selected SAP software to future-proof its business and use data to make more sustainable decisions. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_183175263685a353d3b61ffbc18dc57a24b395640.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_183175263685a353d3b61ffbc18dc57a24b395640.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_183175263685a353d3b61ffbc18dc57a24b395640.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="CP Foods Selects SAP Solutions for Cloud Sustainability" src="./media_183175263685a353d3b61ffbc18dc57a24b395640.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="cp-foods-selects-sap-solutions-for-cloud-sustainability">CP Foods Selects SAP Solutions for Cloud Sustainability</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF and BANGKOK</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced Charoen Pokphand Foods Public Company Limited (“CP Foods”) has selected multiple SAP solutions to drive further growth and competitive advantage and to ensure the sustainability of its products for the future.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="record-report-and-act-on-your-sustainability-goals-with-sap-software">Record, report and act on your sustainability goals with SAP software</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/sustainability/solutions.html">Learn how</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Catering to more than 4 billion people globally, CP Foods is embarking on its next stage of digital transformation with the RISE with SAP, SAP Sustainability Footprint Management, and SAP Sustainability Control Tower solutions. In addition, the SAP EHS Management, environment management application will be implemented to future-proof its business and to gain strategic insight into the sustainability impact of its products, processes and infrastructure globally. The company is a leading integrated agro-industrial and food business that is one of the world’s largest producers of feed, shrimp, poultry and pork. It has operations in 17 countries and exports to more than 50 countries.</p>
  <h2 id="global-net-zero-ambitions">Global Net-Zero Ambitions</h2>
  <p>In line with CP Foods’ goal of becoming the “Sustainable Kitchen of the World,” CP Foods is the first food processing company in the world with near- and long-term forests, lands and agriculture (FLAG) sustainability targets validated by the Science-Based Targets Initiative (SBTi). CP Foods is looking to realize the company’s <a href="https://www.cpfworldwide.com/en/media-center/oversea-operations-coal-free-to-net-zero">Net Zero goals</a> of reducing 42% of Scope 1 and 2 emissions and 30.3% of Scope 3 emissions by 2030 – and 90% of Scope 1 and 2 emissions and 72% of Scope 3 emissions by 2050. To achieve these goals, the company is implementing SAP Sustainability solutions to record, report and act on real-time sustainability data, driving carbon accounting at both corporate and product levels.</p>
  <p>“Net Zero is the only solution to climate change,” CP Foods CEO Prasit Boondoungpraser said. “It is important to us to understand and reduce our impact on the planet, so we create food that is not only safe and nutritious for people but also green and clean for the earth. Feeding our livestock, farming our food and transporting it to people’s plates incurs emissions we have to be able to record and report. With RISE with SAP and SAP Sustainability solutions, we will have insight into actual emissions automated in real time rather than relying on manual averages, allowing us to make quick, informed and sustainable business decisions for our operations and for the planet.”</p>
  <p>SAP plans to provide a technology foundation that will support CP Foods in complying with forthcoming carbon regulations in various markets, including the EU Carbon Border Adjustment Mechanism (EU C-BAM) and U.S. SEC climate risk disclosures.</p>
  <p>Key to reducing total emissions, CP Foods will focus on supply chain emissions, with its emissions mostly falling under Scope 3. CP Foods will work with the Customer Success organization at SAP, leverage YASH Technologies’ sustainability expertise and build on Amazon Web Services (AWS) to implement SAP Sustainability solutions. Doing so will allow it to record and report on its Scope 1 and 2 emissions in Thailand and select Scope 3 (3.1 and 3.4) for its feed business in Thailand covering both FLAG and non-FLAG emissions. The next phase of implementation will extend in scope to cover operations around the world.</p>
  <h2 id="cloud-sustainability">Cloud Sustainability</h2>
  <p>Paul Marriott, president of SAP Asia Pacific &#x26; Japan, said: “Sustainability is a huge opportunity for businesses across Asia. Using RISE with SAP and our sustainability solutions, CP Foods is getting ahead of forthcoming emissions regulation and future-proofing its business by using data to make more sustainable decisions. It can use those insights to drive more operational efficiencies, optimize supply chains, and differentiate its business against competitors.”</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-our-approach-to-sustainability-and-our-aspirations-for-a-world-with-zero-emissions-zero-waste-and-zero-inequality">Learn more about our approach to sustainability and our aspirations for a world with zero emissions, zero waste and zero inequality</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/sustainability/our-approach.html">Explore our journey</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>About SAP</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As a global leader in enterprise applications and business AI, SAP (NYSE:SAP) stands at the nexus of business and technology. For over 50 years, organizations have trusted SAP to bring out their best by uniting business-critical operations spanning finance, procurement, HR, supply chain, and customer experience. For more information, visit <a href="http://www.sap.com">www.sap.com</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Note to editors:</strong><br>To preview and download broadcast-standard stock footage and press photos digitally, please visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/photos">www.sap.com/photos</a>. On this platform, you can find high resolution material for your media channels.</p>
  <p><strong>For customers interested in learning more about SAP products:</strong><br>Global Customer Center: +49 180 534-34-24<br>United States Only: 1 (800) 872-1SAP (1-800-872-1727)</p>
  <p><strong>For more information, press only:</strong><br>Rizka Laksmi, <a href="mailto:rizka.laksmi@sap.com">rizka.laksmi@sap.com</a>, WIB<br>Lesa Plingen, +49 622 776 9000, <a href="mailto:lesa.plingen@sap.com">lesa.plingen@sap.com</a>, CET<br><a href="mailto:SAP%20Press%20Room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>This document contains forward-looking statements, which are predictions, projections, or other statements about future events. These statements are based on current expectations, forecasts, and assumptions that are subject to risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results and outcomes to materially differ. Additional information regarding these risks and uncertainties may be found in our filings with the Securities and Exchange Commission, including but not limited to the risk factors section of SAP’s 2023 Annual Report on Form 20-F.<br>© 2024 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.<br>Please consider our <a href="https://www.sap.com/corporate/en/legal/privacy.html">privacy policy</a>. If you received this press release in your e-mail and you wish to unsubscribe to our mailing list please contact <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a> and write Unsubscribe in the subject line.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-ehs-management</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-footprint-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Close the Labor Gap with Socially Conscious Hiring]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/close-the-labor-gap-with-socially-conscious-hiring</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/close-the-labor-gap-with-socially-conscious-hiring</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Turn random acts of social good into programs that benefit marginalized workers, their communities, and the business itself]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f04c09c36bcc5fddd8e1cb43a7c965a5d71b13a5.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f04c09c36bcc5fddd8e1cb43a7c965a5d71b13a5.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1f04c09c36bcc5fddd8e1cb43a7c965a5d71b13a5.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Diverse group of employees standing arm in arm in an office hallway" src="./media_1f04c09c36bcc5fddd8e1cb43a7c965a5d71b13a5.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1044">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="close-the-labor-gap-with-socially-conscious-hiring">Close the Labor Gap with Socially Conscious Hiring</h1>
        <p>Turn random acts of social good into programs that benefit marginalized workers, their communities, and the business itself.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Throughout the world, countries are struggling with an acute labor shortage that shows no sign of abating. In the United States, a smaller workforce will be the key economic challenge of the foreseeable future, according to the <a href="https://www.uschamber.com/economy/what-to-expect-from-the-economy-in-2024#:~:text=Curtis%20Dubay&#x26;text=A%20smaller%20workforce%20will%20define,that%20can%20support%20their%20spending.">U.S. Chamber of Commerce</a>. The numbers are daunting: Even if every unemployed worker today were to fill an open job in their respective industry, the organization says, there would still be millions of unfilled positions.</p>
  <p>But what if businesses redefined the labor pool itself? Doing so would mean looking beyond the ranks of the statistically employed and unemployed. Instead, businesses would tap into a less obvious but large group of people who are not participating in the formally recognized labor market. Many of these people would like to work but have been marginalized from the workforce for a variety of systemic or discriminatory reasons.</p>
  <p>This includes people from less-advantaged populations; individuals with a criminal record; people with physical, mental health, or developmental challenges; those with a history of substance abuse; and people with low educational attainment or without traditional qualifications.</p>
  <p>A study by <a href="https://www.hbs.edu/managing-the-future-of-work/Documents/research/hiddenworkers09032021.pdf">Harvard Business School</a> (HBS) estimates there are more than 27 million of these “hidden workers” in the United States, and similar proportions across the UK and Germany. “The sheer magnitude of this population reveals the potential impact that their substantial re-absorption into the workforce would have,” the study says.</p>
  <p>Many businesses have reached out to engage these populations through their corporate social responsibility (CSR) efforts. Such measures might include changing degree/educational attainment requirements for a small segment of jobs. Or businesses might hire two or three people with a physical or mental disability, or a criminal record, or who belong to an underrepresented population in the local community.</p>
  <p>But often, these are ad hoc measures that, while admirable, tend to fizzle out. Even if they do have some success, they may fail to grow or expand. As the HBR study points out, such isolated CSR efforts can “inherently reinforce the myth that hiring hidden workers is an act of charity or corporate citizenship, rather than a source of competitive advantage.”</p>
  <p>By taking a more purposeful approach with their hiring programs and other CSR-driven initiatives, organizations can transform random acts of corporate social responsibility into long-lasting, far-reaching, repeatable programs. These programs would benefit marginalized workers, the communities they live in, and the business itself.</p>
  <p>Such initiatives would need to address the needs of both the community and the business. They should involve agencies that deeply understand the specific needs of the demographic being hired. Additionally, they should provide wraparound services that go beyond the job. Vitally, these programs need to use data and technology to identify community needs, track the effects of initiatives and encourage uptake in other parts of the business. In other words, it’s not just about <em>doing</em> – it’s about doing with purpose and a goal in mind.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="managing-social-impact--the-s-in-esg">Managing social impact – the S in ESG</h3>
        <p>A complete guide to measuring and managing social impact.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="/resources/measuring-social-impact-s-in-esg">Dive in</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“There is a need, says Eric Eng, a college admission expert and the founder and CEO of <a href="https://admissionsight.com/">AdmissionSight</a>, “for companies to shift from piecemeal initiatives to systemic and strategic approaches that can truly impact underserved communities and build a stronger labor market.”</p>
  <p>By taking a more purposeful approach with their hiring programs and other CSR-driven initiatives, organizations can transform random acts of corporate social responsibility into long-lasting, far-reaching, repeatable programs. These programs would benefit marginalized workers, the communities they live in, and the business itself.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e2a750a701d40250060dbc25b71ca98b07f07ad9.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e2a750a701d40250060dbc25b71ca98b07f07ad9.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1e2a750a701d40250060dbc25b71ca98b07f07ad9.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="A diverse group of smiling businesspeople talking together during a meeting in an office boardroom" src="./media_1e2a750a701d40250060dbc25b71ca98b07f07ad9.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="from-isolated-acts-to-full-fledged-efforts">From isolated acts to full-fledged efforts</h2>
  <p>There are as many wrong ways to pursue a CSR hiring initiative as there are right ways. Often, these efforts are started by a passionate employee whose enthusiasm is a key part of what drives the program. But with that dependency, the program is apt to languish should the employee leave or lose interest.</p>
  <p>Initiatives also fail if their benefits – whether to the business or the community – go unrecognized. This can be due to a lack of rigor in measuring results or a failure to adequately match program elements to community or demographic needs.</p>
  <p>For instance, a study by workforce researcher <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/starbucks-founder-howard-schultz-you-can-do-right-by-your-people-and-your-shareholders-at-the-same-time/ar-AA1kY8vg">The Burning Glass Institute</a> found that simply dropping degree requirements doesn’t significantly affect the hiring of people from diverse groups. The act of applying for a job, the organization says, is contingent not just on whether the individual has the required education credentials but also on whether they could imagine themselves working for a particular company or in a specific sector. This finding reinforces the importance of – beyond removing candidate qualifications – actively encouraging applicants who may never have considered themselves as potential employees.</p>
  <p>A company that has fully embraced socially conscious hiring is MOD Pizza, a fast-casual pizza brand founded by a husband-and-wife team (former owners of Seattle Coffee Company, later acquired by Starbucks). <a href="https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Why-MOD-Pizza-Loves-Hiring-Ex-Cons-13205951.php">Their vision</a>: building a business with a positive social impact.</p>
  <p>Soon after opening, MOD Pizza embraced what’s known as impact hiring, including people with backgrounds of incarceration, homelessness, drug addiction, and intellectual and physical disabilities. It worked with local and national organizations to learn what these individuals needed to thrive on the job, from skill-building to financial assistance during a crisis. It then partnered with various nonprofits to encourage candidates to apply.</p>
  <p>Today, MOD Pizza credits its rapid growth largely to its hiring method. The business today has more than 2,500 employees, <a href="https://www.scrapehero.com/location-reports/Modpizza-USA/">over 550 locations</a> in the United States and Canada, and <a href="https://www.zippia.com/mod-pizza-careers-31728/revenue/">revenues of US$398 million</a>. Ninety-nine percent of company-owned MOD stores have hired people with employment barriers, <a href="https://news.sap.com/2023/09/mod-pizza-driving-positive-outcomes-investing-in-employees/#:~:text=Today%2C%2099%25%20of%20company%2D,retention%20rate%2C%E2%80%9D%20Eberhardt%20says.">according to Dayna Eberhardt</a>, chief people officer at the company, and these hiring practices have led to a more engaged and equitable workforce. These workers “have a higher sense of belonging, a faster rate of promotion, and a higher retention rate,” she says.</p>
  <h2 id="building-a-socially-conscious-hiring-program">Building a socially conscious hiring program</h2>
  <p>MOD Pizza offers several best practices for creating a socially conscious hiring method that benefits both marginalized workers and the business. Some of these core elements include the following:</p>
  <h3 id="match-efforts-to-the-needs-of-the-local-community">1. Match efforts to the needs of the local community</h3>
  <p>Businesses need to understand the specific barriers preventing people in the community from attaining stable employment. They can get these insights by mapping the company’s locations with external data sources that reveal challenges affecting nearby neighborhoods, such as a lack of public transportation, low graduation rates, poor access to healthcare, or limited housing affordability.</p>
  <p>Similarly, businesses can map the geographic location of where employees and job candidates tend to live to identify “applicant deserts” – areas in the community where the company has not historically hired, despite their proximity to their operations. Knowing this, businesses can increase their outreach and visibility in these areas.</p>
  <p>Romanita Matta-Barrera, Chief Workforce Officer for <a href="https://greatersatx.com/">greater:SATX</a>, an economic development partnership in San Antonio, Texas, is leading efforts to address the gap between available jobs and community members who could fill them – 56% of whom are Hispanic.</p>
  <p>“There are jobs available, and often employers wonder where the people are and, at the same time, we see a lot of individuals who have been systematically looking for jobs and have not had access,” she says. “So, we’ve taken a very serious, deep dive into how we can address this to meet not only the needs of our growing employers but to also ensure that our community and its members are being maximized.”</p>
  <p>The organization has worked with Accenture Federal Services, which has embarked on a program to recruit individuals with little to no IT experience from an area of the city with a high level of poverty and a low level of educational attainment. Accenture partnered with several workforce agency partners to identify potential employees and provide them with basic skills training. They also offered wraparound services to address issues like transportation and childcare.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_168db644370231078a951e04cc321e367c1167f1c.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_168db644370231078a951e04cc321e367c1167f1c.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_168db644370231078a951e04cc321e367c1167f1c.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Group of people at a bus stop" src="./media_168db644370231078a951e04cc321e367c1167f1c.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div data-valign="middle">Often employers wonder where the people are and, at the same time, we see a lot of individuals who have been systematically looking for jobs and have not had access.</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div data-valign="middle">Romanita Matta-Barrera, Chief Workforce Officer, greater:SATX</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Training is run similarly to an apprenticeship program, with candidates given three to six months of skill-building, which often leads to full employment, she says. Accenture also targeted a summer high school internship program in the same region to engage the youth population.</p>
  <p>As AdmissionSight’s Eng notes, “addressing systemic poverty and adverse childhood experiences requires a multifaceted approach.” It’s a way of thinking, he says, that “involves creating pathways to quality education and vocational training, ensuring that these are accessible to all individuals.”</p>
  <h3 id="match-efforts-to-business-needs">2. Match efforts to business needs</h3>
  <p>The actions companies take to address community barriers should ideally reflect what the company produces, the services it provides, and what employees are passionate about. This ensures not only that CSR initiatives are meaningful to the community but that they also resonate with the company’s core mission and values.</p>
  <p>Enter MOD Pizza, whose industry faces particularly acute hiring challenges. According to the <a href="https://www.restaurantdive.com/news/national-restaurant-association-job-growth-not-recession-likely-in-2023/643664/">National Restaurant Association</a>, 79% of restaurant operators report difficulty hiring, and 62% are understaffed. This is amid a monthly labor turnover in the hospitality and food service sector at 5.4%, which is twice the national average.</p>
  <p>Meanwhile, <a href="https://aspe.hhs.gov/topics/human-services/incarceration-reentry-0">more than 600,000 individuals</a> are released from prison each year in the United States, and <a href="https://www.prisonpolicy.org/blog/2022/02/08/employment/">60% of those with federal convictions are jobless</a>. Yet <a href="https://www.fair360.com/medialib/uploads/2016/09/Paulk-Presentation-Hiring-Ex-Offenders-09142016.pdf">multiple case studies</a> have shown this population of workers to exhibit high employee loyalty. MOD Pizza’s matchup of business and community needs is a win for both employer and employee.</p>
  <p>In San Antonio, meanwhile, Ernst &#x26; Young (EY) has become more innovative in its hiring process by tapping into the local pool of two-year college students. This matches EY’s specific business needs because – as Matta-Barrera points out – even if applicants had a four-year college degree, they would have to be retrained for EY’s system anyway. As part of the process, EY revamped its onboarding process and engaged its employee resource groups to ensure these new hires were not overwhelmed by entering a corporate environment.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_194e89449df2729abb70702953fc9701b20dcc70f.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_194e89449df2729abb70702953fc9701b20dcc70f.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_194e89449df2729abb70702953fc9701b20dcc70f.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="A businessperson is making a presentation for his colleagues, using a digital tablet and pointing to the board." src="./media_194e89449df2729abb70702953fc9701b20dcc70f.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p>The actions companies take to address community barriers should ideally reflect what the company produces, the services it provides, and what employees are passionate about.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="benefits-of-having-neurodiverse-workers">Benefits of having neurodiverse workers</h3>
        <p>Unlock the potential of neurodiverse workers with the right hiring approach.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="/resources/the-win-win-potential-of-hiring-neurodiverse-workers">Learn more</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="go-beyond-the-job-to-provide-wraparound-services">3. Go beyond the job to provide wraparound services</h3>
  <p>Businesses soon discover that socially conscious hiring extends far beyond offering a job. It also means providing additional supports that are specific to the demographic. For instance, one manufacturer that wanted to increase local hiring learned that many potential applicants did not have reliable transportation to the jobsite. The company worked with employees to become qualified ride-share drivers and provided them with a company car to give these new hires a ride to work.</p>
  <p>In another case, when an automotive supplier began hiring people who were homeless to work at the company, it realized it needed to provide these workers with new shoes.</p>
  <p>Jeffrey Korzenik, economist and author of <em>Untapped Talent: How Second Chance Hiring Works for Your Business and the Community,</em> emphasizes the need for combining quality candidates with cost-effective support systems. <a href="https://hbr.org/2022/10/how-employers-can-set-formerly-incarcerated-workers-up-for-success">In a recent article</a>, he says the most advanced practitioners of what he calls the “second-chance model” of hiring provide social workers, “navigators,” psychologists, or life coaches to these employees. For example, he says, U.S. Rubber Recycling employs a psychiatric rehabilitation counselor, and Nehemiah Manufacturing uses social workers instead of HR professionals.</p>
  <p>One manufacturer that wanted to increase local hiring learned that many potential applicants did not have reliable transportation to the jobsite. The company worked with employees to become qualified ride-share drivers and provided them with a company car to give these new hires a ride to work.</p>
  <p>Businesses should work with local agencies, nonprofits, and community organizations that are already supporting the hiring demographic. These organizations understand these individuals’ most pressing issues and the most effective interventions. As the HBR report says, groups like these have credibility with the workers and understand their needs. “Partnering with such groups helps companies develop, launch, and refine a program to make hidden workers integral to their talent management programs,” the report says.</p>
  <p>When Toyotetsu Texas, a supplier to Toyota Motor Manufacturing Texas’s San Antonio plant, began hiring individuals with intellectual and physical disabilities, it partnered with the Texas Workforce Commission’s Vocational Rehabilitation Services agency, which provides wraparound services to these individuals. The company also created internal job coaches and mentors, and provided plant tours and hands-on experiences to help potential employees determine whether the environment would be a good fit for them.</p>
  <p>“These are individuals who have the competencies to work well in this type of environment with the right internal processes such as mentorship coaching and other accommodations,” Matta-Barrera says.</p>
  <h3 id="measure-success-and-scale">4. Measure success and scale</h3>
  <p>Lastly – but also essentially – businesses need to understand the effect their programs are having in order to sustain and grow these efforts. Too often, the program becomes a line item with a cost assigned to it and no measure of the value it’s providing.</p>
  <p>Businesses should collect data such as the number of individuals hired through these programs, their retention rates, and their progression within the company, and pull it together into a dashboard for quick and easy access.</p>
  <p>Data collection is something MOD Pizza has been intentional about doing. For all of 2022 and into early 2023, employees with justice involvement were promoted at a rate 1.2% greater than the company baseline, <a href="https://flaggerforce.com/blog/industry-interview-with-mod-pizza/">says Robin Hamm, MOD Pizza’s vice president of social impact.</a> Some of these employees hold leadership positions in the company’s stores and support centers. Some also serve as general managers, district managers, and regional directors. And in an industry with staggering attrition rates, these employees were also retained at a rate 6% greater than the company baseline.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d724f8eb4b3bedea8080c9b894ac7dbd1d7c01e0.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d724f8eb4b3bedea8080c9b894ac7dbd1d7c01e0.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1d724f8eb4b3bedea8080c9b894ac7dbd1d7c01e0.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Three coworkers reviewing data on a laptop in an office." src="./media_1d724f8eb4b3bedea8080c9b894ac7dbd1d7c01e0.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1493" height="1120">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p>Dashboards can also help businesses share the details of successful CSR programs across different locations within the company so they can be replicated without reinventing the wheel – or making costly mistakes. For instance, if one business unit has established a program to donate used laptops to underserved students, other divisions could see what makes this program work well and set up similar programs in their communities.</p>
  <p>Businesses should collect data like the number of individuals hired through these programs, their retention rates, and their progression within the company, and pull it together into a dashboard for quick and easy access.</p>
  <p>These dashboards could work as a sort of recommendation engine if they’re populated with pre-vetted agencies and organizations to work with, or actions proven to support communities, based on the barriers to employment they help overcome, including transportation and mentorship programs, charitable giving, and educational and employment opportunity programs.</p>
  <p>Beyond the business itself, organizations should also measure how their efforts are affecting the community overall. Even if it’s not a direct result, are rates of homelessness, graduation rates, Internet access, or poverty levels rising or falling?</p>
  <p>For instance, <a href="https://stories.starbucks.com/uploads/2023/05/2022-Starbucks-Global-Environmental-Social-Impact-Report.pdf">the Burning Glass Institute</a> conducted a project with Starbucks examining the effect of the company’s tuition assistance program on employees’ career trajectories after they left the company. What they learned: These employees often went on to increasingly successful careers that – over time – would strengthen the overall community by fueling economic growth and improving the standard of living for their own families.</p>
  <h2 id="a-new-way-of-hiring">A new way of hiring</h2>
  <p>When it comes to the labor shortage, the problem is not that there aren’t enough people – it’s that employers are not using the potential of the whole community. This is forcing organizations to rethink how they design their hiring programs so they can be more employable to more people.</p>
  <p>Going even further, they need to discover how they can help people coming from these communities who face challenges many employers cannot even imagine.</p>
  <p>By investing in efforts to aid marginalized workers, businesses can make use of formerly untapped labor resources, and by doing so, support their own growth, boost economic development in the community and, ultimately, elevate their brand reputation in the eyes of consumers, employees, and investors.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/what-is</category>
            <category>stage/acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[UN Plastics Treaty: Good for Business and the Planet]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/un-plastics-treaty-good-for-business-and-planet</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/un-plastics-treaty-good-for-business-and-planet</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is part of the Business Coalition for a Global Plastics Treaty, which supports a legally binding UN treaty to end plastic pollution.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/circular-economy</category>
            <category>product/sap-green-token</category>
            <category>product/sap-responsible-design-and-production</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-sustainability-solutions</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Private Equity and Renewable Energy: How Investors Can Set Themselves Up for Digital Transformation Success]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/private-equity-renewable-energy-digital-transformation-success</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/private-equity-renewable-energy-digital-transformation-success</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Private equity firms are a huge driver of renewable energy sources. Read about the need for scalable solutions to support this growth.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/enterprise-resource-planning</category>
            <category>news-tag/renewable-energy</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Widening Your Sustainability Scope]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/widening-sustainability-scope-2-scope-3</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/widening-sustainability-scope-2-scope-3</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Businesses are measuring Scope 2 and 3 effects of their operations beyond their corporate walls. That requires strong supply chain data.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>core-topic/environmental-compliance</category>
            <category>industry/automotive</category>
            <category>content-type/what-is</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Driving Progress in Sustainability, Adoption, and AI: The 2024 SAP Innovation Award Winners]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2024/04/2024-sap-innovation-award-winners</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2024/04/2024-sap-innovation-award-winners</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The 2024 SAP Innovation Award winners have utilized SAP solutions and AI to achieve remarkable results. Learn more about the winners.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/executive-blog</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>sap-award/sap-innovation-awards</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[We Can’t Achieve Net Zero Without the Circular Economy]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/we-cant-achieve-net-zero-without-the-circular-economy</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/we-cant-achieve-net-zero-without-the-circular-economy</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Net zero and the circular economy go hand in hand. Read to learn how businesses, like SAP, and non-corporate bodies can accelerate progress.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/circular-economy</category>
            <category>news-tag/net-zero</category>
            <category>product/sap-green-token</category>
            <category>product/sap-responsible-design-and-production</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-data-exchange</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-sustainability-solutions</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Meeting the New SEC Emissions Policies: We Already Have All the Technology We Need]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/new-sec-emissions-policies-sap-technology</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/new-sec-emissions-policies-sap-technology</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New SEC emissions policies require disclosure of Scope 1 and 2 emissions. At SAP, we embrace the SEC’s ruling. Read about why.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-emissions</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-footprint-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[From CSRD Reporting to Sustainable Business Outcomes]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/from-csrd-reporting-to-sustainable-business-outcomes</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/from-csrd-reporting-to-sustainable-business-outcomes</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[By leveraging SAP Sustainability solutions, organizations can move beyond compliance, like CSRD reporting, and operationalize sustainability.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/compliance</category>
            <category>news-tag/esg</category>
            <category>news-tag/green-ledger</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-data-exchange</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-footprint-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-sustainability-solutions</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP CSR's eBook Celebrates a Year of Global Impact]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/sap-csr-ebook-celebrates-global-impact</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/sap-csr-ebook-celebrates-global-impact</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The impact of SAP CSR in 2023 is a testament to the power of collective action and shared vision. Read to find out how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1aa60aead41f035043e44cbfe1f53c8c65e859485.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1aa60aead41f035043e44cbfe1f53c8c65e859485.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1aa60aead41f035043e44cbfe1f53c8c65e859485.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP CSR’s eBook Celebrates a Year of Global Impact" src="./media_1aa60aead41f035043e44cbfe1f53c8c65e859485.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-csrs-ebook-celebrates-a-year-of-global-impact">SAP CSR’s eBook Celebrates a Year of Global Impact</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Reflecting on the past year, one event stands out vividly in my memory: the Social Enterprises World Forum (SEWF) in Amsterdam, the Netherlands. For those unfamiliar, imagine a global assembly where more than 1,500 entrepreneurs from 82 countries dedicated to societal and environmental missions come together. These enterprises prioritize people and the planet, reinvesting their profits to advance their respective causes. Witnessing the energy and innovation in Amsterdam was a powerful reminder of why SAP has emphasized social entrepreneurship for the second consecutive year.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>It makes me proud to think about the 676 SAP colleagues who, in 2023, participated in our pro bono consulting programs, offering their expertise to these visionary social entrepreneurs. As in previous years, this collaboration has proven mutually beneficial, with 74% of our employees reporting a positive, lasting impact on their careers. Furthermore, 96% of the supported organizations and 77% of their beneficiaries have seen significant improvements. These numbers speak volumes about the shared value of our engagement.</p>
  <p>But the 2023 SEWF wasn’t just a personal highlight; it marked the beginning of another significant milestone. We announced our investment in the <strong>Social Enterprise People and Planet First Verification</strong> with Good Market and SEWF. This initiative aims to set a global standard for recognizing organizations prioritizing social and environmental impacts. Social enterprises can now also identify themselves on SAP Business Network, the world’s largest B2B commerce platform. This breakthrough can make it easier for these businesses to explore new business-to-business opportunities while also helping SAP customers achieve their goals of being more environmentally and socially responsible. Saying it’s a win-win situation is a bit cliché, but in this case it’s actually true.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-is-powering-equitable-access-to-economic-opportunity-education-and-employment-and-the-circular-economy">SAP is powering equitable access to economic opportunity, education and employment, and the circular economy</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/our-values/csr.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Working with SEWF shows how much we believe in working together and driving towards collective impact. I’ve said it before and I’ll say it again: we can’t do this by ourselves. Working with others is the key to driving the kind of systemic change our world needs. This idea is a big part of what we stand for at SAP, and is at the heart of our corporate social responsibility (<a href="/topics/csr">CSR</a>) strategy.</p>
  <p>This idea of working together really comes to life in our collaboration with <strong>UNICEF and Generation Unlimited</strong>. In 2023 – the fourth year of our partnership – we set out to make a real difference by not just developing the skills of young people but also finding jobs in the SAP ecosystem. Launching the SAP Educate to Employ program is a big step in that direction. Helping 25 young people get jobs with SAP in each of our pilot countries – Nigeria, Kenya, South Africa, and the Philippines – might not sound like a lot, but it’s a huge deal for each of those young people. For them, it’s a gateway to a sustainable livelihood, offering them not just gainful employment but a chance to build a career, achieve financial stability, and make meaningful contributions to their communities and the broader world. It’s about unlocking their potential and enabling them to participate in the digital and green economy. By the end of the year, we saw amazing results. While more than 2,500 had already passed the aptitude test, over 1,000 young people in Africa finished our “Boost Your Career with SAP Skills” course and more than 500 got through the first big part of their training.</p>
  <p>But, what’s a year recap without some high-level numbers? Let’s dive into some impressive <strong>numbers from 2023</strong>. More than 20,000 of our SAP colleagues volunteered over 140,000 hours. Our initiatives reached over 2.8 million young people – almost half girls – and supported over 41,000 teachers. Our partner network reached 1 billion people in over 140 countries. These stats are just the tip of the iceberg, showing our big reach and impact together with our partners.</p>
  <p>Building on this, our signature partnerships with Africa Code Week, Meet and Code, and Latin Code Week have always been at the heart of our achievements. As we handed over these initiatives in 2023, we took a moment to reflect and evaluate Africa Code Week and Latin Code Week outcomes more deeply. For instance, by empowering 14.6 million participants with the education, knowledge, and ICT skills needed to participate in the digital future, <strong>Africa Code Week</strong> has increased the likelihood that beneficiaries will realize higher earnings during their working lives. Common Good Marketplace estimates that Africa Code Week catalyzed up to US$1 billion in social value for program participants between 2015 and 2022 based on future increased income.</p>
  <p>As we close the chapter on 2023 and look ahead, the journey we’ve embarked upon at SAP CSR is a testament to the power of collective action and shared vision. The stories, numbers, and outcomes shared in our eBook reflect our commitment to making a meaningful difference. <a href="https://d.dam.sap.com/a/Gnggenc/SAP%20CSR%20in%20Review%202023.pdf?rc=10">Read the full eBook.</a></p>
  <p>Thank you to everyone who has been a part of this journey. Your passion, dedication, and commitment are what drive us forward.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Alexandra van der Ploeg is global head of Corporate Social Responsibility at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="follow-sap-news-on-linkedin-to-stay-up-to-date">Follow SAP News on LinkedIn to stay up-to-date</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news">Connect with us</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>non-sap-event/africa-code week</category>
            <category>news-tag/csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/generation-unlimited</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/social-entrepreneurship</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Business Network Digitalizes Procurement for VAT E-Invoicing Mandates]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/sap-business-network-digitalizes-procurement-e-invoicing</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/sap-business-network-digitalizes-procurement-e-invoicing</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With VAT e-invoicing mandates on the rise, buyers and suppliers can join SAP Business Network for trusted, simplified procurement automation.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/financial-management</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/accounting</category>
            <category>news-tag/digitalization</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Great Data-Driven Auto Distribution Rally]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/the-great-data-driven-auto-distribution-rally</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/the-great-data-driven-auto-distribution-rally</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[To keep up with customers, automakers need to up their data game. Vehicles are changing, but the sales model is stuck in neutral.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1354ead36c3a8ed04a5ef33f01c05c22da44f4ae1.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1354ead36c3a8ed04a5ef33f01c05c22da44f4ae1.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1354ead36c3a8ed04a5ef33f01c05c22da44f4ae1.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Car Workers Inspecting Production Line" src="./media_1354ead36c3a8ed04a5ef33f01c05c22da44f4ae1.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1044">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="the-great-data-driven-auto-distribution-rally">The Great Data-Driven Auto Distribution Rally</h1>
        <p>Vehicles are changing, but the sales model is stuck in neutral. To keep up with customers, automakers need to up their data game.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>By Randy Garrison and Chuck Mazurek</p>
  <p>A few of Ford Motor Company’s recent recruits are a good indication of where the legacy auto company is headed. The <a href="https://www.detroitnews.com/story/business/autos/ford/2022/02/10/ford-hires-away-tesla-engineering-director-work-advanced-evs/6739919001/">hirings</a> of former Apple and Tesla execs lay bare the company’s ambition to move away from internal combustion engines (ICEs) and to electric vehicles (EVs) – and even more so, to a technology- and software-focused company. Ford’s head, Jim Farley, says the <a href="https://www.latimes.com/environment/newsletter/2023-09-14/ford-ceo-jim-farley-talks-up-the-companys-ev-future-boiling-point">changes</a> he’s implementing – such as developing a new EV platform for release in 2025 – are “not an EV revolution” but instead are “a digital shift to a digital product.”</p>
  <p>But already in 2024, the company has <a href="https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/ford-reduce-f-150-lightning-production-2024-01-19/">cut back production</a> of their flagship electric truck, the <a href="https://www.reuters.com/business/autos-transportation/ford-reduce-f-150-lightning-production-2024-01-19/">F-150 Lightning</a>, because of lower-than-predicted demand.</p>
  <p>In their cohort of older original equipment manufacturers (OEMs), Ford is far from alone in struggling to remake its business.</p>
  <p>The automotive industry can be divided into two eras: Before Tesla and During Tesla. That’s a reflection of how much has changed in auto-land in the past two decades. Consumer buying habits, vehicles technology, and mobility options – Uber, car sharing, e-bikes – have all changed, and Tesla stands as the leading example of how automaking and marketing are also changing. As a vertically integrated, direct-to-consumer (DTC), native electric company, Tesla is currently the <a href="https://money.usnews.com/investing/articles/the-10-most-valuable-auto-companies-in-the-world">most valuable</a> vehicle manufacturer in the world. Its valuation in 2023 rose to as much as three times that of Toyota – long in the top spot, but now in second place – despite Toyota selling roughly five times as many cars as Tesla in the first half of that year. Farley noted that Ford’s current distribution model costs an estimated $2,000 more per vehicle versus Tesla’s integrated approach, with most of that extra cost attributed to advertising and inventory.</p>
  <p>For traditional automakers, as Ford’s experience shows, keeping up has been a challenge. The fragmentation of every step of the old-school process, including the relationship structure between OEMs and dealers, means siloed systems and data, which hamper automakers’ abilities to adapt and compete.</p>
  <p>Thriving in this new era of electrical vehicles and other modes of transportation requires new ways of making, selling, and servicing cars. Accepting these changes first and foremost means getting a better handle on the data. With that data, they’ll be able to make informed business model choices, streamline production, understand who is buying their product and why, and how it’s being used. Oh, and of course, all of that will add up to making more money. Making these changes won’t be easy, but there are strategies to make it more efficient.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_135e58689f6e6c5e54d774c7463839586a88ae866.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_135e58689f6e6c5e54d774c7463839586a88ae866.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_135e58689f6e6c5e54d774c7463839586a88ae866.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="White, young salesman talking to a middle-aged white couple in a car showroom." src="./media_135e58689f6e6c5e54d774c7463839586a88ae866.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1493" height="1120">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="stuck-in-neutral">Stuck in neutral</h2>
  <p>In the United States, the traditional dealership system hasn’t changed much over the years from what’s considered to be the <a href="https://www.cnn.com/2022/04/30/cars/why-we-buy-cars-this-way/index.html">first-ever dealership in Detroit in 1898</a> to the <a href="https://www.newsweek.com/why-cant-you-buy-car-way-buy-computer-453657">legal morass</a> that exists today. Florida, for example, recently banned DTC sales, but only for legacy automakers; non-dealership brands are allowed. Adherence to this model differs around the world. For example, many Asian countries, such as Malaysia, have long allowed direct sales; Japan sees a mixed model, with OEMs owning varying stakes in dealerships. But for the largest Western brands, changing the established, independent dealer-distribution model has been challenging.</p>
  <p>In the late-2000s, Tesla rolled up with its completely owned DTC sales model, with fixed prices and Tesla-employed sales staff. It’s a streamlined, vertically integrated operation in which Tesla has access to all the data about all their vehicles and customers.</p>
  <p>Other upstarts in the automotive space, such as electric truck pioneer Rivian and China’s fast-growing BYD, are also DTC. DTC auto companies don’t work with independent dealerships, so they don’t have that extra dealership margin on top of the cost. They have stores (Tesla), “hubs” and “spaces” (Rivian), and “studios” (Lucid) – all names for brand-owned places where vehicles are displayed. Plus, they have data.</p>
  <p>“That ownership of the customer experience, it’s the ownership of the customer preferences, the demand profiles, patterns, the market insights,” says Neil Ganguli, senior managing director at U.S.-based FTI Consulting.</p>
  <p>Not that Tesla is without its own challenges and, to be fair, it did start up in a vastly different auto environment in which it was almost the only game in town for a premium EV, points out Steve Young, managing director at UK-based automotive consultancy ICDP. Young says the comparison between old and new isn’t fair. Tesla had a cost advantage because it was spending less money – on advertising, for example, and as much as $35 less per employee hour in labor costs, <a href="https://www.businessinsider.com/ford-gm-stellantis-pay-raise-uaw-contract-tesla-labor-costs-2023-10">according to reports</a>. But for years, it also <a href="https://jalopnik.com/tesla-loses-a-lot-of-money-selling-cars-but-makes-it-a-1846768094">lost money</a> on each vehicle sold. Tesla’s competition has increased even as the company added capacity, Young notes, leading to price discounts, lower third- and fourth-quarter 2023 earnings, and a big market capitalization hit. Then there was that end-of-<a href="https://apnews.com/article/tesla-autopilot-recall-driver-monitoring-system-8060508627a34e6af889feca46eb3002">2023 recall</a> of almost all Teslas sold in the U.S. to address autopilot problems.</p>
  <p>Nevertheless, Tesla owns the customer data and, in that vital regard, older companies are playing catch-up. OEMs don’t have the “muscle memory, this is not DNA that they have already,” Ganguli says, whereas the newer automakers have DTC built into their standard operating procedures and are strategizing completely differently. “Their systems, their processes, their governance are wired that way. There is no legacy and changing the mentality and needing new skills,” he says.</p>
  <p>To illustrate the extreme silo-fication conventional OEMs must combat, consider the issue of sales incentives.</p>
  <p>Anyone who’s shopping for wheels is aware of incentives for lease or purchase. Auto companies budget billions of dollars every year for those incentives, which are often stacked (i.e., offered one on top of the other). OEMs lacking full visibility across the sale process may end up selling the car at a loss and not even realize it. And they don’t understand the customer network because they don’t have access to the data about their customers. But the dealerships do.</p>
  <p>OEMs making gas vehicles also have the pressure of <a href="https://electrek.co/2023/10/20/colorado-partially-adopts-californias-ev-rules-but-falls-short-of-2035-ban/">EV deadlines</a> in several states in the United States, in <a href="https://www.canada.ca/en/environment-climate-change/news/2022/12/let-it-roll-government-of-canada-moves-to-increase-the-supply-of-electric-vehicles-for-canadians.html">Canada</a>, and <a href="https://ec.europa.eu/commission/presscorner/detail/en/IP_22_6462">in the EU</a>, where most countries are mandating 100% EV new car sales by 2035. So they’re adopting aggressive changes to transform their businesses into leaner, meaner, greener machines that can compete with Tesla and its DTC kin.</p>
  <ul>
    <li><a href="https://thedriven.io/2023/05/24/volvo-to-end-uk-dealerships-as-it-transitions-to-tesla-style-sales-model/">Volvo</a> is going all in with a full DTC sales model like Tesla’s, starting in the UK, to be followed by Sweden, then other European countries.</li>
    <li>Volkswagen’s parent company, VW Group, is aiming for major operational changes to <a href="https://www.cnn.com/2023/11/27/business/volkswagen-brand-no-longer-competitive/index.html">improve competitiveness</a>.</li>
    <li>GM wants to be considered a <a href="https://insideevs.com/news/537914/gm-tech-company-tesla-value/">tech company</a> – a refrain heard from CEO Mary Barra <a href="https://www.detroitnews.com/story/business/autos/general-motors/2018/10/29/ceo-mary-barra-wants-people-think-gm-tech-company/1808690002/">as early as 2018</a> – by providing software platforms and more EV models.</li>
    <li>Ford’s Jim Farley, speaking at a June 2022 strategy conference, also <a href="https://www.thedrive.com/news/ford-ceo-jim-farley-says-direct-sales-no-ads-will-sell-future-evs">said</a>, “We’ve got to go to non-negotiated price. We’ve got to go to 100% online … no inventory, it goes directly to the customer, 100% remote pickup and delivery.”</li>
  </ul>
  <p>Unfortunately, inefficient infrastructure and systems mean they’re driving uphill.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ffa3770f80a6b9f5d5ff739c47bd56ba9c435149.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ffa3770f80a6b9f5d5ff739c47bd56ba9c435149.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1ffa3770f80a6b9f5d5ff739c47bd56ba9c435149.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Robotic arms assembling a line of pickup trucks on a production line" src="./media_1ffa3770f80a6b9f5d5ff739c47bd56ba9c435149.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1669" height="1120">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="tech-in-park">Tech in park</h2>
  <p>Underpinning these business model challenges is a high degree of technical debt. OEMs are relying on decades-old technology systems that are on their last legs – if they’re walking at all.</p>
  <p>“The issue is that the legacy manufacturers have got legacy – it’s in the label,” as Steve Young puts it. Legacy covers a lot of ground in this case: products, production equipment, distribution agreements, and IT systems. “They’ve got existing networks, they’ve got combustion engine product lines still and they need to have them because that’s what’s funding their EV development, and still what consumers want to buy,” says Young.</p>
  <p>And buying trends, changed by e-commerce and accelerated by the pandemic, have meant an increase in the number of car and truck buyers who are fine with doing the entire transaction online. Instead of wandering through a dealer lot to see what’s available, shoppers do their research online, test drive one or two of the best options, then go back online to configure and finalize the sale, notes Peter Wells, professor at Cardiff University’s <a href="https://www.cardiff.ac.uk/research/explore/research-units/centre-for-automotive-industry-research">Centre for Automotive Industry Research</a> (CAIR). “They know what they want; they don’t need to be ‘sold’ in that sense. And I think a lot of U.S. dealerships are still selling,” he says.</p>
  <p>“It’s going to be more and more prevalent that, at least for software-defined vehicles (SDVs), sales are going to be more DTC-oriented," says Ganguli, noting that SDVs are basically computers with wheels, which supports a simpler buying process: the customer chooses a few options and that’s it, because a single car can be customized, and later upgraded, quite easily via software updates. It’s the proverbial win-win: simpler for the customers, much more efficient for the OEMs. <a href="https://www.wardsauto.com/industry-news/wards-intelligence-unveils-automakers-sdv-rankings-tesla-bev-oems-take-lead">According to Wards Auto</a>, the only established automakers that are making a showing in that regard are Mercedes-Benz, Volvo, and BMW. When OEM systems can’t meet customer expectations, or keep up the pace of software development, it leaves the door open for even more competition. Even Amazon is getting in on the act with a recent agreement to sell Hyundai cars through Amazon.com.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1932cc003e34bc28ee14e6c871a54923a072a552d.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1932cc003e34bc28ee14e6c871a54923a072a552d.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1932cc003e34bc28ee14e6c871a54923a072a552d.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="In a data center full of monitors, a businessman stands before a big screen with an interactive world map on it." src="./media_1932cc003e34bc28ee14e6c871a54923a072a552d.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="2160">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="racing-to-resiliency">Racing to resiliency</h3>
        <p>Learn how automotive suppliers can drive new growth amid disruption.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/grow/industry/automotive.html">Read more</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="driving-modernization">Driving modernization</h2>
  <p>To keep up, automakers must speed up the modernization process, taking better advantage of the data they have while making changes to get their hands on more. They will need to take simultaneous steps in changing internal processes and IT systems, while exploring options for new distribution models. The following are key ideas and options in each of these areas.</p>
  <h2 id="change-strategies">1. Change strategies</h2>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Put change management first</strong></li>
  </ul>
  <p>Auto companies might think modernizing is an IT project, says Steve Young, but that’s the wrong approach: it’s really a gigantic change-management project. Large, outdated legacy systems can’t be changed at the flick of a switch, he says, and neither can the behaviors of thousands of employees across OEMs and dealerships. “To get that degree of data and process integration and the alignment of objectives, the alignment of goals, the lines of thinking, is a huge change-management program,” he says.</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Prepare for privacy and the Right to Repair</strong></li>
  </ul>
  <p>“It’s Official: Cars Are the Worst Product Category We Have Ever Reviewed for Privacy,” is the title of a Mozilla Foundation 2023 vehicle <a href="https://foundation.mozilla.org/en/privacynotincluded/articles/its-official-cars-are-the-worst-product-category-we-have-ever-reviewed-for-privacy/">privacy report</a>. There’s a <a href="https://theconversation.com/the-battle-over-right-to-repair-is-a-fight-over-your-cars-data-213052">massive amount of data</a> being brokered back and forth between the vehicle and the OEM, and there are no fully developed <a href="https://jalopnik.com/massachusetts-is-trying-to-protect-data-privacy-in-cars-1850849741">privacy standards</a> applicable to this data yet. OEMs will need to make this issue a priority so changes to systems and dealer models don’t run into roadblocks later on.</p>
  <p>Vehicle data is also part of the conversation <a href="https://www.wired.com/story/fight-right-repair-cars-turns-ugly/">around the Right to Repair Act</a>. Currently, repair data is completely separate from vehicle data, which includes personal info such as driver behavior, subscription choices, and connected cellphone data, along with more general data such as road and weather conditions. Dealers have their own systems to get data, and OEMs have theirs.</p>
  <p>Additionally, vehicle data needs to be available to independent repairers so they can fix a vehicle. In the U.S., if a repairer isn’t sponsored by an OEM or OEM certified (which is expensive for the repair shop), they won’t have that data. In Europe, they have the right to that data, but that doesn’t mean they’re able to get it easily.</p>
  <p>One solution is to create applications that keep personal data and vehicle performance data entirely separate. Then privacy considerations for the former won’t impede upon using the latter for maintenance.</p>
  <h2 id="change-technology">2. Change technology</h2>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>The one-application-at-a-time approach</strong></li>
  </ul>
  <p>This method means building around the exterior of existing technology systems. Companies first identify specific problems, then those problems are separated and updated. That way, particular processes can be modernized without disturbing the integrity of the remaining legacy environment, which can shuffle along until all of it has been replaced or retired.</p>
  <p>This cautious approach results in a long path of interoperability between old and new, but it’s the most cautious approach. On the other hand, it buffers – but doesn’t really reduce – legacy technology. The idea is that it will see itself out eventually.</p>
  <p>Nobody’s doing wholesale revamp, says Ganguli, but they are milking their legacy technology. “[They’re] harvesting it until it’s not needed, and then building this new capability on the back of the new business,” he says.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_165e099889971565f99d9ddc159777d8e374b9df4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_165e099889971565f99d9ddc159777d8e374b9df4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_165e099889971565f99d9ddc159777d8e374b9df4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="A high-level view of a road running through a green field." src="./media_165e099889971565f99d9ddc159777d8e374b9df4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>The greenfield approach</strong></li>
  </ul>
  <p>Another option OEMs can choose is the greenfield approach, which is treating a new plant – for EV batteries or semiconductors, for example – like a startup, where they can build new systems and experiment with new operating models.</p>
  <p>In this way, companies reduce their technical debt not by rewriting old systems, but by gradually making them less of the overall portfolio as new assets come online. Unlike the one-at-a-time approach, integration with older systems is minimized. It’s a gradual approach, but reduces the risk associated with turning off manufacturing lines and systems to do hard switchovers.</p>
  <p>In a variation of this idea, some OEMs are increasingly partnering with specialist companies, not just for automotive parts but for software components and platforms. They won’t own the entire vehicle ecosystem, and farming some of that out is a quicker path to modernizing.</p>
  <p>“They do need to keep a foot in both camps – the ICE world and the EV world – for at least some time to come,” says Young. “I think that the way to handle the ICE world as that declines within their total portfolio is probably more through joint ventures and alliances.”</p>
  <h2 id="explore-dealership-and-distribution-models">3. Explore dealership and distribution models</h2>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Dealers as service centers</strong></li>
  </ul>
  <p>Because of the steady increase in DTC sales, the data roles of the OEM and the dealership will likely be switched. The dealer will be the customer-facing contact, but the OEMs will have the data, which it will share (or not) with their dealer network, says Young.</p>
  <p>Ganguli notes that disruption is inevitable and expects some dealerships will close up shop. There will be a bifurcation, he says; sales and advertising will happen at OEM-owned showrooms, and former dealerships will operate mostly as independent service centers.</p>
  <p>The fee-based agency model – which means a single fixed price and a fixed dealer fee for every car – is gaining some popularity, particularly in Europe. But it also has a data problem, says Young. The OEMs don’t have the skills or relationship with customers to customize deals, he says, so they end up painting with a very broad brush in terms of promotions, incentives, and customer communications. “Everybody gets $5,000 off, but actually half of them would have bought with $1,000 off,” Ganguli offers as an example.</p>
  <p>“Dealership salespeople today are practicing dynamic pricing on a deal-by-deal basis, pitching an offer at the highest [price] level they think the customer will accept.” Under the agency model, OEMs take on that responsibility, but will be challenged to do a better job than the dealers – without the benefit of being face to face, he says.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="racing-into-a-new-world">Racing into a new world</h3>
        <p>Learn how to unlock brand value with mobility services</p>
        <p><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2023/03/962c14d3-687e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Read the whitepaper</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Dealerships-as-a-service</strong></li>
  </ul>
  <p>This isn’t necessarily a bad thing for dealers, however. Consider the EV: compared to the thousands of moving parts in an ICE vehicle, EVs have just a handful. A Tesla car, for example, has about 24 parts – total. While that means less work and money for <em>maintenance</em>, EV <em>repairs</em> could be more expansive and expensive. According to a joint SAP/Reuters report, <em><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/dg/na-dealer-of-the-future-reuters-events-report/index.html">The Dealer of the Future</a></em>, almost half a dealer’s revenue already comes from service and parts.</p>
  <p>“This is a case where tighter alignment between OEM and dealer could benefit both. If OEMs can share connected-car data on performance with their dealers, dealers could offer predictive maintenance to their customers before a fault or breakdown occurs,” says the report.</p>
  <p>And, ironically, this is also a case in which old meets new: GM dealers have been <a href="https://jalopnik.com/gm-dealers-have-been-quietly-repairing-teslas-for-over-1849803291">repairing Teslas</a>. If vehicle data is portable, as suggested by the Right to Repair discussion, then dealerships may become less obligated to a single automotive brand and may switch allegiances or add new brands in a fluid manner.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c86737418265e86ad3d450790da5ef3a3f16d6ea.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c86737418265e86ad3d450790da5ef3a3f16d6ea.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1c86737418265e86ad3d450790da5ef3a3f16d6ea.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Illustration of a car in a wind tunnel." src="./media_1c86737418265e86ad3d450790da5ef3a3f16d6ea.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3198" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="driving-into-the-future">Driving into the future</h2>
  <p>How the industry will shake out is very much still to be determined. As car brands plan for the future, sustainability is, of course, a prime consideration. Volkswagen, for example, is aiming for a complete circular strategy, says Peter Wells of CAIR. The company’s goal is to maintain ownership of their cars beyond the first lease term and through the vehicle’s entire lifecycle – from manufacturing through to sales, aftercare, and beyond. At the end of a vehicle’s usefulness, it gets deconstructed – also by Volkswagen.</p>
  <p>“What the Volkswagen Group is currently trying to do is basically own the circle,” says Wells. “They’re trying to control the entire lifecycle of the vehicle. That’s a huge kind of data exercise there because they’ve got to track those vehicles.”</p>
  <p><a href="/resources/digital-twins-at-work">Digital twins</a>, autonomous vehicles, networked roadway infrastructure, even <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Terrafugia">flying vehicles</a> – whatever current or future technologies you can envision, odds are someone is exploring it.</p>
  <p>“The underpinning technologies are changing really fast,” Wells says. “That’s an extra layer of uncertainty on top of the global restructuring that’s going on. And so you have this perfect storm of electrification, digitalization, and global restructuring, and a huge uncertainty as to the future kind of role of the car in our lives.”</p>
  <p>Better collection, use, and sharing of data is the way forward for all automotive companies. The old-school OEMs need to address their data deficiencies to be competitive in this new world. And they need to step on it.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/business-transformation</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>stage/acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Vestas: Powering Quality in the Supply Chain]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/vestas-powering-quality-in-supply-chain</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/vestas-powering-quality-in-supply-chain</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Vestas, a major wind turbine manufacturer, launched a supply chain quality initiative powered by SAP solutions and SAP Business Network.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>industry/oil-gas-energy</category>
            <category>news-tag/renewable-energy</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Building the Future Factory: A Special Report]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/building-the-future-factory-a-special-report</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/building-the-future-factory-a-special-report</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Dive beneath the buzzwords to find profitable steps forward for manufacturers, from sustainability to security to supply chain.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e319dcec96d029e6ff75199d1249eaa1b8d4741c.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e319dcec96d029e6ff75199d1249eaa1b8d4741c.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1e319dcec96d029e6ff75199d1249eaa1b8d4741c.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="A factory roof covered with solar photovoltaic panels" src="./media_1e319dcec96d029e6ff75199d1249eaa1b8d4741c.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1044">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="building-the-future-factory-a-special-report">Building the Future Factory: A Special Report</h1>
        <p>Dive beneath the buzzwords to find profitable steps forward for manufacturers, from sustainability to security to supply chain.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>By Derek Slater</p>
  <p>The factory of the future will be more:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Modular, flexible, and agile</li>
    <li>Efficient and profitable</li>
    <li>Interconnected, both internally and to business partners</li>
    <li>Sustainable, for both its environment and community</li>
  </ul>
  <p>Easy to say, but ever so complicated to do?</p>
  <p>Plenty of companies struggle with the capital investments, workforce requirements, and the data-savvy to build a factory of <em>today</em>, let alone <em>tomorrow</em>.</p>
  <p>Further, to try to decipher future developments is to wade smack into a jungle of jargon and “consultantese,” from industry 4.0 and software-defined factories to analog front ends (AFEs) and 4D printing. (Yes, 4D – that’s not a typo.)<a href=""><sup>1</sup></a></p>
  <p>Nevertheless, business as usual won't cut it. Today's environment of “permacrisis,” as SAP's Richard Howells says in <a href="/resources/supply-chain-innovation-whats-next">an expert panel discussion</a> – wars, pandemic hangover, shipping backups, extreme weather events, energy costs, unstable countries – stresses traditional factories and supply chains to the breaking point. And the planetary reverberations of manufacturing, its by-products, its resources, and energy use, are existential.</p>
  <p>Fortunately, “in manufacturing, sustainability is profitability,” SAP's Mike Lackey notes in the same discussion. Increasing efficiency and agility while decreasing waste <em>will</em> feed the bottom line. In other words, building the future factory is about making goods and making money. And not just in this quarter, but for decades to come.</p>
  <p>Delving into the concrete topics underneath the pie-in-the-sky vision and through the jargon jungle, it's clear that technical progress is happening on all fronts, at a dizzying rate. Forward-looking manufacturers can take advantage of those developments now, to profit despite permacrisis challenges, while building toward tomorrow.</p>
  <p>Here are key takeaways from our special report, with links to further details in nine in-depth articles exploring the future factory. Learn how to make smart workforce and technology investments on the way there, and how to create more value beyond the factory walls in your broader supply chain.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15a56767d95d6e6b71b3c4377faaa4965c6ac597e.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15a56767d95d6e6b71b3c4377faaa4965c6ac597e.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_15a56767d95d6e6b71b3c4377faaa4965c6ac597e.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Two men wearing hardhats and looking at a laptop on the factory floor." src="./media_15a56767d95d6e6b71b3c4377faaa4965c6ac597e.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="the-regenerative-factory">The regenerative factory</h2>
  <p>What might a factory look like in a decade or two? Let's start by looking at <strong>how sustainability will shape tomorrow’s factories</strong>, because sustainability equals profitability, as <a href="/resources/profitable-purpose-the-future-of-business-sustainability">SAP Insights research has confirmed</a>.</p>
  <p>The lead article of our special report, “<a href="/blogs/the-sustainable-factory-of-the-future">The Sustainable Factory of the Future</a>,” sounds a perhaps counterintuitive note: the average factory footprint may be much smaller than today’s.</p>
  <p>For decades, manufacturing has focused on repeatable efficiency at an ever-greater scale. Today’s driving force, on the other hand, is increasingly a demand for more agility: for example, the ability to shift manufacturing from one place to another based on demand, capacity, or disruptive events, as well as the need to produce more customized products, rather than identical widgets. Moving to a smaller form factor also has positive implications for sustainable – or, better, regenerative – operations.</p>
  <p>“The regenerative principle is to return things better than before,” says Stanford researcher Trond Undheim. “The larger the scale, the more steel and carbon you are using, and the more difficult it becomes to disassemble. Regeneration is all about disassembly, leaving no trace, actually leaving it better.”</p>
  <p>It’s not just about disassembly; today’s ongoing operations benefit too. The use of smaller facilities requires greater efficiency, using less space and power. It also suggests multiple, dispersed production points located closer to where the manufactured goods will be used, reducing the financial and environmental costs of delivery.</p>
  <p>Whatever the size and scale, prominent manufacturers such as Interface, Siemens, and Tesla offer strategies for future factories to address all these areas:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Carbon:</strong> Cut emissions faster. Spot issues and prioritize improvements by using Internet of Things (IoT) data. Store (sequester) carbon in products, as well as in the factory itself (in cement and other building materials).</li>
    <li><strong>Waste:</strong> Use analytics to find advanced ways to reduce waste. Additive manufacturing yields less scrap. Reduce raw material use; recycle waste on site; think “circularly” about products through end-of-life.</li>
    <li><strong>Power:</strong> Go beyond solar with renewable sources, low-emissivity windows that reduce heating and cooling costs, green hydrogen power, and improved battery and passive energy-harvesting technology for local power storage.</li>
    <li><strong>Water:</strong> Capture and use rainwater; detect leaks with digital twins; treat and reuse wastewater on-site; use green and blue roofs to reduce or manage runoff.</li>
  </ul>
</div>
<div>
  <h2 id="dive-beneath-the-buzzwords-to-find-profitable-steps-forward-for-manufacturers-from-sustainability-to-security-to-supply-chain">Dive beneath the buzzwords to find profitable steps forward for manufacturers, from sustainability to security to supply chain.</h2>
  <p>Factory</p>
  <ul>
    <li>“<a href="/blogs/the-sustainable-factory-of-the-future">The Sustainable Factory of the Future</a>”</li>
    <li><em><a href="/resources/profitable-purpose-the-future-of-business-sustainability">Profitable Purpose: The Future of Business Sustainability</a></em> – SAP Insights Research</li>
    <li>“<a href="/resources/production-logistics-and-the-new-ot">Production Logistics and the New OT</a>”</li>
    <li>“<a href="/resources/how-industry-4-0-factories-can-still-embrace-the-past">Retrofitting: How Industry 4.0 Factories Can Still Embrace the Past</a>”</li>
    <li>“<a href="/blogs/twelve-security-issues-for-evolving-factories">12 Security Issues to Address as Your Factories Evolve</a>”</li>
  </ul>
  <p>The workforce</p>
  <ul>
    <li>“<a href="/resources/advanced-manufacturing-skills-workers-will-need">Advanced Manufacturing Skills Workers Will Need</a>”</li>
    <li>“<a href="/resources/hunting-for-advanced-manufacturing-talent-four-moves">Four Steps for Hunting for Advanced Manufacturing Talent</a>”</li>
  </ul>
  <p>The supply chain and business networks</p>
  <ul>
    <li>“<a href="/resources/contract-manufacturing-supply-chains-blind-spot">Contract Manufacturing: Supply Chains’ Blind Spot</a>”</li>
    <li>“<a href="/resources/supply-chain-innovation-whats-next">Supply Chain Innovation: What’s Next?</a>”</li>
    <li>“<a href="/blogs/landscape-view-into-value-chain-relationships">A Landscape View into Value Chain Relationships</a>”</li>
  </ul>
  <p>The full manufacturing lifecycle</p>
  <ul>
    <li>“<a href="/resources/circular-path-to-sustainability-for-manufacturers">A Circular Path to Sustainability for Manufacturers</a>”</li>
    <li><em><a href="/research/capacity-capture-a-new-approach-to-discovering-business-value">Capacity Capture: A New Approach to Discovering Business Value</a></em></li>
    <li>– SAP Insights Research</li>
  </ul>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>Style</div>
      <div>Additional Reading</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
<div>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1baba0487f6216dd702d52864638cddf23866002b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1baba0487f6216dd702d52864638cddf23866002b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1baba0487f6216dd702d52864638cddf23866002b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Person holding a tablet with performance check screen software, with an automated wireless robot arm in the background" src="./media_1baba0487f6216dd702d52864638cddf23866002b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1803" height="1120">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="the-smarter-factory">The smart(er) factory</h2>
  <p>Now let’s turn to the <strong>rapid advance of industrial smarts</strong>, which is happening in both the IT arena and in shop floor operating technology (OT).</p>
  <p>Tomorrow’s factory will make those of yesterday, sit in the corner with a dunce cap.</p>
  <p>A raft of technologies are already converging, including both traditional IT elements (cloud computing, edge computing, artificial intelligence, augmented reality, 5G wireless) and new OT devices and capabilities (advanced robots, cobots, autonomous transport, additive manufacturing machines, computer vision). This convergence is what many describe as “<a href="https://www.sap.cn/products/scm/industry-4-0/industry-4-0-strategy.html">industry 4.0</a>” – technologies that make possible “<a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/what-is-a-smart-factory.html">smart factories</a>” with new levels of process automation, greater efficiency and utilization, right-time right-place inventory, and increased safety.</p>
  <p>This much, you already know. And some of the near-term possibilities are easy to envision. Already in 2024, a humanoid-style robot built by Figure.ai learned, reportedly in 10 hours of training time, how to make coffee <a href="https://twitter.com/adcock_brett/status/1743987597301399852">by watching humans do it</a>, then trying, failing, and improving. The distance between that extremely expensive prototype Keurig-butler and a robotic system that learns complex assembly line tasks through computer vision isn’t far.</p>
  <p>But you also know that other, currently unforeseen smart-factory advances will lurk further over the horizon.</p>
  <p>So how to be prepared to assimilate new technology constantly, rather than seeing each wave render current machines or whole factories obsolete? That’s one motivator behind the idea of software-defined factories, where more flexible, programmable shop floor equipment can add features, change configurations, and connect to new systems with software updates rather than hardware swaps.</p>
  <p>However, as “<a href="/resources/production-logistics-and-the-new-ot">Production Logistics and the New OT</a>” find, staying on top of changes in operational advances relies on process and personnel as much as on technology: <strong>The time for meaningful IT/OT collaboration is truly overdue</strong>.</p>
  <p>When these historically siloed teams cooperate effectively, their companies can get better end-to-end visibility of manufacturing processes, machine health, efficient staffing and inventory movement, and much more while building a flexible technical architecture that more readily absorbs change and integrates whatever’s next.</p>
  <p>Companies including Pfizer, Chobani, and Kohl's show ways to cross this long-standing divide:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Involve both functions earlier</strong> in each other’s projects.</li>
    <li><strong>Provide training and exposure</strong> for OT people in IT processes, and vice versa.</li>
    <li><strong>Set up CIOs</strong>, most often from an IT background, as leaders and learners-in-chief – actively diving into OT technology.</li>
    <li><strong>Create leadership development programs</strong> that bring IT and OT people together.</li>
    <li><strong>Address the divide head-on with humor and empathy.</strong> Try an exercise in which each side role plays the other.</li>
    <li>Consider <strong>using cybersecurity as a natural starting point</strong> for tighter IT/OT collaboration (see the next point).</li>
  </ul>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1932cc003e34bc28ee14e6c871a54923a072a552d.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1932cc003e34bc28ee14e6c871a54923a072a552d.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1932cc003e34bc28ee14e6c871a54923a072a552d.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="In a data center full of monitors, a businessman stands before a big screen with an interactive world map on it." src="./media_1932cc003e34bc28ee14e6c871a54923a072a552d.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="2160">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="the-secure-factory">The secure factory</h2>
  <p>About <strong>that security thing, in this highly connected factory...</strong></p>
  <p>A shop full of networked, intelligent machines needs to rethink its approach to security. Ransomware attacks knocking over manufacturing operations in the past few years have made this abundantly clear. The so-called attack surface is expanding as more OT comes online and data drives more automated processes.</p>
  <p>In “<a href="/blogs/twelve-security-issues-for-evolving-factories">12 Security Issues to Address as Your Factories Evolve</a>,” our experts list key steps, including:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Increase visibility.</strong> “Manufacturers will need to clarify the data flows between the IT and OT networks, as well as the assets that bridge this gap – for example, addressing the Internet of Things (IoT), edge computing, and building automation systems.”</li>
    <li><strong>Protect power supplies and building automation systems.</strong> IT/OT security keeps adding more potential targets to defend. Local generation and storage create new challenges for safety, security, and reliability.</li>
    <li><strong>Consider mobile vulnerabilities.</strong> The fast-changing world of autonomous shop floor tools that use new communication protocols that aren't yet well tested for security.</li>
    <li><strong>Raise your threat awareness game.</strong> “Another strong pillar of defense is maintaining knowledge of the common tactics, techniques, and procedures enacted by adversaries and forming an accurate view of your organization’s posture relative to them,” says former chief information security officer Dawn Cappelli.</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="converting-the-old-factory-into-a-new-factory">Converting the old factory into a new factory</h2>
  <p>Last but not least: <strong>retrofitting to bring older factories into the game</strong>.</p>
  <p>Elon Musk could scare up €5 billion to build Tesla’s “Gigafactory Berlin” from scratch, chock-full of automation and AI. Maybe your company doesn’t have that kind of money sitting around.</p>
  <p>Does that mean you stay on the sidelines? Do you need billions for a brand-new shop to even get into this smart-factory game? Do old factories <em>really</em> have to sit in the corner wearing a dunce cap?</p>
  <p>Happily, they don’t. “<a href="/resources/how-industry-4-0-factories-can-still-embrace-the-past">How Industry 4.0 Factories Can Still Embrace the Past</a><u>”</u> explains why and how modernization strategies can connect older machines and buildings to modern data-driven manufacturing operations.</p>
  <p>True, it’s not as simple as slapping sensors on everything; collecting terabytes of environmental and performance data doesn’t guarantee you’ll find the right signals needed for predictive maintenance or more efficient materials movement. However, careful analysis of likely areas of improvement, the data types needed, and cost-benefit tradeoffs can lead to targeted investment and big payoff.</p>
  <p>For example:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Shift-by-shift, smart sensor data can provide granular insights to increase throughput.</li>
    <li>Supply chain sensor data can improve the traceability of raw material flow, indicating if a manufacturer is spending unnecessary time sourcing and procuring raw materials.</li>
    <li>Correlating real-time environmental and machine performance data may indeed reveal risks for machine and assembly line downtime.</li>
    <li>Networking and geolocation technologies can help track the movement of materials and goods, spotting inefficiencies, low inventory levels, or misplaced palettes.</li>
    <li>Combining new data sources over time can help build an increasingly valuable digital twin of an older facility and its workflows.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>The experience of companies like Spirit AeroSystems and Gary Works provides modernization guidance tips:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Ongoing employee training and assessment is vital.</li>
    <li>IT and OT teams need clear, shared goals (notice a theme here?).</li>
    <li>Top executives have to lead the change management charge.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_182a158f9d99affeb797faa6a70c25ffd02004499.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_182a158f9d99affeb797faa6a70c25ffd02004499.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_182a158f9d99affeb797faa6a70c25ffd02004499.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Four workers in hard hats talking by machinery in a modern factory" src="./media_182a158f9d99affeb797faa6a70c25ffd02004499.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1493" height="1120">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="the-future-manufacturing-workforce">The future manufacturing workforce</h2>
  <p>New factories require new skills. In “<a href="/resources/advanced-manufacturing-skills-workers-will-need">Advanced Manufacturing Skills Workers Will Need,”</a> experts foresee how common roles will change. For instance:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Production planners</strong> will use predictive analytics to anticipate machine downtime or late-arriving materials; work out solutions, such as predictive machine maintenance or purchasing more materials in advance; and look for continuous improvement ideas to reduce waste.</li>
    <li><strong>Line leaders</strong> will spend less time creating reports and more time coaching and problem solving with their team members.</li>
    <li><strong>Machine operators</strong> will probably have more general training, oversee more machines at once, and work with AI tools for problem solving and light maintenance. They may rely on voice and gestural commands to operate the equipment.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>These changes put a premium on flexibility, continuous learning, and problem-solving skills for all manufacturing employees.</p>
  <p>Finding or creating the workforce for these challenges will involve a mix of strategies, as noted in “<a href="/resources/hunting-for-advanced-manufacturing-talent-four-moves">Four Steps for Hunting for Advanced Manufacturing Talent,”</a> including:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Rewriting job descriptions.</strong> You may find help with this from industry associations or other groups. Research Institute AIM Photonics worked with MIT to develop advanced job descriptions specific to the photonics industry.</li>
    <li><strong>Reskilling current employees.</strong> Bosch plans to spend €1 billion over five years to reskill employees in advanced tech areas ranging from AI to electric vehicle engineering, <a href="https://www.businessinsider.com/reskilling-employees-is-a-priority-for-companies-like-bosch-2022-3"><em>Business Insider</em> reports</a>.</li>
    <li><strong>Partnering with local educational institutions to expand the talent pool.</strong> In southern China, Guizhou Equipment Manufacturing Vocational College has created new courses covering digital process design, advanced machine tools, and debugging industrial robots. It provides specific retraining for workers in all career stages, including laid off and unemployed persons, as detailed in <a href="https://www.autodesk.com/design-make/articles/upskilling-employees">an Autodesk article</a>.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>Refurbishing your workforce and investing in local education is also part of how the future factory provides regenerative benefits to its local community.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="how-manufacturing-adapts-to-disruption">How Manufacturing Adapts to Disruption</h3>
        <p>Learn how manufacturers are becoming more flexible without breaking the bank.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="/resources/hunting-for-advanced-manufacturing-talent-four-moves">Read the guide</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="beyond-the-factory--the-future-supply-chain">Beyond the factory – the future supply chain</h2>
  <p>Inevitably, the future factory will connect more directly to more partners – that's the only way to work toward real-time, decision-making, based on demand.</p>
  <p>Your <strong>contract manufacturers (CMs)</strong> may be your closest partners. Yet typically this is an area of limited (i.e., almost zero) visibility in manufacturers’ supply chains. “<a href="https://www.sap.com/insights/viewpoints/contract-manufacturing-supply-chains-blind-spot.html">Contract Manufacturing: Supply Chains’ Blind Spot</a><u>”</u> explains why: it's not fundamentally a tech issue, it's a problem of trust, trust, trust!</p>
  <p>Germany's LkSG law (also known as the Supply Chain Due Diligence Act) demands more visibility into a manufacturer’s supply chain – both EU- and worldwide – to help weed out labor abuse and similar problems. But whether you're solving for compliance or something else, every disruption or change can present a chance to improve supply chain performance too. Example: during the pandemic, Haier Group, based in China, mobilized its supply chain, including CMs, to share information through a homegrown cloud application. Its CM partners reported results, including a reduction in cycle time, reduced procurement costs, and increased customer orders.</p>
  <p>How to improve visibility and collaboration with CMs:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Communicate to partners that regulatory requirements are an opportunity</strong> to improve processes and profits for both OEMs and CMs.</li>
    <li><strong>You go first</strong> in sharing systems and data with your contract manufacturing partners. Show trust to earn trust and provide value to gain value.</li>
    <li><strong>Rework contracts</strong> to formally spell out how the parties will work together in a mutually beneficial way, as opposed to just defining a transactional model. For example, a <em>Harvard Business Review</em> article details a method of contracting that uses a “<a href="https://hbr.org/2022/11/3-ways-to-build-trust-with-your-suppliers">vested sourcing model</a>.”</li>
  </ul>
  <p>With trust improving, improved <strong>supply chain technology</strong> should surely yield better performance – right? But somehow, often, it doesn’t.</p>
  <p>In “<a href="https://www.sap.com/insights/viewpoints/supply-chain-innovation-whats-next.html">Supply Chain Innovation: What’s Next?</a><u>,”</u> three experts explore why roughly eight out of 10 supply chain tech projects fail, and how to flip that ratio.</p>
  <p>Their recommendations include:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Innovation benefits from <strong>a digital officer</strong> who can “paint a picture of the possible” to secure investment in pilot projects.</li>
    <li>However, they then have to let go of successful pilots and <strong>hand ownership over to the business.</strong></li>
    <li>Innovators and project leads should <strong>“show return over and over.”</strong></li>
    <li><strong>Get your innovation funding model right.</strong> Pilots are often funded from centralized technology budgets, but then quickly the model should shift to the infrastructure budget plus co-funding from business lines and factories.</li>
    <li><strong>Shared goals</strong> help get the plants to invest.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_12c9be569b9e544b90067c1078fcc44a42a41a702.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_12c9be569b9e544b90067c1078fcc44a42a41a702.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_12c9be569b9e544b90067c1078fcc44a42a41a702.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Businesspeople having a roundtable discussion" src="./media_12c9be569b9e544b90067c1078fcc44a42a41a702.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="beyond-the-factory--understand-the-value-you-create">Beyond the factory – understand the value you create</h2>
  <p>As we said at the outset – there’s a lot of detail to consider and work through. Here’s a parting idea to help clear the mind and prioritize decisions: <strong>start by reexamining how your company creates value</strong>.</p>
  <p>A factory is one link in a chain, and (ostensibly) the whole chain is designed to deliver something of great value to a customer who really needs it. Consultant Simon Wardley argues that a better understanding of how value is created in, and by, the product should yield smarter business decisions, resulting in better factory design and use.</p>
  <p>Seems obvious? Wardley contends most companies fail at this fundamental level: “My experience has been that organizations are not very strong at understanding users, they’re much poorer at understanding users’ needs, and they can be quite poor at understanding the chain of components required to meet those needs.”</p>
  <p>· He says lack of visibility beyond the next step in the value chain is one culprit.</p>
  <p>· Failure to map your competitive space is another – accounting for change over time, such as a gradual commodification of components.</p>
  <p>Test your future-factory assumptions with Wardley's insights in “<a href="https://www.sap.com/insights/viewpoints/landscape-view-into-value-chain-relationships.html">A Landscape View into Value Chain Relationships</a>.” You’ll gain a fresh outlook on familiar terrain.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>1 Analog front ends are sensors that can capture and digitize multiple types of analog signal. 4D printing creates products that change in response to time or conditions, for example, camouflage clothes that adjust hue or pattern to match their surroundings.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/trends-predictions</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Goes the Distance with EV Fleet Digitalization]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/sap-goes-the-distance-ev-fleet-digitalization</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/sap-goes-the-distance-ev-fleet-digitalization</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Longtime partners SAP and Mercedes-Benz are transforming the sustainable EV experience with digitalized corporate fleet management.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1300ce8d341537d322ce2ddfe25ec1e05ce2fbf64.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1300ce8d341537d322ce2ddfe25ec1e05ce2fbf64.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1300ce8d341537d322ce2ddfe25ec1e05ce2fbf64.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Goes the Distance with EV Fleet Digitalization" src="./media_1300ce8d341537d322ce2ddfe25ec1e05ce2fbf64.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-goes-the-distance-with-ev-fleet-digitalization">SAP Goes the Distance with EV Fleet Digitalization</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Electric vehicles (<a href="/topics/electric-vehicles">EVs</a>) are transforming the mobility experience in corporate fleet management. A great example is the partnership between <a href="https://www.mercedes-benz.com/en/">Mercedes-Benz</a> and SAP where the companies are both customers and vendors to each other. Mercedes-Benz is using SAP solutions to digitalize its omnichannel buying experience, and SAP is the first customer using its own technology to manage the company’s vehicle fleet in Germany.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As longtime partners, SAP and Mercedes-Benz have a history of shared knowledge for mutual competitive advantage. The fleet management program is grounded in the companies’ similar business philosophies and product road maps.</p>
  <p>Mercedes-Benz has committed to move the company’s B2B business to 100% digital and plans to sell 25% of all new cars online by 2025. The company selected <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm/commerce-cloud.html">SAP Commerce Cloud</a> to help support this mission. It will create a future-proof composable commerce portfolio designed to reliably power the company’s digital strategy, including a standardized offering across different markets. It will also simplify processes and reduce time-to-market.</p>
  <h2 id="benefits-of-digitalized-fleet-management">Benefits of Digitalized Fleet Management</h2>
  <p>From the SAP employee’s perspective, ordering a company EV couldn’t be simpler. Instead of time-consuming manual research and back and forth communication with the car dealer, employees can use <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/spend-management/solutions.html">the guided buying capability in SAP Ariba solutions</a> to order the EV they want directly from the Mercedes-Benz online catalog. They can choose the features they want, such as car make and model, color, and equipment packages, within SAP’s pre-set guidelines.</p>
  <p>“The car configurator automates the EV selection process end-to-end, eliminating manual steps and saving time while providing the employee with a highly personalized experience,” said Steffen Krautwasser, head of SAP’s global car fleet. “Automating the approval process assures data consistency and eliminates the need for manual quality checks.”</p>
  <p>There’s a tremendous convenience factor in captured EV data as well. In one pilot program for select EVs in SAP’s fleet, the digital twin will automatically track mileage. Drivers will no longer need to manually enter mileage every time they recharge, and SAP can use this data to better manage the fleet.</p>
  <h2 id="connected-data-drives-sustainable-business">Connected Data Drives Sustainable Business</h2>
  <p>Once ordered, EVs are tracked as assets in SAP’s financial system. After delivery, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/digital-vehicle-suite.html">SAP Digital Vehicle Suite</a> creates a digital twin that can capture relevant, secure data across the EV’s lifetime. SAP’s fleet management team can track CO2 emissions based on green energy usage, mileage, and the number of vehicles on the road. Krautwasser envisioned reporting this data to support the company’s global sustainability commitments.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-digital-vehicle-suite-delivers-a-holistic-approach-to-vehicle-sales-and-data-management">SAP Digital Vehicle Suite delivers a holistic approach to vehicle, sales, and data management</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/digital-vehicle-suite.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“Performance data from the EV digital twin can help corporate fleet managers guide employees in choosing the best vehicle for their driving needs,” said Krautwasser. “Over time, drivers can better understand travel ranges between charges.”</p>
  <p>Data is expected to help address so-called range anxiety, alerting EV drivers when their vehicle needs a charge and, most important, where to recharge. Mercedes-Benz is investing in charging infrastructure to create an ecosystem that would be integrated with public and private charge point providers in the U.S., China, and Europe.</p>
  <p>The partnership also reflects a shared commitment to sustainability. Mercedes-Benz has committed to become carbon neutral by 2038, and transition to 100% electric vehicles by 2030 wherever possible. SAP is transitioning the company’s vehicle fleet for employees in Germany to all EVs by 2025 as part of its corporate commitment to be carbon neutral by 2030.</p>
  <h2 id="omnichannel-is-fastest-path-to-customer-love">Omnichannel Is Fastest Path to Customer Love</h2>
  <p>The digital experience is extremely important for customers who expect convenience and quality. Organizations in many industries have shifted to an omnichannel strategy that offers people their preferred experience, whether online or in-person, building brand loyalty and repeat business.</p>
  <p>“We want to provide a seamless journey for employees as they research, select, purchase, and enjoy their vehicle,” said Krautwasser. “The most exciting part of our EV fleet management strategy is how we can use our knowledge to enhance the employee experience. Through data and digital services, we can get closer to our employees and act quickly based on their feedback, making improvements and introducing new offerings that keep us on top of trends and support SAP’s sustainability commitment.”</p>
  <p>EVs represent a profound business model shift for the entire automotive supply chain as automakers sell direct to customers, provide digital services from vehicle data, and explore new revenue opportunities. It’s clear that Mercedes-Benz and SAP are going the distance for a sustainable and satisfying driving experience.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Susan Galer is a communications director at SAP. Follow her @smgaler.<br>Top photo courtesy of SAP employee Jude Calvin Parong.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-sap-news-delivered-to-your-inbox-once-a-week">Get the latest SAP news delivered to your inbox once a week</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/nl/sap-news-center-newsletter/index.html">Sign up</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/automotive</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-twin</category>
            <category>news-tag/e-mobility</category>
            <category>news-tag/electric-vehicles</category>
            <category>news-tag/mercedes</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>product/sap-commerce-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[CEV Technologies and SAP Fuel E-Mobility Revolution in Croatia’s Retail Sector]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/cev-technologies-e-mobility-croatia-retail-sector</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/cev-technologies-e-mobility-croatia-retail-sector</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[To realize the potential of convenient charging within the customer experience, CEV Technologies implemented SAP E-Mobility in Croatia.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/automotive</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/electric-vehicles</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
            <category>product/sap-e-mobility</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP's Journey to Net Zero 2030]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/sap-journey-to-net-zero-2030</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/sap-journey-to-net-zero-2030</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Since 2009, SAP has been on a net-zero journey to create positive economic, environmental, and social impact within planetary boundaries.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11ecba87d269260aeacea6663afbf43090e156723.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11ecba87d269260aeacea6663afbf43090e156723.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_11ecba87d269260aeacea6663afbf43090e156723.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP’s Journey to Net Zero 2030" src="./media_11ecba87d269260aeacea6663afbf43090e156723.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="saps-journey-to-net-zero-2030">SAP’s Journey to Net Zero 2030</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>The world faces increasing climate and social crises. Comprehensive <a href="https://www.ipcc.ch/report/sixth-assessment-report-cycle/">assessments</a> have given us a deeper understanding of the science and the role of industry. As a global technology company supporting the vast majority of the world’s business, SAP needs to lead from the front with our ambitions and actions. That is why SAP has committed to achieve net-zero emissions across our value chain by 2030.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Since 2009, <a href="/2021/10/integrating-climate-action-end-to-end">SAP has been on a sustainability journey</a> with the objective to create positive economic, environmental, and social impact within planetary boundaries. Along the way, we have learned a great deal about measuring economic, social, and environmental performance and integrating sustainability into our business strategy. Central to this effort has been a continuous effort to decarbonize our business. Setting ambitious targets and leveraging digital solutions have proven crucial.</p>
  <p>Raising our ambition to achieve net-zero emissions is a key element of our approach to sustainability, which looks across the interconnected areas of holistic steering and reporting, climate action, the circular economy, and social responsibility.</p>
  <h2 id="what-does-net-zero-mean">What Does Net Zero Mean?</h2>
  <p>Net zero is a state where the greenhouse gases going into the atmosphere are balanced by removal out of the atmosphere. Corporate net-zero pledges have gained significant traction as <a href="https://zerotracker.net/">half of the world’s largest companies</a>, representing an annual aggregate revenue of US$27 trillion, are committed to net zero.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="together-we-can-enable-a-future-with-zero-emissions-zero-waste-and-zero-inequality">Together, we can enable a future with zero emissions, zero waste, and zero inequality</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/sustainability.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>There are <a href="https://netzeroclimate.org/what-is-net-zero-2/#:~:text=Net%20zero%20refers%20to%20a,the%20need%20for%20net%20zero.">a number of definitions of net zero</a> and how companies can achieve it. SAP follows the Science Based Targets initiative’s (SBTi) <a href="https://sciencebasedtargets.org/news/sbti-launches-world-first-net-zero-corporate-standard">Net-Zero Standard</a>, which provides a credible and independent assessment of corporate net-zero target setting in line with climate science. The continually improving standard enables companies to align their climate actions with limiting global warming to 1.5°C. SAP became a member of SBTi in 2017 and was the first German company with a science-based carbon reduction target for 2050. In 2019, SAP raised its commitment and adopted a 1.5°C science-based emissions reduction target. We announced our net zero by 2030 ambition in early 2022, bringing this commitment forward by 20 years.</p>
  <p>Achieving net-zero emissions across our entire value chain means that all our emissions across all emission sources need to be either eliminated or, up to certain limits, compensated for. These emission areas, known as scopes, include those from our own operations, those generated by the energy we purchase to run operations, and finally, the largest area, external emissions such as those incurred by employee travel, items procured, and customer data center use.</p>
  <h2 id="targeting-our-entire-value-chain">Targeting Our Entire Value Chain</h2>
  <p>SAP’s net-zero plan is implemented through a comprehensive and integrated approach that involves all functions in the company, customers, suppliers, partners, and other stakeholders. We have established a cross-company program team involving experts from different lines of business to plan and implement our net-zero transformation. Reducing emissions from the use of SAP software will be the primary area for reductions, followed by purchased goods and services. The SAP net zero by 2030 approach includes:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Accelerating the transformation of on-premise customers to the cloud through our market-leading <a href="/2023/07/rise-grow-with-sap-net-zero-journey">RISE with SAP and GROW with SAP offerings</a></li>
    <li>Enhancing direct investments in renewable energy sources and operating our internal and external data centers on 100% renewable electricity</li>
    <li>Reducing emissions by improving the energy efficiency of best-in-class data centers – our own, our co-locations, and hyperscalers – with sustainable programming and a cloud carbon footprint calculator for all SAP cloud solutions</li>
    <li>Strengthening <a href="/2023/07/sap-key-suppliers-reduce-carbon-emissions">engagement with key suppliers</a> to commit to net zero and deliver carbon-neutral products and services</li>
    <li><a href="/2021/11/sap-accelerates-move-to-emission-free-car-fleet">Electrifying the vehicle fleet</a>, promoting green mobility, and enabling hybrid work situations</li>
    <li>Compensating for emissions by investing in <a href="/2023/09/sap-funded-trees-help-reforestation-programs">high-quality, nature-based solutions</a>, such as reforestation, renewable energy, and community development, that have verified environmental and social benefits</li>
    <li>Enabling our customers and partners by adding sustainability features and functions into our core offerings, such as SAP S/4HANA, SAP Ariba solutions, and SAP SuccessFactors solutions, and by giving them tools, guidance, and best practices to measure, manage, and reduce their emissions through our <a href="https://www.sap.com/sustainability.html">portfolio of dedicated sustainability solutions</a> including SAP Sustainability Footprint Management, SAP Sustainability Data Exchange, SAP Sustainability Control Tower, and SAP Responsible Design and Production</li>
    <li>Accurately measuring and reporting emissions using the Greenhouse Gas Protocol and the Science Based Targets initiative and showing progress and performance through platforms such as CDP, EcoVadis, and the Dow Jones Sustainability Index</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="capturing-the-opportunities-of-net-zero">Capturing the Opportunities of Net Zero</h2>
  <p>We have many achievements to build on, but we also are charting new territory. 2030 is not far away. The challenges increase the farther we move upstream and downstream into our value chain. Despite the complexities, there are enormous opportunities ahead as we establish further success with our net-zero efforts.</p>
  <p>From a business perspective, focusing on net zero means reducing risk, improving SAP’s operational efficiency, and delivering cost savings by reducing our energy consumption and waste and optimizing our processes and resources. Net-zero action helps increase our market competitiveness by creating new products and services that meet the growing expectations of customers, partners, and regulators for low-carbon and sustainable solutions. We’ll also be better at attracting and retaining top talent who are increasingly discerning about their employer’s sustainability actions. We’ll offer a compelling case to investors who used focused criteria to inform their holdings. Finally, we’ll continue to enhance <a href="/2024/01/what-industry-analysts-say-about-sap-sustainability">our reputation with industry media and analysts as a leader and innovator in sustainability</a>. And most importantly, we’ll reduce our overall carbon emissions to provide much-needed relief for the over-accumulation of greenhouse gases in the atmosphere.</p>
  <p>With an increased sense of urgency, we recognize the responsibility, as well as the opportunity, to step up and drive a faster transformation toward a sustainable future. Not only must we accelerate our own net-zero transformation, but we must help other businesses and industries reinvent themselves as well. Only a fundamental transformation of our global economy will allow us to limit global warming to 1.5°C. It’s vital that we build sustainability into the very nature of how we do business.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Daniel Schmid is chief sustainability officer at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/climate-action</category>
            <category>news-tag/net-zero</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fusing Sustainability and AI for Inclusive Global Progress]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/fusing-sustainability-and-ai-for-global-progress</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/fusing-sustainability-and-ai-for-global-progress</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP's strides in sustainability and AI spotlight the transformative potential of technology in addressing pressing global challenges.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f29678d2dd5a96294e959a47b0429eb656706b10.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f29678d2dd5a96294e959a47b0429eb656706b10.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1f29678d2dd5a96294e959a47b0429eb656706b10.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Fusing Sustainability and AI for Inclusive Global Progress" src="./media_1f29678d2dd5a96294e959a47b0429eb656706b10.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="fusing-sustainability-and-ai-for-inclusive-global-progress">Fusing Sustainability and AI for Inclusive Global Progress</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>The echoes of the 28<sup>th</sup> UN Climate Change Conference’s (<a href="/topics/cop28">COP28</a>) groundbreaking commitments lingered as the annual <a href="/topics/sap-at-davos">World Economic Forum (WEF) in Davos</a> became the epicenter of global dialogues this month. Against this backdrop, SAP’s innovative strides in sustainability and artificial intelligence (AI) spotlighted the transformative potential of technology in addressing pressing global challenges.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP’s presence at both events exemplifies the seamless connection between environmental commitment and technological innovation. The nearly 100 initiatives SAP was involved in at COP28 last month demonstrated the company’s unwavering focus on fostering collaboration across governance, the private sector, and civil society, which, coupled with a commitment to transparency, also resonated with Davos’ core values.</p>
  <p>For example, the “From Farm to Consumer” showcase emphasizing intelligent agriculture solutions at COP28 and the WEF Collaboration Village at Davos both showed the power of technology, such as how AI can optimize all industry practices and foster collaboration across the supply chain. This embodies SAP’s multifaceted approach to innovation.</p>
  <p>The company’s strategies involve valuing carbon assets, supporting collaborative supply chains, and actively backing local climate initiatives. <a href="/2024/01/what-industry-analysts-say-about-sap-sustainability">Recent studies</a> highlight how SAP solutions can seamlessly integrate sustainability into core business strategies, giving companies a competitive edge. By treating emissions tracking with the same rigor as financial transactions, <a href="https://www.sap.com/sustainability.html">SAP solutions can enable data-driven decision-making for positive environmental impact</a>.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="record-report-and-act-with-sap-sustainability-solutions">Record, report, and act with SAP Sustainability solutions</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/sustainability.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="navigating-the-ai-landscape-responsibly">Navigating the AI Landscape Responsibly</h2>
  <p>As the WEF in Davos unfolded, the pervasive enthusiasm for AI became evident along the promenade. A dedicated pavilion called “AI House” served as a testament to the technology’s significance in shaping the future. SAP’s commitment to innovation aligns with the forum’s pulse, offering a glimpse into how AI can transform industries and societies.</p>
  <p>AI’s impact on the global workforce was a central concern at Davos. The International Monetary Fund (IMF) warns that the AI revolution could affect almost 40% of jobs worldwide, including highly skilled ones. In industrialized countries, this number could surge to 60%. The integration of AI in various industries can exacerbate inequalities, especially in terms of job displacement. However, SAP believes the time is right to explore the implications and the steps required for this future. One of the first mind shifts may be seeing AI as a coworker rather than a software tool.</p>
  <p>SAP’s approach seeks to mitigate potential inequalities. The company didn’t merely showcase innovation at Davos; it actively engaged in discussions to address the complexities surrounding AI and find solutions for a responsible approach.</p>
  <h2 id="striking-the-balance-a-global-perspective">Striking the Balance: A Global Perspective</h2>
  <p>SAP recognizes the broader, global context of responsible AI, particularly with varying regulatory standards in the U.S. and China. The discussions at Davos provided a platform for SAP to advocate for a harmonized approach to AI regulation, which is especially relevant for the EU. The company’s commitment to finding the right balance resonated in discussions about regulatory standards, emphasizing the need for global cooperation to navigate the evolving landscape of AI. This global perspective gains profound meaning when viewed through the lens of COP28.</p>
  <p>COP28 concluded with a landmark decision by nearly 200 countries to transition away from fossil fuels in energy systems. The renegotiated text emphasized a just, orderly, and equitable shift, aiming to achieve net-zero emissions by 2050. This signifies a global move, committing nations to tripling renewable energy use by 2030 and doubling energy efficiency. The resolution proposes the first-ever phase-out of fossil fuels, accelerating coal’s exit, boosting renewable energy, and emphasizing energy efficiency. However, the resolution falls short of a complete commitment due to opposition from economically reliant countries like Saudi Arabia. And despite progress, vulnerable island nations stress the need for inclusive decision-making, as they face immediate threats from climate change and depend on global solidarity for survival.</p>
  <h2 id="hand-in-hand-ai-and-climate-action">Hand-in-Hand: AI and Climate Action</h2>
  <p>It’s crucial to recognize AI’s broader role in climate action. Scaling proven applications and technology, AI has the potential to unlock insights that could help mitigate 5% to 10% of global greenhouse gas emissions by 2030 and significantly bolster climate-related adaptation and resilience initiatives. Approximately 87% of executives view AI as having the potential to address climate issues, making it a key player in the fight against climate change.</p>
  <p>AI contributes to climate protection not only by helping to reduce emissions but also by helping to navigate unavoidable climate change impacts and provide essential capabilities that enable climate action. SAP, alongside its dedication to AI ethics, wants to ensure that <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence.html">its AI solutions</a> drive sustainability strategies and contribute to a more resilient and adaptive world.</p>
  <p>SAP believes that working together and being open and transparent are key to solving bigger challenges. It’s not just about cool tech; it’s about creating real connections. As AI evolves, SAP’s dedication to a responsible and inclusive future shows the power of teamwork in making a difference.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-us-on-linkedin-to-stay-up-to-date">Connect with us on LinkedIn to stay up-to-date</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news">Follow SAP News</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>non-sap-event/cop28</category>
            <category>non-sap-event/wef-davos</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Palm Oil and SAP Software Give Ugandan Farmers New Hope]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/kopgt-sap-ugandan-oil-palm-farmers</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/kopgt-sap-ugandan-oil-palm-farmers</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The Kalangala Oil Palm Growers Trust (KOPGT) works with SAP software to support Ugandan oil palm farmers sustainably. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/agribusiness</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-rural-sourcing-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[What Industry Analysts Say About SAP Sustainability]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/what-industry-analysts-say-about-sap-sustainability</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/what-industry-analysts-say-about-sap-sustainability</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Industry analysts assess the sustainability performance of companies across industries. Learn about what they had to say about SAP.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e36ed2496934d2a62eef72bc90f762db5c48d221.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e36ed2496934d2a62eef72bc90f762db5c48d221.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1e36ed2496934d2a62eef72bc90f762db5c48d221.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="What Industry Analysts Say About SAP Sustainability" src="./media_1e36ed2496934d2a62eef72bc90f762db5c48d221.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="what-industry-analysts-say-about-sap-sustainability">What Industry Analysts Say About SAP Sustainability</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>For nearly 15 years, SAP has committed to being a <a href="/topics/sustainability">sustainability</a> leader both in our operations and through our sustainability product offerings for customers. Industry analysts review and assess the sustainability performance of companies across industries. SAP has recently been assessed by some of the most important analyst firms for both our own sustainability performance and the sustainability solutions we offer customers.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Gartner, an independent analyst firm, recently published a report titled “<a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/dg/sap-rated-positively-in-sustainability/index.html">Sustainability Assessment: SAP</a>.” A report from analyst firm IDC earlier this year, “Sustainability Index for Software Providers: SAP”, noted SAP performed “exceptionally well.” The published <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2023/05/d2950cf3-737e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.rc.html?campaigncode=CRM-Y23-IMM-21123823">IDC report</a> highlights how SAP is leading by example as a sustainable vendor.</p>
  <p>It’s abundantly clear that businesses need to urgently address sustainability challenges. Companies are adopting new technology solutions to help them manage sustainability across many different dimensions, from environmental issues like energy, water, and waste, to social issues like diversity and human rights, to governance and reporting issues.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d31b118dcbe3ac649ef3a08129aad3c3e6a33702.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d31b118dcbe3ac649ef3a08129aad3c3e6a33702.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1d31b118dcbe3ac649ef3a08129aad3c3e6a33702.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_1d31b118dcbe3ac649ef3a08129aad3c3e6a33702.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="986">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>Source: Gartner. Click to enlarge.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Business leaders are looking for the best tools that allow them to quantify, analyze, and act on real-time, accurate, and shareable sustainability data throughout their end-to-end operations. With SAP’s ERP-centric solutions, financial and non-financial data can be brought together for holistic decision-making. Business leaders can not only manage their productivity and operating results but connect that information with sustainability-related data to help make climate protection measurable, diversity and inclusion visible, and ethical responsibility transparent.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="record-report-and-act-with-sap-sustainability-solutions">Record, report, and act with SAP Sustainability solutions</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/sustainability.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP has a unique role to play in supporting our customers’ sustainability efforts. SAP customers produce 87% of the world’s global commerce. That means our products and services can help the vast majority of companies driving the global economy organize their supply chains, transportation, and financial data in a way that can enable an equitable, circular economy and net-zero emissions.</p>
  <p>Sustainability data in ERP is the foundation for holistic, integrated sustainability management. As the leader in enterprise resource management, SAP has more than 50 years of experience helping businesses across 25 industries optimize resources.</p>
  <p>Our comprehensive portfolio is designed to help customers find the solutions they need to run their business processes and enterprise more efficiently, with offerings such as SAP Business Network, business process transformation solutions, SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP), and the SAP Customer Experience portfolio. Our solutions, increasingly powered with AI capabilities, can help customers not only in their own operations, but across their entire value chain – from calculating product-level carbon footprints, to ensuring diversity and inclusion, to protecting human rights. In addition, SAP’s broad ecosystem of partners can support customers with industry- and technology-specific consulting and implementation, advancing SAP’s “sustainable by design” approach.</p>
  <p>SAP leads by example as well, having committed to net-zero emissions across our entire value chain by 2030. We also <a href="/2021/12/sap-leads-sustainability-rankings">have been recognized</a> as the leading software firm in the Dow Jones Sustainability Indices for 15 years and as a leader in environmental transparency and action by CDP, an international organization considered the gold standard of environmental reporting.</p>
  <h2 id="whats-next">What’s Next</h2>
  <p>Sustainability is not an end state, it’s a state of being. In that respect, companies should adopt an approach that constantly evolves and adapts to remain sustainable. SAP is dedicated to advancing sustainable business through our own operations and our comprehensive portfolio of solutions that can help other companies with their end-to-end sustainability management. Across the business network and our wide solution portfolio, SAP supports our customers in tackling their biggest sustainability challenges.</p>
  <p>Try the free <a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/dg/sap-rated-positively-in-sustainability/index.html">SAP Sustainability Navigator</a> tool, and read the full <a href="https://www.gartner.com/reprints/?id=1-2FWN452Z&#x26;ct=231213&#x26;st=sb">complimentary Gartner Sustainability report</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Daniel Schmid is chief sustainability officer at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-sap-news-on-linkedin">Connect with SAP News on LinkedIn</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news">Follow us</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Gartner, Sustainability Assessment: SAP, 11 December 2023, Ed Anderson, Fabio Di Capua<br>GARTNER is a registered trademark and service mark of Gartner, Inc. and/or its affiliates in the U.S. and internationally and is used herein with permission. All rights reserved. This graphic was published by Gartner, Inc. as part of a larger research document and should be evaluated in the context of the entire document. The Gartner document is available upon request from SAP.<br>Gartner does not endorse any vendor, product or service depicted in its research publications and does not advise technology users to select only those vendors with the highest ratings or other designation. Gartner research publications consist of the opinions of Gartner’s research organization and should not be construed as statements of fact. Gartner disclaims all warranties, expressed or implied, with respect to this research, including any warranties of merchantability or fitness for a particular purpose.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Turning Agricultural Waste into Buildings]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/turning-agricultural-waste-into-buildings</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/turning-agricultural-waste-into-buildings</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Find out how a sustainable construction-material entrepreneur brought her idea to life by engaging local communities.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11ff1654bf1679391f4ffabdc421a48dedfe40db0.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11ff1654bf1679391f4ffabdc421a48dedfe40db0.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_11ff1654bf1679391f4ffabdc421a48dedfe40db0.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Workers bent over in a large agricultural field in southern India." src="./media_11ff1654bf1679391f4ffabdc421a48dedfe40db0.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1044">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="turning-agricultural-waste-into-buildings">Turning Agricultural Waste into Buildings</h1>
        <p>A sustainable construction-material entrepreneur brought her idea to life by engaging local communities.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>By Lauren Gibbons Paul</p>
  <p>Sometimes, just having a question is enough. That’s how Shriti Pandey, founder and CEO of Strawcture Eco, started a sustainable construction-materials company – despite having virtually no work experience.</p>
  <p>Back home for a 2016 fellowship in India after graduate school in New York, Pandey saw local farmers burning “stubble,” the waste that results from the unusable portion – often 50% of the total weight – of agricultural crops. Farmers burn that byproduct because they can’t make any money from it. Pandey’s business started with a question: What if we could turn that stubble into a material for sustainable construction?</p>
  <p>She had no experience in construction – or any kind of industry – only a degree in civil engineering. And she was a young woman entering an industry largely made up of older men. Pandey did have one advantage: She knew how to approach people and get their input and support for new ideas. This skill became very important when her small team had to engage with farmers to buy waste products from their crops. Barreling in from the outside and demanding a community do things differently, especially given language and cultural barriers, is a formula for failure, she says. Engaging in a meaningful, two-way interchange is the only way to do this work.</p>
  <p>This approach led to Strawcture Eco’s first product, a panel for building as sturdy as steel or concrete, but more affordable and sustainable – as well as some unexpected adventures, like managing the construction of a 75-bed rural COVID-19 hospital in just 45 days.</p>
  <p>The film <em>She Run the World</em> is part of SAP’s Roads to Regeneration series, produced in partnership with Hot Docs. SAP Insights spoke to Pandey about how community engagement has informed her business and career.</p>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b5d305a32c7b85791487ed0e662700a9f598ff71.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b5d305a32c7b85791487ed0e662700a9f598ff71.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1b5d305a32c7b85791487ed0e662700a9f598ff71.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="One of eight documentaries created by Hot Docs and produced by SAP. Part of the Roads to Regeneration compilation." src="./media_1b5d305a32c7b85791487ed0e662700a9f598ff71.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="319" height="179">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://d.dam.sap.com/m/aawW7zb/hls.m3u8">Roads to Regeneration - She Run The World</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>en-US</div>
      <div>English</div>
      <div><a href="https://d.dam.sap.com/o/s7Mct1x/SAP922411-en%5C%5C_us-English?rc=19">https://d.dam.sap.com/o/s7Mct1x/SAP922411-en\\_us-English?rc=19</a></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="sap-insights-what-was-your-core-idea-behind-strawcture-eco">SAP Insights: What was your core idea behind Strawcture Eco?</h2>
  <p><strong>Shriti Pandey:</strong> There's so much agricultural surplus residue – the byproduct of crop harvesting – especially in an agrarian country like India. While we're talking so much about climate change and resource waste, it seemed to me there were genuine renewable raw materials available that no one was using. We are literally burning waste, cutting trees, and then making materials in the factory that require so much fossil fuel. So the core question was, can this waste be converted into valuable products that reduce our reliance on fossil-based energy? That’s what I was obsessed about.</p>
  <h2 id="q-did-you-encounter-barriers-when-you-were-trying-to-break-into-the-construction-space-especially-as-a-young-woman">Q: Did you encounter barriers when you were trying to break into the construction space, especially as a young woman?</h2>
  <p>Pandey: I started Strawcture in 2018. I was 26. I had one year of experience working in New York, no prior work experience in India at all. So the idea was quite daunting to me. And I had no buddies to start the project with. It was not just about being young, but also because I was a solo founder.</p>
  <p>Until I started Strawcture, I thought there was no difference in the opportunities men and women get. I grew up as one of a set of triplets in a small town in India. I had the privilege of an upbringing where my parents were very capable of providing an education for my sister, brother, and me. They never told us what to do, which people think happens a lot in smaller towns and villages in India. I had complete freedom, which is why I thought I could even do this without questioning.</p>
  <p>It was only when I started my company that I realized that the world is not free of discrimination. I got exposed to a very male-dominated industry. Very early on after starting Strawcture, there was this government conference around green materials. As I stepped into that room, I vividly remember that it only had men in it, mostly in their 40s or older. And they all just looked at me, clearly thinking, “Who is she?” I felt for a second that I was in the wrong room. So I left. I asked somebody outside, “Is this the right room?” They said yes. So I went back in, and I didn’t know where to sit or who to talk to.</p>
  <p>It took me a while to get used to it. Before you can get other people to accept you, you also have to accept that you belong. So for me, that was the first step of the journey. Once I felt more confident, I started networking. Now, once they see me on stage as a speaker, there's a level of credibility, of substance. So people are more willing to approach me.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1071e3d8dcc85b3d1d0aabc48f450d2cb12891b35.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1071e3d8dcc85b3d1d0aabc48f450d2cb12891b35.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1071e3d8dcc85b3d1d0aabc48f450d2cb12891b35.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="In this school auditorium in Delhi, the walls, ceiling and stage flooring are made from recycled agricultural waste. Photo courtesy of Shriti Pandey." src="./media_1071e3d8dcc85b3d1d0aabc48f450d2cb12891b35.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="2160">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="q-its-only-five-years-later-but-these-days-are-you-seeing-more-participation-in-the-construction-industry-by-young-or-older-women">Q: It’s only five years later, but these days, are you seeing more participation in the construction industry by young or older women?</h2>
  <p><strong>Pandey:</strong> Yes, definitely. I see more women in these spaces as different stakeholders now, even a lot of women investors who are in the climate tech space.</p>
  <h2 id="q-what-happened-to-your-business-and-your-research-during-the-pandemic-shutdowns">Q: What happened to your business and your research during the pandemic shutdowns?</h2>
  <p><strong>Pandey:</strong> The lockdown happened in India in March 2020, and I had traveled from Delhi to my village for my mother's birthday. I ended up being there for a year. Our line of business is very tactile, very physical. If you don't meet people, they won’t understand, no one will buy. So everything came to a halt for three months.</p>
  <p>Then someone from the SELCO Foundation NGO approached us to build some COVID-19 hospitals. At that point, they could take the risk and let a new technology be tested in that scenario. So, we grabbed that opportunity. There were a lot of companies building COVID hospitals. We ended up building ours the fastest. We built a 75-bed, full COVID [treatment] hospital with 12 doctors in 45 days. The community immediately showed up needing medical services, which they previously had gone without.</p>
  <p>We built three more hospitals made from waste after that – our materials went to the walls and the ceilings. We also made all the furniture. The only thing we didn’t make other than medical equipment was the flooring. But we did everything else. And our materials were also used on the external facades of the building.</p>
  <h2 id="q-where-did-the-hospital-designs-and-plans-come-from-and-what-did-the-process-look-like">Q: Where did the hospital designs and plans come from? And what did the process look like?</h2>
  <p><strong>Pandey:</strong> The NGO gave us the plans and the patch of land in Masaurhi Block, Patna. They wanted to build where governmental services like healthcare and infrastructure were not present. So, this was not in the middle of the city, which made it more challenging. Being a civil engineer became helpful. We made all the structural drawings. We did everything – the plumbing, civil, electrical, which was not even our forte.</p>
  <p>Travel was a challenge. The police commissioner would only give our team permission to move outside of the village when the work was done, so we ended up living on-site for 45 days. I actually ended up living in the hospital itself as it was being built. I’ll never forget that.</p>
  <p>Because everything was locked down, we couldn’t bring in contractors or construction workers. I really learned about getting the community involved in these things. We went into the villages and announced, we've been told to make this hospital for your community. Help us find workers. The next day, almost half of the village showed up, like 100 people. Someone said I'm a carpenter, I'm an electrician, I'm a plumber. Everybody in the village ended up working on that project under our direction. This is during the month of June in India, which is like 48 degrees Celsius (118 degrees Fahrenheit).</p>
  <h2 id="q-you-were-under-30-years-old-at-that-time-and-you-built-a-hospital">Q: You were under 30 years old at that time, and you built a hospital!</h2>
  <p><strong>Pandey:</strong> I was 28. If it wasn’t during COVID-19, they wouldn’t have let me do it.</p>
  <h2 id="q-where-are-your-research-and-development-efforts-focused-these-days">Q: Where are your research and development efforts focused these days?</h2>
  <p><strong>Pandey:</strong> We are working a lot with biomimicry, a relatively new field where architects and product designers look to nature before they go into the lab. For example, how a bee would make its honeycomb. Those are some of the most geometrically stable structures. You can learn a lot from them to apply to making houses that are very earthquake-resistant.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_13ee708d2c78caf083b2fccdc9c3cff9914dfab25.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_13ee708d2c78caf083b2fccdc9c3cff9914dfab25.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_13ee708d2c78caf083b2fccdc9c3cff9914dfab25.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="A farmer works in a paddy field near Mysore in southern India. Photo courtesy of Shriti Pandey." src="./media_13ee708d2c78caf083b2fccdc9c3cff9914dfab25.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="2160">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p>That led to us creating these frame systems that are honeycomb in shape. There’s so much inspiration in nature, in terms of physics, science, and biology.</p>
  <p>We also launched a felt product that can be used for sound and thermal insulation. We were doing a project in Rajasthan, which is one of the hottest desert regions in the world, and the community asked, why do you use so much of the traditional glass wool insulation? Why not use animal-residue material like wool? Nothing is more insulating. That led us to look at the value chain of wool that is not sold for textile use and to a number of pastoralists in India who do sheep shearing, and then to us making 100% biodegradable felt.</p>
  <p>If we were not engaged with the community, we wouldn’t know how to even collect it.</p>
  <h2 id="q-in-the-film-you-talked-about-how-in-small-villages-nothing-goes-to-waste-what-did-you-learn-from-them">Q: In the film, you talked about how in small villages nothing goes to waste. What did you learn from them?</h2>
  <p><strong>Pandey:</strong> When I lived in a village for a year with a family that was living in a very low-cost, makeshift house, I witnessed that, whether it is their structures, the way they cook, the way they engage with each other in the community – they will not let anything go to waste. It's the perspective that when you don't have a lot, there's just no room to waste.</p>
  <p>And that made me realize that waste is only a waste if you waste it. It's a choice. We can look at it differently. Everything that's coming out of a factory, every construction site, demolition, and everything in our houses that we don't need any more is a possible resource for some added-value product. It’s a mind shift.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <h4 id="read-more-in-this-series">Read more in this series</h4>
  <div class="collection">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h6 id="editorial">Editorial</h6>
        <p><a href="/blogs/300-days-of-sun">300 Days of Sun: Communities Power Their Own Future</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>
        <h6 id="editorial-1">Editorial</h6>
        <p><a href="/blogs/a-case-for-carbon-accountability">A Case for Carbon Accountability</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>
        <h6 id="editorial-2">Editorial</h6>
        <p><a href="/blogs/restoring-peatlands">Restoring Peatlands, Nature’s Carbon Sponges</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>
        <h6 id="editorial-3">Editorial</h6>
        <p><a href="/blogs/road-to-regeneration-waste-to-life">Road to Regeneration: Waste to Life</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>
        <h6 id="editorial-4">Editorial</h6>
        <p><a href="/blogs/road-to-regeneration-beautiful-poison">Turning Toxic Coal Mine Waste into the Stuff of Art</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div><a href="/videos/roads-to-regeneration-series">Roads to Regeneration collection</a></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>sidebar</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>core-topic/sustainable-business-operations</category>
            <category>content-type/expert-opinions</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Is Supply Chain Innovation Even Possible in an Era of Tighter Regulation?]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2024/01/is-supply-chain-innovation-possible-era-tighter-regulation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2024/01/is-supply-chain-innovation-possible-era-tighter-regulation</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[When it comes to supply chain regulation, compliance and innovation are not mutually exclusive. Investing in advanced technologies can help.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/executive-blog</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/catena-x</category>
            <category>non-sap-event/wef-davos</category>
            <category>product/sap-integrated-business-planning-for-supply-chain</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Measuring Social Impact – the S in ESG]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/measuring-social-impact-s-in-esg</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/measuring-social-impact-s-in-esg</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Defining terms, setting scope, tracking regulations – it’s messy. Here’s how to start measuring and managing social impact.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>core-topic/environmental-compliance</category>
            <category>content-type/what-is</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>