<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/product/sap-ehs-management/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[CP Foods Selects SAP Solutions for Cloud Sustainability]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/cp-foods-selects-sap-solutions-for-cloud-sustainability</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/cp-foods-selects-sap-solutions-for-cloud-sustainability</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[CP Foods has selected SAP software to future-proof its business and use data to make more sustainable decisions. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_183175263685a353d3b61ffbc18dc57a24b395640.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_183175263685a353d3b61ffbc18dc57a24b395640.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_183175263685a353d3b61ffbc18dc57a24b395640.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="CP Foods Selects SAP Solutions for Cloud Sustainability" src="./media_183175263685a353d3b61ffbc18dc57a24b395640.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="cp-foods-selects-sap-solutions-for-cloud-sustainability">CP Foods Selects SAP Solutions for Cloud Sustainability</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF and BANGKOK</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced Charoen Pokphand Foods Public Company Limited (“CP Foods”) has selected multiple SAP solutions to drive further growth and competitive advantage and to ensure the sustainability of its products for the future.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="record-report-and-act-on-your-sustainability-goals-with-sap-software">Record, report and act on your sustainability goals with SAP software</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/sustainability/solutions.html">Learn how</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Catering to more than 4 billion people globally, CP Foods is embarking on its next stage of digital transformation with the RISE with SAP, SAP Sustainability Footprint Management, and SAP Sustainability Control Tower solutions. In addition, the SAP EHS Management, environment management application will be implemented to future-proof its business and to gain strategic insight into the sustainability impact of its products, processes and infrastructure globally. The company is a leading integrated agro-industrial and food business that is one of the world’s largest producers of feed, shrimp, poultry and pork. It has operations in 17 countries and exports to more than 50 countries.</p>
  <h2 id="global-net-zero-ambitions">Global Net-Zero Ambitions</h2>
  <p>In line with CP Foods’ goal of becoming the “Sustainable Kitchen of the World,” CP Foods is the first food processing company in the world with near- and long-term forests, lands and agriculture (FLAG) sustainability targets validated by the Science-Based Targets Initiative (SBTi). CP Foods is looking to realize the company’s <a href="https://www.cpfworldwide.com/en/media-center/oversea-operations-coal-free-to-net-zero">Net Zero goals</a> of reducing 42% of Scope 1 and 2 emissions and 30.3% of Scope 3 emissions by 2030 – and 90% of Scope 1 and 2 emissions and 72% of Scope 3 emissions by 2050. To achieve these goals, the company is implementing SAP Sustainability solutions to record, report and act on real-time sustainability data, driving carbon accounting at both corporate and product levels.</p>
  <p>“Net Zero is the only solution to climate change,” CP Foods CEO Prasit Boondoungpraser said. “It is important to us to understand and reduce our impact on the planet, so we create food that is not only safe and nutritious for people but also green and clean for the earth. Feeding our livestock, farming our food and transporting it to people’s plates incurs emissions we have to be able to record and report. With RISE with SAP and SAP Sustainability solutions, we will have insight into actual emissions automated in real time rather than relying on manual averages, allowing us to make quick, informed and sustainable business decisions for our operations and for the planet.”</p>
  <p>SAP plans to provide a technology foundation that will support CP Foods in complying with forthcoming carbon regulations in various markets, including the EU Carbon Border Adjustment Mechanism (EU C-BAM) and U.S. SEC climate risk disclosures.</p>
  <p>Key to reducing total emissions, CP Foods will focus on supply chain emissions, with its emissions mostly falling under Scope 3. CP Foods will work with the Customer Success organization at SAP, leverage YASH Technologies’ sustainability expertise and build on Amazon Web Services (AWS) to implement SAP Sustainability solutions. Doing so will allow it to record and report on its Scope 1 and 2 emissions in Thailand and select Scope 3 (3.1 and 3.4) for its feed business in Thailand covering both FLAG and non-FLAG emissions. The next phase of implementation will extend in scope to cover operations around the world.</p>
  <h2 id="cloud-sustainability">Cloud Sustainability</h2>
  <p>Paul Marriott, president of SAP Asia Pacific &#x26; Japan, said: “Sustainability is a huge opportunity for businesses across Asia. Using RISE with SAP and our sustainability solutions, CP Foods is getting ahead of forthcoming emissions regulation and future-proofing its business by using data to make more sustainable decisions. It can use those insights to drive more operational efficiencies, optimize supply chains, and differentiate its business against competitors.”</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-our-approach-to-sustainability-and-our-aspirations-for-a-world-with-zero-emissions-zero-waste-and-zero-inequality">Learn more about our approach to sustainability and our aspirations for a world with zero emissions, zero waste and zero inequality</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/sustainability/our-approach.html">Explore our journey</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>About SAP</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As a global leader in enterprise applications and business AI, SAP (NYSE:SAP) stands at the nexus of business and technology. For over 50 years, organizations have trusted SAP to bring out their best by uniting business-critical operations spanning finance, procurement, HR, supply chain, and customer experience. For more information, visit <a href="http://www.sap.com">www.sap.com</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Note to editors:</strong><br>To preview and download broadcast-standard stock footage and press photos digitally, please visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/photos">www.sap.com/photos</a>. On this platform, you can find high resolution material for your media channels.</p>
  <p><strong>For customers interested in learning more about SAP products:</strong><br>Global Customer Center: +49 180 534-34-24<br>United States Only: 1 (800) 872-1SAP (1-800-872-1727)</p>
  <p><strong>For more information, press only:</strong><br>Rizka Laksmi, <a href="mailto:rizka.laksmi@sap.com">rizka.laksmi@sap.com</a>, WIB<br>Lesa Plingen, +49 622 776 9000, <a href="mailto:lesa.plingen@sap.com">lesa.plingen@sap.com</a>, CET<br><a href="mailto:SAP%20Press%20Room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>This document contains forward-looking statements, which are predictions, projections, or other statements about future events. These statements are based on current expectations, forecasts, and assumptions that are subject to risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results and outcomes to materially differ. Additional information regarding these risks and uncertainties may be found in our filings with the Securities and Exchange Commission, including but not limited to the risk factors section of SAP’s 2023 Annual Report on Form 20-F.<br>© 2024 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.<br>Please consider our <a href="https://www.sap.com/corporate/en/legal/privacy.html">privacy policy</a>. If you received this press release in your e-mail and you wish to unsubscribe to our mailing list please contact <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a> and write Unsubscribe in the subject line.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-ehs-management</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-footprint-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Business Case for Tackling Inequality]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/business-case-tackling-inequality</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/business-case-tackling-inequality</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Inequality is a key lever in achieving climate resilience and adaptation. Read to learn how companies can be part of this critical effort.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/esg</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>product/sap-ehs-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How SAP Helps Businesses Streamline Their Emissions Declarations]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/sap-ehs-management-streamline-emissions-declarations</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/sap-ehs-management-streamline-emissions-declarations</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP EHS Management helps support teams throughout the process of aggregating, preparing, and analyzing their environmental data.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-emissions</category>
            <category>news-tag/esg</category>
            <category>news-tag/greenhouse-gas-emissions</category>
            <category>product/sap-ehs-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Safeguarding Employee Welfare at Motor Oil with Real-Time Incident Reporting]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/02/motor-oil-safeguarding-employee-welfare</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/02/motor-oil-safeguarding-employee-welfare</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Read to find out why Motor Oil, Corinth Refineries S.A. selected SAP EHS Management to help streamline its incident management processes.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15d0dcd3a1d15d04bed4848a596bb2a6f0ac3f331.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15d0dcd3a1d15d04bed4848a596bb2a6f0ac3f331.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_15d0dcd3a1d15d04bed4848a596bb2a6f0ac3f331.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Safeguarding Employee Welfare at Motor Oil with Real-Time Incident Reporting" src="./media_15d0dcd3a1d15d04bed4848a596bb2a6f0ac3f331.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="safeguarding-employee-welfare-at-motor-oil-with-real-time-incident-reporting">Safeguarding Employee Welfare at Motor Oil with Real-Time Incident Reporting</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Motor Oil, Corinth Refineries S.A. is an energy group based in Greece. It was founded in 1970 and its refinery in the region of Corinth counts among the top refineries in Europe.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The company plays a leading role in crude oil refining and marketing of petroleum products in the country as well as the greater Eastern Mediterranean region, supplying its customers with a wide range of high-quality products. Motor Oil produces 185,000 barrels of crude oil each day with a workforce of 2,500 employees and exports to more than 45 countries. The refinery, along with its ancillary plants and fuel distribution facilities, constitutes the largest privately-owned industrial complex in Greece.</p>
  <p>Recently, Dimitrios Michalopoulos, head of Industrial Applications at Motor Oil, explained how the company improved environmental, health, and safety processes. This is of significant importance to the company’s success in keeping incidents at a minimum and ensuring a safe work environment for its employees.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="register-for-the-industry-40-empowered-people-report">Register for the Industry 4.0 Empowered People report</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/dg/empowered-people/index.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="replacing-manual-incident-management-processes">Replacing Manual Incident Management Processes</h2>
  <p>For many years, incident management processes were cumbersome and manual. “We have three categories of incidents: incidents where someone was hurt like through a fire, near misses, and safety observations,” Michalopoulos said. “In the past, the incident management process was based on spreadsheets. In the case of an incident, refinery engineers had to fill a predefined form and e-mail it to our health and safety department. As there were no predefined field values, employees were free to enter texts without getting any system-based assistance and control.” He continued: “As a result, it was very difficult to generate any relevant KPIs as the entire process was manual.”</p>
  <p>The assignment of incident managers was carried out by the health and safety section head without adequate traceability on what happened when and who was actually acting as the responsible incident manager.</p>
  <p>“The investigation and root cause analysis process was executed completely offline, and corrective or preventive actions that were decided to be executed resulted from the investigation process. All of that was recorded in shared spreadsheet files and progress was communicated via e-mail,” he added. “It is obvious that the monitoring of corrective or preventive actions was a cumbersome and time-consuming task for all incident managers. The preparation of KPIs and reports based on unstructured data was a challenging and manual process with a high risk of human error.”</p>
  <p>The company had to take a new approach to overcome the challenges. “All the above challenges related to an insufficient quality of incident management. The amount of time required for managing this on a daily basis, including preparing KPIs and reports, led us to the decision of deploying a new and integrated solution based on SAP ERP,” Michalopoulos explained.</p>
  <h2 id="project-objectives-and-key-factors">Project Objectives and Key Factors</h2>
  <p>In terms of objectives and key factors, Michalopoulos identified increasing employee participation in and awareness of health and safety processes as one of the key objectives for the project. “We wanted to introduce an intuitive way to make incident reporting easier for everyone in the refinery,” he said.</p>
  <p>Additionally, standardizing incident management processes was another important objective for the company. Based on the refinery’s official procedures, it was important to Motor Oil that every employee should be able to report an incident or a safety observation. To raise employee awareness, the company also set up a rewards program.</p>
  <h2 id="meeting-strategic-goals-with-a-modern-solution">Meeting Strategic Goals with a Modern Solution</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="watch-a-video-to-learn-more-about-sap-ehs-management">Watch a video to learn more about SAP EHS Management</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/ehs-management-health-safety.html?video=ae9b45db-997d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Motor Oil evaluated <a href="/topics/sap-ehs-management">SAP Environment, Health, and Safety Management</a> and determined that the SAP EHS Management, incident management application best covered its requirements. “We can rely on it,” Michalopoulos said, adding “our IT infrastructure is based on SAP. Therefore, we wanted to benefit from leveraging integrated data from other SAP solutions and be able to prepare consolidated reports without developing complex interfaces.”</p>
  <p>Motor Oil deployed the incident management capabilities with its health and safety section as the business owner. “All 1,500 refinery employees can now use the system and the interactive forms can be filled by everyone,” Michalopoulos remarked. Moreover, the solution is used by the incident managers in the health and safety section as well as by refinery section and refinery department heads, which comprise about 50 people.</p>
  <h2 id="improved-and-automated-reporting">Improved and Automated Reporting</h2>
  <p>“We deployed the new system in July 2021 with assistance from Real Consulting IT Business Solutions S.A. Therefore, it has been productive for only a few months and it is still early to determine safe metrics about the benefits,” Michalopoulos said. “Overall, the quality of our health and safety processes and the time required for managing incidents have significantly improved.” So far, Motor Oil has seen:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Increased employee awareness and higher compliance with internal and external safety regulations and standards</li>
    <li>Standardized and eased incident reporting on a tablet for all 1,500 refinery employees and the management team</li>
    <li>Time savings of 25%-30% in managing incidents and reporting, thanks to automated workflows, predefined KPIs, and interactive forms allowing them to focus on higher value-add tasks</li>
    <li>Availability of up-to-date online reports with the latest incident information details, enabling fast decision-making and advanced analytics</li>
    <li>Simplified and documented incident investigation and root cause analysis processes automatically trigger corrective and preventive actions that can be monitored and tracked with regard to progress</li>
    <li>Cost savings thanks to the integration with the company’s human resources system, which runs on SAP solutions, to immediately access refinery employee details</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="new-solution-supports-corporate-goals">New Solution Supports Corporate Goals</h2>
  <p>SAP EHS Management helps Motor Oil meet its corporate goals. “The nature of Motor Oil Group’s business operations, such as refining, storage, transportation, and marketing of petrochemical products, make occupational health and safety a matter of high importance and a top priority to us. Our management’s commitment to ensure a safe working environment is absolute and permanent. We take an ongoing and systematic approach for the improvement of health and safety issues,” Michalopoulos said. “Based on this strategy, SAP EHS Management plays a vital role to us.”</p>
  <p>The company’s future plans include implementing additional software components. “Our <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/s4hana-erp.html">SAP S/4HANA</a> greenfield implementation is in progress and considered the digital core of the transformation process at our company. In addition, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/cloud-analytics.html">SAP Analytics Cloud</a> was selected as our strategic tool for planning and budgeting processes at group level.”</p>
  <p>Request a <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/ehs-management-health-safety.html">demo</a> to learn how to respond and recover while ensuring the safety of employees and customers in times of change with integrated environmental, health, and safety management. Read a <a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/dg/empowered-people/index.html">report</a> on how empowering employees with intelligent systems and data can help them manage unforeseen events in near real time and make more informed decisions.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Karin Fent is senior director of global Customer Success Digital Supply Chain at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>industry/oil-gas-energy</category>
            <category>product/sap-ehs-management</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>