<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/product/sap-e-mobility/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[CEV Technologies and SAP Fuel E-Mobility Revolution in Croatia’s Retail Sector]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/cev-technologies-e-mobility-croatia-retail-sector</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/cev-technologies-e-mobility-croatia-retail-sector</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[To realize the potential of convenient charging within the customer experience, CEV Technologies implemented SAP E-Mobility in Croatia.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/automotive</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/electric-vehicles</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
            <category>product/sap-e-mobility</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Labs India: A Pioneer in Transitioning to Electric Vehicles]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/sap-labs-india-pioneer-transitioning-to-electric-vehicles</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/sap-labs-india-pioneer-transitioning-to-electric-vehicles</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Over the past decade, the transportation team at SAP Labs India implemented various initiatives to encourage employees to use EVs.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/automotive</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-emissions</category>
            <category>news-tag/decarbonization</category>
            <category>news-tag/electric-vehicles</category>
            <category>industry/travel-transportation</category>
            <category>product/sap-e-mobility</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Five Ways Automakers and Suppliers Can Prepare for the Future of Mobility]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/five-ways-automotive-industry-future-of-mobility</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/five-ways-automotive-industry-future-of-mobility</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[EVs, mobility-as-a-service, operational resilience, and digital retail are shaping the future of mobility in the automotive industry.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/automotive</category>
            <category>news-tag/catena-x</category>
            <category>news-tag/electric-vehicles</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-e-mobility</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-industry-network-for-automotive</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[End-to-End Electric Vehicle Charging Management with coneva and SAP E-Mobility]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/electric-vehicle-charging-management-coneva</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/electric-vehicle-charging-management-coneva</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[To enable companies to adapt their EV fleets’ energy consumption to local generation capacity, SAP teamed up with coneva. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/automotive</category>
            <category>news-tag/electric-vehicles</category>
            <category>product/sap-e-mobility</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Electrify Your Car Fleet with Ease]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/videos/electrify-your-car-fleet-with-ease</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/videos/electrify-your-car-fleet-with-ease</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Bela Peterson, product owner for Smart Charging at coneva, shows us how easy it is for companies to charge their car fleets at the office,...]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/video</category>
            <category>news-tag/electric-vehicles</category>
            <category>product/sap-e-mobility</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Introduces E-Mobility Solution for Electric Vehicle Fleet]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/02/sap-e-mobility-solution-ev-fleet</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/02/sap-e-mobility-solution-ev-fleet</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is applying its own e-mobility enterprise software to achieve the goal of an emissions-free car fleet by 2030.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f2e6d93c35becc557821fc7ed743ef1675c177c4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f2e6d93c35becc557821fc7ed743ef1675c177c4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1f2e6d93c35becc557821fc7ed743ef1675c177c4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Introduces E-Mobility Solution for Electric Vehicle Fleet" src="./media_1f2e6d93c35becc557821fc7ed743ef1675c177c4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-introduces-e-mobility-solution-for-electric-vehicle-fleet">SAP Introduces E-Mobility Solution for Electric Vehicle Fleet</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Beginning with Austria, SAP is applying its own e-mobility enterprise software to achieve the goal of an emissions-free car fleet by 2030.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The e-mobility transformation is underway, and chances are good that you are witnessing it on the streets of your own town. More and more consumers are choosing electric-powered transport over the internal combustion engine, and this despite supply chain disruptions due to the ongoing global pandemic.</p>
  <p>As battery range improves, charging infrastructure expands, and government incentives gain traction, the popularity of electric vehicles (EVs) <a href="https://www.rolandberger.com/en/Insights/Publications/E-Mobility-booms-despite-the-pandemic.html">appears to be taking off</a>. According to the Electric Vehicle World Sales Database, in 2021 all regions witnessed strong <a href="https://www.ev-volumes.com/">increases in EV sales</a>, with growth rates three to eight times higher than for the overall light-vehicle market. By 2026, <a href="https://www.bcg.com/publications/2021/why-evs-need-to-accelerate-their-market-penetration">according to a BCG study</a>, EVs will account for more than half of light vehicles sold globally.</p>
  <p>But there are still hurdles to overcome. Case-in-point is a charging infrastructure that is unevenly distributed and cannot keep up with demand. For example, Europe only has around <a href="https://www.reuters.com/world/us/five-facts-state-us-electric-vehicle-charging-network-2021-09-01/">62 public charging points</a> per 100,000 inhabitants, while the U.S. has roughly 37 charge points on the same per-capita basis. This is causing many potential EV converts to take a “wait-and-see” stance until they are assured of a viable charging infrastructure in their area.</p>
  <p>The successful transition to e-mobility will therefore require huge <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2021/09/19/how-to-meet-the-demand-of-ev-infrastructure-and-maintain-a-stable-grid/?guccounter=1&#x26;guce_referrer=aHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuZ29vZ2xlLmNvbS8&#x26;guce_referrer_sig=AQAAAGe8ekyPOciu-TGbgfCwhPudGlf8Zw3PXfJGKdyHhB11ULnWaRdby3cPGZwxCEF8Dl8sJsDyY_Ym5kzshncALcYunE5ZWHhAUemKukl2YWOUXTFgP0kZNiJ7eBSC-TrHLzziTH6sK5D5Zgm2s5A3HjOS5hUDIY3fay-No8XdcWse">investments in infrastructure</a> and related technologies. Industry experts agree that demand can only be satisfied through a <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2021/09/19/how-to-meet-the-demand-of-ev-infrastructure-and-maintain-a-stable-grid/">range of options,</a> which includes semi-public charging options like privately run charging stations, office and retail parking lots, home garages, and government-provided locations.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-accelerates-its-move-to-an-emission-free-car-fleet">SAP Accelerates Its Move to an Emission-Free Car Fleet</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/11/sap-accelerates-move-to-emission-free-car-fleet">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="sap-e-mobility-intelligent-charging-experience">SAP E-Mobility: Intelligent Charging Experience</h2>
  <p>Establishing a ubiquitous charge-point network is only one side of the coin. Charge-point providers will also need to provide consumers an easy, intelligent, and automated charging experience. Think of the one-click online-shopping experience consumers have become accustomed to and you get the idea. Achieving this level of service requires an intelligent software platform that is interconnected with other mobility-related business tasks and immediately recognizes the charging profile of your vehicle when you register at the charging point.</p>
  <p>In September 2021, <a href="/2021/09/sap-e-mobility-solution-sustainable-electric-vehicles">SAP launched</a> SAP E-Mobility, a standardized, cloud-based solution that provides a complete package that enables charge point operators to run their business efficiently and profitably.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_119ce1ae56b92d9cc66762d568b744f6093e77f3e.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_119ce1ae56b92d9cc66762d568b744f6093e77f3e.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_119ce1ae56b92d9cc66762d568b744f6093e77f3e.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Ulrich Scholl, VP and chief product manager for SAP E-Mobility" src="./media_119ce1ae56b92d9cc66762d568b744f6093e77f3e.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="600" height="600">
    </picture>“SAP E-Mobility is targeted at companies where mobility is the core business, such as logistics companies managing large vehicle fleets or mobility-as-a-service providers such as public transit, municipalities, and private ground transportation,” explains Ulrich Scholl, vice president and chief product manager for SAP E-Mobility.
  </p>
  <p>The enterprise-grade capabilities of SAP E-Mobility offer integration with other software solutions for expense reimbursement management, analytics, cost management, billing, and invoicing.</p>
  <h2 id="transition-to-an-emissions-free-car-fleet-by-2030">Transition to an Emissions-Free Car Fleet by 2030</h2>
  <p>Since 2009, SAP has made sustainability a key pillar of its corporate strategy and annually discloses its own sustainability performance in an <a href="https://www.sap.com/integrated-reports/2020/en.html">integrated report</a>. It is only logical, therefore, that SAP would use the business software it develops to increase its own operational efficiency. This is exactly what the company is doing with SAP E-Mobility.</p>
  <p>To make good on its promise to <a href="/2021/03/sap-carbon-neutrality-goal-2023">become carbon neutral</a> by 2023, SAP is applying the standard solution for its own electric vehicles, which comprise nearly one-fifth of its total fleet of around 27,000 company cars. Battery electric vehicles have been part of the company’s fleet since 2010, and their share is growing as part of the company’s <a href="/2021/11/sap-accelerates-move-to-emission-free-car-fleet">transition to an emissions-free fleet</a> by 2030. Coupled with the decision to go 100% electric by latest 2030 is a pledge to employees that the charging infrastructure at its facilities can meet growing demand.</p>
  <h2 id="e-vehicle-charging-infrastructure-flexibility-is-key">E-Vehicle Charging Infrastructure: Flexibility Is Key</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-targets-carbon-neutrality-by-2023">SAP Targets Carbon-Neutrality by 2023</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/03/sap-carbon-neutrality-goal-2023">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The SAP Austria office in Vienna was the company’s first corporate location to implement SAP E-Mobility. Currently one-quarter of the 400 company cars at SAP Austria are battery electric vehicles, with a significant transition to electric planned in the coming years.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_181ebe12abba9fc0664656385118b1ae2e67856e9.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_181ebe12abba9fc0664656385118b1ae2e67856e9.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_181ebe12abba9fc0664656385118b1ae2e67856e9.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Charging station at SAP in Vienna" src="./media_181ebe12abba9fc0664656385118b1ae2e67856e9.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2400" height="1500">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p><em>Photo courtesy of Michael Gruber.</em></p>
  <p>The charging infrastructure is operated by SAP’s facility management team in Vienna as part of its overall responsibility for asset management. Charging capacity is supplemented by a photovoltaic system that is also connected to the electricity grid.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c9b49f090338e3e88dd8377c9f429bfed5ee9eb0.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c9b49f090338e3e88dd8377c9f429bfed5ee9eb0.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1c9b49f090338e3e88dd8377c9f429bfed5ee9eb0.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Steffen Krautwasser, head of Global Car Fleet at SAP" src="./media_1c9b49f090338e3e88dd8377c9f429bfed5ee9eb0.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="600" height="600">
    </picture>“Flexibility is key to any enterprise charging concept because employees want to be able to charge their cars at work, public charging points, and private charging points at home,” says Steffen Krautwasser, head of Global Car Fleet at SAP. “The operation of our charging infrastructure in Austria is based on our strategic adoption road map of SAP E-Mobility and marks a critical milestone for adoption at our other locations.”
  </p>
  <p>Strong fluctuations in office use during the pandemic have shown the importance of flexibility. Close coordination between the fleet manager and facilities manager in creating an adaptable strategy is of the utmost importance. SAP E-Mobility enables flexible charging at work and supports reimbursement of private charging at home via <a href="https://www.concur.com/">SAP Concur</a> software for travel and expense management.</p>
  <h2 id="charge-point-sharing-for-sustainable-e-mobility-in-cities">Charge-Point Sharing for Sustainable E-Mobility in Cities</h2>
  <p>Some cities and communities are looking to bridge the current shortage in public charging capacity by opening private charging infrastructure to the public. “Since the number of public charging stations is increasing more slowly than demand, it is particularly relevant to open up semi-public charging points to as many users as possible,” says Scholl.</p>
  <p>This is where the versatility of SAP’s new solution comes through.</p>
  <p>“SAP E-Mobility gives us the ability to open up access and billing options to any user, and we can scale the system to new requirements rapidly as required,” says Robert Diglas, head of regional facilities for SAP in Austria, Switzerland, Central Europe, and Ukraine. “For example, the flexible solution will enable us to open up our charging points to customers and business partners if and when we decide to do so.”</p>
  <p>But SAP’s e-mobility vision extends well beyond the office parking lot. In 2021, the company started a co-innovation project with UnternehmerTUM, the city of Munich, and other partners from the mobility and energy industries. Together, they are developing new concepts based on <a href="https://mobility.unternehmertum.de/en/citizen-mobility-1">Citizen Mobility</a> to improve charge-point coverage in German cities.</p>
  <p>The integration of private charge points is just one focus area, according to Scholl. “With SAP E-Mobility, we are just beginning to help our customers and partners turn mobility as a service into a reality,” he says. “The collaboration with innovative partners and real-life testing by citizens has delivered innovative use cases and thoughtful insights into how sustainable e-mobility, as one mode of urban transportation, can work in the future.”</p>
  <p>Customers and partners can experience the SAP E-Mobility solution in action at the company’s <a href="https://blogs.sap.com/2021/12/15/sap-e-mobility-charging-infrastructure-lab-opens/">e-mobility lab locations</a> in Walldorf, Germany, and Bangalore, India.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/automotive</category>
            <category>product/sap-e-mobility</category>
            <category>industry/utilities</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP E-Mobility: Enabling Sustainable Mobility]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/sap-e-mobility-solution-sustainable-electric-vehicles</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/sap-e-mobility-solution-sustainable-electric-vehicles</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn more about the new cloud-based solution SAP E-Mobility and the new benefits coming your way for electric vehicles.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ab0a1efd18faa7aa854e3a865ca5a76765e8fdf6.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ab0a1efd18faa7aa854e3a865ca5a76765e8fdf6.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1ab0a1efd18faa7aa854e3a865ca5a76765e8fdf6.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP E-Mobility: Enabling Sustainable Mobility" src="./media_1ab0a1efd18faa7aa854e3a865ca5a76765e8fdf6.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-e-mobility-enabling-sustainable-mobility">SAP E-Mobility: Enabling Sustainable Mobility</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Sustainable mobility with SAP E-Mobility: there is now nothing in the way for buying electric vehicles in the future. The new cloud-based solution helps companies to operate electric vehicle charging infrastructures at scale to drive the transition to sustainable and convenient electric mobility.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Electric vehicles (EVs) are becoming increasingly popular. New EV registrations globally rose by 168% during the first half of 2021 compared to 2020. In total, 2.65 million EVs were purchased and have been hitting the streets. According to EV Volume analysts, electric vehicles are trending toward 6.4 million units by the end of 2021.</p>
  <p>Charging stations are often a challenge to more rapid EV growth as public stations total 28,000 in the U.S. and 20,000 across Europe. This is reason enough to use the standardized cloud-based SAP E-Mobility solution, planned for availability September 24, 2021, to address not only public but also non-public and semi-public charging points.</p>
  <p>As a first step, SAP is addressing company car fleets with charging points at the site or branch as well as at a driver’s home. Since the number of public charging stations is increasing more slowly than their demand, it is particularly relevant to increase the utilization of semi-public charging points and make the best possible use of them. It is also a relief when employees charge company vehicles at the private charging station at home. Complex billing processes, which can be easily and neatly covered, play a decisive role in all scenarios.</p>
  <p>However, the solution offers much more; it is the basis for controlling and managing all business processes pertaining to the charging point. Complex processes that were previously prevalent along the value chain — from delivery point operators to companies to electric vehicle owners — are considerably simplified.</p>
  <h2 id="greater-flexibility-for-fleet-managers-with-sap-e-mobility">Greater Flexibility for Fleet Managers with SAP E-Mobility</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="the-electrification-of-mobility-challenges-and-opportunities-for-travel-and-transportation-operators">The Electrification of Mobility: Challenges and Opportunities for Travel and Transportation Operators</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/04/e-mobility-travel-transportation-operators">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Fleet managers also benefit. For example, the solution provides necessary charging data — charging total, location, date, duration, vehicle — to the connected accounting and finance software in order to perform cost center allocations or to initiate a corresponding reimbursement of private electricity costs of the vehicle owner. This happens in an automated manner via standard financial processes, such as travel expense reports.</p>
  <p>On the facility manager’s side, SAP E-Mobility means more than just simplified billing. Via a dashboard, the status of all charging stations can be seen at any time, and defective stations can be swiftly repaired. This means facility managers always have an up-to-date overview of the available charging columns, which is also the case on the part of the charging column operators and thus enables comprehensive user and location management.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f80bc364d79c7eac8fa594a8783a48660bb815f7.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f80bc364d79c7eac8fa594a8783a48660bb815f7.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1f80bc364d79c7eac8fa594a8783a48660bb815f7.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP E-Mobility screenshot" src="./media_1f80bc364d79c7eac8fa594a8783a48660bb815f7.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1428" height="954">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p>The results are overall faster workflows and higher charging point availability, supporting a better user experience as well as a positive total cost of ownership (TCO), which helps to further increase the acceptance of electric cars.</p>
  <p>In addition, the solution simplifies the deployment of new charging infrastructure and is hardware independent. Operators can easily integrate new charging stations into the network as well as monitor and bill them via standard communication protocols. SAP uses the Open Charge Point Protocol 1.6 standard for this purpose. For charging point operators and businesses, the new solution thus offers maximum flexibility with very little effort.</p>
  <h2 id="extensive-partner-ecosystem-enables-complete-solution">Extensive Partner Ecosystem Enables Complete Solution</h2>
  <p>To be able to offer companies a comprehensive solution consisting of hardware, software, services, and support, SAP relies on a network of certified e-mobility partners.</p>
  <p>SAP E-Mobility is an important part of this, offering all stakeholders — charging station operators as well as companies and drivers — significantly simpler processes than the market is currently offering. Due to such solutions, not only is the necessary infrastructure expanded more quickly and flexibly, but companies also receive standardized e-mobility processes that support them in achieving their CO2 targets, and at the same time promote the broader use of electric vehicles. One example: partners such as energy service providers implement application scenarios such as “charging from self-generated photovoltaic electricity” or “vehicle to grid” and thus support the production of sustainable energy while simultaneously using the vehicle as a storage location.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="deliver-innovative-solutions-on-the-road-to-new-mobility-while-running-a-profitable-automotive-business">Deliver innovative solutions on the road to new mobility, while running a profitable automotive business</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/automotive.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="learn-more-about-the-new-sap-e-mobility-solution"><a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/automotive.html">Learn more about the new SAP E-Mobility solution</a>.</h3>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Hagen Heubach is global vice president and head of the Automotive industry business unit at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/automotive</category>
            <category>news-tag/discrete-industries</category>
            <category>news-tag/electric-vehicles</category>
            <category>product/sap-e-mobility</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>