<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-topic/cloud/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Elevating the RISE with SAP Experience]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2024/06/elevating-rise-with-sap-experience</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2024/06/elevating-rise-with-sap-experience</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn more about the elevated RISE with SAP experience that is improving services and delivery for customers end-to-end.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16f71bd27ee4db299c2fe36e929f4108d8ce4d936.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16f71bd27ee4db299c2fe36e929f4108d8ce4d936.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_16f71bd27ee4db299c2fe36e929f4108d8ce4d936.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Elevating the RISE with SAP Experience" src="./media_16f71bd27ee4db299c2fe36e929f4108d8ce4d936.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="elevating-the-rise-with-sap-experience">Elevating the RISE with SAP Experience</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>According to Albert Einstein, “Life is like a bicycle. To keep your balance, you must keep moving.” He had a point! The same is true of business.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-sapphire-taking-business-to-the-next-level-in-the-era-of-ai">SAP Sapphire: Taking Business to the Next Level in the Era of AI</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/events/sapphire/news-guide.html">Read the news guide</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Successful businesses keep moving and evolving, especially in times of rapid change and macroeconomic uncertainty. And given the current volatility, business transformation is no longer optional; it’s imperative.</p>
  <p>Knowing this, we launched RISE with SAP in 2021 not as a technical IT migration approach, but as a comprehensive solution designed to drive broad business transformation. With 6,000 customers having selected RISE with SAP, we know we cannot stop moving either. And I was <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZZ1yFoALzAs">thrilled to share at SAP Sapphire this year</a> how we are taking the RISE with SAP experience to the next level and improving services and delivery for customers end-to-end.</p>
  <p>Here are some key takeaways.</p>
  <h2 id="evolving-how-we-engage-with-customers">Evolving How We Engage with Customers</h2>
  <p>Navigating the transformation of today’s complex system landscapes and business processes is like orchestrating a symphony with countless instruments and moving parts. To succeed, we need to keep refining our engagement approach to better manage the intricacies of our customers’ complex architecture at an unprecedented level of detail.</p>
  <p>To this end, we’re making a lot of changes in how we engage with customers, including strengthening the role of the enterprise architect (EA). The EA harmonizes all elements and guides the customer throughout their cloud journey.</p>
  <h2 id="enhancing-methodologies">Enhancing Methodologies</h2>
  <p>We know the biggest challenge for any cloud transformation is to make the system landscape more agile and enable innovation — quickly. We’ve been listening and have introduced solutions. For example, our <strong><a href="/2024/04/transform-confidence-rise-with-sap-methodology">RISE with SAP Methodology</a></strong> is a significant step forward in creating a consistent experience for all RISE with SAP customers, independent of their individual cloud journeys. Now, a dedicated enterprise architect guides customers through the RISE with SAP Methodology to enhance onboarding and provides transparency throughout the project with key milestone checks, q-gates, and checklists that ensure consistent quality and more predictable timelines throughout the implementation process.</p>
  <p>This new offering is included in our <strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/rise.html#migration">SAP RISE Migration and Modernization</a></strong> program, which is designed to give customers the confidence to migrate even the most complex ERP systems to the cloud. By enabling our customers to integrate and extend SAP S/4HANA with a clean core approach, we ensure our customers experience better maintainability and lower total cost of ownership.​ Because legacy ERP systems often carry technical debt and, let’s face it, code is also a liability not just an asset. The more code you have, the more you have to optimize, debug, and modernize. And this is something we all need to actively work against.</p>
  <h2 id="introducing-partner-training-and-validation">Introducing Partner Training and Validation</h2>
  <p>We are also making it easier for RISE with SAP customers to identify partners to help with complex SAP S/4HANA Cloud transformations. It is essential for our partner ecosystem to follow the RISE with SAP Methodology as well. For customers to onboard successfully, there needs to be a close alignment between SAP, the customer, and implementation partner. This is why we are training and validating partners to use the RISE with SAP Methodology and will collaborate closely with partners to provide consistency and quality.</p>
  <p>We are also introducing the <strong>RISE with SAP Validated Partner</strong> recognition, which verifies a partner’s adherence to the RISE with SAP Methodology and our q-gates, giving businesses the confidence to know that they are fully leveraging the potential of cloud-based innovations from SAP. Almost 90% of all SAP implementations are overseen by partners, so training and validating them is a key part of our strategy to ensure consistency and quality for customers.</p>
  <h2 id="building-a-seamless-end-to-end-tool-chain">Building a Seamless End-to-End Tool Chain</h2>
  <p>As a former SAP CIO, I’ve felt the challenges (and pain) of large-scale transformation. I know the pressure CIOs are under to show tangible business outcomes quickly. It’s why true business transformation requires a holistic approach, not a simple technology lift and shift.</p>
  <p>We deliver the most complete business transformation suite in the industry. With the range of capabilities on offer today — including SAP Signavio, SAP LeanIX, and SAP Cloud ALM solutions as well as SAP Business Technology Platform — we have an amazing set of tools to bring out the best in businesses. Now, we are bringing them more closely together as one end-to-end seamless tool chain to make it easier to manage the process, system, and data landscape holistically.</p>
  <p>With our recently announced <a href="/2024/06/sap-enters-agreement-to-acquire-walkme">agreement to acquire <strong>WalkMe</strong></a>, we plan to further strengthen our ability to deliver successful business transformation across applications, processes, systems, and people. ​WalkMe will help us incorporate user-centric adoption, enablement, and productivity capabilities alongside our Business Transformation Management portfolio of SAP Signavio and SAP LeanIX solutions. And WalkMe’s AI capabilities will complement our process AI with user intelligence, improving the capabilities of our <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/ai-assistant.html">generative AI copilot Joule</a> to help people get work done faster.​</p>
  <h2 id="sap-business-ai-new-frontier-for-business-transformation">SAP Business AI: New Frontier for Business Transformation</h2>
  <p>In 2024, SAP Sapphire has been an opportunity for us to showcase how we are introducing in a new era of optimized business operations, with all the IT complexity concealed behind intuitive, AI-powered user experiences.</p>
  <p>We highlighted the progress we are making embedding Joule throughout our enterprise portfolio and the enormous potential we see for AI to support both customers and partners in their RISE with SAP journey. I was thrilled to announce that starting in Q4 of 2024, customers and partners can leverage generative AI-powered assistance for their RISE with SAP clean core success plan.</p>
  <p>We are also bringing new consulting capabilities to Joule, aimed at simplifying SAP implementations for partners. The new consulting capability draws insights from SAP product documentation and the SAP community to provide consultants with vital information and is planned to be available in the second half of this year.</p>
  <h2 id="business-transformation-more-than-an-it-project">Business Transformation: More Than an IT Project</h2>
  <p>At SAP, we understand that true business transformation is more than an IT project. It requires a holistic approach and not a simple technological lift and shift. That’s why we are putting the people, methodologies, financial incentives, tools, partner practices, and SAP Business AI in place to ensure our customers not only have compelling reasons to move to the cloud, but also a compelling experience.</p>
  <p><strong>Learn more:</strong></p>
  <ul>
    <li>Watch the replay of the <strong><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZZ1yFoALzAs">Customer Keynote at SAP Sapphire</a></strong></li>
    <li>Read all the announcements in the <strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/events/sapphire/news-guide.html">SAP Sapphire News Guide</a></strong></li>
  </ul>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Thomas Saueressig is a member of the Executive Board of SAP SE leading Customer Services &#x26; Delivery.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-news-and-coverage-from-sap-sapphire-in-2024">Get the latest news and coverage from SAP Sapphire in 2024</h3>
        <p><em><a href="/topics/sap-sapphire">Read more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/blog/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/blog/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/blog/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/blog/article-read-more</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/executive-blog</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>product/sap-leanix</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-signavio</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[RHI Magnesita Refines Technology Landscape with RISE with SAP]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/rhi-magnesita-refines-technology-landscape-rise-with-sap</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/rhi-magnesita-refines-technology-landscape-rise-with-sap</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn why RHI Magnesita, global leader in refractories, has chosen RISE with SAP to rebuild and streamline its technology infrastructure.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1352659f91be85216647ebf5e52a4aeba522c1850.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1352659f91be85216647ebf5e52a4aeba522c1850.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1352659f91be85216647ebf5e52a4aeba522c1850.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="RHI Magnesita Refines Technology Landscape with RISE with SAP" src="./media_1352659f91be85216647ebf5e52a4aeba522c1850.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="rhi-magnesita-refines-technology-landscape-with-rise-with-sap">RHI Magnesita Refines Technology Landscape with RISE with SAP</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>BARCELONA</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="https://www.sap.com/index.html">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) announced that RHI Magnesita (LSE: RHIM), has chosen the RISE with SAP solution to rebuild and streamline its technology infrastructure for continued growth in the refractory industry.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-sapphire-taking-business-to-the-next-level-in-the-era-of-ai">SAP Sapphire: Taking Business to the Next Level in the Era of AI</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/events/sapphire/news-guide.html">Read the news guide</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>A global leader in refractories, RHI Magnesita provides essential parts of the infrastructure that we use and need in our everyday lives. Supplying high-grade refractory products, systems and solutions, RHI Magnesita has 47 main production sites across the world, and ships its products to more than 100 countries.</p>
  <p>With its vision to sustainably manage heat to build a better world, RHI Magnesita needed a technology foundation that would allow end-to-end interaction across its customers, suppliers and business partners across all geographies, end markets and product lines. Choosing to implement a multi-tier landscape consisting of both SAP S/4HANA Cloud Private Edition and SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition, RHI Magnesita is now equipped to redefine all its technology processes and landscape.</p>
  <p>Ticiana Kobel, Executive VP Legal &#x26; Digital Transformation at RHI Magnesita, stated, “With the revamped digital landscape that we will shape together with SAP, RHI Magnesita will transform into a digitally fortified company, centered around our customers and driven by data. The transition to SAP S/4HANA Cloud marks a pivotal moment in RHI Magnesita’s journey toward unparalleled efficiency, agility, and innovation which will enable us to unlock real-time insights, streamline operations, and enhance decision-making across our global network.”</p>
  <p>With SAP S/4HANA Cloud, RHI Magnesita will have one unified view of its operations and supply chain, reducing its infrastructure footprint, and poises itself for better integration of future acquisitions while delivering cost savings.</p>
  <p>“RHI Magnesita is embarking on a true digital transformation that will see the streamlining of several landscapes that will allow it to leverage the cost savings, scalability and flexibility that comes with moving to the cloud,” said Alexander Klaeger, President of SAP MEE. “Already a leader in the industry, I’m excited to see RHI Magnesita use SAP S/4HANA Cloud to sustainably provide infrastructure the world needs.”</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="http://news.sap.com/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-news-and-coverage-from-sap-sapphire-in-2024">Get the latest news and coverage from SAP Sapphire in 2024</h3>
        <p><em><a href="/topics/sap-sapphire">Read more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><strong>Media Contacts:</strong><br>Elisabeth Wursche, +43 664 620 74 27, <a href="mailto:elisabeth.wursche@sap.com">elisabeth.wursche@sap.com</a>, CET<br>Lesa Plingen, +49 6227 76 9000, <a href="mailto:lesa.plingen@sap.com">lesa.plingen@sap.com</a>, CET<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>This document contains forward-looking statements, which are predictions, projections, or other statements about future events. These statements are based on current expectations, forecasts, and assumptions that are subject to risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results and outcomes to materially differ. Additional information regarding these risks and uncertainties may be found in our filings with the Securities and Exchange Commission, including but not limited to the risk factors section of SAP’s 2023 Annual Report on Form 20-F.<br>© 2024 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Roca Group Looks to the Future Through RISE with SAP]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/roca-group-looks-to-future-rise-with-sap</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/roca-group-looks-to-future-rise-with-sap</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn how Roca is leveraging the last SAP technology and innovations, including RISE with SAP, to boost its digital transformation.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16c0e3912183718e90a860d4272af02f88676684b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16c0e3912183718e90a860d4272af02f88676684b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_16c0e3912183718e90a860d4272af02f88676684b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Roca Group Looks to the Future Through RISE with SAP" src="./media_16c0e3912183718e90a860d4272af02f88676684b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="roca-group-looks-to-the-future-through-rise-with-sap">Roca Group Looks to the Future Through RISE with SAP</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>BARCELONA</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced that Roca Group, one of the world’s leading bathroom fixtures and design companies has selected SAP S/4HANA and the RISE with SAP solution as it embarks on its next phase of digital transformation, focused on integrating and standardizing its IT systems.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-sapphire-taking-business-to-the-next-level-in-the-era-of-ai">SAP Sapphire: Taking Business to the Next Level in the Era of AI</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/events/sapphire/news-guide.html">Read the news guide</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>A family-owned business with over 100 years of heritage, a presence in 170 markets, and more than 21,500 employees and nearly 80 factories globally, Roca Group had embraced digitalization to remain competitive and relevant in the dynamic sanitary industry. Having made several acquisitions over the years, Roca Group saw RISE with SAP as the ideal solution to consolidate various IT systems into one IT landscape. Roca’s decision in choosing SAP S/4HANA Cloud was driven by the desire to increase efficiency and the ability to make informed, real-time, data-driven business decisions.</p>
  <p>“Roca Group’s strategy is based on a long-term future vision supported by innovation, technology and sustainability,” said Albert Magrans, CEO of Roca Group. “Moving to SAP S/4HANA enables Roca to leverage the last technology and innovations of SAP software to boost our digital transformation. We are looking forward to faster execution speed, the enhancement of functionality with the Joule copilot, real-time analytics and further innovations from SAP and its ecosystem.”</p>
  <p>“Roca Group and SAP have collaborated closely for a number of years, with Roca trusting SAP with multiple SAP implementations,” said Manos Raptopoulos, VP of SAP Europe, Middle East and Africa. “Roca’s IT strategy is fully aligned with its business transformation with SAP solutions as an integral part of this strategy. Our close partnership allows our teams to have real-time insight into their business transformation, allowing for seamless integration of SAP solutions as they embark on their SAP S/4HANA Cloud journey.”</p>
  <p>In choosing SAP S/4HANA Cloud and various cloud solutions from SAP, such as SAP Customer Experience, SAP Ariba and SAP SuccessFactors solutions, Roca Group continues to be well-positioned to leverage SAP’s integrated suite of solutions that will enhance customer experience and potentially open up new business opportunities. In adopting a clean core approach, the group will have a single platform for its production centers and logistics platforms, tapping onto the SAP Integrated Business Planning for Supply Chain solution for demand and production planning, and the SAP Transportation Management application for transport management. With these solutions implemented, the operations already using them have seen a cubic capacity of their transports rise by 10%.</p>
  <p>Additionally, Roca plans to use SAP SuccessFactors to improve learning programs, manage global payroll and enhance the employee self-service portal through SAP’s suite of solutions in addition to travel expense management with SAP Concur solutions.</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="http://news.sap.com/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-news-and-coverage-from-sap-sapphire-in-2024">Get the latest news and coverage from SAP Sapphire in 2024</h3>
        <p><em><a href="/topics/sap-sapphire">Read more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><strong>Media Contacts:</strong><br>Belén Martinez, +34 914 567 220, <a href="mailto:belen.martinez@sap.com">belen.martinez@sap.com</a>, CET<br>Lesa Plingen, +49 6227 76 9000, <a href="mailto:lesa.plingen@sap.com">lesa.plingen@sap.com</a>, CET<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>This document contains forward-looking statements, which are predictions, projections, or other statements about future events. These statements are based on current expectations, forecasts, and assumptions that are subject to risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results and outcomes to materially differ. Additional information regarding these risks and uncertainties may be found in our filings with the Securities and Exchange Commission, including but not limited to the risk factors section of SAP’s 2023 Annual Report on Form 20-F.<br>© 2024 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Introduces a New Validation Recognition for Service Partners]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/new-rise-with-sap-validated-partner-recognition</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/new-rise-with-sap-validated-partner-recognition</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The new RISE with SAP Validated Partner SAP recognition helps customers with complex SAP ERP landscapes starting their journey.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a157e78734853652179498700d8b366ba88f70cd.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a157e78734853652179498700d8b366ba88f70cd.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1a157e78734853652179498700d8b366ba88f70cd.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Introduces a New Validation Recognition for Service Partners" src="./media_1a157e78734853652179498700d8b366ba88f70cd.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-introduces-a-new-validation-recognition-for-service-partners">SAP Introduces a New Validation Recognition for Service Partners</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Customers Can More Easily Identify Partners with Deep Expertise and Experience in Large and Complex RISE with SAP Implementations</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <table>
          <thead>
            <tr>
              <th>Text Large</th>
            </tr>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td>The <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/rise.html#migration">RISE with SAP Migration and Modernization program</a> helps bring renewed focus on the cloud transformation journey by enabling smooth, secure migration of on-premise SAP ERP Central Component (SAP ECC) and SAP S/4HANA customers to the cloud.</td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-sapphire-taking-business-to-the-next-level-in-the-era-of-ai">SAP Sapphire: Taking Business to the Next Level in the Era of AI</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/events/sapphire/news-guide.html">Read the news guide</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>One of the key pillars of the program is RISE with SAP Methodology. The methodology is designed to provide a consistent approach — from planning to go-live to ongoing operations and evolution — that can meet customers’ business transformation goals leveraging specific implementation stages and success KPIs.</p>
  <p>To support customers’ RISE with SAP transformations, SAP is <a href="https://www.sap.com/events/sapphire/news-guide/erp.html#sap-validated-partner-designation">training and validating partners to use RISE with SAP Methodology</a> and collaborating closely with these partners on quality and consistency. By following the methodology, customers can drive predictable timelines for implementations and provide progress transparency with key milestone assessments.</p>
  <p>SAP customers with complex SAP ERP landscapes starting their journey to RISE with SAP can now identify their ideal cloud transformation partner through the new <strong>RISE with SAP Validated Partner</strong> recognition.</p>
  <p>These select partners meet elevated capability and experience criteria for the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/rise.html">RISE with SAP offering</a>, have proven experience in large enterprise engagements, and demonstrate their implementation approach is aligned with <a href="/2024/04/transform-confidence-rise-with-sap-methodology">RISE with SAP Methodology</a>. Using this methodology, the validated partners can ensure customers are cloud compliant and innovation ready, with an accelerated time to value.</p>
  <p>Partners that have been validated as part of this program include Accenture, Capgemini, Deloitte, EY, IBM, Infosys, NTT DATA, and PwC.</p>
  <p>In addition to adhering to the principles of RISE with SAP Methodology, these validated partners complement it in several ways, such as by leveraging specialized tools, templates, architecture patterns, and pre-configured solutions that speed up transformation of our enterprise customers. Additional eligible partners will be validated in the second half of 2024.</p>
  <p>“Empowering our partners with RISE with SAP Methodology isn’t just about alignment; it’s about forging a standardized path to success,” said SAP Chief Partner Officer Karl Fahrbach. “By formalizing our engagement model, we reinforce a commitment to excellence, ensuring every project delivers with precision and consistency, driving unparalleled results for our most valued customers. Our partners can lead the way with our support, igniting a paradigm shift in how we approach innovation and collaboration.”</p>
  <p>Companies also have the option to leverage <a href="https://partnerfinder.sap.com/partnerNavigator?designation=rise&#x26;q=&#x26;queryType=partner">SAP Partner Finder</a> and the <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2022/06/426a3ea2-3f7e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Competency Framework</a> to find the expertise they need, no matter their business challenges, company size, industry, or location. Partners that have attained the essential level have met the minimum training and delivery requirements for delivering RISE with SAP implementations. This gives customers confidence that the partner has the necessary level of maturity and has demonstrated customer success through effective project delivery.</p>
  <p>RISE with SAP Validated partners are required to attain the expert level of multiple competencies, including RISE with SAP S/4HANA Cloud Private Edition, SAP Business Technology Platform, and SAP Business Process Transformation. These designated partners must also maintain bi-annual performance requirements and eligibility checks with a focus on clean core quality gates.</p>
  <p>For additional information regarding the <a href="/2024/01/rise-with-sap-migration-and-modernization-cloud-first-business-strategy">RISE with SAP Migration and Modernization program</a> and the importance of partners, read “<a href="https://community.sap.com/t5/enterprise-resource-planning-blogs-by-sap/partners-are-vital-to-your-company-s-success-when-transitioning-to-cloud/ba-p/13616168">Partners Are Vital to Your Company’s Success When Transitioning to Cloud ERP</a>.”</p>
  <p>Eric van Rossum is chief marketing officer for Cloud ERP at SAP.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-news-and-coverage-from-sap-sapphire-in-2024">Get the latest news and coverage from SAP Sapphire in 2024</h3>
        <p><em><a href="/topics/sap-sapphire">Read more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Four SAP Customers Are Successfully Driving Transformation in Their Businesses]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-sapphire-sap-customers-drive-business-transformation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-sapphire-sap-customers-drive-business-transformation</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In their SAP Sapphire keynote, Scott Russell and Thomas Saueressig talked to four customers about using SAP to deliver high-value results.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c4521f798d991573b94b36fd1f60cfe20d3399cf.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c4521f798d991573b94b36fd1f60cfe20d3399cf.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1c4521f798d991573b94b36fd1f60cfe20d3399cf.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="How Four SAP Customers Are Successfully Driving Transformation in Their Businesses" src="./media_1c4521f798d991573b94b36fd1f60cfe20d3399cf.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="how-four-sap-customers-are-successfully-driving-transformation-in-their-businesses">How Four SAP Customers Are Successfully Driving Transformation in Their Businesses</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>This week at SAP Sapphire, four industry-leading companies joined SAP Executive Board Members Scott Russell and Thomas Saueressig on stage in Orlando to discuss how they are using SAP technology to deliver high-value results for their businesses.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="taking-business-to-the-next-level-in-the-era-of-ai">Taking Business to the Next Level in the Era of AI</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/events/sapphire/news-guide.html">Read the news guide</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Russell told the crowd that customer stories and conversations is what SAP Sapphire is all about, saying that what makes the event special is having “a collective group that comes together, both here in the room and virtually, and being able to understand how SAP can bring out your best.”</p>
  <p>Russell emphasized that the news from SAP Sapphire is a “demonstration of our commitment to continually innovate, to continually strive to bring more creative value to your business.”</p>
  <p>He noted that a perfect example of this is the announcement that <a href="/2024/06/sap-enters-agreement-to-acquire-walkme">SAP has entered into an agreement to acquire WalkMe</a>, a leader in digital adoption platforms. Reflecting on the acquisition, Russell said “We are obsessed not only about great applications and great platforms to deliver value for your business, we also care passionately about the transformation journey to get there.”</p>
  <p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/live/ZZ1yFoALzAs?si=mbPWUzgttHga-_PR">Embed from www.youtube.com</a></p>
  <p>As Chief Revenue Officer, Russell noted that every day 300 million people log on to SAP cloud applications to run their businesses. “And obviously we can never take that for granted,” he said. “You have choice, you have options. We strive to be at our best to help you be at yours. The way we measure success is in your terms, because ultimately [as a] market leader in business AI, we hold ourselves to the highest standards. Why? Because that’s what you expect.”</p>
  <p>A big part of the transformation journey many customers are taking is moving to the cloud with RISE with SAP. “We are super proud of our cloud journey and [that] we are helping you transform your business,” Russell said. “More than 6,000 customers have already moved to RISE with SAP. Of those 6,000 customers in the last 12 months, over 1,000 have already gone live.”</p>
  <h2 id="puretech-scientific-speed-and-scalability-is-key">PureTech Scientific: Speed and Scalability is Key</h2>
  <p>Russell was first joined on stage by Brian Hardee, CIO of <a href="https://www.puretechscientific.com/">PureTech Scientific LLC</a>, a global leader in the production of glycolic acid used in a variety of industries and applications. As a recent carve-out by a private equity owner from a much larger global manufacturer, PureTech had to quickly migrate its operations to its own systems. But without an IT team of its own this was initially a daunting challenge. The new company chose SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition because of its many benefits.</p>
  <p>“For us, it was an easy choice because first, we have no IT team,” Hardee said. “We have no internal training team, and we also had a very tight timeline with respect to the exit. So, we needed a solution that would enable us to move forward with speed, efficiency, and scalability. I could be confident that the infrastructure was being managed and secure. And that left us with an awesome choice for growth as well.”</p>
  <p>Scalability and rapid implementation were key factors in the choice of GROW with SAP, Hardee noted: “It was a great fit and gave us a platform for scalability for future bolt-ons, acquisitions, and so forth. So that’s the main reason. And SAP has an awesome suite of tools that enable that rapid implementation. And there was no other way we were going to do it without an internal IT team and without the access to the training material and the testing and so on.”</p>
  <p>And speaking of rapid implementation, PureTech went live on SAP in just 15 weeks, standardizing a business with an 85-year history on a common platform. Hardee gave some advice on how to make a project successful: “Use the tool set that SAP provides – SAP Activate methodology does work! And if you have the opportunity, sign up for the SAP Preferred Success program because it gives you a direct line to someone in SAP so that if you or your integrator doesn’t know the answer, SAP can point you to the right direction very quickly. So that helps with the speed of transformation.”</p>
  <h2 id="tropicana-brands-group-all-about-agility-and-time">Tropicana Brands Group: All About Agility and Time</h2>
  <p>Tropicana is a household name to many consumers, known chiefly for its juice and other beverage products. But while the brand is more than 75 years old, <a href="https://www.tropicanabrandsgroup.com/">Tropicana Brands Group</a> is just a bit over two years old, having been recently spun-off as a stand-alone group.</p>
  <p>Jeff Lischett, CIO of the US$3 billion organization, joined Russell to talk about how his company relied on RISE with SAP to make its “Project Harvest” IT separation and transformation project successful.</p>
  <p>Lischett noted that speed and agility was the key value proposition for the project. “We needed a platform that was able to accelerate, move with us, pivot with us, as we were going through this in a very accelerated timeline,” he said. “When you bring the technology and couple it with the unified business architecture powered by SAP, the choice for us was clearly RISE with SAP. Tropicana really needed a fit for purpose. Where we came from was going to be entirely different than where we were going, and this modern ERP, in terms of leaner, simpler, more streamlined ways of working, was really at the core of what we needed across the value chain.”</p>
  <p>Tropicana Brands Group took its European business operations live on SAP just 11 months after it started the design work, followed by North America three months later. “That was pressure testing!” Lischett said. “In just over a year, we had a fully implemented, end-to-end digital core and technology foundation for Tropicana Brands. We have a technology and a platform now that is really going to – no pun intended – rise to meet the challenge of our growth ambition.”</p>
  <p>“Ruthless prioritization” and change management were key to the project’s success, Lischett said. “I’m the biggest evangelist and advocate of change management,” he said. “You need it. You need it at the front, you need it during, you need it at the end. One thing that I would’ve probably done slightly differently is [to have] stayed with it longer at the end.”</p>
  <p>Tropicana is already seeing the impact of the project and specifically its focus on a clean core. “The most impactful value we’ve seen [goes] back to that clean core,” Lischett said. “Just in the months that followed, the ability to … bring the development forward, to build on top of the core that we have with enhancements and optimizing at a speed ratio that you just haven’t seen.”</p>
  <p>When asked about what role AI will play in his company, Lischett focused mainly on the human side of the technology. “Ironically, from the standpoint of being a technologist … AI in my mind, in terms of how I lead it, [needs to be] human-centered first and foremost, ensuring that we’ve got the right culture, responsible use, and effective use,” he said. “The gift of time is really the value creator that I see in AI and being able to work more efficiently and being able to take that time and translate it into what matters to you.”</p>
  <h2 id="responsibly-enabling-critical-systems">Responsibly Enabling Critical Systems</h2>
  <p>Russell handed over the stage to Saueressig, who recently launched the <a href="/2024/04/cloud-transformation-adoption-revolution-expectations-outcomes-meet">new Customer Services &#x26; Delivery Board area</a>. Saueressig noted that 25% of the world’s commerce already runs through more than 6,000 RISE with SAP customers worldwide, and that SAP supports the most critical business processes on the planet.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <picture>
          <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1dc5f09272052858aaeb01a0eec06423efb162249.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
          <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1dc5f09272052858aaeb01a0eec06423efb162249.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
          <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1dc5f09272052858aaeb01a0eec06423efb162249.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
          <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_1dc5f09272052858aaeb01a0eec06423efb162249.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="683">
        </picture>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>With that comes “the responsibility and the accountability to provide you with the most reliable and secure infrastructure,” Saueressig said. “That’s the reason why we co-engineered together with our partners from AWS, Microsoft Azure, Google Cloud Platform, and many others, to ensure that you have the highest level of quality and availability.”</p>
  <p>Echoing the theme of speed and adaptability, he noted that fast adoption of technology is critical. “Today, it’s not about the big fish that eats the small fish, it’s about the fast fish that eats the slow,” he cited. “At the end of the day, [our] ambition is to transform your system landscape to create a more flexible architecture, which enables fast adoption of innovations and ultimately, value realization. … And we take our responsibility seriously to really help you thrive in this ever-changing environment.”</p>
  <h2 id="fresenius-se-from-complexity-to-standardization">Fresenius SE: From Complexity to Standardization</h2>
  <p>Ingo Elfering, CIO of global healthcare conglomerate <a href="https://www.fresenius.com/">Fresenius</a>, knows something about speed: his team migrated 29 system landscapes containing more than 134 systems in less than 15 months. He joined Saueressig on stage to provide some insights into his company’s transformation project.</p>
  <p>As a company that has grown through many acquisitions, Fresenius had a highly heterogenous IT landscape. “We never quite integrated them,” Elfering said. “So, a really complex landscape …, [with] all sorts of interfaces and other applications attached to it. That was our starting point.”</p>
  <p>Fresenius’ management realized the company needed to change and become more efficient and effective to set itself up for ongoing success. It went all-in, doing four major transformations at the same time. As Elfering noted, “We not only did the RISE with SAP migration, we also did a complete cloud migration of our data centers worldwide; an outsourcing with a partner to become a more global team; and a global change of our network, including a whole bunch of security additions into our space.”</p>
  <p>Since it works in the healthcare and pharmaceutical space, Fresenius has a lot of regulatory requirements that it must adhere to, making the project more challenging than it might be in other industries. “You do a lot more technical documentation, testing, and so forth. So, from that perspective, regulations like GxP, good manufacturing or critical infrastructure, they were new to SAP in that instance in RISE with SAP. And we did it together. And I find that quite remarkable.”</p>
  <p>The <a href="/2023/06/fresenius-rise-with-sap-moves-sap-systems-cloud">new system has now been live</a> for just over a year and the company has seen many benefits. “We have a better speed on the underlying systems,” Elfering said. “We have a new infrastructure stack that works well. The main benefit for us will come as we [reinvent] the company. … We have some systems that doubled and tripled in size. So, it’s possible to leverage SAP quite quickly in these types of environments. From that perspective, I’m very happy with where we are. … We now have all the foundations in place to be able to execute our next phase of changes, our consolidation, our simplification, and in the cloud.”</p>
  <p>Finally, Elfering believes that healthcare is an area where AI can make a significant difference. “Healthcare always has been data-rich and insights-poor. … And the only way to get there, in our opinion at least, is to be on a cloud-based infrastructure in the first place. Because otherwise you don’t have the same performance or capabilities.”</p>
  <h2 id="clean-core-drives-agility">Clean Core Drives Agility</h2>
  <p>The idea of a “clean core” and a unified, simplified system underlies all these customer transformation stories. And it’s even more important in the context of agility and adaptability when it comes to taking advantage of the latest innovations in AI.</p>
  <p>“It’s super important for us to be clear that the clean core is not just for the sake of the clean core,” Saueressig said. “It’s a means to get to an innovation- and upgrade-ready system to be able to embrace these innovations. Because at the end of the day, legacy systems often have this technical depth that limits agility.”</p>
  <p>Saueressig admitted that even SAP has struggled with this, noting that the company had millions of lines of custom code in its systems. An internal analysis of all SAP customers showed that more than 65% of their custom code was unused in the past 12 months. “Code is also a liability, not just an asset,” he said. “And this is something we need to actively work against.”</p>
  <h2 id="hitachi-high-tech-corporation-clean-and-simple-benefits">Hitachi High-Tech Corporation: Clean and Simple Benefits</h2>
  <p>Saueressig invited Takuya Sakai, general manager of the Digital Transformation Business Group at <a href="https://www.hitachi-hightech.com/">Hitachi High-Tech</a>, on the stage to talk more about the benefits of system simplification and clean core. In 2019, Hitachi High-Tech <a href="https://www.sap.com/asset/dynamic/2023/07/d237f8b9-7e7e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">initiated a project</a> to simplify its business processes and digitize its management information. With its existing business processes fragmented across overseas sales offices, headquarters, and manufacturing sites, the organization needed to change to accelerate its business and set itself up for future growth. It chose SAP S/4HANA to help it build its new foundation for ongoing growth.</p>
  <p>Hitachi was running SAP R/3 but had significantly customized it with 9,000 add-ons across four instances, resulting in a lot of custom code. This resulted in many errors every day and large operational costs every year, Sakai said. And with the cost of validating so many add-ons, the company only did a major version update once in 12 years.</p>
  <p>To move to a more standardized and flexible system, Hitachi High-Tech adopted a two-tier architecture model. Taking advantage of development flexibility, the company deployed SAP S/4HANA Cloud Private Edition for its headquarters and group companies in Japan and SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition for its overseas sales offices. The adoption of SAP S/4HANA Cloud allows Hitachi High-Tech to take advantage of the functionality offered by SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP) for application development, data management, automation, integration, analytics, and AI.</p>
  <p>With the new system, Hitachi High-Tech reduced its 9,000 add-ons to just 750, allowing it to easily upgrade its ERP core. “Upgrading our old ERP took about a year and a half from the planning stage,” Sakai said. “However, with clean core, we can now do an upgrade every year in about 40 days. An upgrade every year keeps the clean core fresh and means new features can be delivered to our business quickly, like AI or process automation.”</p>
  <p>But achieving – and keeping – a clean core “requires patience,” Sakai said. Executives must understand the purpose of the transformation project and employees must overcome the pain that comes with a transformation project. “This is the most difficult thing,” he said. “The IT department must properly understand the new technology and suggest how to use it correctly. Then together we embark on the journey to the transformation.”</p>
  <h2 id="supporting-business-transformation-and-accelerating-time-to-value">Supporting Business Transformation and Accelerating Time to Value</h2>
  <p>Accelerating and improving time-to-value for customers is very important to SAP, according to Saueressig.</p>
  <p>“We are now bringing together all of our assets … in a seamless, end-to-end tool chain,” he said. “We want to holistically support your business transformation according to the dimensions of applications, data, processes, and people, which means we bring together and fully integrate SAP LeanIX for the IT landscapes and architecture, SAP Signavio for process management, SAP Cloud Application Lifecycle Management for application management and operational aspects, SAP BTP for integrations, and SAP Build for extensions, but also our telemetry tools, which we can leverage in the cloud.”</p>
  <p>Saueressig’s passion and ambition is to help customers drive innovation adoption. He noted that RISE with SAP is more than just a technical migration: it’s an offering for holistic business transformation as a service to accelerate value realization.</p>
  <p>“Ultimately, we want to help you to bring the best out of our entire holistic portfolio,” he said. “We want to help you to transform, realize agility at scale, achieve more across the entire value chain, and fundamentally transform operations with sustainability at the core. And this is something where I feel that we have a huge opportunity together to make that a reality.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-news-and-coverage-from-sap-sapphire-in-2024">Get the latest news and coverage from SAP Sapphire in 2024</h3>
        <p><em><a href="/topics/sap-sapphire">Read more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/grow-with-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[End-to-End Innovation Is Key to Bringing Out Your Best]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-sapphire-innovation-key-to-bring-out-your-best</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-sapphire-innovation-key-to-bring-out-your-best</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In their keynote, Juergen Mueller and Muhammad Alam demoed and discussed the latest innovations out of SAP Sapphire in 2024.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e38256295162fd6aa4582f624a1a9f11f0f8543b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e38256295162fd6aa4582f624a1a9f11f0f8543b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1e38256295162fd6aa4582f624a1a9f11f0f8543b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="End-to-End Innovation Is Key to Bringing Out Your Best" src="./media_1e38256295162fd6aa4582f624a1a9f11f0f8543b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="end-to-end-innovation-is-key-to-bringing-out-your-best">End-to-End Innovation Is Key to Bringing Out Your Best</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>In their SAP Sapphire Orlando keynote, Executive Board Members Muhammad Alam, SAP Product Engineering, and Juergen Mueller, chief technology officer, shared how the latest SAP innovations will help businesses drive true, end-to-end digital transformation and address their toughest business challenges.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="taking-business-to-the-next-level-in-the-era-of-ai">Taking Business to the Next Level in the Era of AI</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/events/sapphire/news-guide.html">Read the news guide</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In the keynote, which featured several real-world product demos by SAP employees, Alam and Mueller touted the value of SAP’s best-of-breed solutions with an outlook of what the next 50 years of innovation by SAP may look like.</p>
  <p>Who better to inspire the keynote than Hasso Plattner, co-founder and recently retired chairman of the SAP Supervisory Board, who both Alam and Mueller invoked during the session. To spell out SAP’s legacy and vision for the future, Mueller quoted <a href="/2024/05/hasso-plattner-olaf-scholz-farewell-tributes">Plattner’s farewell message</a>: “Keep innovating, keep pushing boundaries, and keep making a difference in the lives of our customers and the world at large.”</p>
  <h2 id="keep-innovating">Keep Innovating</h2>
  <p>To kick off his first SAP Sapphire appearance as the head of SAP Product Engineering, Alam began by describing the importance of harnessing innovation to deliver an end-to-end picture across all business functions and unlock true value.</p>
  <p>Simply put, businesses exist to build and deliver products and services to customers, he explained. But the materials, assets, people, and processes that come together to achieve this task is far from simple. “The reality is that each part of the business is deeply and intricately connected to all the others,” Alam said, meaning a pain point in one area impacts the rest. That’s why SAP’s modular cloud ERP approach is so successful: “We allow our customers to drive true digital transformation as opposed to running systems integration projects disguised as digital transformation,” he added.</p>
  <p>Alam presented <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/grow.html">GROW with SAP</a> as an example of this composability and extensibility, as it can work for and scale to many sizes and types of business. And now, SAP Sales Cloud and Concur Expense are natively integrated into GROW with SAP, making the offering even more comprehensive. Sinit Foto, product manager for UX, Cloud ERP at SAP, joined Alam on stage to show how GROW with SAP and SAP Business AI can help achieve integrated processes, demoing use cases such as communicating with customers about sales quotes, creating expense reports, and supporting financial analyses. In fact, Alam announced that SAP is implementing the demoed application internally to manage sales worldwide. And Mueller emphasized: “We are committed to helping you in this transformative AI moment by creating business outcomes that were unthinkable before. That’s why we’re embedding SAP Business AI deeply in our processes and analytics.”</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <picture>
          <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ab1b55bf13f95fe3a6b47084f96d918d20d0b6d4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
          <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ab1b55bf13f95fe3a6b47084f96d918d20d0b6d4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
          <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1ab1b55bf13f95fe3a6b47084f96d918d20d0b6d4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
          <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_1ab1b55bf13f95fe3a6b47084f96d918d20d0b6d4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="683">
        </picture>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="keep-pushing">Keep Pushing</h2>
  <p>AI was woven throughout the entire keynote, with both Alam and Mueller discussing <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence.html">SAP’s strategy and product enhancements in this space</a>. AI must be high value, easy to adopt into the flow of work, and trustworthy for it to truly transform how we do business, Alam said. “Equally important is whether it’s done in a way where it keeps your data secure and private – and is executed in a responsible manner,” he added. “And that is really the core promise of SAP Business AI.”</p>
  <p>There’s no doubt that AI is a powerful technology, which is why it’s essential that businesses view it as a “responsibility” not just an “opportunity,” Alam said. Megan Fife, executive solution advisor for SAP SuccessFactors, showed how SAP executes on its responsible, reliable, and relevant business AI by demoing how SAP’s AI copilot Joule in SAP SuccessFactors HCM can help fill skills gaps and collaborate across teams, among other meaningful tasks. Key to this endeavor is <a href="/2024/06/joule-microsoft-copilot-unified-work-experience">SAP’s expanded partnership with Microsoft announced earlier in the day</a>, which Scott Guthrie, executive vice president of Cloud and AI at Microsoft, discussed with Alam on stage.</p>
  <p>Mueller echoed the importance of responsible AI, saying that the technology depends highly on data that is reliable and that allows customers to look at their business end-to-end. Here, SAP Datasphere and SAP Spend Control Tower – which was demoed by Orla Cullen, product marketing manager for Data and Analytics at SAP – can help simplify data management and view and manage spend and sustainability data holistically.</p>
  <p>This transformation is supported by <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform.html">SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP)</a>, and Mueller demonstrated the newest generative AI features in SAP Analytics Cloud, SAP Integration Suite, and SAP Build solutions. He showed how Joule can help create and summarize financial reports for controlling teams; generate integration flows between SAP and non-SAP applications; and create custom skills and content based on specific business needs. Greater insights, faster reaction times, and increased productivity are the result. Soon, Mueller added, it will even be possible to enhance and extend Joule’s knowledge by creating custom skills using SAP Build and having the copilot interact with data housed in SAP and non-SAP systems, helping businesses run even more efficiently.</p>
  <p>SAP BTP is the key to being “innovation-ready,” maintaining a clean core, and tailoring standard offerings to unique needs, Mueller explained. More than 24,000 companies running live on SAP BTP, including Blue Diamond Growers and Lufthansa Technik, can attest to this.</p>
  <p>“SAP BTP’s extensibility and enterprise automation capabilities can help businesses turn process insights into actual improvements,” Mueller said. Cecilia Huergo, product manager for SAP BTP, showed this in her demo on how identifying improvement opportunities, realizing needed changes while maintaining a clean core, and gaining an up-to-date view of your IT landscape can be enabled with the combined power of SAP Signavio solutions, SAP LeanIX,, SAP BTP, and ABAP Cloud.</p>
  <h2 id="keep-making-a-difference">Keep Making a Difference</h2>
  <p>The innovations demoed and discussed in Alam and Mueller’s keynote, in addition to <a href="/2024/06/sap-sapphire-news-business-ai-enterprise-cloud-portfolio-cutting-edge-partnerships">the many others announced at SAP Sapphire in 2024</a>, are just the latest steps forward in SAP’s journey to bringing out the best in its customers. “The future is here, and it’s defined by those who innovate first,” Mueller said. “And we are here to give you the right tools at hand, such that you can be a leader not just today, but also tomorrow.”</p>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d468a3b0b7b4a96babee63b887b0c66d1bdc61b2.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d468a3b0b7b4a96babee63b887b0c66d1bdc61b2.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1d468a3b0b7b4a96babee63b887b0c66d1bdc61b2.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Why AI Means Being In The Cloud" src="./media_1d468a3b0b7b4a96babee63b887b0c66d1bdc61b2.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://youtu.be/EnxihshouTE">Why AI Means Being In The Cloud</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Gillian Hixson is an integrated communications specialist at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-news-and-coverage-from-sap-sapphire-in-2024">Get the latest news and coverage from SAP Sapphire in 2024</h3>
        <p><em><a href="/topics/sap-sapphire">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/grow-with-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP's New AI Innovations and Partnerships Deliver Real-World Results]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/ai-innovations-partnerships-sap-sapphire</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/ai-innovations-partnerships-sap-sapphire</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Explore the AI capabilities and ecosystem innovations presented at SAP Sapphire in 2024, all aimed at delivering real-world results.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>news-topic/financial-management</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/abap-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/accenture</category>
            <category>news-tag/ai-ethics</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/aws</category>
            <category>news-tag/bcg</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Generative AI Innovations Take Center Stage at SAP Sapphire in 2024]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-sapphire-generative-ai-center-stage</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-sapphire-generative-ai-center-stage</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A series of generative AI innovations and partnerships announced at SAP Sapphire showcase how SAP is taking business to the next level.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_183c39d6e19efd7774c87954a8bbf7838320ef779.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_183c39d6e19efd7774c87954a8bbf7838320ef779.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_183c39d6e19efd7774c87954a8bbf7838320ef779.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Generative AI Innovations Take Center Stage at SAP Sapphire in 2024" src="./media_183c39d6e19efd7774c87954a8bbf7838320ef779.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="generative-ai-innovations-take-center-stage-at-sap-sapphire-in-2024">Generative AI Innovations Take Center Stage at SAP Sapphire in 2024</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>SAP CEO Christian Klein kicked off SAP Sapphire this week with an upbeat keynote that highlighted the company’s latest business AI innovations, products, and partnerships, which he said will change how people work.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="taking-business-to-the-next-level-in-the-era-of-ai">Taking Business to the Next Level in the Era of AI</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/events/sapphire/news-guide.html">Read the news guide</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“This year is a very special Sapphire,” Klein said. “We are entering a new phase of AI, with endless possibilities for us all.”</p>
  <p>Klein and Chief Marketing and Solutions Officer Julia White used the keynote to outline how AI will deliver real business benefits for different corporate functions and “Bring Out Your Best,” this year’s event theme.</p>
  <h2 id="delivering-on-an-ai-promise">Delivering on an AI Promise</h2>
  <p>Klein emphasized how SAP has delivered on its promise to infuse generative AI throughout its business portfolio, has enabled customers to exploit the potential of business AI, and has positioned the Joule copilot as the new front end for SAP applications.</p>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11a9e312c5b8efe848ea7622ac6bcc8c38c9e5913.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11a9e312c5b8efe848ea7622ac6bcc8c38c9e5913.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_11a9e312c5b8efe848ea7622ac6bcc8c38c9e5913.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Sapphire Opening Keynote: Bring Out the Best in Your Business | 2024" src="./media_11a9e312c5b8efe848ea7622ac6bcc8c38c9e5913.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://youtu.be/gOVQhhm5yO0?si=wkpDopYq0gPK6kWn">SAP Sapphire Opening Keynote: Bring Out the Best in Your Business | 2024</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Together, the two also announced the next evolution and new capabilities in both RISE with SAP and GROW with SAP. Since it was launched over three years ago, more than 6,000 customers have selected RISE with SAP. During his keynote, Klein announced that RISE with SAP will now include a dedicated enterprise architect to guide customers through the RISE with SAP Methodology as well as an integrated tool chain to help manage the process, system, and data landscape holistically across the RISE with SAP life cycle.</p>
  <p>Meanwhile White, broadcasting live from the central showcase on the SAP Sapphire show floor, announced that cloud ERP offering GROW with SAP will now include SAP Sales Cloud and Concur Expense at no additional charge. Whether its managing your finances or managing your expenses, GROW with SAP has you covered, she said.</p>
  <h2 id="ai-momentum">AI Momentum</h2>
  <p>Building on SAP’s business AI momentum, Klein and White also announced a series of expanded partnerships to help companies make the most out of this decisive AI moment. The expanded partnerships include deals with Amazon Web Services (AWS) and Google Cloud. Klein also announced the integration of Microsoft 365 Copilot with Joule, delivering what he described as a “truly differentiated employee experience.”</p>
  <p>Together onstage with customers and SAP Chief AI Officer Philipp Herzig, they showcased how SAP is infusing generative AI throughout the application portfolio and enabling customers to thrive in the AI era.</p>
  <p>“The business AI innovations we’re announcing will not only change how people work with SAP solutions, but how people work overall,” said Klein ahead of his keynote address.</p>
  <h2 id="new-joule-capabilities">New Joule Capabilities</h2>
  <p>Klein announced Joule for consulting capabilities and Joule for ABAP developer capabilities, which will help SAP’s 6-million-strong consultant and developer community to accelerate projects by 30% and implement SAP solutions faster than ever before.</p>
  <p>During his keynote he described business AI as being “an inflection point” and added, “Today’s AI announcements and partnerships build on our commitment to deliver revolutionary technology that drives real-world results, helping customers unleash the agility and ingenuity they need to succeed in today’s fast-moving business landscape.”</p>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16cdfc9fd1fdbbf5cdc9cd5193401b9dfcafd1805.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16cdfc9fd1fdbbf5cdc9cd5193401b9dfcafd1805.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_16cdfc9fd1fdbbf5cdc9cd5193401b9dfcafd1805.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Why Joule Will Change the Way You Work" src="./media_16cdfc9fd1fdbbf5cdc9cd5193401b9dfcafd1805.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://youtu.be/a9j2Q6VVCfM?si=9cdzuqQ27TZ_J3uj">Why Joule Will Change the Way You Work</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“SAP is the only tech company who can infuse AI capabilities right into your business processes and workflows,” he said, saluting the achievements of the 40,000 SAP employees in the Product Development organization.</p>
  <h2 id="shout-out-to-sap-developers">Shout Out to SAP Developers</h2>
  <p>“No other tech company can offer a more powerful platform to transform enterprises to rewrite how business is run.” SAP developers have transformed SAP’s portfolio “from an ERP system that enabled transactions in real time, to a system with modular applications and embedded AI so that you can run intelligent, connected, and sustainable enterprises.”</p>
  <p>“We promised this to you, and we delivered,” Klein told audiences online and the 14,000 customers and partners attending SAP Sapphire in person this week in Orlando. “Now we are using the power of generative AI across our stack to once again revolutionize how businesses run and end users will work in the future.”</p>
  <p>After announcing generative AI copilot Joule in September 2023, Klein confirmed that it will become the new front-end and UX for SAP applications and “will turn your words into action.” Joule is ready for prime time, he declared, “and going forward, it will be embedded out of the box for all our cloud customers.”</p>
  <h2 id="joule-key-to-higher-productivity">Joule: Key to Higher Productivity</h2>
  <p>He predicted that Joule will also become the biggest productivity engine for every SAP end user, and that by the end of the year, 80% of the most used tasks will be managed via Joule and the 300 million end users of SAP products will be 20% more productive.</p>
  <p>While AI is a powerful technology facilitating huge opportunities for business and employees, the SAP CEO emphasized that it is also crucial to offer responsible AI. To that end, he announced that SAP is among the first tech companies to adhere to UNESCO’s AI principles.</p>
  <p>Klein wrapped up the keynote by emphasizing that SAP does not view AI as an end in itself, but rather as a tool to help the world run better and improve people’s lives. “You have my commitment that we will continue to listen to your needs, we will continue to deliver great innovations and we will continue to deliver great outcomes for your company.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-news-and-coverage-from-sap-sapphire-in-2024">Get the latest news and coverage from SAP Sapphire in 2024</h3>
        <p><em><a href="/topics/sap-sapphire">Read more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP and Accenture Collaborate on Getting to Value Faster with SAP Business AI]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/accenture-sap-sapphire-business-ai</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/accenture-sap-sapphire-business-ai</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP and Accenture are working together to help their customers make SAP Business AI and data their No. 1 competitive advantage.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/accenture</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>product/sap-leanix</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-signavio</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Infuses Business AI Throughout Its Enterprise Cloud Portfolio and Partners with Cutting-Edge AI Leaders to Bring Out Customers’ Best]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-sapphire-news-business-ai-enterprise-cloud-portfolio-cutting-edge-partnerships</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-sapphire-news-business-ai-enterprise-cloud-portfolio-cutting-edge-partnerships</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New SAP Business AI innovations and collaborations with partners are igniting ingenuity. Read the news from SAP Sapphire Orlando in 2024.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18ff27978e1178b1dce994986e74f4cc1f6087f26.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18ff27978e1178b1dce994986e74f4cc1f6087f26.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_18ff27978e1178b1dce994986e74f4cc1f6087f26.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Infuses Business AI Throughout Its Enterprise Cloud Portfolio and Partners with Cutting-Edge AI Leaders to Bring Out Customers’ Best" src="./media_18ff27978e1178b1dce994986e74f4cc1f6087f26.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-infuses-business-ai-throughout-its-enterprise-cloud-portfolio-and-partners-with-cutting-edge-ai-leaders-to-bring-out-customers-best">SAP Infuses Business AI Throughout Its Enterprise Cloud Portfolio and Partners with Cutting-Edge AI Leaders to Bring Out Customers’ Best</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>SAP Business AI Innovations and Collaborations with Partners including Google Cloud, Meta, Microsoft, Mistral AI and NVIDIA Ignite Ingenuity</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <table>
          <thead>
            <tr>
              <th>Text Large</th>
            </tr>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td><strong><em>ORLANDO</em></strong> — At its annual SAP Sapphire conference, SAP unveiled generative AI innovations and partnerships that showcase how the company is taking business to the next level in the era of AI.</td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="taking-business-to-the-next-level-in-the-era-of-ai">Taking Business to the Next Level in the Era of AI</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/events/sapphire/news-guide.html">Read the news guide</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>By infusing Business AI across an enterprise cloud portfolio that powers the world’s most mission-critical processes and partnering with companies pushing the edge of what’s possible with AI, SAP is igniting a new wave of insight and ingenuity in global business.</p>
  <p>“The Business AI innovations we’re announcing at SAP Sapphire in 2024 will redefine the way businesses run,” says Christian Klein, CEO and member of the Executive Board of SAP SE. “Today’s AI announcements and partnerships build on our commitment to deliver revolutionary technology that drives real-world results, helping customers unleash the agility and ingenuity they need to succeed in today’s fast-moving business landscape.”</p>
  <h2 id="ai-that-means-business">AI That Means Business</h2>
  <p>As SAP embeds Business AI across its enterprise solutions, it puts rich insights at users’ fingertips, empowering them to deliver better outcomes and elevate the creative problem-solving humans do best. Examples include AI-generated reports in SAP SuccessFactors solutions that give people managers responsibly sourced insights for compensation-related discussions as well as forecasting capabilities in SAP Sales Cloud solutions that predict combinations of salespeople and products most likely to drive sales. Meanwhile, the SAP Business Technology Platform is adding large language models from Amazon Web Services, Meta and Mistral AI to its generative AI hub. This capability in the SAP AI Core infrastructure makes it easier to build generative AI use cases for SAP applications.</p>
  <p>SAP’s generative AI copilot Joule, which quickly sorts and contextualizes data from multiple systems to advance automation and improve decision-making, is expanding throughout the company’s solution portfolio. Joule launched in <a href="/2023/09/joule-new-generative-ai-assistant">SAP SuccessFactors solutions last fall</a> and is now embedded into SAP S/4HANA Cloud solutions and others including SAP Build and SAP Integration Suite. Further expansion by year-end will include SAP Ariba and SAP Analytics Cloud solutions. At Sapphire, SAP also announced <a href="/">plans to further broaden Joule’s scope</a> by integrating it with Microsoft Copilot to surface even richer insights. This deep, bi-directional integration gives users a unified experience built right into the flow of work, enabling seamless access to information from interactions with business applications in SAP and Microsoft 365.</p>
  <p>Reflecting Business AI’s increasing importance, SAP is redoubling its commitment to the principles of relevant, reliable, and responsible AI it pioneered. At Sapphire, SAP is adopting the 10 guiding principles of the UNESCO Recommendation on the Ethics of Artificial Intelligence, which aim to ensure that AI technologies are developed and used in ways that respect human rights, promote fairness and contribute to sustainable development.</p>
  <h2 id="partnerships-that-scale-innovation">Partnerships That Scale Innovation</h2>
  <p>SAP is partnering with best-in-class technology leaders to push the limits of what generative AI can do at an enterprise level. In addition to our expanded collaborations with <a href="/2024/05/aws-sap-generative-ai-new-innovation">AWS</a> and Microsoft, partnerships with Google Cloud, Meta, Mistral AI and NVIDIA ensure SAP can harness the power of AI-ready technology to innovate at speed and deliver richer real-world results.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Google Cloud</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP and Google Cloud are expanding their partnership, using Business AI to help enterprises better predict and mitigate supply-chain risks to minimize disruptions and maintain optimal inventory levels. The companies will integrate Joule and the SAP Integrated Business Planning for Supply Chain solution with Google Cloud’s Gemini models AI assistant and Google Cloud Cortex Framework’s data foundation.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Meta</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP will leverage Meta Llama 3 to generate scripts that render highly customized analytics applications in SAP Analytics Cloud. Meta’s next-generation AI model excels at language nuances and contextual understanding, making it an ideal candidate for translating enterprise business requirements into tangible outcomes.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Mistral AI</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP will also add <a href="/">new large language models from Mistral AI</a>, a global company headquartered in Paris specializing in generative AI, to the generative AI hub capability in SAP AI Core.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>NVIDIA</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP and NVIDIA Corporation advance a <a href="https://blogs.nvidia.com/blog/sap-sapphire-ai-omniverse/">cross-product partnership</a> to embed cutting-edge technologies into enterprise-ready business applications:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>As SAP trains Joule to serve as an AI assistant for the RISE with SAP solution implementations, NVIDIA’s state-of-the-art AI models sift through SAP consulting assets to provide relevant and precise answers to implementation-related questions;</li>
    <li>As SAP embeds Joule in the ABAP Cloud model to generate ABAP code for SAP developers, NVIDIA’s accelerated infrastructure will run, scale, and manage SAP’s generative AI model for ABAP code generation;</li>
    <li>As SAP infuses generative AI into the SAP Intelligent Product Recommendation solution, NVIDIA Omniverse Cloud APIs enable the simulation of complex manufacturing products and configurations as industrial digital twins.</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="cloud-technology-that-drives-agility-and-sustainability">Cloud Technology That Drives Agility and Sustainability</h2>
  <p>Business success in the era of AI means being in the cloud. SAP is making the move easier than ever with initiatives that help customers find partners with the expertise needed for complex SAP S/4HANA Cloud transformations. Further cloud innovations at SAP Sapphire include features that help the world’s organizations measure, manage and execute their sustainability strategies. SAP Sustainability Control Tower and SAP Sustainability Footprint Management solutions now track carbon footprints at scale and help businesses meet regulatory standards.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><a href="https://www.sap.com/events/sapphire/news-guide.html">Learn more in the 2024 SAP Sapphire News Guide</a>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Visit the <a href="/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-news-and-coverage-from-sap-sapphire-in-2024">Get the latest news and coverage from SAP Sapphire in 2024</h3>
        <p><em><a href="/topics/sap-sapphire">Read more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>About SAP</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As a global leader in enterprise applications and business AI, SAP (NYSE:SAP) stands at the nexus of business and technology. For over 50 years, organizations have trusted SAP to bring out their best by uniting business-critical operations spanning finance, procurement, HR, supply chain, and customer experience. For more information, visit <a href="http://www.sap.com">www.sap.com</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Note to editors:</strong><br>To preview and download broadcast-standard stock footage and press photos digitally, please visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/photos">www.sap.com/photos</a>. On this platform, you can find high resolution material for your media channels.</p>
  <p><strong>For customers interested in learning more about SAP products:</strong><br>Global Customer Center: +49 180 534-34-24<br>United States Only: 1 (800) 872-1SAP (1-800-872-1727)</p>
  <p><strong>For more information, press only:</strong><br>Joellen Perry, +1 (650) 445-6780, <a href="mailto:joellen.perry@sap.com">joellen.perry@sap.com</a> PT<br>Marcus Winkler, +49 6227-767497, <a href="mailto:marcus.winkler@sap.com">marcus.winkler@sap.com</a> CET<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>This document contains forward-looking statements, which are predictions, projections, or other statements about future events. These statements are based on current expectations, forecasts, and assumptions that are subject to risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results and outcomes to materially differ. Additional information regarding these risks and uncertainties may be found in our filings with the Securities and Exchange Commission, including but not limited to the risk factors section of SAP’s 2023 Annual Report on Form 20-F.<br>© 2024 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.<br>Please consider our <a href="https://www.sap.com/corporate/en/legal/privacy.html">privacy policy</a>. If you receive this press release in your e-mail and you wish to unsubscribe to our mailing list please contact <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a> and write Unsubscribe in the subject line.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/abap-cloud</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-sales-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-footprint-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[AWS and SAP Unlock New Innovation with Generative AI]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/aws-sap-generative-ai-new-innovation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/aws-sap-generative-ai-new-innovation</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP and AWS are making it easier for customers to embed generative AI into their entire portfolio of business-critical applications.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_104d1ffe68c31e9f2e51bfd7af2878774eaaff54a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_104d1ffe68c31e9f2e51bfd7af2878774eaaff54a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_104d1ffe68c31e9f2e51bfd7af2878774eaaff54a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="AWS and SAP Unlock New Innovation with Generative AI" src="./media_104d1ffe68c31e9f2e51bfd7af2878774eaaff54a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="aws-and-sap-unlock-new-innovation-with-generative-ai">AWS and SAP Unlock New Innovation with Generative AI</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Generative AI hub in SAP AI Core integrates with foundation models in Amazon Bedrock to deliver generative AI-driven insights and streamline manual processes for enterprise customers</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <table>
          <thead>
            <tr>
              <th>Text Large</th>
            </tr>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td><strong><em>SEATTLE and WALLDORF</em></strong> — Amazon Web Services (AWS), an Amazon.com company (NASDAQ: AMZN), and <a href="https://www.sap.com/index.html">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced an expanded, strategic collaboration to transform modern cloud enterprise resource planning (ERP) experiences and help enterprises drive new capabilities and efficiencies with generative artificial intelligence (AI).</td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
        <p>Together, AWS and SAP are striving to make it easier for customers to adopt the RISE with SAP solution on AWS, to improve the performance and efficiency of SAP workloads running in the cloud and to embed generative AI into an enterprise’s entire portfolio of business-critical applications.</p>
        <p>“AWS was the first cloud provider certified to support the SAP portfolio and today, thousands of enterprise companies run SAP solutions on AWS to get the most out of their mission-critical applications,” said Matt Garman incoming CEO at AWS. “Now, AWS and SAP are making it faster and easier for companies to apply generative AI to their core business data to become more efficient, responsive and sustainable.”</p>
        <p>“Partnerships like this collaboration with AWS are critical as we embed generative AI solutions across our ERP applications so that customers can drive innovation at an accelerated pace,” said Christian Klein, Chief Executive Officer of SAP SE. “In addition to delivering modern cloud ERP to our joint customers, we are excited to support Amazon on their own transformation journey as they adopt RISE with SAP for pioneering areas such as Project Kuiper, Amazon’s satellite initiative intended to increase global broadband access.”</p>
        <h2 id="generative-ai-models-from-amazon-bedrock-available-on-the-generative-ai-hub-in-sap-ai-core">Generative AI Models from Amazon Bedrock Available on the Generative AI Hub in SAP AI Core</h2>
        <p>The generative AI hub in SAP AI Core infrastructure provides customers with secure access to a broad range of large language models (LLMs) that can easily be integrated into SAP business applications. With the integration of generative AI models from Amazon Bedrock such as the Anthropic Claude 3 model family and Amazon Titan, SAP customers will be able to access high-performing LLMs and other foundation models (FMs) to build applications customized with their own data. Tens of thousands of customers use Amazon Bedrock to easily, quickly and securely build and scale generative AI applications using FMs from leading AI companies such as AI21 Labs, Anthropic, Cohere, Meta, Mistral AI, Stability AI and Amazon.</p>
        <p>With this integration, SAP customers may accelerate the adoption of generative AI and modernize key business processes built on SAP solutions. These innovations can be used in embedded use cases within RISE with SAP and the intelligent scenario lifecycle management functionality as an integration component or side-by-side directly on SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP). SAP and AWS plan to expand the use of Bedrock capabilities in the generative AI hub to further enable embedded AI functionality within SAP’s portfolio of cloud solutions and applications. This includes additional use cases across finance and product lifecycle management.</p>
        <h2 id="sap-to-use-aws-chips-to-train-and-deploy-future-sap-business-ai-offerings">SAP to Use AWS Chips to Train and Deploy Future SAP Business AI Offerings</h2>
        <p>SAP’s use of <a href="/2023/11/sap-hana-cloud-now-supports-aws-graviton">AWS Graviton3 chips to support SAP HANA Cloud</a> helps to deliver performance gains, cost savings and energy efficiency to SAP. By using Graviton3-based Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (EC2) instances, SAP has realized up to 30% better compute for analytical workloads and an estimated 45% reduction in carbon footprint for SAP HANA Cloud. Now SAP and AWS are collaborating on the next generation of Graviton4 for SAP HANA Cloud and additional SAP applications to continue to improve performance and efficiency. Based on the success of running SAP HANA Cloud on AWS Graviton, SAP plans to use AWS Graviton to support SAP solutions and applications such as SAP BTP, SAP Datasphere, SAP Analytics Cloud and the SAP Cloud ALM solution.</p>
        <p>SAP plans to use <a href="https://aws.amazon.com/machine-learning/inferentia/">AWS Trainium</a> and <a href="https://aws.amazon.com/machine-learning/inferentia/">AWS Inferentia</a> chips, purpose built for AI and machine learning (ML) workloads, for training and deploying future SAP Business AI offerings. Using Trainium and Inferentia2-based instances in a proof of concept, SAP engineers trained and fine-tuned generative AI LLMs in two days versus 23 days with comparable Amazon EC2 instances. By leveraging Trainium’s specialized architecture designed for efficient ML model training, SAP can accelerate the development process while maintaining high levels of accuracy and reliability.</p>
        <h2 id="increased-performance-for-rise-with-sap-on-aws">Increased Performance for RISE with SAP on AWS</h2>
        <p>Thousands of customers have selected RISE with SAP on AWS to run their largest, most complex, global SAP solution implementations. Now generally available, the next-generation Amazon EC2 High Memory U7i instances offer up to 32TiB of memory in a single instance and provide customers the memory and flexibility they need to support expanding SAP HANA database requirements. Amazon EC2 High Memory U7i instances are the first DDR5 memory-based 8-socket offering by a leading cloud provider to improve the performance of memory-intensive applications such as SAP S/4HANA Cloud as part of RISE with SAP.</p>
        <h2 id="amazons-project-kuiper-selects-rise-with-sap">Amazon’s Project Kuiper Selects RISE with SAP</h2>
        <p>Amazon companies, including Twitch, Zappos.com and Zoox Inc., already use SAP software on AWS to support their operations. And now Project Kuiper—Amazon’s satellite broadband network—is deploying RISE with SAP to support its complex supply chain and manufacturing operations and get the best performance and most value out of its mission-critical SAP software. Running SAP solutions on AWS allows Kuiper to take advantage of the latest SAP capabilities embedded in RISE with SAP to help drive impactful transformation, accelerating company decisions and enhancing overall performance and productivity.</p>
        <p>Hundreds of millions of people lack adequate internet access and Project Kuiper’s goal is to help close the digital divide by delivering fast, affordable broadband to a wide variety of customers operating in places without reliable internet connections. Delivering on that vision requires Kuiper to build satellites at an unprecedented rate. RISE with SAP allows the Project Kuiper team to leverage the most reliable and scalable infrastructure to run a modern, cloud ERP as a managed service, so they can focus on innovation instead of IT management.</p>
        <p>To learn more about the SAP and AWS partnership, tune in to the <a href="https://www.sap.com/events/sapphire.html">SAP Sapphire conference</a>, June 3-5, in Orlando.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="join-experts-speakers-and-peers-at-sap-sapphire-in-2024">Join experts, speakers and peers at SAP Sapphire in 2024</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/events/sapphire.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Visit the <a href="/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP at <a href="https://x.com/sapnews">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>About Amazon Web Services</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Since 2006, Amazon Web Services has been the world’s most comprehensive and broadly adopted cloud. AWS has been continually expanding its services to support virtually any workload, and it now has more than 240 fully featured services for compute, storage, databases, networking, analytics, machine learning and artificial intelligence (AI), Internet of Things (IoT), mobile, security, hybrid, media, and application development, deployment, and management from 105 Availability Zones within 33 geographic regions, with announced plans for 18 more Availability Zones and six more AWS Regions in Malaysia, Mexico, New Zealand, the Kingdom of Saudi Arabia, Thailand, and the AWS European Sovereign Cloud. Millions of customers—including the fastest-growing startups, largest enterprises, and leading government agencies—trust AWS to power their infrastructure, become more agile, and lower costs. To learn more about AWS, visit <a href="https://cts.businesswire.com/ct/CT?id=smartlink&#x26;url=https%3A%2F%2Faws.amazon.com%2F&#x26;esheet=53904515&#x26;newsitemid=20240304438993&#x26;lan=en-US&#x26;anchor=aws.amazon.com&#x26;index=12&#x26;md5=74b48ab611b237d4b1c4af457e844e2a">aws.amazon.com</a>.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>About Amazon</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Amazon is guided by four principles: customer obsession rather than competitor focus, passion for invention, commitment to operational excellence, and long-term thinking. Amazon strives to be Earth’s Most Customer-Centric Company, Earth’s Best Employer, and Earth’s Safest Place to Work. Customer reviews, 1-Click shopping, personalized recommendations, Prime, Fulfillment by Amazon, AWS, Kindle Direct Publishing, Kindle, Career Choice, Fire tablets, Fire TV, Amazon Echo, Alexa, Just Walk Out technology, Amazon Studios, and The Climate Pledge are some of the things pioneered by Amazon. For more information, visit <a href="https://cts.businesswire.com/ct/CT?id=smartlink&#x26;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.aboutamazon.com%2F&#x26;esheet=53552459&#x26;newsitemid=20230913559977&#x26;lan=en-US&#x26;anchor=amazon.com%2Fabout&#x26;index=4&#x26;md5=a9213abaf1405cdcf6f92fbf73419565">amazon.com/about</a> and follow @AmazonNews.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>About SAP</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As a global leader in enterprise applications and business AI, SAP (NYSE: SAP) stands at the nexus of business and technology. For over 50 years, organizations have trusted SAP to bring out their best by uniting business-critical operations spanning finance, procurement, HR, supply chain, and customer experience. For more information, visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/">www.sap.com</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Note to editors:</strong><br>To preview and download broadcast-standard stock footage and press photos digitally, please visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/photos">www.sap.com/photos</a>. On this platform, you can find high resolution material for your media channels.</p>
  <p><strong>For customers interested in learning more about SAP products:</strong><br>Global Customer Center: +49 180 534-34-24<br>United States Only: 1 (800) 872-1SAP (1-800-872-1727)</p>
  <p><strong>For more information, press only:</strong><br>Scott Malinowski, +1 (781) 852-3822, <a href="mailto:scott.malinowski@sap.com">scott.malinowski@sap.com</a>, ET<br><a href="mailto:SAP%20Press%20Room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a><br>Amazon.com, Inc. Media Hotline<br><a href="mailto:Amazon-pr@amazon.com">Amazon-pr@amazon.com</a><br><a href="https://cts.businesswire.com/ct/CT?id=smartlink&#x26;url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fpr&#x26;esheet=52838073&#x26;newsitemid=20220829005779&#x26;lan=en-US&#x26;anchor=www.amazon.com%2Fpr&#x26;index=11&#x26;md5=f7f322f746ba4e16da9b2e92d74e349a">www.amazon.com/pr</a></p>
  <p>This document contains forward-looking statements, which are predictions, projections, or other statements about future events. These statements are based on current expectations, forecasts, and assumptions that are subject to risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results and outcomes to materially differ. Additional information regarding these risks and uncertainties may be found in our filings with the Securities and Exchange Commission, including but not limited to the risk factors section of SAP’s 2023 Annual Report on Form 20-F.<br>© 2024 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.<br>Please consider our <a href="https://www.sap.com/corporate/en/legal/privacy.html">privacy policy</a>. If you receive this press release in your e-mail and you wish to unsubscribe to our mailing list please contact <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a> and write Unsubscribe in the subject line.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-business-ai-revolutionary-technology-real-world-results">SAP Business AI: Revolutionary technology, real-world results</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/aws</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[NEC Leverages RISE with SAP and AI to Build Business AI in Move to the Cloud]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/nec-move-to-cloud-rise-with-sap-business-ai</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/nec-move-to-cloud-rise-with-sap-business-ai</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[NEC is migrating to SAP S/4HANA Cloud and adopting a clean-core approach to create a sustainable society through digital transformation.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/aws</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PureTech Scientific Scores Leading Position in the Market with Move to the Cloud]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/puretech-scientific-move-to-the-cloud</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/puretech-scientific-move-to-the-cloud</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[PureTech Scientific has gone live with SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition to position itself for further growth. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c1d9fd2f027e5f5b76f97a625db59c9566ef4528.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c1d9fd2f027e5f5b76f97a625db59c9566ef4528.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1c1d9fd2f027e5f5b76f97a625db59c9566ef4528.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="PureTech Scientific Scores Leading Position in the Market with Move to the Cloud" src="./media_1c1d9fd2f027e5f5b76f97a625db59c9566ef4528.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="puretech-scientific-scores-leading-position-in-the-market-with-move-to-the-cloud">PureTech Scientific Scores Leading Position in the Market with Move to the Cloud</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>BELLE, W. Va.</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced that <a href="https://www.puretechscientific.com/">PureTech Scientific LLC</a>, a global leader in the production of glycolic acid products, with a range of uses from skin care to clean and disinfect, has gone live with SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition to position itself for further growth.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="https://ironpathcapital.com/">Iron Path Capital</a>, a private equity firm that acquired the company in 2023, has significant growth ambitions for PureTech Scientific. The first milestone for PureTech Scientific transformation was the move to the cloud to build a unified technology platform that would fully transition employees, customers and vendors with minimal disruption. Completed in 14 weeks, the implementation has already seen improved operational visibility and more timely transactional discipline.</p>
  <p>“The real-time insights and automation PureTech Scientific plans to gain from implementation of SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition will help to streamline our operations and significantly enhance our ability to serve our customers with greater speed and accuracy,” PureTech Scientific CEO James Kanicky said. “This is just the beginning, and we’re excited for the opportunities ahead as we continue to drive growth and innovation with glycolic acid in the personal care and health care markets.”</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="grow-with-sap-cloud-erp-adoption-with-speed-predictability-and-continuous-innovation">GROW with SAP: Cloud ERP adoption with speed, predictability and continuous innovation</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/grow.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>With its entire ERP now in the cloud, PureTech Scientific, the only North American glycolic acid producer, has real-time insight of its daily production and the ability to employ and automate barcoding. PureTech Scientific is now able to complete SAP goods issue and goods receipt transactions automatically with mobile devices, further reducing time needed for reporting.</p>
  <p>“SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition provides a best-in-class foundation for enterprise scalability, security and compliance,” said James Smith, executive advisor for Iron Path Capital and PureTech board member. “After an impressive 14-week implementation, PureTech Scientific is now able to have real-time business analytics and implement industry-best-practice, fit-to-standard workflows. The commencement of digital manufacturing cloud, barcoding and sales cloud capabilities will eliminate manual transactions, automate production recording and material movements, and employ mobile data collection for improved enterprise productivity and customer satisfaction.”</p>
  <p>Glycolic acid is used as the core agent in multiple industries, ranging from industrials to life science. PureTech Scientific expects the market to grow 10% CAGR over the next five years. SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition was selected specifically to support PureTech Scientific’s vision for growth. With scalability and integration as top priorities, SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition allows the company to now focus on pursuing growth opportunities in new markets and new capabilities for new and existing customers.</p>
  <p>“PureTech Scientific has undergone a significant transformation in the past year,” SAP North America President Lloyd Adams said. “It has completely revamped its ERP system and moved to the cloud. Doing so allows for quick and data-driven business decisions as it enhances its capabilities and deepens its market share in key markets.”</p>
  <p>Learn more at <a href="https://www.puretechscientific.com/">PureTech Scientific</a>.</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="http://news.sap.com/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Media Contacts:</strong><br>Bridget Carroll, +1 (267) 615-3589, <a href="mailto:bridget.carroll@sap.com">bridget.carroll@sap.com</a>, ET<br>Lesa Plingen, +49 622 776 9000, <a href="mailto:lesa.plingen@sap.com">lesa.plingen@sap.com</a>, CET<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>This document contains forward-looking statements, which are predictions, projections, or other statements about future events. These statements are based on current expectations, forecasts, and assumptions that are subject to risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results and outcomes to materially differ. Additional information regarding these risks and uncertainties may be found in our filings with the Securities and Exchange Commission, including but not limited to the risk factors section of SAP’s 2023 Annual Report on Form 20-F.<br>© 2024 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[CP Foods Selects SAP Solutions for Cloud Sustainability]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/cp-foods-selects-sap-solutions-for-cloud-sustainability</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/cp-foods-selects-sap-solutions-for-cloud-sustainability</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[CP Foods has selected SAP software to future-proof its business and use data to make more sustainable decisions. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_183175263685a353d3b61ffbc18dc57a24b395640.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_183175263685a353d3b61ffbc18dc57a24b395640.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_183175263685a353d3b61ffbc18dc57a24b395640.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="CP Foods Selects SAP Solutions for Cloud Sustainability" src="./media_183175263685a353d3b61ffbc18dc57a24b395640.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="cp-foods-selects-sap-solutions-for-cloud-sustainability">CP Foods Selects SAP Solutions for Cloud Sustainability</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF and BANGKOK</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced Charoen Pokphand Foods Public Company Limited (“CP Foods”) has selected multiple SAP solutions to drive further growth and competitive advantage and to ensure the sustainability of its products for the future.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="record-report-and-act-on-your-sustainability-goals-with-sap-software">Record, report and act on your sustainability goals with SAP software</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/sustainability/solutions.html">Learn how</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Catering to more than 4 billion people globally, CP Foods is embarking on its next stage of digital transformation with the RISE with SAP, SAP Sustainability Footprint Management, and SAP Sustainability Control Tower solutions. In addition, the SAP EHS Management, environment management application will be implemented to future-proof its business and to gain strategic insight into the sustainability impact of its products, processes and infrastructure globally. The company is a leading integrated agro-industrial and food business that is one of the world’s largest producers of feed, shrimp, poultry and pork. It has operations in 17 countries and exports to more than 50 countries.</p>
  <h2 id="global-net-zero-ambitions">Global Net-Zero Ambitions</h2>
  <p>In line with CP Foods’ goal of becoming the “Sustainable Kitchen of the World,” CP Foods is the first food processing company in the world with near- and long-term forests, lands and agriculture (FLAG) sustainability targets validated by the Science-Based Targets Initiative (SBTi). CP Foods is looking to realize the company’s <a href="https://www.cpfworldwide.com/en/media-center/oversea-operations-coal-free-to-net-zero">Net Zero goals</a> of reducing 42% of Scope 1 and 2 emissions and 30.3% of Scope 3 emissions by 2030 – and 90% of Scope 1 and 2 emissions and 72% of Scope 3 emissions by 2050. To achieve these goals, the company is implementing SAP Sustainability solutions to record, report and act on real-time sustainability data, driving carbon accounting at both corporate and product levels.</p>
  <p>“Net Zero is the only solution to climate change,” CP Foods CEO Prasit Boondoungpraser said. “It is important to us to understand and reduce our impact on the planet, so we create food that is not only safe and nutritious for people but also green and clean for the earth. Feeding our livestock, farming our food and transporting it to people’s plates incurs emissions we have to be able to record and report. With RISE with SAP and SAP Sustainability solutions, we will have insight into actual emissions automated in real time rather than relying on manual averages, allowing us to make quick, informed and sustainable business decisions for our operations and for the planet.”</p>
  <p>SAP plans to provide a technology foundation that will support CP Foods in complying with forthcoming carbon regulations in various markets, including the EU Carbon Border Adjustment Mechanism (EU C-BAM) and U.S. SEC climate risk disclosures.</p>
  <p>Key to reducing total emissions, CP Foods will focus on supply chain emissions, with its emissions mostly falling under Scope 3. CP Foods will work with the Customer Success organization at SAP, leverage YASH Technologies’ sustainability expertise and build on Amazon Web Services (AWS) to implement SAP Sustainability solutions. Doing so will allow it to record and report on its Scope 1 and 2 emissions in Thailand and select Scope 3 (3.1 and 3.4) for its feed business in Thailand covering both FLAG and non-FLAG emissions. The next phase of implementation will extend in scope to cover operations around the world.</p>
  <h2 id="cloud-sustainability">Cloud Sustainability</h2>
  <p>Paul Marriott, president of SAP Asia Pacific &#x26; Japan, said: “Sustainability is a huge opportunity for businesses across Asia. Using RISE with SAP and our sustainability solutions, CP Foods is getting ahead of forthcoming emissions regulation and future-proofing its business by using data to make more sustainable decisions. It can use those insights to drive more operational efficiencies, optimize supply chains, and differentiate its business against competitors.”</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-our-approach-to-sustainability-and-our-aspirations-for-a-world-with-zero-emissions-zero-waste-and-zero-inequality">Learn more about our approach to sustainability and our aspirations for a world with zero emissions, zero waste and zero inequality</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/sustainability/our-approach.html">Explore our journey</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>About SAP</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As a global leader in enterprise applications and business AI, SAP (NYSE:SAP) stands at the nexus of business and technology. For over 50 years, organizations have trusted SAP to bring out their best by uniting business-critical operations spanning finance, procurement, HR, supply chain, and customer experience. For more information, visit <a href="http://www.sap.com">www.sap.com</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Note to editors:</strong><br>To preview and download broadcast-standard stock footage and press photos digitally, please visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/photos">www.sap.com/photos</a>. On this platform, you can find high resolution material for your media channels.</p>
  <p><strong>For customers interested in learning more about SAP products:</strong><br>Global Customer Center: +49 180 534-34-24<br>United States Only: 1 (800) 872-1SAP (1-800-872-1727)</p>
  <p><strong>For more information, press only:</strong><br>Rizka Laksmi, <a href="mailto:rizka.laksmi@sap.com">rizka.laksmi@sap.com</a>, WIB<br>Lesa Plingen, +49 622 776 9000, <a href="mailto:lesa.plingen@sap.com">lesa.plingen@sap.com</a>, CET<br><a href="mailto:SAP%20Press%20Room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>This document contains forward-looking statements, which are predictions, projections, or other statements about future events. These statements are based on current expectations, forecasts, and assumptions that are subject to risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results and outcomes to materially differ. Additional information regarding these risks and uncertainties may be found in our filings with the Securities and Exchange Commission, including but not limited to the risk factors section of SAP’s 2023 Annual Report on Form 20-F.<br>© 2024 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.<br>Please consider our <a href="https://www.sap.com/corporate/en/legal/privacy.html">privacy policy</a>. If you received this press release in your e-mail and you wish to unsubscribe to our mailing list please contact <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a> and write Unsubscribe in the subject line.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-ehs-management</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-footprint-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[IBM and SAP Plan to Expand Collaboration to Help Clients Become Next-Generation Enterprises with Generative AI]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/ibm-and-sap-generative-ai-new-value-generation-partnership</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/ibm-and-sap-generative-ai-new-value-generation-partnership</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New Value Generation partnership from SAP and IBM includes new generative AI capabilities and industry-specific cloud solutions. Read the news]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1aeeb46bbfcb4f664eb2a3c5eaebfbd24570cce9b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1aeeb46bbfcb4f664eb2a3c5eaebfbd24570cce9b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1aeeb46bbfcb4f664eb2a3c5eaebfbd24570cce9b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="IBM and SAP Plan to Expand Collaboration to Help Clients Become Next-Generation Enterprises with Generative AI" src="./media_1aeeb46bbfcb4f664eb2a3c5eaebfbd24570cce9b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="ibm-and-sap-plan-to-expand-collaboration-to-help-clients-become-next-generation-enterprises-with-generative-ai">IBM and SAP Plan to Expand Collaboration to Help Clients Become Next-Generation Enterprises with Generative AI</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>New Value Generation partnership initiative focused on delivering greater client productivity and innovation with new generative AI capabilities and industry-specific cloud solutions</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <table>
          <thead>
            <tr>
              <th>Text Large</th>
            </tr>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td>
                <p><strong><em>WALLDORF and ARMONK</em></strong></p>
                <hr>
                <p>IBM (NYSE: <a href="http://www.ibm.com/investor">IBM</a>) and <a href="http://sap.com">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced their vision for the next era of their collaboration, which includes new <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/generative-ai.html">generative AI</a> capabilities and industry-specific cloud solutions that can help clients unlock business value.</p>
              </td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="unlock-new-capabilities-with-generative-ai">Unlock new capabilities with generative AI</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/generative-ai.html">Learn how</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“IBM and SAP’s shared approach to generative AI, built on an open ecosystem, trust and purpose-built models, will help empower clients to optimize business outcomes,” said John Granger, Senior Vice President, IBM Consulting. “Our new Value Generation partnership initiative will enable clients to accelerate the path to innovation, competitive advantage and become a next generation enterprise through generative AI.”</p>
  <p>“It makes perfect sense to expand our partnership with IBM to help more customers accelerate their cloud journey leveraging RISE with SAP and realize the transformative benefits of generative AI for business in the cloud,” said Scott Russell, Chief Revenue Officer &#x26; Executive Board Member, Customer Success of SAP SE. “This expanded partnership will help more of our joint customers reach new heights by innovating through the cloud, data and business AI to grow and transform their businesses.”</p>
  <p><a href="https://www.ibm.com/consulting">IBM Consulting</a> and SAP aim to accelerate transformation enabled by RISE with SAP by supporting clients in the following key areas:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Next-Generation AI Business Processes</strong>: Together, the companies are exploring opportunities to build new generative AI capabilities for RISE with SAP and infuse AI into SAP business processes across industry-specific cloud solutions and line of business applications. Initially, IBM plans to extend AI capabilities across SAP’s portfolio of cloud solutions and applications, all of which are underpinned by SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP). This includes RISE with SAP, the GROW with SAP solution, financial solutions for the office of the CFO, supply chain management solutions, solutions for human capital management, SAP Customer Experience solutions and intelligent spend management solutions. IBM also plans to leverage SAP Signavio and SAP Business AI solutions to help define next-generation business processes through a proof-of-concept adoption program.</li>
    <li><strong>Next-Generation Industry Innovation</strong>: IBM and SAP plan to build intelligent industry use cases, enabled by data-driven insights, into end-to-end business processes to fuel next-generation industry innovation. These use cases will initially focus on the industrial manufacturing, consumer packaged goods (CPG), retail, defense, automotive and utilities industries. This includes IBM’s recent work with SAP to develop new AI solutions for the CPG and retail industries. As part of this initiative, IBM has begun the development of an extensive portfolio of over 100 AI solutions across industry, line-of-business and product delivery. In addition, IBM plans to develop prescriptive industry value maps that define next-generation business processes and opportunities for impact with AI. Clients will be able to access all of these new AI solutions through the global <a href="https://www.ibm.com/about/innovation-studio">IBM Innovation Studios</a> and <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/innovation.html">SAP Experience Center</a> sites.</li>
    <li><strong>Next-Generation Platform Architecture and Customer Adoption Approach</strong>: Next-generation enterprises require next-generation platform architectures and a modernized approach to customer adoption. Through the Value Generation partnership initiative, IBM intends to provide next-generation reference architectures that enable a clean core approach. To do this, IBM plans to leverage SAP BTP, SAP Signavio and LeanIX solutions. These new reference architectures will help define standards across data, process, systems and device integration, process orchestration and automation. IBM consultants supporting clients on SAP projects can also leverage IBM Consulting Advantage, IBM’s AI services platform, and its portfolio of proprietary methods, assets and Assistants to bring more repeatability and consistency to client delivery. With IBM Consulting Advantage, IBM consultants can transform the way they deliver SAP solutions to boost productivity and mitigate risk by leveraging generative AI to help complete tasks like generation of user stories, test scripts, training and change management content and code creation.</li>
    <li><strong>Next-Generation Ecosystem Expansion</strong>: IBM and SAP plan to partner around their respective employee network groups and “next-gen” communities, such as the business women’s networks at IBM and SAP, the <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/innovation/next-gen-innovation-platform/university-alliances.html">SAP University Alliances</a> program and the <a href="https://jobs.sap.com/content/Military-Veterans/?locale=en_US">Veterans to Work</a> program of SAP and Veterans at IBM to increase the SAP solutions experience in the consulting workforce and develop the next generation of talent. The companies also plan to explore new ways to collaborate on social impact programs, such as training at- risk youth in the IT sector and accelerating the integration of social businesses into global supply chains.</li>
    <li><strong>watsonx Planned Availability on the Generative AI Hub</strong>: IBM Granite Model Series are expected to be accessible for use across SAP’s portfolio of cloud solutions and applications – which is underpinned by the generative AI hub in SAP AI Core. The generative AI hub facilitates relevant, reliable and responsible business AI and provides instant access to a broad range of large language models (LLMs). This expands on IBM and SAP’s collaboration around <a href="https://newsroom.ibm.com/2023-05-02-SAP-to-Embed-IBM-Watson-Artificial-Intelligence-into-SAP-R-Solutions">embedding IBM Watson AI technology into SAP solutions</a>. To further highlight watsonx.ai Granite capabilities, IBM Consulting plans to build extensions using the model on the generative AI hub for select customers.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>This initiative will build on the companies’ over 50-year collaboration based on deep technology, industry and domain expertise and demonstrates the two organizations’ joint commitment to continue to evolve to put clients first and meet market demand.</p>
  <p>IBM Consulting accelerates business transformation for our clients through hybrid cloud and AI technologies, leveraging our open ecosystem of partners. With deep industry and business expertise spanning strategy, experience design, technology, and operations, we have become the trusted partner to the world’s most innovative and valuable companies, helping modernize and secure their most complex systems. Our 160,000 consultants embrace an open way of working and apply our proven, collaborative engagement model, IBM Garage, to scale ideas into outcomes. As the only major global systems integrator inside a technology company, we don’t just advise – we invent and build what’s next together with our clients. Find out more at <a href="http://ibm.com/consulting">IBM.com/consulting</a>.</p>
  <p>To learn more about the Value Generation partnership initiative, visit <a href="https://www.ibm.com/info/sap-value-generation">ibm.com/info/sap-value-generation</a>.</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>About IBM</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>IBM is a leading provider of global hybrid cloud and AI, and consulting expertise. We help clients in more than 175 countries capitalize on insights from their data, streamline business processes, reduce costs and gain the competitive edge in their industries. More than 4,000 government and corporate entities in critical infrastructure areas such as financial services, telecommunications and healthcare rely on IBM’s hybrid cloud platform and Red Hat OpenShift to effect their digital transformations quickly, efficiently and securely. IBM’s breakthrough innovations in AI, quantum computing, industry-specific cloud solutions and consulting deliver open and flexible options to our clients. All of this is backed by IBM’s commitment to trust, transparency, responsibility, inclusivity and service.</p>
  <p>Visit <a href="http://www.ibm.com/">www.ibm.com</a> for more information.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>About SAP</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As a global leader in enterprise applications and business AI, SAP (NYSE:SAP) stands at the nexus of business and technology. For over 50 years, organizations have trusted SAP to bring out their best by uniting business-critical operations spanning finance, procurement, HR, supply chain, and customer experience. For more information, visit <a href="http://www.sap.com">www.sap.com</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Note to editors:</strong><br>To preview and download broadcast-standard stock footage and press photos digitally, please visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/photos">www.sap.com/photos</a>. On this platform, you can find high resolution material for your media channels.</p>
  <p><strong>For customers interested in learning more about SAP products:</strong><br>Global Customer Center: +49 180 534-34-24<br>United States Only: 1 (800) 872-1SAP (1-800-872-1727)</p>
  <p><strong>For more information, press only:</strong><br>Scott Malinowski, SAP, +1 (781) 852-3822, <a href="mailto:scott.malinowski@sap.com">scott.malinowski@sap.com</a><br><a href="mailto:SAP%20Press%20Room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a><br>Jamee Nelson, IBM, <a href="mailto:jamee.nelson@ibm.com">jamee.nelson@ibm.com</a></p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-the-power-of-sap-partners-who-drive-customer-success-delivering-trusted-advice-and-deep-product-knowledge">Learn more about the power of SAP partners, who drive customer success, delivering trusted advice and deep product knowledge</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/partners.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>This document contains forward-looking statements, which are predictions, projections, or other statements about future events. These statements are based on current expectations, forecasts, and assumptions that are subject to risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results and outcomes to materially differ. Additional information regarding these risks and uncertainties may be found in our filings with the Securities and Exchange Commission, including but not limited to the risk factors section of SAP’s 2023 Annual Report on Form 20-F.<br>© 2024 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.<br>Please consider our <a href="https://www.sap.com/corporate/en/legal/privacy.html">privacy policy</a>. If you received this press release in your e-mail and you wish to unsubscribe to our mailing list please contact <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a> and write Unsubscribe in the subject line.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/ibm</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Innovative Cloud ERP at Department of Defense Agencies with SAP S/4HANA Cloud Private Edition]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/dod-agencies-sap-ns2-innovative-cloud-erp</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/dod-agencies-sap-ns2-innovative-cloud-erp</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP NS2 can now officially deploy SAP S/4HANA Cloud Private Edition within the DoD IL4 secure cloud environment. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17fe6b9f04141be0d0702008e758517683085fbcd.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17fe6b9f04141be0d0702008e758517683085fbcd.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_17fe6b9f04141be0d0702008e758517683085fbcd.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Innovative Cloud ERP at Department of Defense Agencies with SAP S/4HANA Cloud Private Edition" src="./media_17fe6b9f04141be0d0702008e758517683085fbcd.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="innovative-cloud-erp-at-department-of-defense-agencies-with-sap-s4hana-cloud-private-edition">Innovative Cloud ERP at Department of Defense Agencies with SAP S/4HANA Cloud Private Edition</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Over the past several years, defense agencies in the United States have become increasingly cloud-centric. The cloud has proven its ability to streamline operations, empower real-time decision making, and support mission success.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As <a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/sap-ns2-achieves-disa-provisional-authorization-pa-of-sap-s4hana-cloud-to-support-enterprise-cloud-operations-for-defense-agencies-302130501.html?tc=eml_cleartime">announced May 2,</a> SAP S/4HANA Cloud Private Edition has received a provisional authorization from the Defense Information and Systems Agency (DISA). This means SAP NS2, an independent subsidiary of SAP that facilitates the adoption of SAP cloud solutions for customers who require enhanced compliance, can officially deploy SAP S/4HANA Cloud Private Edition within the Department of Defense FedRAMP+Impact Level 4 (DoD IL4) secure cloud environment.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="cloud-erp-for-every-business-need-from-mission-critical-operations-to-business-model-innovation">Cloud ERP for every business need: from mission-critical operations to business model innovation</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP S/4HANA Cloud Private Edition enables a cloud experience with the same functional scope and upgrade flexibility that SAP S/4HANA Cloud offers, but with added security and compliance that allows Department of Defense customers a quick adoption of cloud solutions.</p>
  <p>With this new certification, defense customers can choose to adopt a secure cloud ERP solution that supports mission-critical operations in real time, from any location. Once limited to on-premise solutions, which exhausted budget and resources, defense agencies can now migrate operations to the cloud where data is stored on cloud servers and resources can be reallocated to support defense workforces and alternative needs.</p>
  <p>“Obtaining our FedRAMP+DoD IL4 authorization was a tremendous step in supporting our defense and federal agency customers,” said Amy Spruill, senior vice president and general manager of Regulated Industries at SAP. “SAP S/4HANA Cloud will provide the commercial cloud capabilities our customers are looking for while improving their security perimeter and mitigating attacks on critical data.”</p>
  <p>The FedRAMP+DoD IL4 secure cloud environment is dedicated to defense agencies and protected with continuous monitoring, vulnerability scanning, and intrusion detection to ensure Controlled Unclassified Information (CUI) is safeguarded. <a href="https://www.sapns2.com/security-and-trust/">SAP NS2 adheres</a> to National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST) 800-53, FedRAMP®, International Traffic and Arms (ITAR), and FedRAMP+Impact Level 2 (DoD IL2).</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Harish Luthra is CEO of SAP NS2.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/defense-security</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ns2</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Path to AI with Clean Core]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/the-path-to-ai-with-clean-core</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/the-path-to-ai-with-clean-core</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP's Claudio Muruzabal shares about his Customer Advisory role and how SAP customers are winning with intelligent technology, like AI.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1df14be7df416024e279a8fbc6ac26cd297e9f468.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1df14be7df416024e279a8fbc6ac26cd297e9f468.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1df14be7df416024e279a8fbc6ac26cd297e9f468.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="The Path to AI with Clean Core" src="./media_1df14be7df416024e279a8fbc6ac26cd297e9f468.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="the-path-to-ai-with-clean-core">The Path to AI with Clean Core</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>From cloud to generative AI, the list of new and emerging technologies continues to grow in our era of digital intelligence. Yet it’s also the era of inflation, geopolitical tension, supply chain disruption, and countless other challenges. How are businesses supposed to make sense of all these technologies – let alone transform their businesses with them – while simply trying to survive during such a challenging time?</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>That’s where Claudio Muruzabal, chief business officer of SAP SE, steps in.</p>
  <p>Muruzabal is responsible for supporting the Customer Advisory, Solution Area and Services Sales, and Customer Success Management &#x26; Engagement teams at SAP. For more than eight years, he has played an important role in understanding not only an increasingly complex technology landscape but also how businesses actually use the technology at their disposal. He supports teams that help bring SAP customers closer to their goals by leveraging SAP solutions. This begins with advising customers through honest conversations about how they can apply the intelligent capabilities now included in many SAP solutions, such as generative AI.</p>
  <p>I sat down with Muruzabal to find out more about his role, how SAP customers are winning with intelligent technology, and the growing impact of customer success management at SAP.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Q: AI is all the rage today, so let’s start there. What are the biggest opportunities for businesses to use AI?</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><strong>Muruzabal</strong>: Opportunity is everywhere for <a href="/topics/ai">AI</a>. And it’s bigger than just automating processes to increase efficiency, which is what was talked about for the longest time. At SAP, we’re seeing how AI can support relevant business processes to instill innovation and competitiveness. While many players in the industry are focused on developing AI engines and large language models, we are focused on accelerating business value through generative AI. I could talk all day about how AI is transforming data analytics and decision-support systems as well as supply chain optimization, predictive maintenance, and HR. Every day we are discovering new opportunities for customers to leapfrog their competition when they combine the power of generative AI with the context of their business data and processes.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>What are some examples of how SAP customers are using AI, and what value have they realized so far?</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-business-ai-revolutionary-technology-real-world-results">SAP Business AI: Revolutionary technology, real-world results</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>There’s really so much to get excited about when it comes to how our customers are using the AI capabilities included with their SAP solutions. Across industries, workers everywhere are using natural language to instantly get the data insights they need using the SAP Analytics Cloud solution. I like how busy recruiters can tap into generative AI with SAP SuccessFactors solutions to create compelling job descriptions and interview questions in less time. Joule, our AI assistant and copilot, can support end users in getting the right answers on how to get the most of our cloud solutions. With Joule already embedded across the portfolio – generally available in SAP SuccessFactors HCM, SAP Start, and SAP S/4HANA Cloud – we are all excited about the opportunities for our customers.</p>
  <p>All industries can get this unique value, including professional soccer clubs FC Bayern Munich and Hertha BSC that are using a scouting prototype powered by AI to find and develop the next generation of star athletes.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>AI can solve a lot of problems, but what about the underlying foundational technology stack companies have today? What conversations are you having with businesses about their technology investments?</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Early on in our conversations with customers, it’s important to understand how businesses can set up their core, foundational enterprise technology platform running in the cloud. This is critical to establish a journey of innovation including <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence.html">SAP Business AI</a>. Coming back to the foundation, many of our customers have built numerous modifications on top of their core ERP. In order to build a true cloud operating model – essential to embrace innovation including AI – it is critical to move to a clean core model. This means that any modification to the ERP functionality offered by SAP is built outside of the core, using extensibility solutions. This is not a technical topic only. Although clean core contributes to the cost-efficient operation of the platform, the true contribution is bringing flexibility and adaptability to the business, converting the cloud operating model into a unique “innovation as a service” platform.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>What makes SAP unique and stand out to customers with its value proposition?</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP has the unique value of being the global leader in best of suite solutions built with more than 50 years of industry knowledge and ERP technology leadership. On top of this, our leading “best of breed” solutions, such as in HCM, customer experience, intelligent spend and business network, and more, can provide the best functionality and the right integration into the core. Only SAP can offer this value proposition. When we combined this with the cloud operating model – widely adopted by our RISE with SAP customers – we provide exponential value for the innovation as a service proposition.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>How can customers get the most from their investments? What kind of support is there to help them transform and innovate?</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Customer success management is essential in the cloud. It is the end-to-end engagement with our customers, from advisory to sales execution to onboarding, adoption, and consumption. We provide the tools, assets, and content to help accelerate adoption and consumption so as to maximize the value from first use of the solution to full and future use. SAP Preferred Success services can accelerate the time to value even more. To support this motion, deep <a href="/2024/02/driving-customers-business-outcomes-telemetry">telemetry</a> being built into our cloud solutions allows customers and our customer success management leaders to better understand how the solutions are being used while identifying opportunities to expand usage.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Where do advisory services fit into the customer journey?</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Customer advisory services might be the most essential part of the journey with a customer. Successful projects start with the right business case definition, anchored in the best understanding of the industry and business of our customers. With that in mind, our Customer Advisory teams support building the right technical solutions that can support an enterprise architecture. This is the first step in moving in the right direction of building the cloud operating model.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-sap-news-on-linkedin">Connect with SAP News on LinkedIn</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news">Stay up-to-date</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-engagement</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-success</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Expanded SAP Preferred Success Services Fast-Track the Value of Cloud ERP]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/expanded-sap-preferred-success-services-fast-track-cloud-erp</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/expanded-sap-preferred-success-services-fast-track-cloud-erp</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The SAP Preferred Success service for RISE with SAP, premium can deliver more guidance and insight to help optimize cloud ERP. Find out how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a9061bfb24965c3c00629fea26b76b50e8d33ff1.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a9061bfb24965c3c00629fea26b76b50e8d33ff1.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1a9061bfb24965c3c00629fea26b76b50e8d33ff1.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Expanded SAP Preferred Success Services Fast-Track the Value of Cloud ERP" src="./media_1a9061bfb24965c3c00629fea26b76b50e8d33ff1.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="expanded-sap-preferred-success-services-fast-track-the-value-of-cloud-erp">Expanded SAP Preferred Success Services Fast-Track the Value of Cloud ERP</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Navigating disruption and uncertainty is always daunting, especially in economies and industries that evolve at different speeds. The influences of <a href="/topics/ai">AI</a>, post-globalization trends, regulatory changes, constrained capital, and other factors are impacting every region and industry, albeit at different rates and levels of severity.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>By using any of a variety of <a href="https://www.sap.com/services-support/service-offerings/preferred-success.html">SAP Preferred Success</a> services when implementing and adopting SAP S/4HANA Cloud, customers can strategically and effectively handle each change. Their efforts include 44% improved user experiences, 40% faster incident resolution, 38% better enablement and upskilling, and 38% faster time to value from their technology investments, according to a <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2023/05/18fe9a13-717e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Forrester Consulting analysis</a>.</p>
  <p>And now, with the latest offering for SAP Preferred Success, customers are going beyond navigating turbulence. They can also maximize opportunities, reduce risks, and understand how dynamic economic and market forces impact their long-term success.</p>
  <h2 id="introducing-sap-preferred-success-for-rise-with-sap-premium">Introducing SAP Preferred Success for RISE with SAP, premium</h2>
  <p>The SAP Preferred Success service for RISE with SAP, premium can deliver more guidance and insight to help accelerate and optimize the value of the cloud ERP journey, in addition to the foundational services of SAP Preferred Success.</p>
  <p>With personalized services designed to meet unique business needs proactively, customers can realize benefits, including:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Improved productivity</strong> with access to SAP knowledge and best practices</li>
    <li><strong>Accelerated ROI</strong> with tailored guidance and expert support to organize SAP solutions faster and more efficiently</li>
    <li><strong>Fewer risks</strong> by following best practice recommendations that minimize system disruptions and help ensure smooth operations</li>
    <li><strong>Better alignment</strong> by matching SAP solutions with organization goals, capitalizing on the features and innovations of every release</li>
    <li><strong>Higher efficiency</strong> by consistently fine-tuning and providing personalized recommendations aligned with specific business value drivers</li>
  </ul>
  <p>For customers such as <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/customer-stories/kyocera.html">Kyocera Document Solutions Australia</a> (Kyocera), SAP Preferred Success helps create a solid foundation for modernizing business operations. “Using SAP Preferred Success enabled us to accelerate the business acceptance of change and drive a continuous improvement landscape. It has provided an avenue to reevaluate our processes and create a more efficient business,” states Rohan Higgins, chief financial officer of Kyocera Document Solutions.</p>
  <p>As a result of the quality and caliber of the SAP expertise and active engagement, Kyocera has successfully moved 100% of its ERP processes to the cloud, leading to zero manual touchpoints across its forecasting processes. Other customers have realized additional benefits, such as more efficient business processes, smaller database sizes, infrastructure simplification, and reduction of cost centers.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="a-personalized-proactive-partnership-for-the-lifetime-of-your-cloud-solution">A personalized, proactive partnership for the lifetime of your cloud solution</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/services-support/service-offerings/preferred-success.html">Read more on SAP Preferred Success</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP Preferred Success for RISE with SAP, premium can provide additional elements for modernizing business operations, including:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>A dedicated, named enterprise adoption expert</strong> with a strong technical and functional background, who can provide expertise and help orchestrate how-to conversations supporting the build of outcome-focused plans</li>
    <li><strong>Assistance and guidance based on recommended best practices</strong> to help increase the customer’s understanding of its business processes and how the solution is being used</li>
    <li><strong>Ongoing innovation and transformation</strong> through continuous review of the customer’s calendar and plans – including the adoption of entitlements, such as business AI, sustainability, intelligent technologies exploration, and process management</li>
    <li><strong>Clean core guidance and quality checks</strong> for each project phase to help ensure the customer can leverage existing and future innovations within RISE with SAP</li>
  </ul>
  <p>With a dedicated focus on sustainability exploration, SAP Preferred Success for RISE with SAP, premium helps ensure that businesses can embrace a more sustainable future while driving growth and success in the digital age. By leveraging the comprehensive suite of tools and resources provided by SAP and orchestrated by an enterprise adoption expert, organizations can navigate their sustainability initiatives with confidence and precision.</p>
  <p>SAP Preferred Success for RISE with SAP, premium also offers a unique avenue for harnessing the transformative power of AI with cloud ERP. Through a tailored approach, customers are guided by seasoned enterprise adoption experts facilitating a comprehensive exploration of business AI. Customers are then empowered to innovate, automate, and optimize their business processes using the cutting-edge AI capabilities seamlessly integrated into the SAP ecosystem.</p>
  <p>Access to such a wealth of products, tools, and frameworks gives invaluable insights on configuring and customizing AI solutions to suit unique needs. By leveraging built-in AI capabilities from SAP, customers are not only equipped to streamline operations but also to drive innovation and achieve sustained growth in today’s dynamic business landscape.</p>
  <h2 id="accelerating-competitive-outcomes-from-cloud-erp">Accelerating Competitive Outcomes from Cloud ERP</h2>
  <p>As businesses continue to compete in an ever-evolving landscape, the need for innovative solutions that drive growth and efficiency has never been more critical. And SAP Preferred Success for RISE with SAP, premium is ready to help, offering the functional and technical guidance, personalized services, and ongoing support necessary to realize the full potential of the cloud.</p>
  <p>As demonstrated by success stories worldwide, including that of Kyocera, SAP Preferred Success for RISE with SAP, premium is helping customers not only adapt to change but also seize new opportunities for growth. This service is not just a solution; it’s a strategic partnership that can empower organizations to thrive in an ever-evolving world.</p>
  <p>Ready to amplify the impact of your cloud ERP transformation? <a href="https://sap.com/preferred-success">Visit us online</a> or contact your local SAP representative to learn more about SAP Preferred Success for RISE with SAP, premium.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Mine Ecevit is cloud ERP lead for Cloudified Services Sales and Go to Market at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-preferred-success</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[In the Era of AI, Trust Is the Essence of Business]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/era-of-ai-trust-essence-business</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/era-of-ai-trust-essence-business</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Implementing new technology like generative AI requires trust; SAP’s commitment to relevant, reliable, and responsible AI is crucial.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[DeLaval Selects SAP S/4HANA Cloud to Cultivate Cloud Benefits]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/delaval-selects-sap-s-4hana-cloud-to-cultivate-cloud-benefits</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/delaval-selects-sap-s-4hana-cloud-to-cultivate-cloud-benefits</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Global producer of dairy and farming machinery DeLaval has chosen SAP S/4HANA Cloud to transform itself into a data-driven organization.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[AI in ERP: Issues Around Trust]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/videos/ai-in-erp-issues-around-trust</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/videos/ai-in-erp-issues-around-trust</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[It’s important for companies to pay as much attention to trust as they do to technology.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/video</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Navigating Tax Requirements in the Digital Era: Manage Compliance with Cloud ERP]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/tax-transformation-in-the-digital-era-course</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/tax-transformation-in-the-digital-era-course</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[To help tax professionals prepare for and become valuable members of tax transformation projects, SAP is introducing a new course.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_12d216e0addd5a9233a73cb4294d58a8906d2b314.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_12d216e0addd5a9233a73cb4294d58a8906d2b314.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_12d216e0addd5a9233a73cb4294d58a8906d2b314.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Navigating Tax Requirements in the Digital Era: Manage Compliance with Cloud ERP" src="./media_12d216e0addd5a9233a73cb4294d58a8906d2b314.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="navigating-tax-requirements-in-the-digital-era-manage-compliance-with-cloud-erp">Navigating Tax Requirements in the Digital Era: Manage Compliance with Cloud ERP</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>As businesses adapt to digitalization, they encounter various trends reshaping tax compliance. From emerging business models to governments’ digital initiatives, the tax landscape is undergoing significant transformation.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Authorities are starting to involve themselves in business transactions, disrupting well-established business processes and taking control of the invoicing flow between suppliers and buyers. As a result, they have the data needed to prevent tax evasion and start auditing taxpayers automatically or even auto-populating tax returns moving toward tax bills. Additionally, sustainability efforts and climate change regulations further impact tax regulations.</p>
  <p>Amid these shifts, SAP can provide peace of mind to navigate complexities efficiently. By understanding the evolving tax landscape, businesses can leverage SAP solutions to help streamline compliance processes and drive automation to capitalize on emerging opportunities.</p>
  <p>SAP solutions for global tax management are tailored to help address modern tax challenges. <a href="/topics/erp">SAP S/4HANA Cloud</a> can provide transparency and compliance on a global scale, enabling businesses to embed tax requirements in processes.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="pave-the-way-to-strategic-tax-management-and-automated-compliance-with-sap">Pave the way to strategic tax management and automated compliance with SAP</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/tax-management">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Through localized solutions that offer standardized but flexible business processes, a complete suite of solutions facilitates efficient tax management, from e-invoicing to statutory reporting and overall tax compliance. With SAP technology and expertise, businesses can achieve greater accuracy and agility in tax compliance, paving the way for sustainable growth and competitive advantage.</p>
  <p>To help tax professionals prepare for and become valuable members of tax transformation projects, SAP is introducing a new course: <strong><a href="https://open.sap.com/courses/s4htax-pc">Unlocking Tax Transformation with SAP</a></strong>.</p>
  <p>The course is designed to equip professionals with the knowledge needed to navigate today’s tax landscape and learn new capabilities that can be leveraged as part of SAP S/4HANA-enabled transformations to simplify tax compliance.</p>
  <p>The course offers practical strategies to learn about the different tax types, global developments and their business relevance, and the importance of technology with a focus on SAP S/4HANA and SAP solutions for global tax management. It begins on April 30 and <a href="https://open.sap.com/courses/s4htax-pc">enrollment is now open</a>. By enrolling in this course, tax professionals can gain valuable insights into industry best practices and leverage the latest SAP innovations to help optimize their tax processes.</p>
  <p>In a time of rapid change, SAP supports businesses on their journey to tax compliance and growth. Through collaboration with SAP and a commitment to continuous learning, businesses can navigate the complexities of taxation with confidence and achieve their long-term objectives.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Erika Buson is part of Product Marketing for Global Tax Management and Entity Close at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="follow-and-connect-with-sap-news-on-linkedin">Follow and connect with SAP News on LinkedIn</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news">Stay in touch</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/financial-management</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/financial-services</category>
            <category>news-tag/opensap</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Transform with Confidence Using RISE with SAP Methodology]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/transform-confidence-rise-with-sap-methodology</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/transform-confidence-rise-with-sap-methodology</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[We're introducing a new customer onboarding experience and quality check enhancements in RISE with SAP Methodology. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1885c69bbf9dcd29bb29f03d58f391fc97b8d7c88.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1885c69bbf9dcd29bb29f03d58f391fc97b8d7c88.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1885c69bbf9dcd29bb29f03d58f391fc97b8d7c88.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Transform with Confidence Using RISE with SAP Methodology" src="./media_1885c69bbf9dcd29bb29f03d58f391fc97b8d7c88.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="transform-with-confidence-using-rise-with-sap-methodology">Transform with Confidence Using RISE with SAP Methodology</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Today we’re introducing a new customer onboarding experience and quality check enhancements in RISE with SAP Methodology. After April 1, 2024, all customers subscribing to RISE with SAP for the first time will go through this improved experience at no additional cost.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/topics/rise-with-sap">RISE with SAP</a> is a managed cloud offering that can enable customers to unlock continued innovation and transformation by modernizing their business-critical systems and processes in a highly collaborative and measurable way. This offering includes the newly announced <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/rise.html#migration">RISE with SAP Migration and Modernization program</a> that helps bring renewed focus on the cloud transformation journey by enabling smooth, secure migration of on-premise SAP ERP Central Component (SAP ECC) and SAP S/4HANA customers to the cloud. The key pillars of the program are the RISE with SAP Methodology, transformation incentives, and the innovation road map. The program features offerings tailored to each customer’s unique starting point. Its components are differentiated for SAP ECC and SAP S/4HANA customers and can run with a clean core approach, taking advantage of the latest innovations in RISE with SAP.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="cloud-solutions-infrastructure-and-services-combined-to-deliver-a-clear-cloud-migration-path">Cloud solutions, infrastructure, and services combined to deliver a clear cloud migration path</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/rise.html#migration">Explore RISE with SAP</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The cornerstone of the program is the RISE with SAP Methodology. The methodology captures the best practices of successful implementations from thousands of RISE with SAP customers over three years and is designed to provide a consistent approach – from planning to go-live to ongoing operations and evolution – that can meet customers’ business transformation goals. Whether through SAP or partner-led engagements, customers can get a clear path with specific implementation stages and success KPIs to be able to take advantage of speed, agility, and all the benefits of the cloud.</p>
  <p>Today we’re adding enhancements to the RISE with SAP Methodology, including a new onboarding experience and quality checks throughout the project implementation phases. All new RISE with SAP customers will go through this onboarding experience at no additional cost. The new experience provides guided enablement by SAP-assigned onboarding advisors and related tools and services to help customers implement their cloud ERP solutions with clarity and confidence. The onboarding advisors can guide customers through the overall process aligned with the RISE with SAP Methodology and prepare them to get started with their implementation. The new experience also helps simplify best practice implementation of the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/rise/clean-core.html">clean core</a>, helping to make it a more central, actionable, and measurable standard of all implementations. This helps ensure all RISE with SAP customers can benefit from business agility, faster innovation cycles, and improved value realization.</p>
  <p>The new improvements to the RISE with SAP Methodology include:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Expert onboarding guidance through embedded launch activities:</strong> A dedicated SAP advisor can deliver 1:1 enablement sessions to help educate customers on the RISE with SAP Methodology, clean core strategy, and related tools for implementation. Also, there are role-based, recorded enablement sessions covering business process best practices, solution architectures, and other strategic topics leading up to the go-live milestone. Check out this <a href="https://community.sap.com/t5/enterprise-resource-planning-blogs-by-sap/jumpstart-your-cloud-erp-journey-with-guided-enablement-in-rise-with-sap/ba-p/13679776">blog</a> on embedded launch activities to get a full view on what enablement resources are delivered through this new onboarding experience with RISE with SAP.</li>
    <li><strong>Clean core-focused success plan, runbook, and quality checks:</strong> We’ve developed a clean core success plan with clear milestones and KPIs. The clean core success plan is now added to the SAP Activate road map viewer, where customers – with the support of SAP advisors and partners – can review the recommended actions in uniquely created road maps, aligning their needs with best practices to help continually unlock business value faster. We’re also adding new quality gate checks to validate that the actual implementation is in line with recommended clean core best practices before customers proceed to the next project phase. The outcome of the quality gate is the SAP clean core report with feedback and recommendations on how to implement the clean core strategy. These recommendations are recorded and tracked via the updated runbook in the SAP Cloud ALM solution. To learn more, read a <a href="https://community.sap.com/t5/enterprise-resource-planning-blogs-by-sap/new-quality-check-enhancements-with-a-focus-on-clean-core-implementation/ba-p/13679681">blog post</a> on this topic.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>We’ll continue to deliver more tools, templates, training, and oversight to help make it easier for customers to execute an optimal migration or transition to the cloud and achieve their business objectives. Coming later this year is the RISE with SAP system transition workbench. This tool will help the technical implementation of migrating to cloud ERP by providing digital access to SAP-approved best practices and guidance for migrations, automation of tasks, health, and system checks. Stay tuned as we get ready to share more on this in the coming weeks.</p>
  <p>To learn more, join us for our upcoming webinar on May 23, where we will go deeper into this new onboarding experience in the RISE with SAP Methodology. Register <a href="https://event.on24.com/wcc/r/4573875/470481A80AAF443E29CBBDD9B1C29F4B/5433671?partnerref=PressRelease">here</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>Panda Priyadarsana is SVP and GM of Customer Services &#x26; Delivery and head of Cloud ERP at SAP.</p>
        <p>Photo courtesy of SAP employee Juelma Guerreiro.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="receive-weekly-news-highlights-from-the-sap-news-center">Receive weekly news highlights from the SAP News Center</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/nl/sap-news-center-newsletter/index.html">Sign up now</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[GROW with SAP: Add-On Packages Expand the Value of Cloud ERP for Growing Businesses]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/grow-with-sap-add-on-packages-expand-cloud-erp-value</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/grow-with-sap-add-on-packages-expand-cloud-erp-value</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New GROW with SAP add-on packages strengthen financial and HR management practices to become strategic pillars for growth.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/financial-management</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/grow-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[RISE with SAP: Add-On Packages Help Businesses Transform Finance and Supply Chain]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/rise-with-sap-finance-and-supply-chain-add-on-packages</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/rise-with-sap-finance-and-supply-chain-add-on-packages</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With the RISE with SAP add-on packages for finance and supply chain, customers can reap significant value from their cloud ERP investment.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/financial-management</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-supply-chain</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Driving Progress in Sustainability, Adoption, and AI: The 2024 SAP Innovation Award Winners]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2024/04/2024-sap-innovation-award-winners</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2024/04/2024-sap-innovation-award-winners</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The 2024 SAP Innovation Award winners have utilized SAP solutions and AI to achieve remarkable results. Learn more about the winners.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/executive-blog</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>sap-award/sap-innovation-awards</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Business Networks Suited to Accelerate Value from AI Applications]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/business-networks-accelerate-ai-value</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/business-networks-accelerate-ai-value</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With AI, SAP Business Network is transforming procurement, supply chain, logistics, asset management, and related operational processes.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15e0d95e80161ad4a740661b2e1b7221590a04ffa.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15e0d95e80161ad4a740661b2e1b7221590a04ffa.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_15e0d95e80161ad4a740661b2e1b7221590a04ffa.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Business Networks Suited to Accelerate Value from AI Applications" src="./media_15e0d95e80161ad4a740661b2e1b7221590a04ffa.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="business-networks-suited-to-accelerate-value-from-ai-applications">Business Networks Suited to Accelerate Value from AI Applications</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>With the gathering pace of headlines touting artificial intelligence in the business press, one could be forgiven for assuming that all facets of the enterprise stand to benefit equally from its application – everything from the electric stapler to the espresso machine to the ergonomic furniture.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>But in reality, some functions are much better suited than others to gain from AI. The deeper the reservoir of data associated with an operational process – and the broader the sharing of that data not only within an organization but among its trading partners as well – the greater the potential for AI to bolster collaborative capabilities, instill operational resilience, and unlock exponential value.</p>
  <p>By facilitating the convergence of trading partners’ operational data, cloud-based networks strengthen transparency and foster collaboration across interconnected processes such as procurement, supply chain, logistics, and asset management. The vast troves of data accumulated from these functions – and the insights they reveal – bear significant implications for forecasting demand, planning inventory, sourcing components, procuring labor, maximizing utilization, managing logistics, gauging sustainability, achieving compliance, and securing financing. Yet the sheer volume of such data, sometimes spanning billions or more transactions, can defy human interpretation in the quest to optimize decision-making.</p>
  <p>That’s where artificial intelligence comes in.</p>
  <p>As the world’s largest B2B collaboration platform, <a href="https://www.sap.com/businessnetwork">SAP Business Network</a> facilitates hundreds of millions of transactions per year, capturing a unified, end-to-end view of spend. So prodigious is the cloud-based network’s volume – exceeding US$5.3 trillion in commerce annually, greater than the gross domestic product of every nation except the United States and China – that, through innovations in predictive and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/spend-management/innovations.html#ai">generative AI</a> technologies, SAP Business Network is transforming procurement, supply chain, logistics, asset management, and related operational processes, with the goal that every business runs as an intelligent, sustainable enterprise.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-people-processes-and-systems-across-multiple-enterprises-to-digitalize-transactions">Connect people, processes, and systems across multiple enterprises to digitalize transactions</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/businessnetwork">Check out SAP Business Network</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The cloud is uniquely fit for the task of delivering simplicity within a many-to-many network of trading partners. A network’s features, from its search functionality to the matching of buyers with suggested suppliers, must aid the dual goals of transparency and ease of use. Predictive and generative AI capabilities augment businesses’ ability to discover trading partners on the basis of complementary resources, mutual value, and strategic alignment. With every successive use, generative AI sharpens its ability to anticipate operations professionals’ requirements to match supply with demand. Meanwhile, AI helps businesses to automate their most time-consuming procurement and supply chain activities through predictive mechanisms as well, hastening the ability to arrive at better, more informed decisions. When applied to the broadest possible sets of operational data, AI removes the guesswork from business-to-business commerce and replaces it with new leads, renewed confidence, and resilient supply chains.</p>
  <p>With these objectives in mind, <a href="/topics/business-network">SAP Business Network</a> is transforming its powerful discovery functionality into a simple chat prompt this year. Also in 2024, generative AI will enable SAP Business Network to create catalog content based on existing data in the network, detect potential errors within invoices, and obtain quote requests from buyers via natural-language, on-screen dialogue with matched suppliers. Integrating AI capabilities into SAP Business Network thus promises to reshape the trading partner experience by enabling buyers to reach far more suppliers with precision for the specific goods and services they produce. Trading partners large and small benefit equally from the increased flow of accurate, detailed, and complete information identifying each other’s offerings and competitive advantages.</p>
  <p>As AI technologies take shape and mature, infusing intelligence natively into business processes, digital commerce platforms are certain to introduce many enhanced capabilities. Naturally, with its scale and history of innovation, you can expect SAP Business Network to lead the way. But you’ll know the moment that artificial intelligence has truly transformed enterprise software when its features subtly blend in, almost imperceptibly, to simplify everyday operational processes, making business applications more intuitive and predictive for trading partners. That is our vision for AI at SAP Business Network, where the intelligence may be increasingly artificial but the commitment to customer success is invariably genuine.</p>
  <p>For further information on SAP Business Network and how we are equipping enterprises with AI and other digital tools needed to counter disruption, visit <a href="https://www.sap.com/businessnetwork">sap.com/businessnetwork</a> and <a href="https://www.sap.com/ai">sap.com/ai</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Jörn Keller is executive vice president and chief product officer of SAP Business Network.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-sap-news-on-linkedin-to-stay-in-touch">Connect with SAP News on LinkedIn to stay in touch</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news">Follow us</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Churchill Downs Makes Play for Growth with Cloud Solutions from SAP]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/churchill-downs-cloud-grow-with-sap</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/churchill-downs-cloud-grow-with-sap</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Churchill Downs has selected GROW with SAP to support its financial technology transformation. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_132d042893e3fab23f4d34925b1701fd3ad6ec788.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_132d042893e3fab23f4d34925b1701fd3ad6ec788.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_132d042893e3fab23f4d34925b1701fd3ad6ec788.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Churchill Downs Makes Play for Growth with Cloud Solutions from SAP" src="./media_132d042893e3fab23f4d34925b1701fd3ad6ec788.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="churchill-downs-makes-play-for-growth-with-cloud-solutions-from-sap">Churchill Downs Makes Play for Growth with Cloud Solutions from SAP</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) announced that Churchill Downs Incorporated (NSQ: CHDN, “CDI”) has selected the GROW with SAP solution to support the company’s financial technology transformation as CDI continues to grow within the racing, online wagering and gaming entertainment industries.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>CDI has chosen cloud solutions from SAP to serve as its technology foundation for the financial systems across its portfolio of 27 properties in 14 states, including Churchill Downs Racetrack (“Churchill Downs”), the home of the Kentucky Derby. CDI’s significant technology transformation builds on the company’s partnership with SAP as a signature partner and the first official technology partner serving Churchill Downs, the Kentucky Derby and the Kentucky Oaks.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-s4hana-cloud-public-edition-ready-to-run-cloud-erp">SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition: Ready-to-run cloud ERP</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/s4hana.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>By adopting SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition, CDI can benefit from the ready-to-run cloud ERP that delivers the latest industry best practices and continuous innovation. Additionally, choosing SAP Business Technology Platform and SAP SuccessFactors solutions allows CDI to leverage the cloud to streamline its data sources while using business data to make informed strategic decisions underpinning business transformation. From creating engaging employee experiences with SAP SuccessFactors solutions to running business analytics to understand and predict data, CDI plans to be able to integrate business data from various acquisitions, allowing it to have one, unified view of its business operations.</p>
  <p>“Cloud solutions from SAP will enable us to streamline our financial processes and support the significant long-term growth of our company,” said Marcia Dall, CDI Executive Vice President and Chief Financial Officer. “We are excited to work with SAP to innovate and evolve our financial technology platform with cloud solutions from SAP.”</p>
  <p>“Churchill Downs Incorporated has a long history of entertaining and delighting people,” SAP North America President Lloyd Adams said. “By choosing SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition and several other cloud-based solutions, CDI now can integrate data across its portfolio and make data-driven decisions that help the company reach its goals. This is an incredible example of how companies invest in SAP solutions to help them grow.”</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="http://news.sap.com/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Media Contacts:</strong><br>Mallory Kuno, +1 (425) 239-9362, <a href="mailto:mallory.kuno@sap.com">mallory.kuno@sap.com</a>, ET<br>Lesa Plingen, +49 622 776 9000, <a href="mailto:lesa.plingen@sap.com">lesa.plingen@sap.com</a>, CET<br><a href="mailto:SAP%20Press%20Room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>This document contains forward-looking statements, which are predictions, projections, or other statements about future events. These statements are based on current expectations, forecasts, and assumptions that are subject to risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results and outcomes to materially differ. Additional information regarding these risks and uncertainties may be found in our filings with the Securities and Exchange Commission, including but not limited to the risk factors section of SAP’s 2023 Annual Report on Form 20-F.<br>© 2024 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>news-tag/grow-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Combine the Power of AI with Business Context Using SAP HANA Cloud Vector Engine]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2024/04/sap-hana-cloud-vector-engine-ai-with-business-context</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2024/04/sap-hana-cloud-vector-engine-ai-with-business-context</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The latest quarterly release introduces the SAP HANA Cloud vector engine, enhancing capabilities with AI technology to tackle complex issues.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/executive-blog</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP's Adoption Revolution: When Expectations and Outcomes for Cloud Transformation Meet]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2024/04/cloud-transformation-adoption-revolution-expectations-outcomes-meet</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2024/04/cloud-transformation-adoption-revolution-expectations-outcomes-meet</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The new Customer Services & Delivery Board area at SAP will make it easier and faster for customers to adopt cloud solutions.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/executive-blog</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>