<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/quantum-computing/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Quantum-Inspired Solution for Enterprise Optimization]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/quantum-inspired-computing-enterprise-optimization</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/quantum-inspired-computing-enterprise-optimization</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP and Fujitsu collaborated to test out Fujitsu’s new quantum-inspired computing solution for optimization. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>news-tag/quantum-computing</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Experts at the Forefront of Quantum Computing Exploration]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/sap-experts-at-forefront-quantum-computing-exploration</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/sap-experts-at-forefront-quantum-computing-exploration</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is collaborating with forward-thinking innovators to discover how quantum computers can solve industry-specific business problems.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/quantum-computing</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Milestone Toward Quantum for Enterprise Applications]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/vehicle-space-quantum-poc-enterprise-applications</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/vehicle-space-quantum-poc-enterprise-applications</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP recently presented the integration of IBM Quantum services into the vehicle space optimization component as a proof of concept.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/enterprise-applications</category>
            <category>news-tag/quantum-computing</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Quantum Tech 2022: A Stampede of Unicorns Is Headed for Your Industry]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/04/quantum-tech-2022</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/04/quantum-tech-2022</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Quantum technologies will become practical business tools with benefits for many industries addressing seemingly intractable societal issues.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/quantum-computing</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP and Quantum Technologies]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/sap-and-quantum-technologies</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/sap-and-quantum-technologies</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Quantum technologies may currently seem like no more than a speck on the horizon, but SAP has the megatrend firmly in its sights.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11225dca7729fd160462e16d3527d33d50f4ad2cb.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11225dca7729fd160462e16d3527d33d50f4ad2cb.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_11225dca7729fd160462e16d3527d33d50f4ad2cb.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP and Quantum Technologies" src="./media_11225dca7729fd160462e16d3527d33d50f4ad2cb.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-and-quantum-technologies">SAP and Quantum Technologies</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Minus 273°Celsius: That’s how cold it needs to be for a quantum computer to operate. These highly sensitive devices also need protection from external influences, such as temperature changes and radiation; otherwise, they may simply stop working. It’s hard to imagine that these machines and the technologies they will enable might soon be competing with classical computers on certain tasks.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Will quantum computers usher in a <a href="https://www.iks.fraunhofer.de/en/topics/quantum-computing.html">golden age of information technology</a>? Which quantum technologies can SAP deploy? The SAP Security Research team is tasked with looking into these questions and exploring ways of harnessing the exponential computer power quantum computing promises. At the same time, protecting business-critical data must remain a priority, because as quantum computing advances, its raw computing power poses an increasing threat to today’s encryption schemes as quantum technologies might decode them relatively quickly.</p>
  <p>“We began looking into quantum technologies about five years ago. We’re now examining its implications for areas such as data security,” says Andrey Hoursanov, strategy lead for Quantum Technology at SAP Security Research.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="what-businesses-need-to-consider-today-to-prepare-for-the-quantum-era">What Businesses Need to Consider Today to Prepare for the Quantum Era</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/08/prepare-for-the-quantum-era">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="quantum-computers-are-quicker-and-not-binary">Quantum Computers Are Quicker and Not Binary</h2>
  <p>Experts agree on the huge potential of quantum technologies, which comprise quantum computing, communication, simulation, sensing, and post-quantum cryptography. According to a <a href="https://www.consultancy.uk/news/24361/quantum-computing-market-to-reach-1-trillion-by-2035">study by McKinsey</a>, quantum computing could have a global market value of US$1 trillion by 2035.</p>
  <p>Already, annual investments across the world are estimated to be <a href="https://www.qureca.com/overview-on-quantum-initiatives-worldwide/">US$22.5 billion</a>, and analysts at IDC <a href="https://blogs.idc.com/2019/12/02/top-10-worldwide-enterprise-infrastructure-2021-predictions/">predict</a> that 25% of the Fortune Global 500 will gain competitive advantage from quantum computing by 2023.</p>
  <p>Quantum computing represents a paradigm shift in data processing. A classical computer is an electronic device that processes information in binary bits that can assume only one of two possible states, 1 or 0. By contrast, the processes in a quantum computer take place at the physical particle level. The basic units of information in a quantum computer are quantum bits, or “qubits.” They follow the laws of superposition, interference, and entanglement, which means that they can occupy more than one state at the same time and are interdependent – allowing data to be processed simultaneously rather than sequentially. Computing power might <a href="https://www.iks.fraunhofer.de/en/topics/quantum-computing.html">increase exponentially</a> for some algorithms with each additional qubit.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>Learn more: <a href="/2019/02/understanding-quantum-technology">What is Quantum Technology?</a></p>
        <p>“If quantum technologies realize their potential, we may in the future be able to solve complex tasks that even the most powerful supercomputers fail at today,” says <a href="/2021/08/prepare-for-the-quantum-era">Martin Heinig</a>, head of New Ventures and Technologies at SAP.</p>
        <p>In logistics, for example, the optimal route, mode of transportation, and product quantity for deliveries could be identified at each point in the supply chain and updated in real time as conditions change. For other industries too, enterprise software solutions from SAP could simulate business processes more easily and infinitely faster.</p>
        <p>Quantum technologies could also massively accelerate machine learning in SAP solutions by making artificial intelligence (AI) super-intelligent and allowing training data to be fed into the software more quickly.</p>
        <h2 id="making-conventional-encryption-quantum-safe">Making Conventional Encryption Quantum-Safe</h2>
        <table>
          <thead>
            <tr>
              <th colspan="2">Promo</th>
            </tr>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td>
                <h3 id="learn-more-about-the-sap-innovation-center-network">Learn more about the SAP Innovation Center Network</h3>
              </td>
              <td><strong><a href="https://icn.sap.com/">Learn more</a></strong></td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
        <p>But the benefits of the immense computing power promised by quantum technologies also pose a major challenge to conventional encryption methods. Encryption schemes that were considered safe by classical computing standards are no match for quantum computing paradigms. Quantum hackers could use this immense computing power to quickly crack encryption keys in conventional cryptographic systems, read encrypted messages, and create fake signatures. Customers expect SAP to ensure the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of their business-critical data and processes at all times.</p>
        <p>For SAP, preparing for the quantum era means securing critical and sensitive data using post-quantum and quantum-resistant cryptosystems.</p>
        <p>SAP continuously analyzes new cryptographic algorithms and has already developed several proofs of concept to test the feasibility of algorithms that researchers have deemed “quantum-safe” and capable of guarding against hacker attacks, data leaks, and espionage.</p>
        <h2 id="what-sap-is-doing">What SAP Is Doing</h2>
        <p>SAP has been conducting research into quantum technologies for many years and has built up considerable expertise in the process.</p>
        <p>According to Hoursanov, who has been driving SAP’s quantum technologies initiative from the get-go: “Many customers are already asking where SAP is on its quantum tech journey. After all, we have shared interests in exploiting the technology. It’s about optimizing supply chains, logistics, warehouse management, perhaps portfolio optimization in financial services. And, finally, it’s about data security.”</p>
        <p>The SAP Security Research team is highly committed to the quantum security community. They prototyped embedding a quantum-safe signature scheme for software packages. And their work on identifying use cases and weak points in quantum communication involves checking data during transmission and the key distribution and management infrastructure.</p>
        <p>Making quantum technologies commercially viable requires cooperation between industry and academia and involvement in multidisciplinary consortia. SAP is part of the <a href="https://qt.eu/">EU Quantum Flagship</a>, one of the EU’s largest research initiatives, and a founding member of both the <a href="https://qt.eu/about-quantum-flagship/the-quantum-flagship-community/quic/">European Quantum Industry Consortium</a> and the <a href="https://www.qutac.de/?lang=en">Quantum Technology and Application Consortium</a>, where it is working with leading experts, quantum technology players, and future consumers of quantum technologies – many of which are SAP customers.</p>
        <p>Although quantum technologies cannot yet be fully deployed for practical reasons, it is already clear that they offer enormous opportunities in data processing, particularly when it comes to secure communication and solving complex problems efficiently. SAP has a significant stake in this exploration journey.</p>
        <table>
          <thead>
            <tr>
              <th>Promo</th>
            </tr>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td>Hoursanov shares his point of view on some frequently asked questions about quantum technologies.</td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/quantum-computing</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[What Businesses Need to Consider Today to Prepare for the Quantum Era]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/prepare-for-the-quantum-era</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/prepare-for-the-quantum-era</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 16 Aug 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[To prepare for the quantum era, SAP is working with leading experts and quantum technology players in academia and industry on developments.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18dacefe3a1724d79f5c851489294e522ea541aa1.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18dacefe3a1724d79f5c851489294e522ea541aa1.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_18dacefe3a1724d79f5c851489294e522ea541aa1.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="What Businesses Need to Consider Today to Prepare for the Quantum Era" src="./media_18dacefe3a1724d79f5c851489294e522ea541aa1.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="what-businesses-need-to-consider-today-to-prepare-for-the-quantum-era">What Businesses Need to Consider Today to Prepare for the Quantum Era</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Quantum technology has enormous potential for science, industry, and society. The research in this area has gained strong momentum in recent years, sparking a <a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/technology/2021/04/07/duality-quantum-startup-accelerator/">mini startup boom</a>. Quantum computing is of particular importance here. With the rise of quantum computing we might be able to solve complex tasks in the future that even the most powerful supercomputers fail at today.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The most discussed use cases for quantum computers are the ones where complex models that require enormous combinatorial computation power are applied to a problem. This includes combinatorial optimization problems such as supply chain logistics, where coordinating and identifying the most efficient route for goods to travel to market has been one of the most sought-after goals for both business and science.</p>
  <p>Another domain of application could be financial services, where market prediction models are used for predicting important, disruptive events to the broader economy to drive portfolio decisions. Quantum computing is also expected to enhance machine learning, which may accelerate for instance the training of neural networks.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-innovation-center-network-curiosity-courage-determination">SAP Innovation Center Network: Curiosity, Courage, Determination</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://icn.sap.com/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="still-in-early-days-but-advancing-fast">Still in Early Days, but Advancing Fast</h2>
  <p>Quantum computing is a multi-year journey. While the quantum computing market is expected to reach <a href="https://analyticsindiamag.com/top-countries-pumping-money-into-quantum-computing-technology/">$1.7 billion by 2026</a>, nobody yet knows when we will see widespread adoption at an enterprise scale. Companies including IBM, Google, Honeywell, and IonQ are making progress harnessing quantum-computational units (qubits) for early-stage computers.</p>
  <p>However, it is still unclear when a general-purpose quantum computer superior to classical computers in solving business-relevant problems will be available. Several major technical and conceptual challenges need to be overcome first including increasing the number of qubits, while keeping or extending their coherence-time (useful time) and their inter-connectivity.</p>
  <p>SAP’s approach is to work with leading experts and quantum technology players in academia and industry on developments in this field. We are assessing the timescale as well as potential domains of application and how they might impact the future of SAP and our customers.</p>
  <h2 id="now-is-the-time-to-prepare-for-the-quantum-era">Now Is the Time to Prepare for the Quantum Era</h2>
  <p>While quantum computing opens many new doors in a wide variety of fields, it can also be a security threat. With the advances in quantum computing, conventional cryptographic schemes are becoming more vulnerable. That’s why it’s critical for businesses to prepare for post-quantum cryptography today that is resistant to attacks by both classical and quantum computers. The SAP Security Research team in the <a href="https://icn.sap.com/">SAP Innovation Center Network</a> is highly engaged in quantum security and currently works on benchmarking post-quantum cryptography algorithms and more.</p>
  <p>Cryptography is the last line of defense against data breaches. When all other security measures have failed, encryption provides the last barrier that protects company secrets against unauthorized access. The current progress in the development of quantum computers and their ability to break conventional encryption schemes requires companies to act now. Considering the longevity of sensitive information in government affairs or the pharmaceutical industry, this data could be collected today and stored until a powerful quantum computer is available to decrypt them.</p>
  <p>To be prepared once a quantum computer becomes available, businesses need to think ahead. A good starting point is a relevance and impact analysis to help plan for the inevitability of consequences and their cost. This analysis also includes identifying uses cases that could benefit from applying quantum computing. The better equipped businesses are to recognize and prepare for the opportunities and risks posed by quantum computing, the more likely they are to be able to continue doing business in the future. Businesses are then well advised to work closely with industry leaders and academic partners to exchange research results, build strategic road maps, and find common applications and use cases in different areas.</p>
  <h2 id="no-business-can-do-it-alone">No Business Can Do It Alone</h2>
  <p>SAP works with industry leaders and top research centers and participates in several initiatives to explore quantum technology and potential use cases. For instance, SAP has been involved in the <a href="https://qt.eu/">EU Quantum Flagship</a> from the beginning and is a founding member of the <a href="https://qt.eu/about-quantum-flagship/the-quantum-flagship-community/quic/">European Quantum Industry Consortium</a> (QuIC), and others.</p>
  <p>Most recently, SAP joined the new <a href="https://www.qutac.de/?lang=en">Quantum Technology and Application Consortium</a> (QUTAC) along with global corporations such as BASF, BMW, Bosch, and others to advance developments in quantum computing for practical application. Within QUTAC, SAP will drive the use of quantum computing in logistics, production, or procurement. Our focus is on developing software applications to optimize transport routes, supply chains, or production plans. This can help companies reduce costs, improve delivery reliability, or avoid empty runs.</p>
  <p>At SAP, we work to leverage the advances in quantum tech for our customers while protecting their business-critical data. I’m excited for the quantum future ahead of us — stay tuned for more to come!</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Martin Heinig is head of New Ventures and Technologies at SAP.</em><br><em>This piece was originally published on LinkedIn.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/quantum-computing</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-innovation-center-network</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[You Don’t Have to Be a Physicist to Unleash the Business Power of Quantum Tech]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/unleash-business-power-quantum-technologies</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/unleash-business-power-quantum-technologies</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The next era of quantum technologies promises a huge leap forward for business innovation as experts launch a quantum industry network.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ba863d34171f39623e458a2a76994036bf718c84.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ba863d34171f39623e458a2a76994036bf718c84.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1ba863d34171f39623e458a2a76994036bf718c84.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="You Don’t Have to Be a Physicist to Unleash the Business Power of Quantum Tech" src="./media_1ba863d34171f39623e458a2a76994036bf718c84.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="you-dont-have-to-be-a-physicist-to-unleash-the-business-power-of-quantum-tech">You Don’t Have to Be a Physicist to Unleash the Business Power of Quantum Tech</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Although <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2019/02/28/what-is-quantum-technology/?sh=528b6588606a">quantum technologies</a> may not boast an established market or industry standards – let alone dominant players – that’s all about to change. Optimistic global <a href="https://www.consultancy.uk/news/24361/quantum-computing-market-to-reach-1-trillion-by-2035">forecasts</a> tout quantum computing’s potential to revolutionize industries while an eclectic group of experts in Europe just launched a quantum industry network.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="intelligent-enterprises-are-changing-the-world-for-the-better">Intelligent enterprises are changing the world for the better</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/intelligent-enterprise.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="unleashing-your-inner-quantum-physicist">Unleashing Your Inner Quantum Physicist</h2>
  <p>You don’t necessarily have to understand the intricacies of quantum physics to experience its value. Anyone that’s had an MRI has benefited from <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2019/02/28/what-is-quantum-technology/?sh=5997e9ad606a">quantum sensing</a>, which has been around for decades in medical diagnostics. Quantum computing, quantum simulation, and quantum internet are advancing at different levels of maturity.</p>
  <p>“Quantum technologies take the faster, better innovation race of the past 75 years to another innovation level,” said Laure Le Bars, research project director at SAP. “In this second revolution, we’ll understand the theory behind it better and be able to control it more with a progressive, incremental approach, collaborating to explore the possibilities and benefit from each other’s ideas.”</p>
  <h2 id="quantum-tech-innovation-network">Quantum Tech Innovation Network</h2>
  <p>Le Bars was recently appointed president of the <a href="https://qt.eu/about-quantum-flagship/the-quantum-flagship-community/quic/">European Quantum Industry Consortium (QuIC)</a>, a non-profit organization dedicated to explore quantum innovation for the region and, by extension, worldwide. Founded to serve as a collaborative network of networks, QuIC’s members come from companies of all sizes and industries, including small and mid-sized businesses (SMBs), venture capitalists, academia, research, government, and industrial associations.</p>
  <p>“Building a strong community of quantum technology experts from all sectors is the best way to boost European industry competitiveness,” said Le Bars. “We will support excellence in research and business as we help bring structure and continuity to quantum technology research, innovation, and eventual development and deployment of these technologies.”</p>
  <h2 id="equitable-platform-for-quantum-exploration">Equitable Platform for Quantum Exploration</h2>
  <p>As a co-founding member of QuIC, SAP’s strategy is aligned with the association’s commitment to business networks for fair and equitable innovation that helps organizations become <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/intelligent-enterprise.html">intelligent enterprises</a>.</p>
  <p>For example, it’s no coincidence that two-thirds of the organization’s current members are SMBs and startups. The QuIC ecosystem was designed to attract SMBs, giving them entrée to the latest technologies and a strong market voice. <a href="https://www.pwc.fr/fr/assets/files/pdf/2019/11/en-france-pwc-point-of-view-quantum-computing-2019.pdf">Research</a> shows that startups (40%) and universities (33%) comprise the majority of players involved with quantum computing.</p>
  <p>“We’re providing SMBs with direct access to the expertise of our members who can share their knowledge and clout across industries, academia, and government,” said Le Bars. “They can exchange ideas and might even find project partners to develop solutions for customers. <a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/industry-cloud.html">SAP’s industry cloud</a> is a perfect example of the power of networks for fast innovation.”</p>
  <h2 id="collaboration-with-european-commission-to-fuel-quantum-progress">Collaboration with European Commission to Fuel Quantum Progress</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="quantum-computers-challenge-blockchains-invincibility">Quantum Computers Challenge Blockchain’s Invincibility</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2020/06/quantum-resistant-blockchain-invincibility-challenge">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>QuIC is also collaborating with the <a href="https://ec.europa.eu/info/index_en">European Commission</a> as part of that organization’s commitment to regional quantum technology progress.</p>
  <p>“We want to work with a representative group of companies to help bring research out of the lab and into the real world with practical applications across industrialized products,” said Dr. Gustav Kalbe, head of the High Performance Computing and Quantum Technologies unit at the European Commission. “QuIC helps us understand what support the industry needs, allowing us to develop EU policies that facilitate market entry and opportunity materialization.”</p>
  <h2 id="opening-the-doors-to-quantum-technologies">Opening the Doors to Quantum Technologies</h2>
  <p>Dr Kalbe’s unit at the European Commission develops and carries out the organization’s policies on high performance computing and quantum technologies. A long-time European Commission official, Dr Kalbe has been involved in the agency’s quantum-related policy initiatives since its start in quantum information processing and communications (QIPC) over 20 years ago.</p>
  <p>“Bringing together the industry at-large, we can foster a virtuous cycle of continuous innovation between organizations making the machines and those who will use them,” he said. “We can collectively address use cases, manufacturing ability, product usability, interoperability, and standardization. As different industry players interact on pre-built operating systems with testing and pilots, they’ll have more time to target the next level of complexity, integrating new components for faster market growth from quantum advantage.”</p>
  <p>QuIC has designated working groups to build strategic industry road maps, identify gaps in the quantum technology sector, and explore applications and use cases. Some groups will explore pre-standardization and IP-related issues that typify new industries.</p>
  <p>“We’re not defining IP or standards, but our members will collaborate with other stakeholders like standardization bodies and each other to discuss what baselines are needed for quantum technology advancement,” said Le Bars. “Similarly, we won’t become a university, but we’ll collaborate with institutions of higher learning to define the people skills we need and share that with educational organizations that are defining curricula.”</p>
  <h2 id="quantum-tech-made-easy-for-business">Quantum Tech Made Easy for Business</h2>
  <p>The good news for business leaders is that you won’t have to be a quantum physicist to use these technologies as they emerge.</p>
  <p>“Pioneers are asking questions about how to integrate quantum with their products and business plans,” said Dr. Kalbe. “Many industries will see results from the brilliant entrepreneurs and engineers who will find the most innovative and unexpected ways of using quantum technologies in everyday business.”</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Follow me @smgaler</em><br><em><a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2021/06/28/you-dont-have-to-be-a-physicist-to-unleash-the-business-power-of-quantum-tech/?sh=3d7cdd6d442a">This blog also appeared on SAP BrandVoice on Forbes</a>.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
            <category>news-tag/quantum-computing</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>