<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/asset-management/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cloud-Based Visibility Equips Trading Partners to Counter Supply Chain Disruption]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/cloud-based-business-networks-equip-trading-partners</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/cloud-based-business-networks-equip-trading-partners</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Enterprises rely increasingly on cloud-based business networks to extend visibility, facilitate collaboration, and stay ahead of disruption.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17eccb1dbc9662324e6f79b18766a0335800c285f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17eccb1dbc9662324e6f79b18766a0335800c285f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_17eccb1dbc9662324e6f79b18766a0335800c285f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Cloud-Based Visibility Equips Trading Partners to Counter Supply Chain Disruption" src="./media_17eccb1dbc9662324e6f79b18766a0335800c285f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="cloud-based-visibility-equips-trading-partners-to-counter-supply-chain-disruption">Cloud-Based Visibility Equips Trading Partners to Counter Supply Chain Disruption</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>With geopolitical conflict and climate change roiling global shipping corridors from the <a href="https://www.arabnews.com/node/2463151/business-economy">Suez Canal</a> to <a href="https://www.reuters.com/business/panama-canal-does-not-plan-transit-restrictions-least-until-april-2024-02-07">Panama</a> and <a href="https://apnews.com/article/persian-gulf-oman-strait-hormuz-3a906e909be2ce63c87c1b208ed05baa">elsewhere</a>, enterprises rely increasingly on cloud-based business networks and artificial intelligence (AI) applications to extend visibility, facilitate collaboration, and ensure they stay one step ahead of the looming threat of disruption.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Meanwhile, as legislation to bolster transparency in supply chains <a href="https://www.bundesregierung.de/breg-en/service/archive/supply-chain-act-1872076">takes</a> <a href="https://minister.homeaffairs.gov.au/jasonwood/Pages/modern-slavery-act-delivers-transparency-in-supply-chains.aspx">hold</a> <a href="https://oag.ca.gov/SB657">around</a> <a href="https://laws.justice.gc.ca/eng/acts/F-10.6">the</a> <a href="https://www.consilium.europa.eu/en/press/press-releases/2023/12/14/corporate-sustainability-due-diligence-council-and-parliament-strike-deal-to-protect-environment-and-human-rights">world</a>, the digital platforms through which trading partners carry out interconnected operational processes have become indispensable for managing risk, advancing sustainability objectives, and verifying adherence to ethical business practices – even as volatility in international commerce gathers pace.</p>
  <p>After rebounding from several years of logjammed seaports, idled factories, and quarantined workers, many businesses find that though COVID-19 has receded, disruption stubbornly persists. Yet visibility across all aspects of the supply chain – from sourcing raw materials and managing logistics capacity to securing working capital solutions and managing dispersed physical assets – remains paramount in the quest to ensure business continuity, instill operational resilience, and deepen competitive advantage.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-business-network-powers-transparency-resiliency-and-sustainability">SAP Business Network powers transparency, resiliency, and sustainability</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-network.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>To help provide businesses with the 360-degree visibility and collaborative capabilities they require across complex trading relationships, SAP Business Network can connect people, processes, and systems across multiple enterprises to help digitize transactions, harness data-driven insights, and create transparent, resilient, and sustainable supply chains. Through <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-network/solutions.html#active_tab_item_1602592051931">SAP Business Network for Procurement</a>, trading partners can gain process efficiencies, improve supply assurance, and achieve business process and regulatory compliance by increasing operational transparency. With <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-network/solutions.html#active_tab_item_1602592257238">SAP Business Network Supply Chain Collaboration</a>, companies can achieve supply chain visibility by enabling plan-driven automation, optimizing capacity and inventory, and streamlining workflow. Aided by <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-network/solutions.html#active_tab_item_1602592296240">SAP Business Network for Logistics</a>, shippers and carriers can work together in unison, track and trace goods in transit, and achieve transparency throughout the supply chain by optimizing logistics processes, increasing on-time deliveries, and mitigating third-party risk. Relying on <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-network/solutions.html#active_tab_item_1660146110353">SAP Business Network Asset Collaboration</a>, owners, operators, and service providers can strengthen joint processes and the flow of shared information through a single, consistent version of asset master data to help streamline asset maintenance processes and reduce maintenance costs. With the benefit of <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-network/solutions.html#active_tab_item_1660146142567">SAP Business Network for Finance</a>, trading partners can enhance payment security, free up working capital through early-payment discounts, and leverage access to capital bound up in outstanding receivables.</p>
  <p>By linking together the routine business processes of trading partners, cloud-based networks establish the breadth of data necessary to apply predictive and generative AI applications to yield meaningful insights and outcomes. Through large language models and other forms of machine learning, cloud-based applications create new content with characteristics resembling that which precedes it. With every successive effort, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/spend-management/innovations.html#ai">generative AI</a> sharpens its ability to tailor desired content.</p>
  <p>As the world’s largest platform for business-to-business commerce, SAP Business Network can present an ideal setting for generative AI, in that it helps bring together an extremely large volume of trading partners across hundreds of millions of transactions representing US$5.3 trillion in commerce annually. Later this year, generative AI capabilities in SAP Business Network will be able to help detect errors and present automatic summaries when businesses create invoices. AI will also enable the network to help enrich catalog content and discovery posting responses for suppliers.</p>
  <p>SAP Business Network has accumulated significant structured content over many years to help generate broad operational insights for trading partners. When buyers, suppliers, carriers, and financing solution providers share operational data with each other in real time, the mutual value they create can be exponential rather than additive, enabling all participants in commerce to plan ahead with confidence, continuity, and enduring resilience.</p>
  <p>For further information on SAP Business Network and how we are equipping enterprises large and small with the digital tools needed to counter disruption, visit <a href="https://www.sap.com/businessnetwork">sap.com/businessnetwork</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Jörn Keller is executive vice president and chief product officer of SAP Business Network.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="stay-in-touch-and-follow-sap-news-on-linkedin">Stay in touch and follow SAP News on LinkedIn</h3>
        <p><em><a href="">Join us on LinkedIn</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/asset-management</category>
            <category>industry/travel-transportation</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-network-for-logistics</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Jowat Doubles Productivity with Smarter Maintenance and Strategic Insight into Asset Management]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/jowat-smarter-maintenance-strategic-insight-asset-management</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/jowat-smarter-maintenance-strategic-insight-asset-management</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With SAP solutions, Jowat empowered its technicians to prioritize work more effectively and make smarter decisions about asset investments.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/asset-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-enterprise-support</category>
            <category>product/sap-integrated-business-planning-for-supply-chain</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Roche Connects Asset Data to Contextualize and Improve Every Decision]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/roche-asset-data-contextualize-improve-decisions</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/roche-asset-data-contextualize-improve-decisions</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Pharmaceutical company Roche has been improving its asset management and maintenance processes with the help of SAP solutions.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f4368188f69034eaee3b53188d1e3cd047f4908b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f4368188f69034eaee3b53188d1e3cd047f4908b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1f4368188f69034eaee3b53188d1e3cd047f4908b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Roche Connects Asset Data to Contextualize and Improve Every Decision" src="./media_1f4368188f69034eaee3b53188d1e3cd047f4908b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="roche-connects-asset-data-to-contextualize-and-improve-every-decision">Roche Connects Asset Data to Contextualize and Improve Every Decision</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>In a recent webinar, Iago Accioli, project manager of Assets at Roche, discussed how the pharmaceutical company has been improving its asset management and maintenance processes from a broader supply chain perspective.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="https://www.roche.com/about/">Roche</a> is one of the world’s largest biotech companies, a leading provider of in-vitro diagnostics and a global supplier of transformative, innovative solutions across major disease areas.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="find-a-balance-between-performance-cost-and-risk-with-sap-asset-performance-management">Find a balance between performance, cost, and risk with SAP Asset Performance Management</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/apm.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="cost-as-a-main-driver-for-asset-intensive-organizations">Cost as a Main Driver for Asset-Intensive Organizations</h2>
  <p>“As a pharmaceutical company, Roche was founded more than 100 years ago in Basel, Switzerland, with both pharma and diagnostics divisions. We are in the middle of an <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/s4hana.html">SAP S/4HANA</a> journey with the goal to harmonize business processes on all sites and divisions around the world,” said Accioli.</p>
  <p>To <a href="/topics/asset-management">manage assets</a> under volatile conditions effectively, just like other asset-intensive organizations, Roche focuses on <strong>reducing maintenance cost</strong> and <strong>increasing asset reliability</strong>, which are key to its customers and patients.</p>
  <p>The challenge is “the handover from original manufacturer to engineering to maintenance and how to interact with each other,” explained Accioli. “We resolve this with these business process harmonization initiatives.”</p>
  <h2 id="risk-resilience-as-an-investment-for-the-future">Risk Resilience as an Investment for the Future</h2>
  <p>SAP suggests three strategies to help companies manage their business holistically, including cost, speed, profit, customer service, and risk:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Connecting supply chains</strong> to the entire business so that information insight flows go quickly from operations to manufacturing, design, and into the business to respond to disruptions</li>
    <li><strong>Contextualizing information</strong> during the work process to equip users with technology to get real-time insights and make decisions during the business process to increase impact</li>
    <li><strong>Collaborating externally</strong> with suppliers, asset operators, OEMs, and logistics providers to ensure that information is flowing beyond the internal network to set up a risk-resilient business while mitigating risk</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="closing-the-loop-between-strategy-and-execution">Closing the Loop Between Strategy and Execution</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="watch-a-video-to-learn-more-about-enterprise-asset-management">Watch a video to learn more about enterprise asset management</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2020/10/9870e39a-b97d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Managing costs and increasing equipment reliability is a major factor and closing the loop between asset strategy and maintenance execution, such as to make assets more reliable and connected to maintenance execution considering different asset type, is a big opportunity.</p>
  <p>“Five to 10 years ago, reliability engineering became a shining topic at Roche, and we discussed where to start, how much we spend on maintenance, what our most important assets were, and where we should spend more energy and money. We standardized processes to classify our equipment into different asset criticalities – high, medium, and low – and, based on each category, we established a maintenance strategy,” explained Accioli.</p>
  <p>“Afterwards, we looked for a tool that would best suit Roche given the amount of data. Now we have an asset and maintenance strategy in place that is reflected in our system. In 2019, we started harmonizing our processes and were pleased that SAP solutions could support us,” he continued.</p>
  <p>In particular, Roche looked to:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/asset-strategy-performance.html">SAP Asset Strategy and Performance Management</a>, which helps with performing criticality evaluations directly in the SAP system instead of spreadsheets. With criticality results reflected in the system, the maintenance strategy can result in preventive maintenance plans. “Roche is in the middle of the journey. No sites are live yet,” said Accioli. Roche is also enabling access to its service providers to get design insights and improve collaboration.</li>
    <li><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/asset-manager.html">SAP Service and Asset Manager</a>, which enables maintenance plans and work orders to be accessible to maintenance technicians so that they can make instant material reservations and get access to maintenance manuals on mobile devices.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>“I expect a significant <strong>decrease of maintenance execution</strong> as we can plan our work better thanks to a mobile-supported solution,” said Accioli. “The experience with the solution is quite good.”</p>
  <p>Roche was already using SAP at different sites with its own work order types and data model, but it was not automated and connected.</p>
  <p>“We also intend to migrate to <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/apm.html">SAP Asset Performance Management</a>, a successor cloud-based application, where Roche’s enhancement ideas have been incorporated,” explained the manager.</p>
  <h2 id="connected-asset-data-helps-contextualize-business-decisions">Connected Asset Data Helps Contextualize Business Decisions</h2>
  <p>For contextualizing every business process through the eyes of maintenance, it is necessary to converge enterprise IT data with equipment and sensor data to run analyses based on algorithms and machine learning technology. Accioli explained: “Being able to schedule maintenance activities is a substantial improvement for maintenance organizations. To monitor both targets and results, we are using <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/cloud-analytics/features.html">SAP Analytics Cloud</a>, which has many good capabilities. We are developing maintenance KPIs with the insights we get from artificial intelligence (AI) and rolling these back into the asset strategy and reliability process. These are particularly good tools.”</p>
  <h2 id="effective-collaboration-across-the-ecosystem-to-build-a-collaborative-supply-chain">Effective Collaboration Across the Ecosystem to Build a Collaborative Supply Chain</h2>
  <p>“For Roche, sharing information and effective collaboration with asset providers and across our ecosystem is particularly important. Vendors and different equipment suppliers must exchange and collaborate on asset data. Operators and service providers should be able to use the network but also manage the work order process,” said Accioli.</p>
  <p>To summarize, the key benefits of SAP Asset Strategy and Performance Management and SAP Service and Asset Manager Accioli sees are:</p>
  <p><strong>SAP Asset Strategy and Performance Management:</strong></p>
  <ul>
    <li>Defining which maintenance strategy applies to which classification of equipment</li>
    <li>Maintaining assessments in the system</li>
    <li>Generating criticality based on assessments</li>
    <li>Reflecting reliability-centered maintenance in the system, including decision trees and supportive templates</li>
  </ul>
  <p><strong>SAP Service and Asset Manager:</strong></p>
  <ul>
    <li>Being a digitized, automated, paperless solution</li>
    <li>Being able to work offline</li>
    <li>Having all maintenance data at hand in one place</li>
  </ul>
  <p>Listen to the webinar recording <a href="https://event.on24.com/eventRegistration/console/apollox/mainEvent?&#x26;eventid=4174635&#x26;sessionid=1&#x26;username=&#x26;partnerref=&#x26;format=fhvideo1&#x26;mobile=&#x26;flashsupportedmobiledevice=&#x26;helpcenter=&#x26;key=56D188F6DDC0731803732D04D9287E5F&#x26;newConsole=true&#x26;nxChe=true&#x26;newTabCon=true&#x26;consoleEarEventConsole=false&#x26;text_language_id=en&#x26;playerwidth=748&#x26;playerheight=526&#x26;eventuserid=616413864&#x26;contenttype=A&#x26;mediametricsessionid=533671932&#x26;mediametricid=5886174&#x26;usercd=616413864&#x26;mode=launch">here</a>. In addition, watch this <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/asset-management-eam.html?video=9870e39a-b97d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff">overview video</a> to learn how to maximize asset health and performance with SAP Intelligent Asset Management solutions and read what <a href="https://www.sap.com/asset/dynamic/2022/09/77fdedf5-7bbb-4ed6-bc18-1d3febe209ca.html">benefits other enterprises achieved</a>. To know more about the role of service and asset management in your industry, <a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/dg/idc-info-brief-on-service-excellence/index.html">download this complimentary paper from IDC</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Karin Fent is senior director of Global Customer Success Digital Supply Chain at SAP.</em><br><em>Top photo credit: Roche</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/asset-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/enterprise-asset-management</category>
            <category>industry/life-sciences</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How a European Utilities Company Makes Maintenance More Efficient, Transparent, and Cost-Effective]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/european-utilities-company-retipiu-makes-maintenance-efficient-transparent-cost-effective</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/european-utilities-company-retipiu-makes-maintenance-efficient-transparent-cost-effective</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Read to learn how Retipiù is increasing productivity and improving customer service with smart asset maintenance using SAP solutions.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16f49651583a397641725139ac5d57886a78fc80f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16f49651583a397641725139ac5d57886a78fc80f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_16f49651583a397641725139ac5d57886a78fc80f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="How a European Utilities Company Makes Maintenance More Efficient, Transparent, and Cost-Effective" src="./media_16f49651583a397641725139ac5d57886a78fc80f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="how-a-european-utilities-company-makes-maintenance-more-efficient-transparent-and-cost-effective">How a European Utilities Company Makes Maintenance More Efficient, Transparent, and Cost-Effective</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>The Italian natural gas and electricity provider RetiPiù S.r.l. is in charge of 2,900 kilometers of gas and electricity networks that serve homes, businesses, and public spaces in 25 towns across the northern Italian province of Monza and Brianza.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="maximize-asset-health-and-performance-with-sap-intelligent-asset-management-software">Maximize asset health and performance with SAP Intelligent Asset Management software</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/supply-chain-management/asset-management-eam.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="managing-ever-complex-asset-networks-at-minimum-cost">Managing Ever Complex Asset Networks at Minimum Cost</h2>
  <p>As these networks grow and become more complex, RetiPiù must ensure safety and reliability through daily maintenance performed by its field workers. It is also crucial for them to quickly identify critical network events and efficiently prioritize, schedule, and track field-service assignments and maintenance activities.</p>
  <p>But disparate asset management systems made it hard to prioritize and schedule maintenance calls. In addition, they were not integrated with the company’s core enterprise resource planning (ERP) system.</p>
  <h2 id="moving-from-reactive-to-predictive-maintenance">Moving from Reactive to Predictive Maintenance</h2>
  <p>To increase efficiency and optimize resources, RetiPiù looked to move from a reactive to a predictive maintenance model. The goal was to understand critical events as early as possible, track and trace issues from alert to resolution, get better visibility into maintenance schedules and work-order status, and use that information to better manage maintenance across the network.</p>
  <p>To meet these goals, RetiPiù required a <strong>unified <a href="/topics/intelligent-asset-management">intelligent asset maintenance</a> system</strong> that workers could access from the field and that was integrated with its intelligent ERP software.</p>
  <h2 id="one-central-asset-intelligence-system-to-speed-up-maintenance-cycles-and-lower-costs">One Central Asset Intelligence System to Speed up Maintenance Cycles and Lower Costs</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-the-industry-40-intelligent-assets-report">Read the Industry 4.0 Intelligent Assets Report</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/dg/intelligent-assets/index.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As its utilities networks continue to grow, RetiPiù S.r.l. deployed <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/s4hana-erp.html">SAP S/4HANA</a> to help improve data quality and access for engineers and back-office teams. Building on that digital transformation, it then added the SAP Enterprise Asset Management solution to help configure digital twins for equipment and activate predictive models respectively. These algorithms help assess and prioritize maintenance requirements and optimize resources. The company leverages the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/iot-data-services.html">SAP Internet of Things (SAP IoT)</a> solution to gather detailed sensor data from across the network assets to share information via mobile applications with field technicians, who get information and update the status of work orders in real time.</p>
  <h2 id="increasing-productivity-and-improving-customer-service-with-smarter-asset-maintenance">Increasing Productivity and Improving Customer Service with Smarter Asset Maintenance</h2>
  <p>The system currently supports thousands of pieces of equipment. In addition to making maintenance simpler and more efficient, asset and maintenance data – including cost data – are immediately available for analysis in <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/s4hana-erp.html">SAP S/4HANA</a>. As a public utility, the real beneficiaries are RetiPiù customers that now have faster activation service. And in addition, RetiPiù benefits by being rewarded by the Italian government for its continually reliable service.</p>
  <p>The most <strong>striking benefits</strong> the utilities company gained are:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>100% increase in assets that can be managed on the network – from 12,000 to 24,000 pieces of equipment</li>
    <li>50% reduction in maintenance cost</li>
    <li>15%-20% less time needed to activate new gas customers</li>
    <li>Increased efficiency and resource optimization</li>
    <li>Improved prioritization of field-service assignments and maintenance tasks</li>
    <li>Improved field operations effectiveness through mobile system access to maintenance staff</li>
    <li>One single platform to manage data and analytics for all assets – creating a fully integrated and transparent maintenance process from order to the field and back</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="real-time-data-transfer-from-technician-mobile-apps-to-back-end-erp-systems">Real-Time Data Transfer from Technician Mobile Apps to Back-End ERP Systems</h2>
  <p>“In choosing an intelligent, predictive maintenance solution, integration with our core ERP systems was key. With <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/s4hana-erp.html">SAP S/4HANA</a> and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/supply-chain-management/asset-management-eam.html">SAP Intelligent Asset Management</a>, we have <strong>one unified system</strong> that provides everyone the visibility they need to work efficiently and effectively,” says Massimo De Filippi, director of Technical and Information Services and Design at RetiPiù S.r.l.</p>
  <p>He continues: “This project has allowed RetiPiù to ensure service continuity and avoid shutdowns. We can provide quality service while also reducing costs. We are a public company, so the ultimate benefit is for the citizens.”</p>
  <p>“By being able to access data and reports in real time, field engineers can intervene promptly whenever issues arise, improving the customer experience and strengthening our reputation as a trusted energy provider,” says Mario Carlo Borgotti, managing director of RetiPiù.</p>
  <p>In regard to future plans and after being live with the gas network, RetiPiù now has a template for rolling out intelligent asset management and predictive maintenance to its electricity and public lighting networks. As the next step, it will enable simulation of maintenance requirements for new assets that have yet to be added and include geolocation services for route optimization.</p>
  <p>To learn more about how to enable intelligent asset management processes, <a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/dg/intelligent-assets/index.html">download the report</a>, “The Building Blocks of Industry 4.0 with Intelligent Assets.”</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Karin Fent is senior director of Global Customer Success Digital Supply Chain at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/asset-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/enterprise-asset-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>industry/utilities</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Taking Customer Service to the Next Level with a Digital Asset Network]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/taking-customer-service-to-next-level-with-digital-asset-network</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/taking-customer-service-to-next-level-with-digital-asset-network</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Find out how SAP solutions help BITZER digitally connect its refrigeration technology, in turn helping its customers optimize operations.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_163ef4d834deb3b0900f53468e35f963d350e4934.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_163ef4d834deb3b0900f53468e35f963d350e4934.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_163ef4d834deb3b0900f53468e35f963d350e4934.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Taking Customer Service to the Next Level with a Digital Asset Network" src="./media_163ef4d834deb3b0900f53468e35f963d350e4934.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="taking-customer-service-to-the-next-level-with-a-digital-asset-network">Taking Customer Service to the Next Level with a Digital Asset Network</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>You may not see BITZER’s products, but you can feel their effects everywhere, from fresh foods to pleasantly air-conditioned buildings and reliably cooled industrial complexes.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>With local roots in Germany and a global presence, the BITZER group is represented in more than 90 countries with 72 locations and over 3,800 employees. The company has been providing innovative products and services for 87 years. Its products maintain the optimum temperature in buses, trains, and buildings as well as ensure foods stays fresh at all times on their way to consumers.</p>
  <h2 id="transforming-to-aid-customers-and-gain-competitive-edge">Transforming to Aid Customers and Gain Competitive Edge</h2>
  <p>I recently spoke with BITZER’s Eugen Bonelis, digital solution manager, and Christian Stenzel, director of Organization and IT.</p>
  <p>Bonelis started by saying, “To support BITZER’s innovation and future growth strategy, the company set an objective to transform from a compressor manufacturer to a provider of compressor-enabled services. With the transformation of our business model, customer service would be taken to the next level.”</p>
  <p>“To achieve this goal, we needed a central platform that would allow us to digitally connect our compressors to enable customers to monitor machine status in real time, access configuration data and documentation, and review operational reports,” he continued,</p>
  <p>This network provides solutions for remote troubleshooting to keep machines running efficiently while helping BITZER transform its business model, future proof the enterprise for changing market dynamics, and keep its competitive edge.</p>
  <h2 id="asset-network-manages-compressor-performance-and-digitizes-enterprises">Asset Network Manages Compressor Performance and Digitizes Enterprises</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="register-for-the-industry-40-intelligent-assets-report">Register for the Industry 4.0 Intelligent Assets Report</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/dg/intelligent-assets/index.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>By integrating a suite of SAP solutions to digitally connect its refrigeration technology, BITZER is helping its customers optimize operations and tap into new digital solutions.</p>
  <p>For example, <a href="https://insights.sap.com/what-is-iot-internet-of-things/">Internet of Things (IoT)</a>-enabled compressors and solutions provide situational awareness of the real-time operation in the new digital network. This facilitates tailored customer alerts based on sensor readings, status reports, and data analytics services, helping to provide an overview of the customer’s ecosystem in a service-oriented interface.</p>
  <p>“We can now connect applications, processes, and people through SAP solutions to distribute information and deploy operation analytics,” Stenzel explained. “By monitoring operational data remotely in real time and using advanced data analytics, we can instantly identify operational issues and offer actionable insights, including spare parts preorder capabilities, shortening downtime and supporting customized operational reports.”</p>
  <h2 id="developing-a-customer-centric-experience">Developing a Customer-Centric Experience</h2>
  <p>Bonelis discussed the importance of great customer engagement, saying, “It’s important to be close to your customers, be creative, and provide solutions to their needs. With SAP Business Technology Platform and SAP Asset Intelligence Network, we can provide 360-degree information that enables an outstanding customer focus.”</p>
  <p>The benefits are clear. Major outcomes BITZER achieved include:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Complete, real-time overview of customer product portfolios and product history</strong>, from the initial order throughout the entire lifecycle of the compressor with the BITZER Digital Network, which connects all BITZER products to the cloud</li>
    <li><strong>Increased ability to break down information and departmental silos</strong>, operating as a single company focused on customer outcomes while growing the business</li>
    <li><strong>A basis for BITZER’s partners to transform their own business models</strong> into a service provider for refrigeration</li>
    <li><strong>Enhanced customer satisfaction</strong>, enabling the business to digitize and tap into new product, service, and market opportunities while customers regard BITZER as a valuable partner</li>
    <li><strong>Increased revenues by providing new services</strong> spanning equipment monitoring, operational reports, and instant remote assistance in the event of defects</li>
    <li><strong>Reduced compressor downtime</strong> thanks to data analysis capabilities, leading to a competitive advantage for both BITZER and its customers</li>
    <li><strong>Increased energy efficiency</strong> through optimization of compressor operation by leveraging BITZER’s know-how</li>
  </ul>
  <p>BITZER worked with the SAP Services and Support team to create the new asset network and connect its customers’ refrigeration and air conditioning products and related operational data in the cloud.</p>
  <p>“The support of SAP, especially the Customer First program, has been very important for us. We have exchanged many ideas that have led to exciting new initiatives for our company,” remarked Stenzel. “You can’t buy digitalization, but you can simplify the way toward it. Working with the SAP Services and Support team helped us combine SAP software, business- and customer-focused know-how, as well as customer-focused innovation to create instant value for our customers.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="optimize-asset-performance-with-sap-asset-intelligence-network">Optimize asset performance with SAP Asset Intelligence Network</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/asset-intelligence-network.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="to-learn-more-about-how-to-enable-intelligent-asset-management-processes-download-the-intelligent-asset-report">To learn more about how to enable intelligent asset management processes, <a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/dg/intelligent-assets/index.html">download</a> the “Intelligent Asset Report.”</h3>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Karin Fent is senior director of Global Customer Success Digital Supply Chain at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/asset-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
            <category>news-tag/internet-of-things</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>