<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/catena-x/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hannover Messe: What Can AI Do for Manufacturing?]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/hannover-messe-ai-manufacturing</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/hannover-messe-ai-manufacturing</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[At Hannover Messe 2024, SAP and its partners showed how they are embedding AI to help companies achieve excellence in manufacturing.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/catena-x</category>
            <category>news-tag/hannover-messe</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-x</category>
            <category>product/sap-digital-manufacturing</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Is Supply Chain Innovation Even Possible in an Era of Tighter Regulation?]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2024/01/is-supply-chain-innovation-possible-era-tighter-regulation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2024/01/is-supply-chain-innovation-possible-era-tighter-regulation</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[When it comes to supply chain regulation, compliance and innovation are not mutually exclusive. Investing in advanced technologies can help.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/executive-blog</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/catena-x</category>
            <category>non-sap-event/wef-davos</category>
            <category>product/sap-integrated-business-planning-for-supply-chain</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Truly Sustainable Businesses Gain a Competitive Advantage]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/sap-sustainability-research-study-wave-3</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/sap-sustainability-research-study-wave-3</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Ahead of the UN Climate Change Conference COP28 in Dubai, UAE, SAP Insights has released the results of its Wave 3 sustainability study.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/catena-x</category>
            <category>non-sap-event/cop28</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-insights</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Supply Chain Issues Keeping CEOs Up at Night]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2023/11/supply-chain-issues-keeping-ceos-up-at-night</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2023/11/supply-chain-issues-keeping-ceos-up-at-night</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Supply chain issues keep executives up at night, but SAP is working to leverage the power of generative AI for supply chain resilience.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17fce40551915dfea41e19d0bfc190fb085838212.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17fce40551915dfea41e19d0bfc190fb085838212.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_17fce40551915dfea41e19d0bfc190fb085838212.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Supply Chain Issues Keeping CEOs Up at Night" src="./media_17fce40551915dfea41e19d0bfc190fb085838212.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="supply-chain-issues-keeping-ceos-up-at-night">Supply Chain Issues Keeping CEOs Up at Night</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Building risk-resilient supply chains is one of the top issues CEOs are discussing on earning calls and in board rooms around the globe. The issue has gone from one priority among many to business critical. And CEOs are no longer just pursuing lower costs, shorter lead times, and higher quality.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Instead, they are recognizing the need to resolve supply chain disruptions in an integrated way, bridging the silos of various functions and going beyond dealing with supply chain disruptions as they occur.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="a-risk-resilient-and-sustainable-supply-chain-is-one-that-is-connected-contextualized-and-collaborative">A risk-resilient and sustainable supply chain is one that is connected, contextualized, and collaborative</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Taking a macro-view is also something governments have begun doing. Just think of the huge investments to “bring supply chains home”; for example, <a href="https://commission.europa.eu/strategy-and-policy/priorities-2019-2024/europe-fit-digital-age/european-chips-act_en">€43 billion in the EU</a> for semiconductors or <a href="https://www.whitehouse.gov/briefing-room/statements-releases/2023/04/17/fact-sheet-biden-harris-administration-announces-new-private-and-public-sector-investments-for-affordable-electric-vehicles/">$100 billion in the U.S.</a> for sustainable energy. At the same time, diversifying supply chains and complying with new regulations keeps increasing their complexity.</p>
  <p>Companies take various approaches to these challenges, such as de-coupling their supply chains by building up costly inventories for critical components. Another option is reshoring or nearshoring, which brings manufacturing and supplier relationships closer to core markets, ideally in countries with similar political and economic systems. But all of these strategies come with downsides, including the cost of operations in globally competitive markets.</p>
  <p>At SAP, our vision is to embrace interconnected supply chains and optimize material flows — sustainably — with digital technologies. We believe in intelligent strategies to reduce supply chain uncertainties for the long-term by helping industries redefine their operations and by creating value chains that are more intelligent, connected, and responsive.</p>
  <h2 id="supply-chain-convergence-increases-agility">Supply Chain Convergence Increases Agility</h2>
  <p>Companies that resolve supply chain disruptions in an integrated manner bridge the silos of various functions such as procurement, logistics, or manufacturing. That’s how they can truly alleviate the impact to their organizations. Supply chain functions need to work in concert and extend into their ecosystem of suppliers. Even the most accurate supply chain plan is meaningless if material suppliers cannot commit to volumes and lead times. Through integrating supply chain planning, such as demand and supply plans with procurement collaboration, manufacturers have a much stronger strategic lever to avoid downstream shortages.</p>
  <p>At SAP, we call this approach <strong>design-to-operate</strong>. Our strategy is to deeply connect all relevant functions in a supply chain along end-to-end value chains and business processes. Going beyond the four walls of your own enterprise, into your ecosystem of suppliers and sub-suppliers — that’s the ultimate way to tackle supply chain challenges. In the case of supply shortages, for example, it is imperative to analyze the impact to the organization.</p>
  <p>With SAP Integrated Business Planning, <a href="https://blogs.sap.com/2022/07/05/how-network-aware-supply-chain-planning-drives-resiliency/">affected production orders can be quickly identified</a>. Impacted customer orders and revenue at risk are visible and informed actions can be taken to mitigate any shortages, for example, by changing production schedules. The SAP Digital Manufacturing system knows immediately about the changed production plan for the next shifts and adjusts labor and resources accordingly. Logistics departments in SAP Extended Warehouse Management orchestrate the new material flow, <a href="https://blogs.sap.com/2023/04/14/sap-digital-manufacturing-and-ewm-integration-using-manage-staging-2.0-app/">moving the right raw materials into production</a>, and asset maintenance activities are re-scheduled to adhere to the new production priorities.</p>
  <p>As a result, supply chain leaders who follow a design-to-operate paradigm are highly agile and can take critical actions quickly to deal with supply chain disruptions.</p>
  <h2 id="saps-industry-business-networks-a-new-paradigm">SAP’s Industry Business Networks: A New Paradigm</h2>
  <p>Entire industries are recognizing the benefits of going beyond the four walls of their own enterprise. Consider a car company investigating faulty engines coming from one of their production lines. Now imagine it can trace the failure not only to a particular batch of components from one supplier but then dig even deeper to identify faulty basic parts from the supplier’s supplier. Instead of having to recall thousands of vehicles, it needs to recall only a few.</p>
  <p>Solving problems this way requires a mindset for radical collaboration as well as technology for efficient, cross-company data exchange. <a href="https://catena-x.net/en/">Catena-X</a> is an open network that enables just that. It guarantees interoperability by defining common standards. The network is not owned by a single business and data providers keep their data sovereignty. For instance, they define for how long and for which purpose their data can be used. On the other hand, consumers can trust that data comes from a reliable source.</p>
  <p>SAP is one of the founding members of Catena-X, together with five other companies. Since 2020, the initiative has grown to <a href="https://catena-x.net/fileadmin/_online_media_/231012_1_CAT_007_List_of_Members_EN.pdf">170 international auto makers, suppliers, and</a> IT companies. Among them are Germany’s biggest car companies as well as many small and medium enterprises. Catena-X may soon become the industry’s standard.</p>
  <p>Naturally, the <a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/automotive/industry-network-automotive.html">SAP Business Network for the automotive industry</a> is ready for Catena-X. It readily connects Catena-X to SAP’s broad portfolio of automotive IT solutions to trace parts, measure carbon emissions and manage demand, capacity and quality. Recently, SAP announced business networks for more industries, including <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-network/industries.html">high tech, industrial manufacturing, consumer products, and life sciences</a>, with more to come.</p>
  <h2 id="generative-ai-adds-new-types-of-intelligence">Generative AI Adds New Types of Intelligence</h2>
  <p>A key tool in solving supply chain complexity challenges is artificial intelligence (AI). Even before the recent groundbreaking advances in large language models (LLMs) and generative AI, our supply chain solutions have been infused with both “traditional” and “advanced” AI.</p>
  <p>For instance, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/integrated-business-planning.html">SAP Integrated Business Planning for Supply Chain</a> creates demand forecasts based on historical demand patterns, but it also leverages advanced machine learning capabilities to improve forecast demand with point-of-sales data and improve planning quality using self-healing master data and lead time predictions. In the future, generative AI will enable completely new types of intelligent capabilities like these:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Facilitating human-machine interaction:</strong> Users will soon be able to interact with their system much more naturally via our new embedded <a href="/2023/09/joule-new-generative-ai-assistant">generative assistant Joule</a>. For example, they will be able to ask which of customer X’s demands for product Y are still unfilled in Central America. Joule will give the answer, intelligently combining data from various systems and domains because it will be embedded throughout the SAP cloud enterprise portfolio.</li>
    <li><strong>Supporting creativity:</strong> Much like a sparring partner, generative AI can help designers, engineers, and product managers create new product ideas in an innovation cycle and iterate them with SAP Enterprise Product Development.</li>
    <li><strong>Transforming unstructured data:</strong> Consider a truck arriving at a warehouse with inbound cargo. The clerk knows what cargo to expect and this is saved in an SAP system. However, what is really on the truck is written on a loading list, often in paper form. Making this data available digitally has been possible for quite a while and is known as optical character recognition (OCR). What’s new is that generative AI tools can now match the unstructured loading list to the structured data already in the system — in a split second.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>Leveraging AI for companies to scale and sustain business operations will no longer be optional. Consider the increasing labor shortage facing manufacturing companies, among others. They will have a shortfall of up to 85 million employees by 2030 — roughly the population of Germany!</p>
  <p>By automating mundane tasks with advanced AI capabilities, we will bridge the human resources gap and enable experts to focus on what really matters: making data-backed business decisions.</p>
  <p>Human and artificial intelligence work hand in hand — it’s a duet, not a duel.</p>
  <p>We already help our customers build risk-resilient supply chains and deeply connect enterprises to run productive, agile and automated operations. Now, by also leveraging the power of generative AI, we will ensure that supply chain resilience doesn’t have to be something that keeps CEOs up at night.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Thomas Saueressig is a member of the Executive Board of SAP SE, SAP Product Engineering.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/blog/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/blog/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/blog/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/blog/article-read-more</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/executive-blog</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/catena-x</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>product/sap-digital-manufacturing</category>
            <category>product/sap-extended-warehouse-management</category>
            <category>product/sap-integrated-business-planning-for-supply-chain</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Can the Chemicals Industry Capitalize On Carbon Reduction Opportunities?]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/chemicals-industry-sustainability-carbon-reduction-opportunities</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/chemicals-industry-sustainability-carbon-reduction-opportunities</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Companies in the chemicals industry that look to sustainability and carbon reduction will be able to future-proof their business.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10349c35f3512c6fdd74903bfb6f42dba5cc51705.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10349c35f3512c6fdd74903bfb6f42dba5cc51705.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_10349c35f3512c6fdd74903bfb6f42dba5cc51705.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="How Can the Chemicals Industry Capitalize On Carbon Reduction Opportunities?" src="./media_10349c35f3512c6fdd74903bfb6f42dba5cc51705.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="how-can-the-chemicals-industry-capitalize-on-carbon-reduction-opportunities">How Can the Chemicals Industry Capitalize On Carbon Reduction Opportunities?</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>The chemicals industry is a $4 trillion business employing upwards of 20 million people. While a consumer of high volumes of energy and resources, it is also at the forefront of developing energy efficiencies, low carbon and renewable raw materials and fuels, chemical energy storage, and materials from CO2 capture. It is also uniquely positioned to pioneer and promote circular economy models by innovating for the easier reuse and recycling of materials.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>It is simultaneously the third highest contributor to carbon emissions in the industrial sector and the best placed industry to decarbonize products across a multitude of industries.</p>
  <p>As a result of its position high upstream in the supply chain, the chemicals industry can often seem invisible. Its products sit in the value chain of key industries including agriculture, pharmaceuticals, and consumer goods, making up a significant proportion of their Scope 3 emissions. But change is coming that will make companies more accountable for these previously hidden emissions. New legislation such as the European Corporate Sustainability Reporting Directive (CSRD) will reveal the carbon footprint of the chemicals industry as companies with more than 250 employees will be required to report their GHG emissions, including those that lie in Scope 3.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="create-innovative-new-products-increase-agility-and-drive-greener-growth">Create innovative new products, increase agility, and drive greener growth</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/chemicals.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="a-vision-for-the-chemicals-industry">A Vision for the Chemicals Industry</h2>
  <p>In order to meet new legal requirements and identify opportunities for emissions reduction, the chemicals industry needs to look beyond its current tools and collaborations to upgrade the quality of data — based on primary information rather than averages and estimates — and share access to it. Aligning data structures and using the same semantics will encourage competition among suppliers, galvanizing them to manufacture chemical products with ever lower carbon footprints, benefiting all downstream customers as well as the climate. To realize this vision, the solution will receive actual data from suppliers upstream, using a standardized methodology, allowing companies to calculate their own product carbon footprint so it can then be shared with downstream customers. For broad adoption, this carbon data exchange tool needs to be relatively simple while allowing for secure data exchange.</p>
  <p>The automotive industry already has a blueprint that the chemicals industry can adopt. It tracks material flows digitally throughout the entire supply chain. Catena-X allows companies to share standardized emissions data from their supply chain with confidence based on technology that provides an auditable chain of custody. This offers car manufacturers the information they need to make strategic decisions to reduce the carbon footprint of their products, embrace circularity, and increase the adoption of circular business models such as battery recycling. Some of the chemical companies that supply the automotive industry are already involved, such as BASF.</p>
  <p>“As an energy-intensive industry at the beginning of nearly all value chains, the chemical sector plays a key role in reducing global carbon footprint in manufacturing and beyond. Carbon footprint transparency at product level is a fundamental step to achieve this,” said Alessandro Pistillo, director of Digital Strategic Projects at BASF. “BASF is a founding member and very active contributor in global initiatives focused on Scope 3 transparency and product carbon footprint standardization such as Together for Sustainability in the chemical sector, as well as Catena-X and the Global Battery Alliance in the automotive and battery value chain respectively. At the same time, BASF is also a leading member of WBCSD-PACT, whose framework is geared toward ensuring cross-sectoral interoperability.”</p>
  <h2 id="improved-accuracy">Improved Accuracy</h2>
  <p>Historically, industry averages and secondary data have been used to estimate carbon footprints. The cornerstone of the vision for the chemicals industry involves a significant improvement in GHG emissions data, a step that will provide much greater emissions transparency for the industry itself and for its customers. SAP has been working with the World Business Council for Sustainable Development (WBCSD) since 2021 as an innovation partner and has been involved in the Partnership for Carbon Transparency (PACT) initiative, helping to develop the global standards, methodology, and technological infrastructure needed for product-level emission accounting and exchange.</p>
  <h2 id="collaborative-data-exchange">Collaborative Data Exchange</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="record-report-and-act-on-your-sustainability-goals-with-sap">Record, report, and act on your sustainability goals with SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/sustainability.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The desire and the frameworks for the chemicals industry to collaborate already exist. They date back to 1985, with the establishment of the Responsible Care program and the 2011 formation of industry body Together for Sustainability, a worldwide initiative to raise sustainability standards in the chemicals industry’s supply chain. Its members include some of the world’s largest chemical groups, represented by their chief procurement officers. Despite the industry’s ability and willingness to cooperate, and its current pilot IT system for sharing upstream product carbon footprint information, it is still on the cusp of data exchange.</p>
  <p>“Footprint data is there,” said Michael Sambeth, global enterprise architect at SAP. “It can be calculated using out-of-the-box solutions from SAP; now it needs to flow across the supply chain.”</p>
  <p><a href="/topics/catena-x">Catena-X</a> led to the launch of the SAP Sustainability Data Exchange application, which was designed specifically with security in mind, to exchange standardized carbon footprint data along the value chain. SAP Sustainability Data Exchange uses the carbon data standards established by WBCSD PACT. With a high proportion of Together for Sustainability members already using SAP ERP systems, they are well placed to be able to leverage SAP Sustainability Data Exchange to exchange this data with their suppliers and customers while adhering to global standards.</p>
  <h2 id="moving-to-a-green-ledger-approach">Moving to a Green Ledger Approach</h2>
  <p>The chemicals industry is a product of its established supply chains, high-volume activities, cost efficiencies, and scalability. It is highly organized and well versed in creating and following methodologies, but it needs to see the value in primary standardized data — and data sharing — for decarbonization.</p>
  <p>A <a href="/topics/green-ledger">green ledger approach</a> will allow businesses to treat their emissions in the same way as their financials. Carbon accounting makes emission “bookings” part of every business transaction in the same way as financial information. This means that a level of detail and confidence is achieved, allowing companies to look at emissions from any angle — by product, organization, profit center, site, factory, equipment, etc. This granularity is the foundation for planning and steering, which cannot be done using averages or highly aggregated figures.</p>
  <p>The decarbonization of a multitude of industries hinges on the ability of the chemicals industry to successfully standardize and exchange carbon footprint data. Only those chemical companies with sustainability at the core of their strategy and the right tools for high-quality emissions accounting will be able to future-proof their business to remain competitive in the face of the ever-evolving legislative changes created to combat the effects of global warming.</p>
  <p>For more information on how SAP helps companies record, report, and act on their sustainability goals, visit <a href="https://www.sap.com/sustainability.html">www.sap.com/sustainability</a>.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-sap-news-on-linkedin">Connect with SAP News on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/catena-x</category>
            <category>industry/chemicals</category>
            <category>news-tag/green-ledger</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-data-exchange</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Are Carbon Accounting Challenges Impeding Progress Toward Net Zero?]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/06/carbon-accounting-challenges-net-zero-progress</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/06/carbon-accounting-challenges-net-zero-progress</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Improving emissions data quality to combat carbon accounting challenges is a clear priority to turn net-zero targets into actionable plans.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-accounting</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-emissions</category>
            <category>news-tag/catena-x</category>
            <category>news-tag/climate-action</category>
            <category>news-tag/green-ledger</category>
            <category>news-tag/net-zero</category>
            <category>product/sap-green-token</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[HANNOVER MESSE 2023: SAP Generates New Data-Driven Insights for Resilient Manufacturing]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/sap-hannover-messe-2023-data-driven-insights-resilient-manufacturing</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/sap-hannover-messe-2023-data-driven-insights-resilient-manufacturing</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[At HANNOVER MESSE 2023, SAP will showcase its unique position to accelerate the journey to resilient manufacturing. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/catena-x</category>
            <category>news-tag/hannover-messe</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-x</category>
            <category>news-tag/oxford-economics</category>
            <category>product/sap-digital-manufacturing</category>
            <category>product/sap-responsible-design-and-production</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dresden Becomes Part of the Global SAP Labs Network]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/dresden-becomes-part-of-sap-labs-network</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/dresden-becomes-part-of-sap-labs-network</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The new SAP location in Dresden is part of the global SAP Labs Network and will further strengthen how developers across SAP collaborate.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/catena-x</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-labs-network</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Deepening Operational Resilience with SAP Business Network for Logistics]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/01/operational-resilience-sap-business-network-for-logistics</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/01/operational-resilience-sap-business-network-for-logistics</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Through SAP Business Network for Logistics, trading partners can plan more accurately, innovate collaboratively, and create value enduringly.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/travel-transportation</category>
            <category>news-tag/catena-x</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[With the Foundation of the Joint Venture Cofinity-X, 10 Partners of the Automotive Industry Will Further Foster the Adoption of the Catena-X Network]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/01/cofinity-x-joint-venture-further-catena-x-network</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/01/cofinity-x-joint-venture-further-catena-x-network</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn more about Cofinity-X, a joint venture of BASF, BMW, Henkel, Mercedes-Benz, SAP, Schaeffler, Siemens, T-Systems, VW and ZF.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>industry/automotive</category>
            <category>news-tag/catena-x</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Five Ways Automakers and Suppliers Can Prepare for the Future of Mobility]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/five-ways-automotive-industry-future-of-mobility</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/five-ways-automotive-industry-future-of-mobility</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[EVs, mobility-as-a-service, operational resilience, and digital retail are shaping the future of mobility in the automotive industry.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/automotive</category>
            <category>news-tag/catena-x</category>
            <category>news-tag/electric-vehicles</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-e-mobility</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-industry-network-for-automotive</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Chasing Zero with SAP Industry Network for Automotive]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/sap-industry-network-for-automotive-greentoken-product-carbon-footprint</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/sap-industry-network-for-automotive-greentoken-product-carbon-footprint</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Solutions like SAP Industry Network for Automotive and GreenToken help enterprises gain insights into their product carbon footprint data.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/automotive</category>
            <category>news-tag/catena-x</category>
            <category>news-tag/chasing-zero</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-industry-network-for-automotive</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hyperconnected Auto Supply Chains Give Electric Vehicles a Jolt of Sustainable Mobility]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/06/automotive-supply-chains-electric-vehicles-sustainable-mobility</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/06/automotive-supply-chains-electric-vehicles-sustainable-mobility</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Industry networks connect makers, suppliers, and customers across the automotive supply chain to bring sustainable products to market faster.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/automotive</category>
            <category>news-tag/catena-x</category>
            <category>news-tag/circular-economy</category>
            <category>news-tag/electric-vehicles</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enabling a Circular Economy Through Industry Network Collaboration]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/circular-economy-automotive-industry-network-collaboration</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/circular-economy-automotive-industry-network-collaboration</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Achieving a circular economy in the automotive industry is key to tackling the environmental challenges. SAP technology supports the shift.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/automotive</category>
            <category>news-tag/catena-x</category>
            <category>news-tag/circular-economy</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-industry-network-for-automotive</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>