<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/carbon-footprint/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Making SAP Events More Sustainable]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/making-sap-events-more-sustainable</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/making-sap-events-more-sustainable</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP's Jenny Bittmann is on a mission to make customer events more sustainable. Read to learn what steps the company is taking to do so.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-footprint</category>
            <category>news-tag/circular-economy</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Data Can Move the Needle on Sustainability]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/data-can-move-the-needle-on-sustainability</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/data-can-move-the-needle-on-sustainability</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Non-profit eXXpedition is collecting data to investigate the causes of and solutions to ocean plastic pollution. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-footprint</category>
            <category>news-tag/circular-economy</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP and Infosys Introduce New Sustainable and Innovative Industry Cloud Solution]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/sap-and-infosys-introduce-sustainable-industry-cloud-solution</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/sap-and-infosys-introduce-sustainable-industry-cloud-solution</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With the SAP-validated partner use case program, Infosys and SAP created a solution to help companies monitor their carbon footprints.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_164f38f864e0733a6806af629b2d24613241a4b15.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_164f38f864e0733a6806af629b2d24613241a4b15.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_164f38f864e0733a6806af629b2d24613241a4b15.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP and Infosys Introduce New Sustainable and Innovative Industry Cloud Solution" src="./media_164f38f864e0733a6806af629b2d24613241a4b15.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-and-infosys-introduce-new-sustainable-and-innovative-industry-cloud-solution">SAP and Infosys Introduce New Sustainable and Innovative Industry Cloud Solution</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>In today’s fast-paced and dynamic business environment, <a href="/topics/sustainability">sustainability</a> is no longer a buzzword; it’s a critical business priority. Investors and customers seek more sustainable business practices from their solution providers and enterprises are keenly focused on integrating sustainability into their operations. This is no easy lift, and it doesn’t happen overnight. Several challenges need to be addressed, including action planning, effective resource allocation, and prioritization.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>For companies to act sustainably, responsibly, and efficiently, they must harness the power of data-driven decisions and advanced technology to reduce their carbon footprint and create sustainable product portfolios. Enter SAP and its broad ecosystem of industry cloud partners with a shared vision to help businesses become strategic, sustainable, intelligent enterprises.</p>
  <h2 id="hack2build-opens-door-for-innovation-and-sustainability">Hack2Build Opens Door for Innovation and Sustainability</h2>
  <p>The <a href="https://events.sap.com/hack2build/en/home">Hack2Build event from SAP</a>, organized by SAP Co-Innovation Lab, is an initiative designed to harness the creativity and speed of prototyping industry cloud solutions by SAP partners in days as opposed to weeks. At a September 2022 Hack2Build event, SAP partner Infosys presented a solution for organizations to identify, track, predict, and refine carbon emissions during sales and operations planning (S&#x26;OP) and make sustainable decisions. The solution, <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2023/08/7affe1f5-847e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Sustainable S&#x26;OP and Carbon Footprint Management</a>, was built using SAP Integrated Business Planning (SAP IBP) for Supply Chain, SAP S/4HANA, SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP), SAP Integration Suite, and SAP Sustainability Footprint Management.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="industry-cloud-solutions-from-sap-and-partners-can-help-you-find-a-competitive-edge">Industry cloud solutions from SAP and partners can help you find a competitive edge</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/industry-cloud.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="framework-for-tracking-emissions-leverages-the-power-of-saps-industry-cloud">Framework for Tracking Emissions Leverages the Power of SAP’s Industry Cloud</h2>
  <p>Infosys’ carbon footprint solution calculates carbon emissions based on greenhouse gas protocols and global warming potential factors across an organization’s procurement, production, and distribution processes. It helps calculate key information, such as estimates of CO2e emissions per order level, thereby helping to make decisions that can ensure a smaller carbon footprint. The solution also provides an innovative framework to help companies identify, track, predict, and refine their carbon emissions numbers throughout the entire supply chain process.</p>
  <h2 id="sap-validated-partner-use-case-program-offers-momentum-to-service-partner-solution">SAP-Validated Partner Use Case Program Offers Momentum to Service Partner Solution</h2>
  <p>Infosys’ solution is part of the SAP-validated partner use case program. The program was established to give SAP service partners the ability to showcase, position, and promote solutions and spotlight their expertise of SAP Business Technology Platform, leveraging the power of SAP’s vast customer base and industry networks.</p>
  <p>The SAP-validated partner use case program offers service partners the ability to:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Get amplified market reach</strong>: Increased visibility enables service partners to target a broader audience, opening doors to new markets and untapped opportunities. Leveraging SAP’s robust platform, partners can position themselves strategically and expand their global reach.</li>
    <li><strong>Collaborate and co-innovate</strong>: Participating in the SAP-validated partner use case program can foster collaboration with SAP experts, industry leaders, and customers.</li>
    <li><strong>Access a dynamic ecosystem</strong>: Partners can benefit from SAP’s ecosystem, where they can collaborate, exchange knowledge, and share best practices with some of the industry’s best leaders.</li>
    <li><strong>Develop customer-centric solutions</strong>: The program helps put the customer at the core of solution development. Service partners can gain valuable customer insights though interactions facilitated by SAP, leading to better-tailored products and services that can precisely address users’ pain points.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>The program presents opportunities for both customers and service partners to flourish. By achieving certification, service partners can earn credibility, expand market reach, and foster collaborative innovation with industry giants. Its streamlined processes help accelerate time-to-market, providing a significant advantage in today’s fast-paced business landscape.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-information-training-tools-and-resources-you-need">Get the information, training, tools, and resources you need</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://partneredge.sap.com/en/welcome.html?pexpRequestedURL=%2Fen%2Flibrary%2Feducation%2Fpsd%2F2023%2Fmar%2Fe_oe_te_w_rnbo_31837.html">Visit the SAP Partner Portal site</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The program unlocks a door to a dynamic ecosystem where partners can learn, grow, and develop customer-centric solutions that can meet industry demands head-on. For partners aiming to thrive in their respective industries, this program is a game changer. Service partners are encouraged to embrace the power of the SAP-validated partner use case program and transform their business.</p>
  <p>“Infosys is delighted to publish the Infosys Sustainable S&#x26;OP and Carbon Footprint Management Solution through the SAP-validated partner use case program,” said Atul Chorbele, AVP at Infosys. “We are confident that customers across industries will benefit from adopting this solution.”</p>
  <p>Holger Brammer, Global Partner Ecosystem vice president at SAP, praised this partner solution and the development process: “It was impressive to see how fast Infosys developed this solution on SAP BTP and integrated it with SAP S/4HANA, SAP IBP, and SAP Sustainability Footprint Management. I’m quite confident that this solution will resonate very well with customers.”</p>
  <p>To learn how to build industry innovation on SAP BTP and the SAP-validated partner use case program or get more information about <a href="mailto:lucca.sperl@sap.com">validated use cases on the SAP PartnerEdge site</a>, contact <a href="mailto:lucca.sperl@sap.com">Lucca Sperl</a>, industry cloud innovation program lead. To learn more about Infosys’ solution, <a href="https://www.infosys.com/campaigns/documents/sop-carbon-footprint-management.pdf">visit here</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>Vidya Gugnani is senior director and industry cloud ecosystem lead for Strategic Partners, North America at SAP.<br>Nitin Majahan is COE lead for SAP Industrial Manufacturing at Infosys.</p>
        <p>Top image courtesy of SAP employee Karsten Hohage</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-emissions</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-footprint</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-integrated-business-planning-for-supply-chain</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sustainability Funding Round 2023: Promoting Zero Waste and Zero Emissions at SAP]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/sustainability-funding-round-2023</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/sustainability-funding-round-2023</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The Sustainability Funding Round brings together SAP sustainability leaders worldwide to promote and finance sustainability initiatives.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1cd2d1e153edaa50b3c6b55dcda64e30a680ce56f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1cd2d1e153edaa50b3c6b55dcda64e30a680ce56f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1cd2d1e153edaa50b3c6b55dcda64e30a680ce56f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Sustainability Funding Round 2023: Promoting Zero Waste and Zero Emissions at SAP" src="./media_1cd2d1e153edaa50b3c6b55dcda64e30a680ce56f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sustainability-funding-round-2023-promoting-zero-waste-and-zero-emissions-at-sap">Sustainability Funding Round 2023: Promoting Zero Waste and Zero Emissions at SAP</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Through the <a href="https://www.sap.com/sustainability.html">SAP Sustainability</a> portfolio, we envision helping our customers and partners become a network of intelligent, sustainable enterprises. We continuously work towards leading by example in our sustainable business practices and are providing products and services that help other companies meet their <a href="/topics/sustainability">sustainability</a> goals. To succeed in our efforts, it is essential to engage employees around the world, build their awareness, understanding, and sustainability action.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The Sustainability Funding Round, hosted by our Chief Sustainability Officer, Daniel Schmid, brings together SAP sustainability leaders from over 60 SAP sites worldwide to promote and finance sustainability initiatives brought forward by the SAP sustainability champions and environmental management system leads. This year’s funding round was dedicated to supporting SAP’s transition to a low-carbon, circular business and saw record-breaking participation.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="together-we-can-enable-a-future-with-zero-emissions-zero-waste-and-zero-inequality">Together, we can enable a future with zero emissions, zero waste, and zero inequality</h3>
        <p><em><a href="">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>More than 60 proposals were submitted from sustainability champions across the globe, including ideas on improving our physical office environment, enabling employee volunteering, and raising sustainability awareness for zero emissions and zero waste. A jury consisting of experts from Global Real Estate &#x26; Facilities (GRF), Sustainability, Global Sourcing &#x26; Procurement, SAP Corporate Social Responsibility (SAP CSR), Global Communications, and winners of last year’s funding round thoroughly evaluated all submissions. The 25 highest-rated ideas have received funding from sustainability leaders across the globe and are being implemented until the end of the year.</p>
  <p>Here is a look at some of the funding winners.</p>
  <h2 id="2tonnes-immersive-workshop-france">“2tonnes” Immersive Workshop, France</h2>
  <p>What is measured can be managed. Understanding the size of our actions and collective decisions and calling for a lead to action is a good practice. The “<a href="https://en.2tonnes.org/">2tonnes</a>” immersive workshop helps us understand our carbon footprint and how to reach two tons per person by 2050. 2tonnes is a best-of-breed carbon awareness workshop used by the French government. Around 350 SAP employees have already been trained across multiple workshops.</p>
  <p>One of the main challenges was to find like-minded people to take part in the workshops. This was mitigated with the help of leaders motivating their respective teams and adding the workshop as a part of their team activity. The aim is to continue the project in 2024 and train another 500 employees, accounting for 50% of the total number of employees in Levallois, France.</p>
  <h2 id="waterloo-and-montreal-4-trees-canada">Waterloo and Montreal 4 Trees, Canada</h2>
  <p>To foster climate action, contribute to SAP’s goal to plant 21 million trees, improve air quality, protect biodiversity, and support the UN Decade on Ecosystem Restoration initiative, this initiative focused on planting trees in Montreal and Waterloo, Canada.</p>
  <p>Around 130 native trees were planted in Waterloo in collaboration with Let’s Tree Wilmot, a non-profit organization part of Wilmot Horticulture Society. The project will contribute to community establishment and support reforestation efforts to reestablish a missing forest stratum or prevent erosion due to illicit trial creation. Around 75 trees and shrubs were planted in September in Montreal to enhance Mount Royal, an urban forest at the center of Montreal that is visited by more than 6 million people every year. The project will contribute to the conservation of the mountains and keep the ecosystem strong and resilient.</p>
  <h2 id="green-art-argentina">Green Art, Argentina</h2>
  <p>This project aims to use the circular economy to transform waste into a work of art to show we can add value to things considered unusable. The idea is to work with sustainable artists to create a piece of art using recycled materials that will be displayed permanently at the SAP offices in Buenos Aires, Argentina.</p>
  <p>The materials will be obtained in a cleanup with employees from Buenos Aires and e-waste from our offices. The project envisions reusing waste, transforming it into art, and spreading awareness about reducing and recycling waste among employees when they take part in waste collection and when they view the art. Employees have already cleaned up a river and have gathered the necessary waste materials for the project. Creating the artwork will start as soon as the artist is onboarded as a supplier.</p>
  <p>The 2023 funding round was a tremendous success and showed that employees from all fields and locations can help lead the way towards zero emissions and zero waste.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-sap-news-delivered-to-your-inbox-once-a-week">Get the latest SAP news delivered to your inbox once a week</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/nl/sap-news-center-newsletter/index.html">Sign up</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-footprint</category>
            <category>news-tag/circular-economy</category>
            <category>news-tag/climate-action</category>
            <category>news-tag/net-zero</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How RISE with SAP and GROW with SAP Contribute to SAP’s Net-Zero Journey]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/rise-grow-with-sap-net-zero-journey</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/rise-grow-with-sap-net-zero-journey</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[RISE with SAP and GROW with SAP have strong momentum in helping both SAP and customers achieve ambitious net-zero goals. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-emissions</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-footprint</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-tag/grow-with-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/net-zero</category>
            <category>news-tag/renewable-energy</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Introduces Transactional Carbon Accounting to Accelerate Climate Action]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/sap-introduces-transactional-carbon-accounting</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/sap-introduces-transactional-carbon-accounting</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is well-positioned deliver high-quality carbon accounting to rapidly scale business decarbonization. Learn about the new SAP solutions.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-accounting</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-emissions</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-footprint</category>
            <category>news-tag/climate-action</category>
            <category>news-tag/decarbonization</category>
            <category>news-tag/net-zero</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-data-exchange</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-footprint-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-sustainability-solutions</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Using Weather Analytics to Reduce Food Waste]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/planalytics-weather-analytics-reduce-food-waste</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/planalytics-weather-analytics-reduce-food-waste</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Integrating weather as a demand signal, like with Planalytics, enables businesses to use analytics to drive measurable, repeatable benefits.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-footprint</category>
            <category>topic/data-analytics</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sustainability Takes Flight across Aviation Industry]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/sustainability-aviation-industry</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/sustainability-aviation-industry</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Airplane manufacturers are moving towards a holistic strategy for sustainable design throughout an airplane’s entire life cycle. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/aerospace-defense</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-footprint</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-neutrality</category>
            <category>news-tag/circular-economy</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>product/sap-enterprise-product-development</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[For High-Tech Supply Chains, CO2 Emission Tracking Is Sustainable Business Currency]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/high-tech-supply-chains-co2-emission-tracking</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/high-tech-supply-chains-co2-emission-tracking</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[High-tech industry leaders are making sustainability a core commitment, and it is transforming business models to address climate change.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-footprint</category>
            <category>news-tag/circular-economy</category>
            <category>topic/data-analytics</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>industry/high-tech</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/net-zero</category>
            <category>product/sap-product-footprint-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[What’s Next in High-Growth Digital Innovations]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/whats-next-in-high-growth-digital-innovations</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/whats-next-in-high-growth-digital-innovations</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Five tech experts share what technology advancements are reshaping the future of intelligent, sustainable, networked business in the cloud.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-footprint</category>
            <category>news-tag/covid-19</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-io</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Solvay: One of SAP’s First Customers Is Also One of the Most Sustainable]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/06/solvay-sap-customer-sustainable</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/06/solvay-sap-customer-sustainable</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Solvay produces materials and composite technologies used in everyday life and in the first solar-powered plane to fly around the world.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-footprint</category>
            <category>news-tag/circular-economy</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-extreme-series</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Carbon Footprint Strategy: Measure, Share, Reduce]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/06/carbon-footprint-data-strategy</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/06/carbon-footprint-data-strategy</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Innovation Center Network is developing an interoperable carbon data network to allow customers to share their carbon emission data.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-emissions</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-footprint</category>
            <category>news-tag/climate-action</category>
            <category>news-tag/database-and-data-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[There Can Be No Business Transformation in Isolation from Sustainability]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/06/no-business-transformation-in-isolation-from-sustainability</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/06/no-business-transformation-in-isolation-from-sustainability</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[At SAP Sapphire The Hague, Rohit Nagarajan, president of SAP EMEA North, discussed why sustainability is a transformation imperative.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-footprint</category>
            <category>news-tag/climate-action</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Extending the Reach of SAP Cloud for Sustainable Enterprises]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/extending-sap-cloud-for-sustainable-enterprises</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/extending-sap-cloud-for-sustainable-enterprises</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Cloud for Sustainable Enterprises combines a comprehensive portfolio of solutions to holistically manage sustainability performance.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-emissions</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-footprint</category>
            <category>news-tag/circular-economy</category>
            <category>news-tag/climate-action</category>
            <category>product/sap-cloud-for-sustainable-enterprises</category>
            <category>product/sap-product-footprint-management</category>
            <category>product/sap-responsible-design-and-production</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Why Green Hydrogen Just Might Be the Silver Bullet Against Climate Change]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/green-hydrogen-might-be-silver-bullet-against-climate-change</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/green-hydrogen-might-be-silver-bullet-against-climate-change</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Expectations for green hydrogen to become the fuel of the future are high. Read to learn more about the energy source.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_12e52ba8efa72574cf8018a601d2f5c6afab9e93a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_12e52ba8efa72574cf8018a601d2f5c6afab9e93a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_12e52ba8efa72574cf8018a601d2f5c6afab9e93a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Why Green Hydrogen Just Might Be the Silver Bullet Against Climate Change" src="./media_12e52ba8efa72574cf8018a601d2f5c6afab9e93a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="why-green-hydrogen-just-might-be-the-silver-bullet-against-climate-change">Why Green Hydrogen Just Might Be the Silver Bullet Against Climate Change</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Expectations for green hydrogen to become the fuel of the future are high.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>By 2050, according to <a href="https://www.goldmansachs.com/insights/pages/gs-research/green-hydrogen/report.pdf">research by Goldman Sachs</a>, green hydrogen could supply up to 25% of the world’s energy needs and become a €13 trillion (US$15 trillion) market. But until we get there, current challenges of storing and transporting hydrogen need to be overcome first.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="enable-supplier-transparency-in-your-supply-chain-with-greentoken-by-sap">Enable supplier transparency in your supply chain with GreenToken by SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.green-token.io/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="not-all-hydrogen-is-created-equal">Not All Hydrogen Is Created Equal</h2>
  <p>In the long run, only CO2-free hydrogen produced with the help of renewable energies is sustainable. However, it will be quite a while before there is enough green hydrogen to meet the growing demand. The reason: there is not enough green electricity. Of the many alternative production methods, the most popular today is blue or grey hydrogen produced from natural gas.</p>
  <p>In the future, many industrial processes will use green or blue hydrogen or downstream products made from it, such as ammonia and methanol. Hydrogen can particularly help clean up emission-intensive industries like transportation, chemical iron, and steel production, which account for about 7% of global CO2 emissions each year. But the high number of potential users contrasts with the limited availability and high production costs of hydrogen.</p>
  <h2 id="cross-company-alliances-to-accelerate-the-value-chain">Cross-Company Alliances to Accelerate the Value Chain</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-all-the-cloud-analytics-features-you-need-in-a-single-solution-with-sap-analytics-cloud">Get all the cloud analytics features you need in a single solution with SAP Analytics Cloud</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/cloud-analytics.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In line with the <a href="https://ec.europa.eu/info/strategy/priorities-2019-2024/european-green-deal_en">European Green Deal</a> to reduce emissions at least 55% by 2030 and make Europe climate-neutral by 2050, governments have adopted similar sustainability goals and consider hydrogen a critical component to reach them. <a href="/2021/05/net-zero-emissions-transformation-journey">Companies are also taking action</a> to support green and digital transformations in the EU. For instance, the <a href="https://www.se.com/ww/en/about-us/newsroom/news/press-releases/european-ceo-alliance-emphasizes-cross-industry-collaboration-to-fight-climate-change-5f771e77ccf05b586c3f6508">European CEO Alliance</a> was founded by 12 executives from leading European companies to develop concrete recommendations for action and help companies undergo the green transition. This alliance is driven by the conviction that no company will solve the greatest challenges of our time alone. To succeed, companies need to collaborate across value chains, build partnerships, and work together with governments and academia.</p>
  <p>One project that has emerged from these cross-company efforts is looking at how to accelerate the complete value chain of green hydrogen – from production, transport, storage, and sale, to the energy customer. Instead of operating in silos, these market segments need to be linked together.</p>
  <h2 id="a-data-sharing-platform-as-the-single-source-of-truth">A Data-Sharing Platform as the Single Source of Truth</h2>
  <p>The first prototype of a green hydrogen platform based on <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/cloud-analytics.html">SAP Analytics Cloud</a> looks promising. The platform combines data from all participants of the hydrogen value chain and, therefore, enables better data-driven business decisions. Instead of managing complicated spreadsheets, an energy provider can use the platform as their single source of truth to run simulations and calculate how much energy they can produce, how much they want to sell to the electrolyzer, and how much power they need for vehicles, households, and industries.</p>
  <p>For such platforms to be successful, visibility across the value chain of green hydrogen is a prerequisite. Supply chain solution <a href="https://www.green-token.io/">GreenToken by SAP</a> helps companies to track hydrogen across the entire supply chain, from production to energy customer, via electrolyzers and carriers using blockchain technology. The solution is designed to provide auditable proof of what percentage of the hydrogen is green, blue, or grey. GreenToken can also be used to track <a href="https://www.epa.gov/climateleadership/scope-3-inventory-guidance#:~:text=3%20Emission%20Factors-,Description%20of%20Scope%203%20Emissions,impacts%20in%20its%20value%20chain.&#x26;text=Scope%203%20emission%20sources%20include,downstream%20of%20the%20organization%27s%20activities.">scope 3 CO2 emissions</a> that are caused when hydrogen is imported from far away. Companies can leverage the data to prove that their purchased hydrogen is truly green. They can also see how much CO2 has been created during the journey from production origin to customer site and, therefore, how much they would need to offset to make the hydrogen 100% green again.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Klaus Schimmer is chief innovation architect of Sustainability at SAP.</em><br><em>The article was initially published on the <a href="https://partners.wsj.com/sap/experience-management-in-action/why-green-hydrogen-just-might-be-the-silver-bullet-against-climate-change/">Wall Street Journal</a>.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-emissions</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-footprint</category>
            <category>news-tag/climate-action</category>
            <category>news-tag/climate-change</category>
            <category>product/sap-green-token</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Decarbonization Depends on the Data]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/06/decarbonization-depends-on-data</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/06/decarbonization-depends-on-data</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn how digitalization, data transparency, and collaborative action are key to meeting decarbonization targets in the automotive industry.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10d619ba9f35d98eba2a2b782fbc8fb3ca9f169de.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10d619ba9f35d98eba2a2b782fbc8fb3ca9f169de.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_10d619ba9f35d98eba2a2b782fbc8fb3ca9f169de.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Decarbonization Depends on the Data" src="./media_10d619ba9f35d98eba2a2b782fbc8fb3ca9f169de.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="decarbonization-depends-on-the-data">Decarbonization Depends on the Data</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>The race to zero carbon emissions among car manufacturers <a href="http://www.automobilsport.com/cars-tuning--37,222545,Way-to-Zero-Volkswagen-presents-roadmap-for-climate-neutral-mobility,news.htm">is in full swing</a>. Earlier this month, the world’s largest producer, Volkswagen Group (VW), indicated it would <a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/volkswagen-electric-emissions/insight-how-low-can-you-go-volkswagen-throws-down-the-emissions-gauntlet-idUSL1N2ML25I">support more ambitious CO2 emissions targets</a>, catching European rivals off guard and putting them under pressure to follow suit.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>But the race to “net zero” for the automobile industry is still in the first lap, and the route promises to be long and arduous. Greenhouse gas emissions from the industry account for more than 9% of global emissions – equaling those of the entire European Union. To achieve their individual sustainability targets, companies are dependent on each other for reliable and verifiable data.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="is-your-company-chasing-zero-learn-more">Is your company Chasing Zero? Learn more.</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="http://sap.com/ChasingZero">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="decarbonization-is-all-about-the-data">Decarbonization Is All About the Data</h2>
  <p>Becoming carbon neutral requires managing the carbon footprint of individual products in the supply chain, and to achieve this companies need transparency into the carbon footprints of their upstream suppliers – referred to as <a href="https://ghgprotocol.org/sites/default/files/standards_supporting/FAQ.pdf">scope 3 emissions</a>. The problem is that only 21% of business executives are satisfied with the quality of their environmental data, <a href="/2021/04/sustainability-study-from-sap-actions-challenges">according to a global research study from SAP</a>.</p>
  <p>But more accurate carbon footprint data is on the way. “Until now, companies have been using averages to calculate carbon footprint at a product level because there’s been a lack of accurate, granular emissions data and no consistent methodology,” said John Revess, director Net Zero Transformation at the World Business Council for Sustainable Development (WBCSD). “To remain a part of global supply chains, it will be necessary for companies to accurately calculate the carbon footprint of their products based on measured values,” predicted Revess. As a member of WBCSD, SAP and other companies are defining a <a href="https://www.wbcsd.org/Programs/Climate-and-Energy/Climate/SOS-1.5/Resources/Value-Chain-Carbon-Transparency-Pathfinder-Enabling-decarbonization-through-Scope-3-emissions-transparency">Value Chain Carbon Transparency Pathfinder</a> for the exchange of carbon emissions data.</p>
  <p>“To meet our decarbonization goals, we depend on credible data from our suppliers on the carbon footprints of the components we build our vehicles with,” said Ralf Pfitzner, global head of Sustainability at Volkswagen, at the <a href="https://events.sap.com/sap-sustainability-summit/en/home">SAP Sustainability Summit</a>.</p>
  <p>The two-day online meeting focused on how companies are applying new technologies to reduce their environmental footprint and manage limited resources. “We decided to join SAP in the co-innovation of a digital carbon tracking tool and database, and this is really exciting because there is obviously a demand,” said Pfitzner.</p>
  <p>Volkswagen and SAP are working together toward decarbonization in other ways. In 2020, their CEOs Herbert Diess and Christian Klein joined the <a href="https://www.volkswagenag.com/en/news/2021/03/European-CEO-Alliance-advocates-for-ambitious-climate-strategy.html#:~:text=The%20CEO%20Alliance%20considers%20itself,chain%20and%20rapid%20build%2Dup">CEO Alliance for Europe’s Recovery, Reform, and Resilience</a>. The Alliance’s 10 European business leaders have committed 100 billion to decarbonizing their companies and products and are calling for far-reaching climate protection measures.</p>
  <h2 id="massive-investments-necessary-in-electrification-and-digitalization">Massive Investments Necessary in Electrification and Digitalization</h2>
  <p>VW is <a href="https://www.volkswagen-newsroom.com/en/press-releases/volkswagen-group-raises-investments-in-future-technologies-to-eur-73-billion-6607">investing a hefty €73 billion</a> to help put its decarbonization challenges in the rear-view mirror. The underlying reasons for <a href="/2021/04/sustainability-study-from-sap-actions-challenges">companies’ investments in environmental issues</a> varies, spanning industry regulations (29%) to society’s approval of their organization (27%) and strengthening company reputation (26%). Uncertainty as to how to embed sustainability into business processes and IT systems is seen as the greatest barrier to implementing plans for action, <a href="/2021/04/sustainability-study-from-sap-actions-challenges">one study concludes</a>.</p>
  <p>Despite the challenges, VW’s Pfitzner is optimistic about achieving the company’s decarbonization targets. VW’s head of sustainability expects digitalization to play a major role in this transformation. “Beyond green electricity, there are plenty of opportunities where digitalization will help us reduce our carbon footprint, for example by hooking the manufacturing data into the cloud and having more efficient programming of robots,” he said.</p>
  <p>Pfitzner reiterated <a href="https://www.volkswagenag.com/en/news/stories/2019/12/what-volkswagen-is-doing-for-the-environment.html">VW’s 2050 goal of carbon neutrality</a> along the entire lifecycle of its cars, emphasizing the need for intermediate milestones. “The coming decades will be essential for the transformation of transport and the car industry. By 2030, we intend to reduce the lifecycle carbon footprint of our passenger car portfolio by 30% compared to 2018,” said Pfitzner.</p>
  <h2 id="no-carbon-neutrality-in-isolation">No Carbon Neutrality in Isolation</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sustainability-actions-still-challenging-to-implement-according-to-new-study-from-sap">Sustainability Actions Still Challenging to Implement, According to New Study from SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/04/sustainability-study-from-sap-actions-challenges">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Although nearly two-thirds of the global economy is covered by net zero targets, achieving them will require systems thinking and collaborative action among businesses of a type and scale that has never been done before, <a href="https://www2.deloitte.com/uk/en/pages/press-releases/articles/deloitte-announces-senior-partner-appointments-in-climate-change-and-transport.html">said Hannah Routh</a>, partner, Deloitte UK. “The proof will be in the implementation,” she predicted.</p>
  <p>“No business or country can become net zero in isolation,” said Routh. “Whether you are looking at energy supply, transportation, infrastructure, government, or communities, they all need to act in a coordinated way.”</p>
  <p>One of the biggest challenges for companies, says Routh, is embedding climate transformation into their business strategies and decision-making processes. This requires data transparency, she emphasizes, noting that there is no shortage of data, but the quality and usability of the data must be ensured.</p>
  <p>Nicolas Peter, BMW’s chief financial officer, agrees. “Digitalization helps in a significant way to increase data quality, and, from an auditor’s perspective, data quality is key in order to perform his responsibility in the audit process,” he said at SAP’s Sustainability Summit. Peter left no doubts that BMW is counting on new technologies to help it <a href="https://www.wemeanbusinesscoalition.org/blog/bmw-joins-growing-list-of-automakers-committed-to-bold-climate-action/">achieve its climate targets</a>: “The trend to sustainability has to be accompanied by digitalization. There is no alternative,” said Peter.</p>
  <h2 id="digitalization-supports-decarbonization">Digitalization Supports Decarbonization</h2>
  <p>“CEOs need transparency into their supply chains,” said Thomas Saueressig, head of Product Engineering and member of the Executive Board of SAP SE. “Through its strategic initiative <a href="https://community.sap.com/topics/sustainability/climate21">Climate 21</a>, SAP is launching new solutions that help customers reduce their emissions and manage their carbon footprint.”</p>
  <p>A new integrated set of solutions announced at the SAP Sustainability Summit includes SAP Product Footprint Management, which treats greenhouse gases like a ‘currency’ in the value chain. “Our sustainability management solutions enable companies not only to optimize their production facilities according to top line and bottom line, but also according to greenhouse gas emissions,” said Saueressig. As part of several joint sustainability initiatives with Accenture, <a href="/2021/04/sap-and-accenture-sustainability-better-business">SAP and Accenture are working</a> to develop new SAP solutions that address sustainability and enhance existing core technologies.</p>
  <h2 id="the-need-for-speed">The Need for Speed</h2>
  <p>Setting data quality issues aside, the most important factor for transforming businesses to net-zero is speed, said Deloitte’s Routh. “I think the world can master this, but my concern is whether it can do it quickly enough. The businesses that are going to succeed are the ones that understand and embrace the urgency.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/automotive</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-emissions</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-footprint</category>
            <category>news-tag/chasing-zero</category>
            <category>news-tag/climate-21</category>
            <category>news-tag/climate-change</category>
            <category>news-tag/economics</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Electrification of Mobility: Challenges and Opportunities for Travel and Transportation Operators]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/e-mobility-travel-transportation-operators</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/e-mobility-travel-transportation-operators</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP recently hosted an industry forum about the e-mobility with leading operators and industry value chain actors. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-footprint</category>
            <category>news-tag/electric-vehicles</category>
            <category>news-tag/mobile</category>
            <category>industry/travel-transportation</category>
            <category>news-tag/service-industries</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>