<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/product/sap-learning-hub/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Equipping the Next Generation of Underrepresented Talent for a Career in Tech]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/equipping-next-generation-underrepresented-talent-tech</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/equipping-next-generation-underrepresented-talent-tech</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP’s digital skills initiative helps prepare underrepresented groups for a career in tech through a free SAP Certification course.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1516454e29028b1edfdf3049f7d0417f3f4530c3f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1516454e29028b1edfdf3049f7d0417f3f4530c3f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1516454e29028b1edfdf3049f7d0417f3f4530c3f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Equipping the Next Generation of Underrepresented Talent for a Career in Tech" src="./media_1516454e29028b1edfdf3049f7d0417f3f4530c3f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="equipping-the-next-generation-of-underrepresented-talent-for-a-career-in-tech">Equipping the Next Generation of Underrepresented Talent for a Career in Tech</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>“I just never saw myself in tech.”</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>This is what I heard during my discussion with the first cohort of SAP’s <a href="https://learning.sap.com/digital-skills">digital</a> <a href="https://learning.sap.com/digital-skills?campaigncode=CRM-YD24-ISM-2422141&#x26;source=blog-glo-Unrepped_Talent">skills</a> <a href="https://learning.sap.com/digital-skills">initiative</a>, a program that helps equip underrepresented and underserved groups for a career in the tech industry through participation in a free SAP Certification course.</p>
  <p>How could it be that in a time when companies need to find talent quickly to fill the need for technically skilled roles – a need that is becoming more urgent by the day – there is an entire population of determined, driven people who feel as though they do not belong in the tech industry?</p>
  <h2 id="the-current-state-of-diversity-in-technology">The Current State of Diversity in Technology</h2>
  <p>The numbers speak volumes: only <a href="https://ncwit.org/resource/bythenumbers/">27% of all computing-related jobs are held by women</a>. Only 3% of those jobs are held by Black women and 1% are held by Latina women. For me, it has always been impossible to ignore the lack of representation in the tech industry. I am acutely aware of when I am the only woman in the room – let alone the only Black woman.</p>
  <p>But this is changing. Companies have begun implementing diversity-forward hiring practices to try to minimize barriers for populations that have historically been overlooked. The percentage of <a href="https://www.naceweb.org/diversity-equity-and-inclusion/individuals-with-disabilities/ready-willing-but-still-underemployed/e619e772-a54b-4df6-858c-9ca50717a5a0">employers with diversity recruiting efforts</a> rose from 56% in 2016 to 88% in 2021. Though there is now targeted backlash, numerous employers remain committed to their diversity, equity, and inclusion (DE&#x26;I) goals for the workforce.</p>
  <p>These initiatives have proven to be important to younger generations. In a few years, millennials and Gen Z will make up the majority of our workforce – and they want to work for companies that align with their values. A 2022 survey from the <a href="https://www.naceweb.org/diversity-equity-and-inclusion/individuals-with-disabilities/ready-willing-but-still-underemployed/835bc35a-e4be-42fb-b838-d06086cb87bc">National Association of Colleges and Employers (NACE)</a> found that 76% of recent graduates indicated that <a href="/topics/diversity-and-inclusion">diversity, equity, and inclusion efforts</a> were “very important” or “extremely important” when considering their future employers.</p>
  <h2 id="helping-underserved-groups-break-into-tech">Helping Underserved Groups Break into Tech</h2>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="accelerate-your-career-with-our-digital-skills-initiative">Accelerate your career with our digital skills initiative</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://learning.sap.com/digital-skills?campaigncode=CRM-YD24-ISM-2422141&#x26;source=blog-glo-Unrepped_Talent">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>If we want diverse workforces, we must support and create targeted channels to source diverse talent. It is imperative that these groups – including women, people of color, veterans, and others – are given the resources to excel in high tech. I have seen firsthand how our digital skills initiative is making an impact on individuals and their communities, working to ensure that talent from all backgrounds can participate in this exciting era of technological innovation. At SAP, we offer training on products like <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/s4hana.html?campaigncode=CRM-YD24-ISM-2422141&#x26;source=blog-glo-Unrepped_Talent">SAP S/4HANA Cloud</a> and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp.html?campaigncode=CRM-YD24-ISM-2422141&#x26;source=blog-glo-Unrepped_Talent">SAP ERP</a>, whether through programs like the digital skills initiative or on <a href="https://learninghub.sap.com/?campaigncode=CRM-YD24-ISM-2422141&#x26;source=blog-glo-Unrepped_Talent">SAP Learning Hub</a>, helping anyone interested in jump-starting their career in tech.</p>
  <p>Without diverse perspectives, we leave out too many pieces of the puzzle to see the big picture. This deficit is particularly obvious in technology, given its influence on everything from how we shop to how we govern. It is unsustainable to expect lasting market viability from products that are developed by and marketed to one type of person. Put simply, employing diverse talent is essential to long-term success.</p>
  <h2 id="how-companies-can-recruit-diverse-talent">How Companies Can Recruit Diverse Talent</h2>
  <p>For companies that are looking for the next pool of employees to solve today’s business challenges, it is time to consider non-traditional avenues of talent, like graduates from SAP’s digital skills initiative. Each cohort comes equipped with SAP Certification, self-motivation, and a strong work ethic. This is a special opportunity to pull from a curated group of strong candidates, not just because of their new skills but because of demonstrated curiosity and drive that is not easy to find.</p>
  <p>SAP makes these trained and certified candidates available to recruiters at no charge. Want to get access to SAP-certified, ready-to-hire talent? Interested in adopting a cohort? <a href="https://learning.sap.com/digital-skills/hire-talent?campaigncode=CRM-YD24-ISM-2422141&#x26;source=blog-glo-Unrepped_Talent">Contact us</a> to see how you can start hiring and get involved.</p>
  <h2 id="register-for-the-digital-skills-initiative-as-a-participant">Register for the Digital Skills Initiative as a Participant</h2>
  <p>If you are interested in expanding your career opportunities by learning in-demand skills and achieving an SAP Certification free of charge, apply for the digital skills initiative using the <a href="https://community.sap.com/t5/beginner-corner-blog-posts/digital-skills-initiative-applicant-guide-for-self-study-candidates/ba-p/273119">applicant guide</a>. This is a fantastic opportunity for those who want to make a career switch to tech.</p>
  <p>To those who never pictured themselves in the tech industry, picture it. There is a place for you. Take this as a sign to invest in yourself and create a new path to success.</p>
  <h2 id="making-an-impact-on-future-generations">Making an Impact on Future Generations</h2>
  <p>When I talked with this first cohort of the digital skills initiative, I saw how they take great pride in their certification. For some, these new skills will prove to be life-changing.</p>
  <p>My goal is to support initiatives that aim to ensure that everyone, from all backgrounds, can pursue their interests in finding a career in tech. When we leave these doors closed, we not only rob those shut out of the opportunity, but all of us from the creativity, perspectives, and outcomes they could deliver.</p>
  <p>I am incredibly proud of SAP’s work in empowering people to pursue a career in technology. I believe that we are developing the future of innovation through programs like the digital skills initiative, and I cannot wait to see how similar programs will evolve in the future.</p>
  <p>If you are an NGO, university, or an SAP partner or customer, contact us at <a href="mailto:partners.digitalskills@sap.com">partners.digitalskills@sap.com</a> to learn more. If you are interested in applying to the digital skills initiative, <a href="https://groups.community.sap.com/t5/beginner-corner-discussions/creating-an-sap-account-and-getting-started-in-the-community/m-p/260744">create an SAP account</a> to start your journey.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Etosha Thurman is chief marketing and solutions officer for Intelligent Spend and Business Network at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>product/sap-learning-hub</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How to Boost Your Cloud Adoption]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/how-to-boost-your-cloud-adoption</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/how-to-boost-your-cloud-adoption</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Preferred Success and SAP Learning Hub can provide the training essential for unlocking the full business value of the cloud.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>product/sap-learning-hub</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-preferred-success</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Offers Professionals New Digital Learning and Certification]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/sap-offers-professionals-new-digital-learning-certification</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/sap-offers-professionals-new-digital-learning-certification</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New digital learning and certification from SAP are helping to meet the dramatically growing demand for skilled IT professionals. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15c26622362450c1931dc209600aa9d2d067dc3ff.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15c26622362450c1931dc209600aa9d2d067dc3ff.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_15c26622362450c1931dc209600aa9d2d067dc3ff.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Offers Professionals New Digital Learning and Certification" src="./media_15c26622362450c1931dc209600aa9d2d067dc3ff.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-offers-professionals-new-digital-learning-and-certification">SAP Offers Professionals New Digital Learning and Certification</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced the launch of a new guided premium learning offering with SAP Learning Hub and an enhanced certification program including a new role-based certification for SAP S/4HANA Cloud implementation consultants.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The demand for skilled IT professionals is expected to grow dramatically – up 23% by 2031 in the United States alone, according to the U.S. Department of Labor. To help meet this demand, the <a href="https://learning.sap.com/certifications/sap-certified-associate-implementation-consultant-sap-s-4hana-cloud-public-edition?url_id=text-sapnewscenter-prdteng">new role-based certification for implementation consultants of SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition</a> <a href="">emphasizes</a> core skills and competencies that can be applied across various cloud solutions from SAP and related versions.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="grow-your-skills-future-proof-your-career-learn-sap-for-free-anywhere-anytime">Grow your skills. Future proof your career. Learn SAP for free, anywhere, anytime.</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://learning.sap.com/">Start now</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“The pace of change and the talent shortage call for a new approach to identifying future-focused skills and roles. Instead of focusing on traditional aspects like degrees, job histories and titles, professional competencies become more important,” says Andre Bechtold, senior vice president and head of solution and innovation experience at SAP. “By transitioning to role-based certifications that focus on core skills and competencies, the skillset of a learner becomes more valuable and gains sustainability and more relevance for longer periods of time.”</p>
  <p>Many organizations rely on SAP solutions and skilled professionals to ensure a smooth and fast transition and drive business success. The enhanced SAP Learning Hub provides access to great content and includes four certification attempts per learner per year. Subscribers can receive expert guidance in digital live sessions, on-demand hands-on practice systems, advanced analytics and learning management functionalities. This new digital premium offering marks a major step in the evolution of the SAP Learning portfolio. To meet the rapid pace of technological innovation and the need to quickly gain new and future-proof skills, SAP continues to help organizations learn and become certified faster to maximize their investment.</p>
  <p>With the need for fast, comprehensive and role-based upskilling, the new certification model will make continuous learning and assessments a priority. Starting in early second quarter, these changes will support customers, partners and individuals in gaining skills across the SAP solutions portfolio and keeping them up to date.</p>
  <p><a href="/">Partners can benefit from further advancements</a>, including a tailored partner experience with curated learning journeys, exclusive access to events and subject matter experts. A subscription to SAP Learning Hub, <a href="">partner</a> edition comes with a significantly reduced price per user per year and offers additional chances to earn certifications, as well as improved analysis and tracking features.</p>
  <p>With the move to the cloud in full swing, the enhanced SAP Learning Hub and new certification program help customers and partners meet the challenges of a tight labor market and necessary workforce transformation. Learn more about <a href="https://www.sap.com/training-certification/learning-hub.html?sort=latest_desc">SAP Learning Hub</a> and the <a href="https://learning.sap.com/staying-certified">new certification program</a>.</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="http://news.sap.com/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Media Contact:</strong><br>Martin Gwisdalla, +49 6227 7-67275, <a href="mailto:martin.gwisdalla@sap.com">martin.gwisdalla@sap.com</a>, ET<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>This document contains forward-looking statements, which are predictions, projections, or other statements about future events. These statements are based on current expectations, forecasts, and assumptions that are subject to risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results and outcomes to materially differ. Additional information regarding these risks and uncertainties may be found in our filings with the Securities and Exchange Commission, including but not limited to the risk factors section of SAP’s 2022 Annual Report on Form 20-F.<br>© 2024 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>product/sap-learning-hub</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Powering Business Transformation with Unprecedented Career Growth for SAP Professionals]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/powering-unprecedented-career-growth-sap-professionals</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/powering-unprecedented-career-growth-sap-professionals</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[We all are facing a changing work environment. Read to learn how SAP Learning supports the career growth of SAP professionals.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-certification</category>
            <category>product/sap-learning-hub</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Harsh Reality of Imposter Syndrome: How Companies Can Help Employees Navigate It]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/imposter-syndrome-how-companies-can-help-employees</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/imposter-syndrome-how-companies-can-help-employees</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Many organizations are recognizing imposter syndrome as a persistent experience. Learn how the partner edition of SAP Learning Hub can help.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>product/sap-learning-hub</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rethinking Learning and Change Management with a Cloud Mindset]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/rethinking-learning-and-change-management-with-a-cloud-mindset</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/rethinking-learning-and-change-management-with-a-cloud-mindset</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With companies adopting a cloud mindset, needs and expectations for learning and change management shift. Read to find out how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-activate</category>
            <category>product/sap-enable-now</category>
            <category>product/sap-learning-hub</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP's Vision for Supporting Business Transformation and the Workforce of the Future]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/vision-business-transformation-workforce-of-the-future</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/vision-business-transformation-workforce-of-the-future</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP has a vision for supporting the workforce of the future as humanity enters one of its most transformative phases. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/opensap</category>
            <category>non-sap-event/wef-davos</category>
            <category>product/sap-learning-hub</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-training-and-adoption</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-university-alliances</category>
            <category>news-tag/un-sdgs</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[People Drive Success: RISE with SAP Inspires and Empowers Employees]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/02/people-drive-success-rise-with-sap-training</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/02/people-drive-success-rise-with-sap-training</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[For a successful business transformation, put your people first with a holistic strategy for change management and training. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-enable-now</category>
            <category>product/sap-learning-hub</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-training-and-adoption</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP and the EU TUMO Convergence Center Team Up to Boost Digital Education]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/sap-eu-tumo-convergence-center-digital-education</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/sap-eu-tumo-convergence-center-digital-education</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP and the EU TUMO Convergence Center are helping students and recent graduates understand, utilize, and shape digital technologies.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1712136a51fe7abe9956a3c324ab5b20621fe243a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1712136a51fe7abe9956a3c324ab5b20621fe243a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1712136a51fe7abe9956a3c324ab5b20621fe243a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP and the EU TUMO Convergence Center Team Up to Boost Digital Education" src="./media_1712136a51fe7abe9956a3c324ab5b20621fe243a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-and-the-eu-tumo-convergence-center-team-up-to-boost-digital-education">SAP and the EU TUMO Convergence Center Team Up to Boost Digital Education</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="test-drive-sap-learning-hub-today-with-a-free-trial">Test drive SAP Learning Hub today with a free trial</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/td/sap-learning-hub.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) and the <a href="https://www.convergence.center/">EU TUMO Convergence Center for Engineering and Applied Science</a>, which helps bridge the gap between higher education and industry in Armenia, today said they launched a strategic collaboration aimed at helping university students and recent graduates understand, utilize and shape digital technologies.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“Innovation is what supercharges any science and technology ecosystem, and our collaboration with SAP deploys an innovation platform that is full of promise, not only from an industry perspective but also in terms of leading-edge research and education,” TUMO chief development officer Pegor Papazian said.</p>
  <p>As part of this collaboration, the EU TUMO Convergence Center is now an associate member of the <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/innovation/next-gen-innovation-platform/university-alliances.html">SAP University Alliances program</a>. As such, it will have access to SAP software and learning content, and a partnership with the SAP network, including SAP Next-Gen Labs around the world.</p>
  <p>The SAP Innovation Center Network in Potsdam, Germany, has developed 22 <a href="https://blogs.sap.com/2021/09/27/sap-innovation-center-network-invites-university-students-to-solve-real-world-business-technical-challenges/">innovation exploration challenges</a> for <a href="https://www.convergence.center/tumo-labs">TUMO Labs</a>, a technology, applied science and engineering education hub that is part of the EU TUMO Convergence Center. Students can explore emerging topics such as the future of self-service, augmented access control or augmented extended planning and analysis. In close collaboration with experts at the SAP Innovation Center Network, they will work to formulate proven and validated solutions to industry challenges. The expected outcomes range from user interface mockups and use-case ideas to data exploration and prototype code.</p>
  <p>“Students have the opportunity to put their creativity to work and connect research ideas to real-world business challenges,” said Lukasz Ostrowski, development manager at the SAP Innovation Center Network in Potsdam. “Working with educational institutions like TUMO Labs offers us the chance to find new talent and shape the next generation of enterprise software together.”</p>
  <p>The EU TUMO Convergence Center is currently registering for SAP learning resources, including SAP Learning Hub, <a href="https://learninghub.sap.com/academicedition/registration">academic edition</a> and SAP Learning Hub, <a href="https://learninghub.sap.com/next-gen">edition for SAP Next-Gen</a>. Plans to expand the collaboration are being evaluated and could include <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/innovation/next-gen-innovation-platform/young-thinkers.html">SAP Young Thinkers</a> programs, an SAP Next-Gen Lab in the EU TUMO Convergence Center and a research collaboration with TUMO Labs Berlin.</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="http://news.sap.com/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP on Twitter at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Media Contact:</strong> Benjamin Nickel, +49 170 4920616, <a href="mailto:benjamin.nickel@sap.com">benjamin.nickel@sap.com</a>, CET<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>Any statements contained in this document that are not historical facts are forward-looking statements as defined in the U.S. Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995. Words such as “anticipate,” “believe,” “estimate,” “expect,” “forecast,” “intend,” “may,” “plan,” “project,” “predict,” “should” and “will” and similar expressions as they relate to SAP are intended to identify such forward-looking statements. SAP undertakes no obligation to publicly update or revise any forward-looking statements. All forward-looking statements are subject to various risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results to differ materially from expectations. The factors that could affect SAP’s future financial results are discussed more fully in SAP’s filings with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (“SEC”), including SAP’s most recent Annual Report on Form 20-F filed with the SEC. Readers are cautioned not to place undue reliance on these forward-looking statements, which speak only as of their dates.<br>© 2021 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-innovation-center-network</category>
            <category>product/sap-learning-hub</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-next-gen</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-university-alliances</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Preparing Partners for Their Future with SAP Learning]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/preparing-partners-for-their-future-with-sap-learning</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/preparing-partners-for-their-future-with-sap-learning</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Read to learn how the SAP Learning organization supports the partner ecosystem through offering accessible upskilling opportunities.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1571d8c395f68455a08d2131f47a138e448c6652f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1571d8c395f68455a08d2131f47a138e448c6652f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1571d8c395f68455a08d2131f47a138e448c6652f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Preparing Partners for Their Future with SAP Learning" src="./media_1571d8c395f68455a08d2131f47a138e448c6652f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="preparing-partners-for-their-future-with-sap-learning">Preparing Partners for Their Future with SAP Learning</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>These days, it can be so easy to get bogged down in the day-to-day and lose sight over our big-picture career goals. Where do we want to be five years from now? What kind of skills do we want to have a year from today?</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>While professionals may know they want to advance, they underestimate how much <a href="https://insights.sap.com/importance-upskilling/">upskilling</a>, learning, and certification can help them along that path. A recent <a href="https://home.pearsonvue.com/About/News/2021/Value-of-IT-Certification-study-highlights-benefit.aspx">study</a> underscored the value of certification in career advancement, as more than 60% of participants garnered promotions following their IT certifications. Moreover, this study found intrinsic benefits to certification, including greater confidence, determination for professional success, autonomy, and job satisfaction.</p>
  <p>And it’s true: the more we invest in ourselves – by taking the time and energy to complete certifications and stay current on the latest technologies – the better we feel about the trajectory of our careers.</p>
  <p>As the SAP Learning team helps to expand the SAP ecosystem, which is <a href="/wp-content/blogs.dir/1/files/SAP_IG_US46867020.pdf">estimated</a> to grow the number of professionals by 60% and see partner opportunities reach $260 billion by 2024, we’ve kept this sentiment at the forefront of our commitment to creating easily discoverable and accessible upskilling opportunities for partners.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="explore-sap-learning-hub-partner-edition">Explore SAP Learning Hub, Partner Edition</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/01/c4135f45-c97d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="expanding-opportunities-for-growth-among-partners-and-individual-learners">Expanding Opportunities for Growth among Partners and Individual Learners</h2>
  <p>Along the journey to the Intelligent Enterprise, it’s critical for organizations to upskill their workforce, not only to stay competitive but to foster professional development at the individual level. SAP has long supported learning and enablement throughout the ecosystem, and with the rapid speed of innovations today, we’re providing more and more affordable, role-based learning solutions.</p>
  <p>For example, in February, we launched a new <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/01/04065f45-c97d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff.html">learning offering specifically designed for partners</a> to advance continuous learning across the entire SAP portfolio and help partners stay up-to-date with SAP solutions. Developed with the SAP partner organization, it is designed to fit our partner’s specific business and learning needs. Since launch, it has been successfully adopted by the SAP partner ecosystem, with 30% net-new partners reached in the first six months of being live and thousands of learners currently using the offering to increase their knowledge and skills on SAP solutions and achieve certification.</p>
  <p>What’s more, for the SAP PartnerEdge program, we recently launched a private cloud version of <a href="https://www.sapstore.com/solutions/61162/SAP-Learning-Hub---Partner-Edition">SAP Learning Hub, partner edition</a> to help with increased customization and reporting functionalities.* With this <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/01/c4135f45-c97d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff.html">private cloud version</a>, various roles in a partner organization can benefit from specific options: learners can upskill in a more private environment with company-specific learning content, while administrators can better monitor learning activities and understand the value derived from the solution.</p>
  <h2 id="yielding-success-through-certification">Yielding Success through Certification</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-how-partner-opportunity-expands-as-the-sap-ecosystem-transforms">Read: How Partner Opportunity Expands as the SAP Ecosystem Transforms</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/wp-content/blogs.dir/1/files/SAP_IG_US46867020.pdf">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In addition to creating content to continuously build and maintain SAP skills, <a href="https://learning.sap.com/">SAP Learning</a> emphasizes validation of these skills through certification. As Nagesh Polu, SAP SuccessFactors lead consultant, YASH Technologies, noted, “<a href="https://learning.sap.com/certification">SAP Certification</a> is an important benchmark of expertise. It helps you gain key SAP knowledge and the confidence of your customers. It is a huge asset for any SAP partner.”</p>
  <p>A recent <a href="https://itcertcouncil.org/the-value-of-certification/">whitepaper</a> revealed several proven benefits of certification, including:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Fifty-nine percent of respondents agreed certifications improved implementation of technology.</li>
    <li>More than 71% of respondents agreed or strongly agreed it has increased their ability to solve problems.</li>
    <li>Ninety-four percent of IT decision-makers globally felt that having team members with certification provides value beyond the cost of achieving the certification.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>Reflecting on her certification experience, SAP Analyst Stefania Pabon said, “Without a doubt, SAP Certification has brought me a wide range of possibilities in the job market because it is generally a requirement to have SAP software knowledge.” SAP Senior Analyst Abhishek Paul echoed this view: “SAP Certification opened up a massive sea of opportunities for me. It brings a certain level of respect and is an excellent step toward securing my future.”</p>
  <p>As we make our way through the final quarter of the year and look ahead towards 2022, let’s embrace the learning opportunities in front of us for both our organizations and our own individual growth.</p>
  <p>*The private cloud version is available exclusively for SAP PartnerEdge members (excluding basic SAP PartnerEdge open ecosystem) and requires a minimum subscription of 100 users.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Jan Meyer is senior vice president and head of Learning Systems for SAP Learning.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-certification</category>
            <category>product/sap-learning-hub</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-partneredge</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Find and Create Top Talent with Up-to-Date Technology Certification]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/up-to-date-technology-certification-find-create-top-talent</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/up-to-date-technology-certification-find-create-top-talent</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP technology certifications can help a business perform better at a time when it's never been harder to find and retain the right talent.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a66c150959cdfb37047cddbd1fdf2dcedd03f3c1.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a66c150959cdfb37047cddbd1fdf2dcedd03f3c1.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1a66c150959cdfb37047cddbd1fdf2dcedd03f3c1.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Find and Create Top Talent with Up-to-Date Technology Certification" src="./media_1a66c150959cdfb37047cddbd1fdf2dcedd03f3c1.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="find-and-create-top-talent-with-up-to-date-technology-certification">Find and Create Top Talent with Up-to-Date Technology Certification</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>What do you look for in a job candidate? Skills, experience, and education are probably top priorities. But what if there was another option, a way you could know that a candidate will fulfill their role and support your business because they stay on top of the latest technology standards and trends?</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Now there is, with the right <a href="/2021/05/embrace-continued-learning-certification">certification</a>. Certification is a marker of foundational knowledge and continued learning. So when a candidate comes to you with a respected, up-to-date technology certification, you can trust that they are among the best at what they do.</p>
  <h2 id="win-the-competition-for-top-talent">Win the Competition for Top Talent</h2>
  <p>As the cloud becomes increasingly pervasive, more partners are looking for talented consultants who are certified and willing to stay current on this new and evolving technology. This makes for a significantly more competitive talent market. On top of that, candidates and employees have more needs and demands than ever.</p>
  <p>It’s never been harder to find and retain the right talent. Certification equips you with the tools needed to win the ongoing war for talent in two ways: hiring highly qualified employees and enhancing your existing workforce.</p>
  <p><strong>Find Top Talent</strong></p>
  <p>Certification provides at-a-glance insight into which candidates are highly skilled and motivated. For example, to receive a certification in SAP solutions, a candidate must pass a rigorous and comprehensive exam from SAP. Unlike a physician or certified accountant, technology experts do not need certification to practice in their field, so a technology certification speaks volumes about those who have received it. The certification says that a candidate has gone out of their way to educate themselves on the latest in SAP technology.</p>
  <p><strong>Create Your Own Top Talent</strong></p>
  <p>You may have some of the best in the business working for your company, but if they aren’t certified, how can your customers know your employees are a cut above the rest? Customers today increasingly look for certifications. This reassures them that your business can provide the up-to-date expertise they need. This is because up-to-date certification requires continuous learning to pass the latest exam.</p>
  <p>On top of that, customers are looking toward the cloud to solve their greatest business challenges and enable their digital transformations. Customers like cloud-based solutions because developers are constantly updating these solutions to meet customers’ needs. But this means that your business must do more to stay on top of these changes as cloud technology evolves.</p>
  <p>When your peers say that experience is what matters most when choosing a new job candidate, think twice. The basis for that experience – especially if it is cloud technology – is changing. A candidate who has recently taken an online exam and received a certification from a reputable certification organization has proven that they are committed to advancing their own knowledge and skills and staying current with the latest in technology.</p>
  <h2 id="sharpen-your-competitive-edge">Sharpen Your Competitive Edge</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-learning-hub-your-digital-solution-for-sap-software-skills">SAP Learning Hub: Your digital solution for SAP software skills</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/training-certification/education-courses/learning-hub.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The partner edition of SAP Learning Hub provides the tools, learning content, and practice your employees need to receive certifications from the SAP Global Certification program and to stay current. When a candidate or employee has access to SAP Global Certification and the partner edition of SAP Learning Hub, this means that they are:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Equipped with the latest digital learning content to stay current, available 24×7</li>
    <li>Up to date with comprehensive knowledge of SAP technologies, including cloud solutions from SAP</li>
    <li>Offered access to two certification exams</li>
    <li>Empowered to take “one-attempt” certification exams, a new offering that enables consultants to take an exam once and as needed</li>
    <li>Dedicated to a professional journey of self-improvement and enablement</li>
    <li>Motivated to learn more about technology</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="drive-business-success-with-validated-sap-solution-skills">Drive Business Success with Validated SAP Solution Skills</h2>
  <p>Certified experts in SAP solution skills can help your business perform better. Differentiate yourself with a skilled and trusted workforce that delivers valued outcomes. Increase efficiency and enhance customer satisfaction with up-to-date solution expertise. Certification affirms your experts’ knowledge and the fact that they are current on the latest in technology, which can boost your reputation.</p>
  <p>Today, there is more reason than ever for your employees to take and pass an SAP Global Certification online exam. The SAP PartnerEdge site will soon go live with a new and improved version of <a href="https://partneredge.sap.com/content/partnerfinder/search.html#/">SAP Partner Finder</a>, which matches SAP customers with partners that are prepared to meet their technology needs.</p>
  <p>All SAP partners will need to reenter their business information in the partner finder, and we have included new fields to help our customers and partners connect. The number of consultants who have earned certifications through the SAP Global Certification program, as well as their area of certification, will be listed.</p>
  <p>Get your business ready with a competitive differentiation through SAP Global Certification. You can help your employees receive their certification and stay current with the partner edition of SAP Learning Hub.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-the-power-of-partnership-with-sap">Learn more about the power of partnership with SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="http://www.sap.com/partner">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="find-out-more-about-the-partner-edition-of-sap-learning-hub-and-the-benefits-of-sap-global-certification-at-trainingsapcomcertification">Find out more about the partner edition of SAP Learning Hub and the benefits of SAP Global Certification at <a href="https://training.sap.com/certification/">training.sap.com/certification</a>.</h3>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>product/sap-learning-hub</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-training-and-adoption</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Getting Ahead of the Skills Curve]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/getting-ahead-skills-curve</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/getting-ahead-skills-curve</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Businesses can get ahead of the skills curve by aligning strategic workforce planning and business strategy. Read to learn more!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1be3fe31204da0bc2c881ee5a27f5a8d1f0bd6231.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1be3fe31204da0bc2c881ee5a27f5a8d1f0bd6231.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1be3fe31204da0bc2c881ee5a27f5a8d1f0bd6231.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Getting Ahead of the Skills Curve" src="./media_1be3fe31204da0bc2c881ee5a27f5a8d1f0bd6231.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="getting-ahead-of-the-skills-curve">Getting Ahead of the Skills Curve</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>What’s the uber skill? The ability to constantly learn, evolve, update, or even un-learn relevant skills. Today, training workforces to acquire that mindset of continuous learning is everything. We spoke with Stefan Haenisch, senior vice president of SAP Learning Strategic Initiatives at SAP, to dive deeper into his perspective, especially as he comes out of the World Economic Forum’s summer event, <a href="https://www.weforum.org/events/the-jobs-reset-summit-2021">The Jobs Reset Summit</a>, and recently published an <a href="https://www.weforum.org/agenda/2021/05/back-to-school-4-lessons-in-workforce-skilling/">article</a> for WEF about the critical lessons in workforce skilling and lifelong learning.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-the-skills-you-need-anytime-anywhere-with-sap-learning-hub">Learn the skills you need anytime, anywhere with SAP Learning Hub</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://learninghub.sap.com/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="q-in-your-article-for-the-world-economic-forum-you-discuss-the-importance-of-connecting-business-strategy-to-workforce-skills-can-you-share-what-this-looks-like-and-why-its-so-essential">Q: In your article for the World Economic Forum, you discuss the importance of connecting business strategy to workforce skills. Can you share what this looks like and why it’s so essential?</h3>
  <p><strong>A:</strong> Every company plots out its business strategy. But how often does it think about how this relates and aligns with its people strategy and strategic workforce planning and skill building?</p>
  <p>For example, if our strategy is to use <a href="https://insights.sap.com/what-is-artificial-intelligence/">artificial intelligence (AI)</a> to make our products smarter, we must simultaneously be asking ourselves how we can <a href="https://insights.sap.com/importance-upskilling/">upskill the workforce</a> on the required skills to drive this vision.</p>
  <p>Skill training shouldn’t be an afterthought. Instead, by connecting skills and strategy from the very beginning, companies can proactively adapt and more effectively position themselves for long-term success.</p>
  <h3 id="how-does-an-organization-develop-skills-for-the-future-when-things-are-changing-so-frequently-and-we-cant-possibly-know-what-the-world-will-look-like-in-the-next-couple-of-years">How does an organization develop skills for the future when things are changing so frequently and we can’t possibly know what the world will look like in the next couple of years?</h3>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="how-to-upskill-staff-from-strategy-to-practical-steps">How to Upskill Staff: From Strategy to Practical Steps</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://insights.sap.com/how-to-upskill-guide/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As we saw with <a href="http://news.sap.com/covid-19">the global pandemic</a>, things may go differently than predicted. Companies must embrace ambiguity and disruption when it comes to skills for the future. A recent article in the <a href="https://hbr.org/2020/01/the-transformer-clo">Harvard Business Review</a> noted, “If you focus on building individual micro skills, you may be missing the bigger picture.” Indeed, there are ‘expiration dates’ on technical skills as innovation emerges, so companies must establish a culture that encourages agility and experimentation in the workforce – and, not least, motivates continuous learning – in order to yield sustainable success. Soft skills like dealing with uncertainty, staying curious, as well as embracing and tolerating ambiguity are the foundation of employees being ready for the future. They can then quickly and continuously keep up the relevant hard skills.</p>
  <p><a href="https://www2.deloitte.com/content/dam/Deloitte/global/Documents/HumanCapital/gx-the-future-of-work-post-covid-19-poc.pdf">A recent report from Deloitte</a> asserts that the <a href="https://insights.sap.com/what-is-future-of-work/">future of work</a> in our technology-driven world is about “creating an environment where organizations can optimize human potential” and “empowering workers with agency and choice over what they do, unleashing their interests and passions.” What this means is that the ultimate skill is being able to continuously learn in a constantly changing business environment. Fostering agile, innovative mindsets and curiosity throughout the workforce – promoting not only the <em>need</em> to learn, but the <em>want</em> to learn – helps companies to think big and earn a competitive edge.</p>
  <h3 id="how-do-offerings-at-sap-help-support-strategic-workforce-planning-and-continuous-learning">How do offerings at SAP help support strategic workforce planning and continuous learning?</h3>
  <p>At SAP, we value ongoing learning as part of the foundation for success. In the fast-moving tech sector where skill demand changes faster than in other industries, we’re constantly evolving our learning offerings to support the hard and soft skills needed to help people stay competitive.</p>
  <p>Inside SAP, for example, we look at a long and successful track record in deploying skills management to effective resource management in our consulting business and are now evolving this to support dynamic and forward-looking workforce planning and development.</p>
  <p>Our customers can benefit from our experience as we are incorporating the best practices we learned in people and skills management into our SAP SuccessFactors solutions. When it comes to helping our customers and partners build and sustain SAP product skills, our digital learning offerings, <a href="https://open.sap.com/">openSAP</a> and <a href="https://learninghub.sap.com/">SAP Learning Hub</a>, work to provide easy-to-use, engaging content for learners to explore, build, and maintain relevant skills. Additionally, we help support career planning around the skills that learners are honing, working to provide the right learning journey targeted to each learner’s goals.</p>
  <p>Our mission is to create learning and development opportunity for all across the SAP ecosystem. We aim to empower everyone to successfully build SAP software skills using future-oriented content delivered in different formats to fit individual ways of learning. By better aligning strategic workforce planning and business strategy at the onset, as well as becoming laser-focused on a workplace culture that values agility and curiosity, businesses can get ahead of the skills curve.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning-for-life</category>
            <category>news-tag/opensap</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-certification</category>
            <category>product/sap-learning-hub</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-training-and-adoption</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Enterprise Support Academy: Adapting Technology Support and Enablement for a Hybrid Workforce]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/06/sap-enterprise-support-academy-hybrid-workforce</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/06/sap-enterprise-support-academy-hybrid-workforce</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Work on closing your workforce’s digital skill gaps at any place, any time, and through any device with SAP Enterprise Support Academy.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ee7c3e15705811cfffe16aeee75b11a8a5115f9a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ee7c3e15705811cfffe16aeee75b11a8a5115f9a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1ee7c3e15705811cfffe16aeee75b11a8a5115f9a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Enterprise Support Academy: Adapting Technology Support and Enablement for a Hybrid Workforce" src="./media_1ee7c3e15705811cfffe16aeee75b11a8a5115f9a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-enterprise-support-academy-adapting-technology-support-and-enablement-for-a-hybrid-workforce">SAP Enterprise Support Academy: Adapting Technology Support and Enablement for a Hybrid Workforce</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>The traditional office space may not be disappearing entirely anytime soon. But, many SAP customers are preparing to make dramatic changes in how they support their employees no matter where they are with the SAP Enterprise Support Academy program.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>After a year of significant shifts in the employee experience, organizations worldwide are benefiting from cloud technologies, process automation, and collaborative applications. However, all these changes require a workforce that is skilled to leverage these new tools and user experiences efficiently to drive greater employee satisfaction and better business value.</p>
  <p><a href="https://support.sap.com/en/offerings-programs/enterprise-support/enterprise-support-academy.html">SAP Enterprise Support Academy</a> is designed to help handle this increasingly pressing challenge for SAP customers while reducing their IT costs. Around-the-clock access to expert guidance and high impact knowledge transfer services help enable employees across all roles to build their technical skills and get the full value of their organization’s SAP solutions.</p>
  <h2 id="flexible-access-to-self-paced-live-and-trusted-expertise">Flexible Access to Self-Paced, Live, and Trusted Expertise</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="welcome-to-the-next-generation-learning-management-infrastructure">Welcome to the next generation learning management infrastructure</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://support.sap.com/en/offerings-programs/enterprise-support/enterprise-support-academy/learn.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Since the beginning of this year, more than 17,500 customers have engaged in over 13,800 learning activities – 75% of which covered cloud and hybrid deployment topics. Best of all, they are accessing the program for free through an active subscription of SAP Enterprise Support or SAP Product Support for Large Enterprises.</p>
  <p>SAP Enterprise Support Academy offers a wide range of educational training offerings augmented with an ever-evolving database of 1,200 learning assets:</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="subscribe-to-the-innovation-and-transformation-newsletter">Subscribe to the Innovation and Transformation newsletter</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/nl/sap-innovation-and-transformation-newsletter/index.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="self-paced-learning">1. Self-Paced Learning</h3>
  <p>Guided by prescriptive and social-driven analysis of the individual user’s learning needs and style, SAP Enterprise Support Academy recommends live and on-demand learning support offerings and a personalized learning plan. In addition, our customers can visit <a href="https://support.sap.com/en/offerings-programs/enterprise-support/enterprise-support-academy/learn.html">the SAP Enterprise Support edition of SAP Learning Hub</a> to choose from a catalog of virtual learning options, allowing access to sessions whenever and wherever users want.</p>
  <h3 id="live-virtual-sessions-with-sap-experts">2. Live Virtual Sessions with SAP Experts</h3>
  <p>By collaborating with SAP experts through SAP Enterprise Support guides, our customers can participate in a high impact knowledge transfer on topics including integration, deployment, and system operations. Each session can range anywhere between a 60-minute call to a multi-day training workshop.</p>
  <p>Each live virtual interaction is tailored to help our customers prepare for a migration to SAP S/4HANA on their terms, get answers to their questions, and explore different options for their plans for future <a href="https://insights.sap.com/what-is-digital-transformation/">digital transformation</a>.</p>
  <h3 id="value-maps">3. Value Maps</h3>
  <p><a href="https://support.sap.com/en/offerings-programs/enterprise-support/enterprise-support-academy/value-maps.html">The SAP Enterprise Support value maps</a> work to lead our customers through the knowledge, skills, and services needed to address business challenges and adopt intelligent technologies. The value maps provide direct access to SAP experts, collaboration forums, high impact learning, and prescriptive guidance, so users can achieve meaningful results and unlock new potential for growth.</p>
  <h2 id="ever-expanding-learning-options-to-meet-unique-requirements">Ever-Expanding Learning Options to Meet Unique Requirements</h2>
  <p>No matter the learning experience and topic, we want to help our customers have access to the information they need to move their business forward. This mission underlying SAP Enterprise Support Academy drives our team of SAP experts and support engineers to continuously adapt, integrate, and expand the learning portfolio.</p>
  <p>Every month, we send registered users a newsletter detailing the latest content added to SAP Enterprise Support Academy and the highlights of upcoming sessions. Plus, promotional articles are featured to provide a first look into new offerings being extended to program users.</p>
  <h2 id="a-distinct-opportunity-to-maximize-the-value-of-sap-software">A Distinct Opportunity to Maximize the Value of SAP Software</h2>
  <p>With a good balance of self-paced learning, educational content, and expert guidance, our customers can close their workforce’s digital skill gaps at any place, any time, and through any device.</p>
  <p>That’s the beauty of SAP Enterprise Support Academy. Regardless of role, digital experience, or education, everyone can build up their proficiency in using SAP software – such as SAP S/4HANA and SAP SuccessFactors solutions. And over time, as they apply their new skills, innovative ideas, and process know-how, employees are prepared to successfully achieve expected business outcomes together.</p>
  <p><em>Learn more about <a href="https://support.sap.com/en/offerings-programs/enterprise-support/enterprise-support-academy.html">SAP Enterprise Support Academy</a>. Stay in the conversation by following the SAP Services and Support offerings on <a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/sapsupportinfo">YouTube</a>, <a href="https://twitter.com/SAPDigitalSvcs">Twitter</a>, <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/138840">LinkedIn</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/SAPDigitalBusinessServices">Facebook</a>.</em></p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Silvia Gaber is part of SAP Enterprise Support Academy at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-enterprise-support</category>
            <category>product/sap-learning-hub</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Embrace the Growing Imperative for Continued Learning and Certification]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/05/embrace-continued-learning-certification</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/05/embrace-continued-learning-certification</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Today, there’s real, and often untapped, value to be found in continued learning. SAP Global Certification and SAP Learning Hub can help.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc</category>
            <category>product/sap-learning-hub</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Launches Free Student Offering: SAP Learning Hub, Edition for SAP Next-Gen]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/05/launch-sap-learning-hub-edition-for-sap-next-gen</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/05/launch-sap-learning-hub-edition-for-sap-next-gen</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The new SAP Learning Hub, edition for SAP Next-Gen, provides knowledge and opportunities to the next generation of talent.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>product/sap-learning-hub</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-next-gen</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-training-and-adoption</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-university-alliances</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The New Learning Toolbox for SAP S/4HANA Has Arrived]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/new-learning-toolbox-sap-s4hana</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/new-learning-toolbox-sap-s4hana</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Get a comprehensive overview of the new learning toolbox for SAP S/4HANA, including training, enablement, and courses.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1525efb65050c4567b3172aac225138d2da50bff0.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1525efb65050c4567b3172aac225138d2da50bff0.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1525efb65050c4567b3172aac225138d2da50bff0.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="The New Learning Toolbox for SAP S/4HANA Has Arrived" src="./media_1525efb65050c4567b3172aac225138d2da50bff0.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="the-new-learning-toolbox-for-sap-s4hana-has-arrived">The New Learning Toolbox for SAP S/4HANA Has Arrived</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>The past years have radically altered the manner in which the business world learns. Companies are compelled to become ever more agile and transformative and consequently there will have to be far greater emphasis on enabling workforces.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Meanwhile, a disrupted operating landscape with fresh business challenges requires us to rethink how we train our people. Naturally it makes little sense to be attempting to solve today’s challenges with yesterday’s tools.</p>
  <p>A new toolkit is needed.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="test-drive-sap-learning-hub-today-with-a-free-trial">Test drive SAP Learning Hub today with a free trial</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/td/sap-learning-hub.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="learning-and-enablement-gets-an-update">Learning and Enablement Gets an Update</h2>
  <p>Transforming business always starts with people. Education has therefore taken on ever greater strategic importance in today’s fast-evolving and automated environment, where workers are called upon to undertake new tasks and exhibit different skill sets at a moment’s notice.</p>
  <p>Learning can therefore no longer be considered a single event, but a continuous and ongoing process intrinsic to a modern way of daily life and work. As such, the manner in which training is delivered needs to be reexamined. Learning must be more accessible, easier to consume, and altogether more straightforward and efficient.</p>
  <h2 id="latest-generation-erp-requires-novel-learning-approaches">Latest Generation ERP Requires Novel Learning Approaches</h2>
  <p>The need for a new era of learning holds especially true when it comes to wiring your business up to Intelligent enterprise resource planning (ERP). Making the most out of a state-of-the-art, smart operating system necessitates pairing it with the requisite skilled personnel to run it. The Intelligent Enterprise requires smarter ways of learning.</p>
  <p>Knowledge unlocks the power of SAP S/4HANA, as demonstrated by the latest independent research findings from IDC. We understand that better training delivers considerable benefits. It:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Speeds up deployment timeframes</strong>: 70 hours or more of initial administrator training reduces deployment time by 1.5 months.</li>
    <li><strong>Is a performance enhancer</strong>: When users are well trained on SAP S/4HANA, organizations typically attain 14-times greater improvement in their KPIs.</li>
    <li><strong>Facilitates faster expansion and roll out</strong>: Not only are well trained organizations able to deploy SAP applications faster, but they also enjoy broader and faster deployments across the organization.</li>
    <li><strong>Increases customer satisfaction</strong>: Organizations are 104% more likely to be highly satisfied when users are well trained).</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="companies-like-porsche-and-attune-value-sap-s4hana-and-sap-learning-hub">Companies like Porsche and Attune Value SAP S/4HANA and SAP Learning Hub</h2>
  <p>Organizations are increasingly aware of the growing relevance of continuous learning in the workplace and are noticing the interlinkages between overall business performance and smooth enablement.</p>
  <p><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/01/9e76bbda-c77d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff.html">MHP/ Porsche</a></strong><br>“SAP Learning Hub is a main pillar of our learning strategy and it helps to ensure long-term and sustainable business success. A key outcome among others was the high adoption and certified expertise in SAP S/4HANA Cloud.”</p>
  <p><strong><a href="https://www.sap.cn/documents/2020/11/b8fcad38-be7d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff.html">Attune</a></strong><br>“As an SAP partner, SAP Learning Hub has been a key part of our learning and development strategy. It helps us stay ahead of the game and deliver exceptional value to our customer. One hundred percent of consultants were upskilled on SAP S/4HANA for fashion and vertical business, resulting in higher employee engagement and job satisfaction.”</p>
  <h2 id="sap-augments-learning-offering-for-sap-s4hana-to-reflect-emerging-trends">SAP Augments Learning Offering for SAP S/4HANA to Reflect Emerging Trends</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="book-training-for-sap-s4hana-today">Book training for SAP S/4HANA today</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://training.sap.com/content/sap-s4hana-training-overview">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>What’s new with SAP S/4HANA enablement? Content, scope, and style changes:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>A brand-new user experience (UX) interface for <a href="https://learninghub.sap.com/?sap-outbound-id=03E03105A4AD96CC886B985EC4186A834286EE13">SAP Learning Hub</a>: Customers now enjoy easier access and more personalized learning pathways.</li>
    <li>An expanded envelope for keeping up to date: The portfolio with stay current opportunities has been doubled and is now an integral part of SAP Learning Hub. On a quarterly basis, users can hone their skills with short video highlights, in-depth tutorials, hands-on practice in live training systems, and short 15-min assessments. It is complemented with expert-led live sessions and Q&#x26;A forums.</li>
    <li>Innovative learning approaches: SAP Blended Learning Academy now incorporates the concept of moderated communities while providing enablement for SAP S/4HANA. The learning experience is tailored toward two use cases, for consultancy and integration respectively. It also offers a more guided learning approach.</li>
    <li>Special focused training events, such as SAP S/4HANA transition days and SAP Skills Forum.</li>
    <li>Hundreds of tutorials have been added, including getting started, implementation, and configuration, as well as task tutorials available both in SAP Learning Hub and via the in-app learning Web assistant.</li>
  </ul>
  <p><a href="https://sapvideoa35699dc5.hana.ondemand.com/?entry_id=1_g67beyma&#x26;sap-outbound-id=03E03105A4AD96CC886B985EC4186A834286EE13">Take a video walk-through of the updates</a>.</p>
  <h2 id="solving-the-cloud-migration-skills-gap-learning-on-rise-with-sap">Solving the Cloud Migration Skills Gap: Learning on RISE with SAP</h2>
  <p>One major skills gap for many businesses relates to journeying into the cloud. SAP has been quick off the mark to plug this gap with a plethora of new learning options as part of RISE with SAP. These include:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Live content updates with many expert-led live sessions for RISE with SAP and SAP S/4HANA Cloud lines of business as well as across topics such as extensibility and integration.</li>
    <li>A dedicated RISE with SAP introduction e-learning course that clearly outlines the offering and components.</li>
    <li>An SAP S/4HANA Cloud sandbox available to all subscribers of SAP Learning Hub at no additional cost.</li>
    <li>Twenty SAP Learning Journey guides specific to public cloud offering SAP S/4HANA Cloud and a brand-new SAP Learning Journey to help SAP S/4HANA Cloud, private edition, customers onboard easily and quickly: <a href="https://help.sap.com/doc/221f8f84afef43d29ad37ef2af0c4adf/HP_2.0/en-US/f1e06ba89b8c48f299b0c61069fe31a4.html?zoom=0.7">RISE with SAP S/4HANA Cloud, Private Edition Onboarding Fundamentals Learning Journey</a>.</li>
    <li>Over 40 lines of business SAP Learning Journeys specific to SAP S/4HANA Cloud, private edition, and learners who need to upskill or freshly start their journey to this deployment of choice.</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="discover-more">Discover More</h2>
  <p>SAP is the natural learning and enablement partner for businesses that want to embrace the new world of continuous, flexible learning and those seeking to get the very most out of their Intelligent ERP.</p>
  <p>Find out more about our courses and training tools:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Test drive <a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/td/sap-learning-hub.html">SAP Learning Hub through a free trial</a></li>
    <li>Book an <a href="https://training.sap.com/content/sap-s4hana-training-overview">SAP S/4HANA training</a></li>
    <li>Check out the latest content, including webinars and podcasts, on the <a href="https://events.sap.com/eur/sap-s4hana-training-and-adoption-emea/en/home">SAP S/4HANA events page</a></li>
  </ul>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-learning-hub</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-training-and-adoption</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Transforming Learning for a Digitally Native Future]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/03/digitally-native-future-transform-learning</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/03/digitally-native-future-transform-learning</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[To support readiness for a digitally native future, SAP is simplifying access to learning for all. Learn how the company is staying dynamic.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning-for-life</category>
            <category>news-tag/moocs</category>
            <category>news-tag/opensap</category>
            <category>product/sap-learning-hub</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-training-and-adoption</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Customer-First, Partner-Centric Services of RISE with SAP Brings Resiliency to the Ecosystem]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/customer-first-partner-centric-services-rise-with-sap</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/customer-first-partner-centric-services-rise-with-sap</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The customer-first, partner-centric services of RISE with SAP is the solution for modern enterprises that times demand. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-learning-hub</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Lowers Cost of Test and Demo Environment for Partners and Enhances Real-Time Partner Dashboard to Boost Partner Success]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/sap-lowers-cost-test-demo-environment-partners-enhances-dashboard</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/sap-lowers-cost-test-demo-environment-partners-enhances-dashboard</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP plans to offer partners significantly reduced subscription fees for its test and demonstration environment licenses.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-for-me</category>
            <category>product/sap-learning-hub</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-partner-demo-environment</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-partneredge</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Launches SAP Learning Hub, Partner Edition, Designed Specifically for Partners]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/sap-learning-hub-partner-edition-designed-specifically-partners</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/sap-learning-hub-partner-edition-designed-specifically-partners</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Learning Hub, partner edition, combines all the learning content that partners of the SAP PartnerEdge program require.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1bad38205d59f6cda47d0e9dee1a1f1316512f17d.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1bad38205d59f6cda47d0e9dee1a1f1316512f17d.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1bad38205d59f6cda47d0e9dee1a1f1316512f17d.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Launches SAP Learning Hub, Partner Edition, Designed Specifically for Partners" src="./media_1bad38205d59f6cda47d0e9dee1a1f1316512f17d.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-launches-sap-learning-hub-partner-edition-designed-specifically-for-partners">SAP Launches SAP Learning Hub, Partner Edition, Designed Specifically for Partners</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-in-a-qa-with-max-wessel-and-karl-fahrbach">Learn more in a Q&#x26;A with Max Wessel and Karl Fahrbach</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced the launch of SAP Learning Hub, partner edition. This is the first SAP Learning Hub solution that combines all the learning content that partners of the SAP PartnerEdge program require.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP Learning Hub, partner edition, bundles the necessary learning tools into one affordable solution. It includes access to the entire enablement content portfolio, hands-on practice, and assessments to help partners stay up-to-date on the latest SAP innovations and to keep their certifications current.</p>
  <p>“Learning is a powerful enabler for digital transformation,” said Max Wessel, chief learning officer, SAP. “As SAP and our ecosystem accelerate to the cloud, SAP Learning Hub, partner edition, will help ensure that our partners have the skills and certifications they need to be successful.”</p>
  <p>As today’s digital transformation technology advances and cloud innovations rapidly emerge, SAP experts and partners need to update their relevant skills and knowledge continually. The new edition of SAP Learning Hub, tailored for SAP partners, is built on the existing partner engagement framework and signals SAP’s commitment to partner and customer success.</p>
  <p>“SAP partners with SAP Global Certification are at a premium to help customers become intelligent enterprises by providing high-quality services,” said Karl Fahrbach, chief partner officer, SAP. “As the foundation for customer success, partners, who run almost 90 percent of all SAP implementations, can now benefit from the partner edition of SAP Learning Hub, elevating their experience and better positioning themselves for future success by building, strengthening and validating relevant skills.”</p>
  <p>SAP Learning Hub, partner edition, combines:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Learning content to build product skills for solutions across the SAP portfolio, including leading SAP solutions like SAP S/4HANA and SAP Business Technology Platform</li>
    <li>Access to enablement content for members of SAP PartnerEdge</li>
    <li>Hands-on practice on live SAP software training systems</li>
    <li>Expert-led and peer-to-peer learning environments</li>
    <li>Opportunities to obtain SAP Global Certification digital badges and stay current with technology advances</li>
  </ul>
  <p>With a highly proficient and certified workforce across SAP solution areas, SAP partners can more effectively differentiate themselves, encourage continuous customer engagement and ultimately drive value and success for customers. Certifications not only demonstrate a commitment to deliver excellence in a tangible way but also help to differentiate organizations by verifying high-quality expertise.</p>
  <p>Amid the quick pace of digital transformation – and the subsequent need to adapt quickly and continually – SAP Learning Hub, partner edition, provides a comprehensive solution that covers initial learning content, certification and ongoing training. As new product innovations and releases are available throughout 2021, SAP will update the partner edition learning content to enable partners to keep their knowledge, skill sets and certifications current.</p>
  <p>Starting February 15, 12-month subscriptions will be available exclusively to members of the SAP PartnerEdge program for less than €750. Learn more about SAP Learning Hub, partner edition, by visiting us on the Web. For partners, please visit the <a href="https://partneredge.sap.com/learninghub">SAP PartnerEdge site</a> (requires login). For everyone else, please visit the Web page for <a href="http://sap.com/learninghub">SAP Learning Hub</a>.</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP on Twitter at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a> and <a href="https://twitter.com/SAPPartners4You">@SAPPartners4U</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Media Contact:</strong> Martin Gwisdalla, SAP, +49 (6227) 7-67275, <a href="mailto:martin.gwisdalla@sap.com">martin.gwisdalla@sap.com</a>, CET<br>Jennifer Kohanim, FleishmanHillard, +1 (617) 692-0535, <a href="mailto:erin.albright@fleishman.com">jennifer.kohanim@fleishman.com</a>, ET<br><a href="mailto:SAP%20Press%20Room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>Any statements contained in this document that are not historical facts are forward-looking statements as defined in the U.S. Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995. Words such as “anticipate,” “believe,” “estimate,” “expect,” “forecast,” “intend,” “may,” “plan,” “project,” “predict,” “should” and “will” and similar expressions as they relate to SAP are intended to identify such forward-looking statements. SAP undertakes no obligation to publicly update or revise any forward-looking statements. All forward-looking statements are subject to various risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results to differ materially from expectations. The factors that could affect SAP’s future financial results are discussed more fully in SAP’s filings with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (“SEC”), including SAP’s most recent Annual Report on Form 20-F filed with the SEC. Readers are cautioned not to place undue reliance on these forward-looking statements, which speak only as of their dates.<br>© 2021 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>product/sap-learning-hub</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Customer and Partner Success Through Continuous Learning]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/partner-edition-of-sap-learning-hub-customer-partner-success</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/partner-edition-of-sap-learning-hub-customer-partner-success</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP execs Max Wessel and Karl Fahrbach discuss the new partner edition of SAP Learning Hub, and the benefits for customers and partners.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d1f50b9dd9a49f8a6af7bd66f3dcb83efb9d2a86.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d1f50b9dd9a49f8a6af7bd66f3dcb83efb9d2a86.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1d1f50b9dd9a49f8a6af7bd66f3dcb83efb9d2a86.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Customer and Partner Success Through Continuous Learning" src="./media_1d1f50b9dd9a49f8a6af7bd66f3dcb83efb9d2a86.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="customer-and-partner-success-through-continuous-learning">Customer and Partner Success Through Continuous Learning</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>SAP Chief Learning Officer Max Wessel and SAP Chief Partner Officer Karl Fahrbach discuss the <a href="/">newly announced partner edition of SAP Learning Hub</a>, designed specifically to support partners from the SAP PartnerEdge program.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-launches-sap-learning-hub-partner-edition-designed-specifically-for-partners">SAP Launches SAP Learning Hub, Partner Edition, Designed Specifically for Partners</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="q-can-you-tell-us-what-is-new-about-sap-learning-hub-partner-edition">Q: Can you tell us what is new about SAP Learning Hub, partner edition?</h3>
  <p><strong>Max Wessel:</strong> SAP Learning Hub, partner edition, is our all-new, one-stop-shop for SAP PartnerEdge program partners to develop, cultivate, and validate their SAP skills. This is the first time we’ve created an environment exclusively for partners that houses all SAP product learning content, training systems, certification opportunities, and partner-specific enablement content in an affordable, single-priced package.</p>
  <h3 id="could-you-expand-on-what-this-means-for-partners">Could you expand on what this means for partners?</h3>
  <p><strong>Karl Fahrbach</strong>: The new edition is built based on partner feedback and a key initiative within our Next-Generation Partnering efforts. We are launching this as part of SAP’s ongoing commitment to investing in and equipping partners with the relevant tools they need to drive customer success. Enabling partners with the right skills — along with providing the opportunity to validate their skills in the marketplace via our certifications — enhances our partners’ ability to deliver value to customers and to market their expertise accordingly. Furthermore, we generate trust in our ecosystem among our customers.</p>
  <p>By enhancing the learning and certification journey for our partners and by increasing the opportunity to access these resources, partners are better positioned than ever before to leverage the market opportunity available to them.</p>
  <h3 id="how-is-this-new-offering-designed-to-meet-the-needs-of-todays-partners-in-sap-partneredge">How is this new offering designed to meet the needs of today’s partners in SAP PartnerEdge?</h3>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="explore-sap-learning-hub">Explore SAP Learning Hub</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/training-certification/education-courses/learning-hub.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><strong>MW:</strong> We designed this offering by listening to our partners and our customers. We heard that partners wanted a streamlined way to both train their people and help spur innovation for their customers. With one flat per-learner price, we have lowered the barriers to access, making the partner edition of SAP Learning Hub available for all SAP PartnerEdge members, regardless of size. Now, their subject matter experts can obtain and maintain the skills that their business requires across SAP solution areas.</p>
  <p>SAP Learning Hub, partner edition, combines expert-led and peer-to peer learning, hands-on practice with the latest SAP software releases and innovation, and opportunities to obtain SAP Global Certification. The content is tailored for partners’ specific goals, and where they and their customers are in their digital transformation journeys. The opportunities for certification are especially critical, as a recent <a href="https://www.idc.com/getdoc.jsp?containerId=US45796720">IDC study</a> found that organizations are better positioned to accomplish business objectives, achieve shorter deployment times, and face fewer critical issues when the professionals doing the deployment are certified.</p>
  <p>The current global <a href="/covid-19">pandemic</a> is accelerating an already growing trend of digital transformation, as <a href="https://www.mckinsey.com/featured-insights/coronavirus-leading-through-the-crisis/charting-the-path-to-the-next-normal/coronavirus-is-accelerating-digital-strategy-formulation">McKinsey</a> found in a recent survey, so there is an even greater need for partners to continuously update their relevant skills. As many partners in SAP PartnerEdge continue to work remotely, we have built this offering so that users can access all learning content and features wherever and whenever they learn best.</p>
  <p>Altogether, this solution meets the enablement and performance needs of partners and will continue to evolve as new SAP products, solutions, and innovations are released. With certifications in SAP’s latest technological advances via this exclusive edition of SAP Learning Hub, partners can stand out from the crowd as the preferred choice for customers.</p>
  <h3 id="why-is-it-essential-to-have-partner-specific-and-continuous-learning-content-for-sap-partners">Why is it essential to have partner-specific and continuous learning content for SAP partners?</h3>
  <p><strong>KF</strong>: Today, it is critical to keep up with the rapid pace at which innovations and new solutions regularly emerge. To remain relevant and effective, partners must keep the skills of their workforce—and recognized certifications for those skills—current. According to the <a href="https://www.weforum.org/agenda/2020/01/reskilling-revolution-jobs-future-skills/">World Economic Forum</a>, technology is expected to transform upwards of 1 billion jobs throughout the next decade. It is clear that having and maintaining up-to-date skills is a necessity for partners’ tool kits — not simply a nice-to-have.</p>
  <p>Enabling partners with proficiency in the most up-to-date skills and certifications that align with their specific industry and business needs also helps to further differentiate them in the marketplace and outperform the competition. As <a href="https://www2.deloitte.com/us/en/insights/focus/human-capital-trends/2021/workforce-trends-2020.html/?id=us:2ps:3gl:consem21:eng:cons:010721:nonem:na:F626IEQZ:1209959211:490449631679:b:RLSA_Future_of_Work:HCT21_Diving_Deeper_BMM:nb#beyond-reskilling">Deloitte’s recent report</a> on the top workforce trends driving organizations in 2021 explains, “empowering workers with agency” creates more value. When enterprises shift to a greater focus on their workforce’s learning, their teams are more equipped to “drive growth and navigate uncertainty” moving forward.</p>
  <p>By providing tailored, continuous learning opportunities through SAP Learning Hub, partner edition, our aim is to build on the existing partner engagement framework and maintain the best in class partner ecosystem that continually empowers successful customer outcomes.</p>
  <p>We’re looking forward to providing this resource to help drive success for partners and customers alike in the year ahead.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Sabine Benz is vice president and head of Outbound Go-to-Market for SAP Knowledge and Education.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>product/sap-learning-hub</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-partneredge</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>