<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/sap-award/sap-pinnacle-awards/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Pinnacle Awards: 2024 Finalists and Winners Announced]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-pinnacle-awards-2024-finalists-and-winners</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-pinnacle-awards-2024-finalists-and-winners</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Pinnacle Awards recognize top-performing and innovative partners. Learn more about the SAP Pinnacle Awards 2024 finalists and winners.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11764e94c92ed4681b4c79ee2e132a07bdde6ab9c.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11764e94c92ed4681b4c79ee2e132a07bdde6ab9c.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_11764e94c92ed4681b4c79ee2e132a07bdde6ab9c.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Pinnacle Awards: 2024 Finalists and Winners Announced" src="./media_11764e94c92ed4681b4c79ee2e132a07bdde6ab9c.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-pinnacle-awards-2024-finalists-and-winners-announced">SAP Pinnacle Awards: 2024 Finalists and Winners Announced</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>The SAP Pinnacle Awards, our most prestigious global partner recognition program, shine a spotlight on our top-performing partners that demonstrate excellence in unlocking innovative new ways for customers to run their businesses.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP’s ecosystem plays a key role in our vision to enable every organization and every industry to become a network of intelligent, sustainable enterprises. Through their unique industry expertise, implementation methodologies, complementary solutions, and commitment throughout the Customer Value Journey, partners help customers thrive and succeed with SAP.</p>
  <p>Across 26 categories in the areas of Customer Success, Intelligent Enterprise Realization, Sustainability, and Social Impact, partners are recognized for their outstanding contributions, exponential growth, and simplification. Through delivering cloud innovations that help customers achieve their goals, these partners exemplify dedication to teamwork and embody our vision for partnering excellence.</p>
  <p>Twenty-five of the 2024 winners and finalists were selected from <a href="/topics/ecosystem">SAP’s wide-ranging partner base</a>, using system-generated data on core metrics and key performance indicators. A steering committee of global SAP representatives reviewed, vetted, and ranked the achievements according to our internal criteria, which aligned with SAP’s communicated business strategies.</p>
  <p>The only exception is the Social Impact category, which recognized a partner’s lasting societal impact by leveraging SAP innovation with concrete results. Partner nominations were evaluated and ranked by a panel of jurors consisting of SAP internal and third-party representatives.</p>
  <p>Winners and finalists for all categories will receive a communication package to help them promote their success to their customers, prospects, and the media, including logos for online and physical marketing vehicles. To increase their global exposure, SAP will list the winners and finalists on its Web site for an entire year, in addition to running a comprehensive campaign that promotes these winners and finalists to joint prospects and customers.</p>
  <p>Congratulations to the <a href="https://www.sap.com/partners/pinnacle-awards.html">winners and finalists</a>! We look forward to celebrating your success at SAP Partner Connect and SAP Sapphire.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Karl Fahrbach is chief partner officer at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-pinnacle-awards-showcase-partners-that-have-excelled-in-helping-customers-become-best-run-businesses">SAP Pinnacle Awards showcase partners that have excelled in helping customers become best-run businesses</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/partners/pinnacle-awards.html">Check out this year’s winners and finalists</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>sap-award/sap-pinnacle-awards</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Pinnacle Awards: 2023 Finalists and Winners Announced]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/2023-sap-pinnacle-award-finalists-winners</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/2023-sap-pinnacle-award-finalists-winners</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[2023 SAP Pinnacle Awards winners are dedicated to teamwork and able to deliver innovations that help customers achieve their goals.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>sap-award/sap-pinnacle-awards</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Forter Trust Platform: On the Right Side of Digital Commerce]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/04/forter-trust-platform-digital-commerce</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/04/forter-trust-platform-digital-commerce</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[To combat fraud, the Forter Trust Platform recognizes shoppers through their data profile and authenticates them quickly and automatically.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1452c9c8db651a795c453d665f6511e78d518a805.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1452c9c8db651a795c453d665f6511e78d518a805.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1452c9c8db651a795c453d665f6511e78d518a805.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Forter Trust Platform: On the Right Side of Digital Commerce" src="./media_1452c9c8db651a795c453d665f6511e78d518a805.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="forter-trust-platform-on-the-right-side-of-digital-commerce">Forter Trust Platform: On the Right Side of Digital Commerce</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>If your organization has a stake in preventing fraud across your digital commerce operations, I’ll venture to say that you want Michael Reitblat and his team at Forter on your side.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As co-founder of the preeminent fraud-detection platform on the market – now available on <a href="https://store.sap.com/dcp/en/product/display-0000042467_live_v1/Forter%20Fraud%20Protection">SAP Store</a> – Reitblat told me that he has long experience in the “bad guy space,” building a successful career around staying ahead of bad actors. That means he’s the good guy for those making an honest living selling products and services online, and for buyers and shoppers making purchases digitally.</p>
  <p>Known as “The Trust Platform” for digital commerce, Forter doesn’t focus on keeping people out, rather on creating a seamless customer experience for trusted shoppers. How is this done? Machine learning and automated decisioning. Built upon a data set of billions of online identities, the Forter platform provides accurate decisions on whether the end shopper is who they say they are instantly. This ability to provide real-time decisions also streamlines merchant operations, eliminating any dependence on manual transaction reviews. That’s the key to understanding the value of this great app.</p>
  <p>The truth is that both online consumers and merchants are victimized by sophisticated, well-organized fraud networks, Reitblat explained, stealing and selling data in a chain of hard-to-detect transactions. To counteract that, merchants can inadvertently block shoppers who most need to purchase online because they fit the “wrong profile” – living in a country known for a high preponderance of fraudsters, for example. Someone might live a long distance from a physical retailer and be unable to buy essential items online, through no fault of their own. “We are here to give those buyers access, and that is a great source of pride,” he remarked. Further, if a consumer faces hurdles to online purchasing because of clumsy verification processes, they’ll just shop somewhere else. It is therefore crucial to eliminate false declines and reduce friction throughout the purchase journey.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-the-forter-trust-platform">Learn more about the Forter Trust Platform</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://store.sap.com/dcp/en/product/display-0000042467_live_v1/Forter%20Trust%20Platform%20for%20Digital%20Commerce">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="foiling-scams-through-a-circle-of-trust">Foiling Scams through a Circle of Trust</h2>
  <p>It’s somewhat ironic that the best way to thwart fraud is to operate in an environment of trust. In fact, trust among competitors is at the heart of Forter Fraud Protection. Criminals will target one type of company – a shoe manufacturer, for example – and, when detected, move on to exploit the next, giving them the advantage. “We reverse that asymmetry,” Reitblat said. “If you attack one of our customers, the others are immunized, thanks to an aggregated global network of data. They would never share their data with each other, but they are happy to do it through us.” Simply put, the Forter solution is built to recognize people through their data profile and authenticate them quickly and automatically.</p>
  <p>I asked Reitblat about credit card protection. When a consumer reports a fraudulent charge, he replied, the onus is on the retailer, who is left with the expense and is subject to fines or suspension by the credit card issuers if there are too many instances. I was also curious about how Forter stays in front of the fraudsters. Let’s just say that Reitblat, who grew up in Israel and was once a member of the intelligence community there, has his people. “Detecting security breaches, theft, the dark economy – it’s the same world,” he said. “We have an active research team staying on top of these constantly evolving threats.”</p>
  <h2 id="strength-in-numbers">Strength in Numbers</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="explore-all-that-sap-store-has-to-offer">Explore all that SAP Store has to offer</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="http://store.sap.com/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Reitblat co-founded Forter after working with a cybersecurity company that went through an acquisition – a crushing blow for him. Fortunately, he had reunited with an old high school friend from Jerusalem who also recognized that online commerce was about to take off. “In 2013, we still had to convince investors of the need for an authentication capability, and that it had to be fully automated or otherwise would require too many people to be scalable.” That resistance changed quickly, and today Forter is larger than many of its major customers, processing more than US$250 billion in transaction value per year and employing 500 professionals around the world. The solution is deployed in more than 30 countries.</p>
  <p>The <a href="http://news.sap.com/tags/covid-19">events of the past two years</a> have resulted in a burst of demand that Reitblat and his partner could not have foreseen. Besides the explosion in online shopping, purchasing behavior and customer demographics across industries changed. New retail features appeared, like curbside pickup, buy online/pick up in store (BOPIS), and contactless check-in and check-out in the hospitality industry. New online buyers included senior citizens, students, and those in advancing geographies who had never transacted online before. Additionally, with the sudden surge of orders to be delivered to alternate addresses – holiday gifts, for example, or people purchasing for family members – e-commerce systems had an extra challenge in verifying legitimacy. That process was less complex for Forter customers because its customers were already authenticated in the system.</p>
  <p>Forter Fraud Protection is tightly integrated with SAP Commerce Cloud. Laura Jorgens, director of Partnerships for Forter, acknowledged SAP partner <a href="https://netconomy.net/">Netconomy</a> for its “incredible support” in building out the integration. “Working with SAP and Netconomy feels like one ecosystem pulling together,” she said. “Hats off to the SAP partnership organization.” With the inclusion of Forter’s solution on SAP Store, she added, “SAP has become one of Forter’s most important partners.”</p>
  <p>Why not see for yourself how <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Tp3RHdk5Yic">Forter Trust Platform</a> works? The solution was just <a href="https://store.sap.com/dcp/en/news-blogs/blogs/celebrating-the-20th-year-of-sap-pinnacle-awards-and-partner-innovations-on-sap-store">named</a> an SAP Pinnacle Award finalist in the New App of the Year on SAP Store category. It’s available for download on <a href="https://store.sap.com/dcp/en/product/display-0000042467_live_v1/Forter%20Fraud%20Protection">SAP Store</a>. Or download the SAP and Forter <a href="https://l.forter.com/hubfs/forter-SAP-brochure.pdf">overview brochure</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Rajiv Nema is senior director of SAP Store Partner Solutions.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/financial-management</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/cybersecurity</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-commerce</category>
            <category>news-tag/e-commerce</category>
            <category>product/sap-commerce-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-digital-commerce</category>
            <category>sap-award/sap-pinnacle-awards</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-store</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Pinnacle Award: 2022 Finalists and Winners Announced]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/04/sap-pinnacle-award-2022-finalists-winners</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/04/sap-pinnacle-award-2022-finalists-winners</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP has announced the 2022 finalists and winners of the SAP Pinnacle Award, which recognizes partners. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>sap-award/sap-pinnacle-awards</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Solution Partners Leverage Industry Cloud to Drive Innovation in the Life Science Industry]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/life-science-partners-leverage-industry-cloud</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/life-science-partners-leverage-industry-cloud</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Aug 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP's life science partners are working to build innovative clinical trial analytics and supply chain management solutions on industry cloud.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c435fc1304cbe3bd5aa901a412cdd45bacd87070.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c435fc1304cbe3bd5aa901a412cdd45bacd87070.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1c435fc1304cbe3bd5aa901a412cdd45bacd87070.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Solution Partners Leverage Industry Cloud to Drive Innovation in the Life Science Industry" src="./media_1c435fc1304cbe3bd5aa901a412cdd45bacd87070.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="solution-partners-leverage-industry-cloud-to-drive-innovation-in-the-life-science-industry">Solution Partners Leverage Industry Cloud to Drive Innovation in the Life Science Industry</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Solution partners have been in the news of late, particularly as it relates to industry cloud and the development of new life science solutions for clinical trial analytics and supply chain management. SAP’s industry cloud gives partners access to vertical solutions that help drive tangible business outcomes and sustainable growth.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Purpose-built by SAP in conjunction with partners, these open-platform solutions are interoperable with the intelligent suite and SAP Business Network. Several partners have recently announced breakthroughs that are helping them accelerate business operations, balance cost efficiencies, and simplify the provisioning of high-value vertical solutions. Here are their stories.</p>
  <h2 id="managing-medical-device-compliance-worldwide">Managing Medical Device Compliance Worldwide</h2>
  <p>Germany’s p36 GmbH was recently recognized as a 2021 SAP Pinnacle Award finalist in the Partner Application of the Year, Industry Cloud category. The company worked closely with SAP to develop a best-in-class solution to help businesses in life sciences respond to unique device identification (UDI) requirements for medical devices.</p>
  <p>Built on SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP), p36’s new UDI solution fits into existing IT landscapes with SAP and third-party applications. It provides a holistic, managed UDI service supporting both business and IT operations with active market monitoring and process best practices for different countries – exactly what customers demand from a modern software-as-a-service (SaaS) solution. By doing so, the platform helps p36 customers achieve UDI compliance in order to become and remain competitive globally.</p>
  <p>The annual SAP Pinnacle Awards acknowledge the contributions of SAP partners that have excelled in growing their partnership with SAP and helping their customers meet their goals. “Being nominated as a finalist from more than 20,000 SAP partners worldwide is an incredible recognition of the way we have provided best-in-class cloud solutions for the life science industry. Our continued partnership with SAP has been a major factor in our success, and being a part of SAP’s industry cloud portfolio is the perfect way to support our business strategy of industry-focused SaaS solutions,<em>”</em> said Robin Wennemuth, CEO and co-founder of p36.</p>
  <h2 id="new-standard-for-life-sciences-clinical-trial-supply-operations">New Standard for Life Sciences Clinical Trial Supply Operations</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="life-sciences-industry-digitalizes-for-people-centric-clinical-drug-trials">Life Sciences Industry Digitalizes for People-Centric Clinical Drug Trials</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/08/life-sciences-symetric-people-centric-clinical-drug-trials">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>To better address the specific needs of the clinical supplies practice, SAP, Roche, and Tenthpin recently initiated an industry consortium consisting of numerous life science stakeholders, including clinical trial and interactive response technology system vendors. The consortium is focused on defining and orchestrating optimally aligned supply processes in order to harmonize clinical and commercial supply chain management systems. The next-generation SAP Intelligent Clinical Supply Management solution aims to shape the future of clinical supplies operations.</p>
  <p>To further strengthen its strategic partnership with SAP, Tenthpin opened a <a href="https://www.tenthpin.com/insights/tenthpin-announces-their-global-life-science-innovation-center-powered-by-sap-technology/">Global Life Science Innovation Center</a> that is focused on fostering innovative clinical trial solutions designed on SAP’s industry cloud.</p>
  <p>“The life science industry is at a crossroads and our clients need to reimagine their future,” said Michael Schmidt, Tenthpin partner and co-founder. “There is a strong need for innovation and the opportunity for the industry is significant. The future of the value chain for the life science industry will be data-driven and patient-centric. With the blurring of lines between pharmaceuticals and medical technology, and with the emergence of bioelectronics, the industry will provide integrated healthcare solutions and treatment that go beyond the pill. Innovation capabilities from Tenthpin in support of SAP’s industry cloud will be at the heart of this transformation.”</p>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1231514d1bf9532a4e55d6925212a90efcdad0209.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1231514d1bf9532a4e55d6925212a90efcdad0209.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1231514d1bf9532a4e55d6925212a90efcdad0209.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Intelligent Clinical Supply Management Solution" src="./media_1231514d1bf9532a4e55d6925212a90efcdad0209.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5w8MkedE3BQ&#x26;list=PLdzEJoB6CqJ9RJFQfsmtXrGGxsQ-2iRfK&#x26;index=6">SAP Intelligent Clinical Supply Management Solution</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="cloud-based-clinical-trial-analytics-solution-built-on-sap-btp">Cloud-Based Clinical Trial Analytics Solution Built on SAP BTP</h2>
  <p>In May, Achiral Systems Pvt., Ltd. launched its <a href="https://www.symetricsystems.com/trial-analytics-pr.html">SyMetric Trial Analytics</a> solution and made it available on SAP’s digital marketplace for partner offerings. The new solution provides a harmonized approach to clinical trial analytics, working to deliver increased transparency into performance, more accurate planning for future studies, greater trust in data, and ultimately higher success rates.</p>
  <p>Life science organizations conduct clinical trials worldwide through multiple contract research organizations (CRO). The success of trials depends on study planning and the performance of various sites, CROs, and the experience of researchers. Performance can vary considerably depending on the therapeutic area, the country where research is conducted, and the phase of the study. In most of these organizations, core data is scattered across departments and across multiple spreadsheets. This solution consolidates and aggregates data to bring clarity to analytics.</p>
  <p>“We are working exclusively to provide comprehensive solutions for clinical trials,” commented Uma Janapareddy, managing director of SyMetric. “Through our SAP partnership, we are able to leverage SAP Business Technology Platform to deliver flexible, cloud-based solutions to our customers. We are pleased to announce the launch of SyMetric Trial Analytics on SAP Store as part of SAP’s industry cloud.”</p>
  <p>To further the spirit of collaboration, Tenthpin and Symetic <a href="https://www.tenthpin.com/insights/tenthpin-and-symetric-announce-strategic-partnership/">announced</a> their strategic partnership to build clinical trial solutions. Bringing the industry expertise of Tenthpin with SyMetric’s clinical trial solution know-how, on top of SAP technology, is a winning match to help improve clinical trial processes.</p>
  <h2 id="vertical-solutions-drive-cost-effective-transformation-and-sustainable-growth">Vertical Solutions Drive Cost-Effective Transformation and Sustainable Growth</h2>
  <p>For life science companies, SAP’s industry cloud can provide resilience, efficiency, and flexibility while supporting strategic transformation. Its wide selection of specialized, cutting-edge solutions can be used to enhance and extend business capabilities while maintaining process integrity and compliance.</p>
  <p>Innovators can respond to changing business requirements with applications they can trust while minimizing integration and support costs. They can enable continuous innovation while protecting the security and integrity of business processes. Industry cloud solutions from SAP help increase automation and support business transformation in a safe, controlled way.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Mandar Paralkar is global head of Life Sciences at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/consumer-goods-cpg</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>industry/life-sciences</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>sap-award/sap-pinnacle-awards</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Why Partners Rise with SAP]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/05/why-partners-rise-sap-global-partner-summit</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/05/why-partners-rise-sap-global-partner-summit</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 May 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[At the 2021 SAP Global Partner Summit, SAP is announcing updates to help partners drive customer in the post-pandemic business landscape.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_124f2695176516da3f135c78e53d2015319efbdc6.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_124f2695176516da3f135c78e53d2015319efbdc6.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_124f2695176516da3f135c78e53d2015319efbdc6.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Why Partners Rise with SAP" src="./media_124f2695176516da3f135c78e53d2015319efbdc6.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="why-partners-rise-with-sap">Why Partners Rise with SAP</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Disruption spurs innovation. For businesses to thrive in a rapidly changing business environment, organizations must continuously adapt by reexamining what value they can provide customers. The <a href="/covid-19">pandemic</a> greatly accelerated this need to transform.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>This presents a unique opportunity for SAP and our partner ecosystem to guide customers through their digital transformations. Together, we help customers remain agile by managing their business processes end-to-end in the cloud. As a result of the combined value we deliver to customers, partners and SAP will generate significant cloud growth and recurring revenue.</p>
  <p>To help partners maximize this opportunity, SAP launched a new Partner Success organization, which will drive more proactive engagement from our partner experience managers. They will work with partners on their business plans and priorities. We continue to collect and act on partner feedback for our <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/rise.html">RISE with SAP</a> offering while focusing on improving partner profitability in migrating customers to the cloud.</p>
  <p>SAP is also introducing a new commercial offer and enhancing existing offerings to help partners drive customer success in the post-pandemic business landscape. Here are some details.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="join-the-sap-global-partner-summit-now">Join the SAP Global Partner Summit now</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://events.sap.com/sap-global-partner-summit/en/home">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="enhancing-partner-flexibility-to-support-cloud-adoption">Enhancing Partner Flexibility to Support Cloud Adoption</h2>
  <p>At the beginning of the third quarter of 2021, SAP plans to launch <strong>SAP PartnerEdge Cloud Choice, flex model</strong>, a new revenue share and go-to-market model that provides partners more flexibility to win cloud customers and rewards partners for driving customer adoption. The flex model splits the customer life cycle into two stages, creating opportunities to better compensate partners for delivering effective sales activities <em>and</em> ongoing customer engagement. We are also improving partner cash flow by paying upfront commissions for sales activities and increasing commission rates on renewals. This new model will be available in both the large enterprise and midmarket.</p>
  <h2 id="identifying-the-right-partner-quickly-and-easily">Identifying the Right Partner, Quickly and Easily</h2>
  <p>By the third quarter of 2021, SAP will roll out a new <strong>Partner Finder</strong> to provide greater exposure for partners. This will feature a simple, intuitive, and visual search function for customers to identify the right partner for a specific business or industry without needing an in-depth knowledge of SAP technology or the ecosystem.</p>
  <p>Customers will enjoy a more seamless experience that includes the possibility for partners to provide direct links to <a href="https://urldefense.com/v3/__https:/store.sap.com/dcp/en/?campaigncode=CRM-YD21-SOC-0STORPZ&#x26;source=ppc-SAPSTOREPS-GL-202121&#x26;gclid=EAIaIQobChMIm_7R9uiP8AIVmLd3Ch0Z_g8nEAAYASAAEgJ85PD_BwE__;!!HhhKMSGjjQV-!v_7qQHXHacqE5C74Cg_Il3rk-hqqQ50oeED2UvGqykCDyEm5VuJcTdmcHmBj_SBaAPdyCQ$">SAP Store</a> and <a href="https://urldefense.com/v3/__https:/www.sap.com/partner/find/qualified-packaged-solutions/finder.html?sort=title_asc__;!!HhhKMSGjjQV-!v_7qQHXHacqE5C74Cg_Il3rk-hqqQ50oeED2UvGqykCDyEm5VuJcTdmcHmBj_SB3dkzyYA$">SAP-qualified partner-packaged solutions</a>. On the main page, customers can also learn more about available SAP solutions and certified consultants and even ask the partners to be contacted, which will be a new source of demand generation for our partners. At the end of May, partners will receive an invitation to access the new partner profile editor to maintain their profile in the new Partner Finder, which they will need to complete to be visible to customers and prospects.</p>
  <h2 id="highlighting-partner-contributions-to-customer-success">Highlighting Partner Contributions to Customer Success</h2>
  <p>We are likewise transforming the annual <strong>SAP Pinnacle Award</strong> program to align to our strategy and priorities for creating customer value in the cloud. We will publicly recognize those partners that have delivered superior customer value in close collaboration with SAP and provide partners with the means to market this achievement accordingly. Customers that want to work with the best of the best in the ecosystem will be able to immediately recognize the partner for unique and outstanding contributions to customer success.</p>
  <h2 id="partner-led-customer-success-through-sap-btp-and-industry-cloud">Partner-Led Customer Success Through SAP BTP and Industry Cloud</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-the-power-of-partnership-with-sap">Learn more about the power of partnership with SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/partner.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP aims to foster a best-in-class ecosystem that delivers outstanding cloud implementations to drive customer outcomes and innovation. To achieve this, SAP is investing significantly to train and educate partner consultants and developers with the most relevant and up-to-date learning content so they can develop solutions on <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">SAP Business Technology Platform</a> (SAP BTP).</p>
  <p>With this additional training, SAP partners will be prepared to develop industry cloud offerings, combining partner-built solutions and innovations with integration services, industry content, accelerators, and industry reference architectures. With SAP BTP as its foundation, SAP’s industry cloud helps deliver lower costs for software innovation and faster time to innovation.</p>
  <p>As more partners developing on SAP technologies, we can help customers improve their integrated end-to-end business processes and run apps and data on a unified platform.</p>
  <p>According to a <a href="https://partneredge.sap.com/en/library/education/solutions/ind/industry_cloud/e_ep_forrester_study.html">study from Forrester Consulting</a> commissioned by SAP, partners can expect to close between 50% and 150% more deals in their first year, when compared to a similar solution, using a process model and integration technology within SAP’s industry cloud, in addition to selling bigger deals, closing deals faster, extending contract durations, and improving margins by leveraging SAP BTP.</p>
  <p>SAP is also committed to helping ensure that affordable training accompanies the release of new cloud updates and solutions. SAP is investing to help partners increase their SAP-certified consultants. In total, we aim to grow to 150,000 trained and certified SAP consultants within the SAP ecosystem by the end of 2021.</p>
  <h2 id="empowering-partner-sales-success-with-new-test-and-demo-opportunities">Empowering Partner Sales Success with New Test and Demo Opportunities</h2>
  <p>Since <a href="/2020/06/software-demonstration-environments-customer-partner-success">June 2020</a>, SAP has provided partners with free access to <a href="/2021/02/sap-lowers-cost-test-demo-environment-partners-enhances-dashboard">SAP Partner Demo Environment, shared option</a>. This integrated, pre-configured software demonstration environment expedites sales conversations. SAP is steadily expanding live demo offerings – with more than 50 live scenarios to date – to help partners position the value of the Intelligent Enterprise vision, including SAP BTP, RISE with SAP, and industry cloud.</p>
  <p>Additionally, the SAP Demo Store site has been expanded and offers partners more than 430 demo scenarios. SAP is also offering partners further price reductions for additional core cloud solutions. Since January 2021, we have offered reduced subscription fees for dedicated test, demo, and development systems of RISE with SAP, SAP Digital Supply Chain solutions, and the the database and data management and HR and people management portfolios. Reduced pricing on other cloud solutions is planned for later this year.</p>
  <h2 id="delivering-new-sap-for-me-dashboards">Delivering New SAP for Me Dashboards</h2>
  <p><a href="https://me.sap.com/">SAP for Me</a> is quickly becoming the single point of access for partners to get key actionable insights and data in a digital format. We extended the scope of <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nlJ3Q09DCxs">SAP for Me</a> and added new dashboards and functionalities for SAP PartnerEdge program members. This includes dynamic cards that sales professionals can use to facilitate end-to-end deal execution and that partner contacts can use to have a partner-level view of SAP certifications and partnership insights.</p>
  <p>Before the end of the year, partners will have access to additional insights, such as customer project information, a partner solutions dashboard, and cloud product adoption and renewals. This will give partners a complete overview of their customers’ information and relationship with SAP.</p>
  <p>I look forward to a gradually improving global demand in the second half of 2021 and am confident that the initiatives and opportunities we are creating for our partners will enhance the experience of both partners and customers and drive success — now and in the future.</p>
  <h2 id="additional-reading">Additional Reading</h2>
  <ul>
    <li><strong><a href="/">SAP Ecosystem and SAP Business Technology Platform: Delivering the Intelligent Enterprise for Customers</a></strong>, by Juergen Mueller, chief technology officer and member of the Executive Board of SAP SE</li>
    <li><strong><a href="/2021/02/unified-technology-platform-partners-enable-customer-success">How Partners Enable Customer Success Through a Unified Technology Platform</a></strong>, by Jagdish Sahasrabudhe, CTO of the Global Partner Organization at SAP</li>
  </ul>
  <p>Learn more on how to partner with SAP at <a href="https://www.sap.com/partner.html">sap.com/partner</a> and <strong><a href="https://events.sap.com/sap-global-partner-summit/en/home">join the 2021 SAP Global Partner Summit</a></strong>. Existing partners can find details on <a href="https://partneredge.sap.com/en/partnership/licenses/shared_demo.html">SAPPartnerEdge.com</a>.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>Follow SAP on Twitter at <a href="https://twitter.com/SAPPartnerEdge">@SAPPartnerEdge</a> and <a href="https://twitter.com/SAPPartners4U">@SAPPartners4U</a>,<br>as well as on <a href="https://www.facebook.com/SAPPartnerEdge">Facebook</a>, <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-partneredge/">LinkedIn</a>, and <a href="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCAb6QuwIS4HCCxYoCEWjBog">YouTube</a></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Karl Fahrbach is global partner officer at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-global-partner-summit</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-partner-demo-environment</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-partneredge</category>
            <category>sap-award/sap-pinnacle-awards</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-store</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Announces 2021 Finalists and Winners of the SAP Pinnacle Award]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/2021-sap-pinnacle-award-finalists-winners</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/2021-sap-pinnacle-award-finalists-winners</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP has announced the 2021 SAP Pinnacle Award finalists and winners. Learn more about award-winning SAP partners and their contributions.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>sap-award/sap-pinnacle-awards</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>