<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/idc-marketscape/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Recognized as a Major Player in the IDC MarketScape Experience-Centric Intelligent Digital Workspaces]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/sap-recognized-idc-marketscape-experience-centric-intelligent-digital-workspaces</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/sap-recognized-idc-marketscape-experience-centric-intelligent-digital-workspaces</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In a new MarketScape, IDC has recognized SAP Build Work Zone as a modern, robust solution for digital workplaces. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1bc71d974e0081b3064b32f0acac989c4add119a3.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1bc71d974e0081b3064b32f0acac989c4add119a3.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1bc71d974e0081b3064b32f0acac989c4add119a3.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Recognized as a Major Player in the IDC MarketScape Experience-Centric Intelligent Digital Workspaces" src="./media_1bc71d974e0081b3064b32f0acac989c4add119a3.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-recognized-as-a-major-player-in-the-idc-marketscape-experience-centric-intelligent-digital-workspaces">SAP Recognized as a Major Player in the IDC MarketScape Experience-Centric Intelligent Digital Workspaces</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Today’s digital workplace is constantly evolving, but the way we work is still siloed and complicated. Employees often waste time switching between applications, searching for information, finding data, and seeking recommendations and insights to get work done. They desire an intelligent work experience to boost engagement and productivity.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/workzone.html">SAP Build Work Zone</a> provides a unified, intelligent work experience for the modern workforce.</p>
  <h2 id="idc-marketscape-experience-centric-intelligent-digital-workspaces-recognition">2024 IDC MarketScape: Experience-Centric Intelligent Digital Workspaces Recognition</h2>
  <p>SAP has been recognized as a Major Player in the IDC MarketScape: Worldwide Experience-Centric Intelligent Digital Workspaces 2024 Vendor Assessment (doc # US49741923, January 2024), based on IDC analysts and customer feedback. We believe this recognition acknowledges SAP’s ongoing dedication in delivering a modern, robust digital workplace solution to optimize user engagement and productivity, and to drive overall business agility.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-an-excerpt-of-the-idc-marketscape-report-now">Read an excerpt of the IDC MarketScape report now</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/workzone.html?pdf-asset=c4053575-a87e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b&#x26;page=1">Get the complementary copy</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>IDC defines an intelligent digital workspace as a well-organized system of tools working together to enhance end users’ overall productivity and experiences. This system integrates intentional design, engineering, and artificial intelligence (AI) to provide a customized and seamless view of tools for user tasks. It ensures secure access to resources from any location or device and enables IT and security professionals with complete oversight.</p>
  <p>As stated within this IDC MarketScape report, “Client organizations we interviewed noted that SAP Build Work Zone reinforced the importance of collaboration and knowledge management.”</p>
  <p>Here are the additional highlights on strengths of SAP Build Work Zone noted in the report:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>A unified digital workspace</strong>: SAP Build Work Zone supports building blocks of content, user interface (UI) integration cards, and home page widgets to embed and display SAP or third-party business data in one workspace. Guided experiences sit on top of workflows to guide the user journey.</li>
    <li><strong>Streamlined user tasks</strong>: SAP Task Center is used within SAP Build Work Zone to act as a unified inbox to provide one place for all approvals and to dos. Global announcements can be tracked for reads and to check length of time spent on content items with native SAP analytics, or with third-party tools such as Google Analytics or Qualtrics. Customers have noted that SAP Build Work Zone provided a friendly UI and access to all functionality on the mobile app.</li>
    <li><strong>Seamless connection to a comprehensive product suite</strong>: SAP Build Work Zone is used to connect the SAP suite of capabilities — including SAP S/4 HANA, SAP Success Factors, and SAP Integrated Business Planning solutions — to handle workflow and collaboration of tasks across multiple IT and business users. SAP Build Work Zone offers pre-built workspace templates with public, private, or external access and an impersonation feature to preview workspaces in-context of specific audience segments.</li>
  </ul>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Evolving the Digital Workplace with SAP Build Work Zone</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="unify-experiences-enterprise-wide">Unify Experiences Enterprise-Wide</h3>
  <p>Business users gain centralized access to SAP and non-SAP business applications, processes, and information, including custom-built apps and extensions, from desktop to mobile using SAP Build Work Zone. The solution offers a personalized, role-based user experience, for example, allowing business users to quickly search for applications or information they need, promptly manage tasks and notifications through the integrated inbox, and stay updated on content, apps, workflows, and processes that are seamlessly integrated across the business landscape without constantly switching around applications or leaving their desktops.</p>
  <h3 id="build-workspaces-simpler-and-faster-with-low-code">Build Workspaces Simpler and Faster with Low-Code</h3>
  <p>Business users are empowered to build and customize business sites visually. They can build branded sites, pages, and workspaces for different purposes and complexity. Our pre-built line-of-business content — including home pages, workspaces, integrations, and guided experiences — dramatically accelerates their time-to-value. For example, HR users can create pages for benefits announcements and design workspaces for learning academies. With the flexibility to design a tailored digital experience, business users can organize their work intuitively by bringing together their favorite business applications and unstructured content side-by-side, within a unified environment.</p>
  <p>UI integration cards is a powerful widget to visualize data from back-end systems, allowing business users to quickly gain business insights into, for example, purchasing trends, account receivable overview, or compliance checklist. In addition, guided experiences streamline complex, difficult processes that span multiple systems, transforming them into simple, fast, and error-free experiences. This empowers business users to self-service their way through cross-application processes such as onboarding, returning to work, or submitting parental leave requests with ease and confidence.</p>
  <p>SAP Build Work Zone is part of <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/low-code.html">SAP Build, a portfolio of low-code solutions</a> that enables the people closest to the business problems to create and augment enterprise applications, automation processes, and design workspaces and business sites visually.</p>
  <h3 id="optimize-team-effectiveness-within-and-beyond-the-enterprise">Optimize Team Effectiveness Within and Beyond the Enterprise</h3>
  <p>SAP Build Work Zone is also designed to amplify team effectiveness across internal employees, external customers, partners, and suppliers. Business users can visually create workspaces to facilitate better team engagement through knowledge sharing, streamlined business processes execution, content management, and implementing best practices. They can also leverage surveys, polls, and interactive Q&#x26;A sessions to gather valuable feedback, improving communication and work synergy.</p>
  <p>Many SAP Build Work Zone customers have created purpose-built business sites to actively engage with their external customers, partners, and suppliers. For example, a supplier business site is created for suppliers to self-service various business operations, including supplier onboarding, accessing policies, managing account payables and invoicing processes, and obtaining product knowledge along with Q&#x26;As. By empowering suppliers to address their requirements and needs, not only enhances their engagement and efficiency but also saves internal teams’ time for more impactful, high-value activities.</p>
  <h3 id="unlock-the-future-of-digital-workplaces">Unlock the Future of Digital Workplaces</h3>
  <p>Like many customers and partners, <a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2023/07/b457bfbe-837e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Heartland Dental and Avvale</a> chose SAP Build Work Zone and SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP) to improve more than 5,000 business assistant’s user experience and productivity across more than 1,700 dental practices within the national dental network. Since its initial rollout in 2023, it has been reported that 33 hours per day have been saved across the initial 200 supported offices.</p>
  <p>Looking ahead, SAP remains dedicated to delivering the best-in-class innovations to our customers to enable their business success, such as injecting business AI capabilities by enabling SAP Joule as the digital assistant for intelligent interactions within SAP Build Work Zone.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Learn More</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <ul>
    <li>Read a complimentary excerpt copy of the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/workzone.html?pdf-asset=c4053575-a87e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b&#x26;page=1">IDC MarketScape Experience-Centric Intelligent Digital Workspaces report</a></li>
    <li>Join the <a href="https://community.sap.com/topics/work-zone">SAP Build Work Zone community</a></li>
  </ul>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Sid Misra is vice president for Product Marketing and Solution Management at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><strong>About IDC MarketScape Experience-Centric Intelligent Digital Workspaces</strong><br>This IDC research explores the intelligent digital workspace environment, offering further insights on the pace of adoption, the potential success of technology, and the level of market excitement. This aims to empower IT and business decision-makers to evaluate investments based on their own judgments.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc-marketscape</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-build</category>
            <category>product/sap-build-work-zone</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Cares About Your Company’s Spend]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/sap-cares-about-your-companys-spend</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/sap-cares-about-your-companys-spend</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP spend management and business network solutions continue evolving and improving with time – and 2024 will be no different.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>product/sap-ariba-category-management</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc-marketscape</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-spend</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-concur</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fieldglass</category>
            <category>news-tag/trustradius</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Named a Leader in IDC MarketScape: Worldwide Multi-Enterprise Supply Chain Commerce Network Report]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/sap-leader-idc-worldwide-multi-enterprise-supply-chain-commerce-network</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/sap-leader-idc-worldwide-multi-enterprise-supply-chain-commerce-network</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP has been recognized as a Leader in the IDC MarketScape: Worldwide Multi-Enterprise Supply Chain Commerce Network 2023 Vendor Assessment.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_135f4226168fd5f6686d7e1a231112cde982b97a7.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_135f4226168fd5f6686d7e1a231112cde982b97a7.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_135f4226168fd5f6686d7e1a231112cde982b97a7.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Named a Leader in IDC MarketScape: Worldwide Multi-Enterprise Supply Chain Commerce Network Report" src="./media_135f4226168fd5f6686d7e1a231112cde982b97a7.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-named-a-leader-in-idc-marketscape-worldwide-multi-enterprise-supply-chain-commerce-network-report">SAP Named a Leader in IDC MarketScape: Worldwide Multi-Enterprise Supply Chain Commerce Network Report</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>SAP continues to act on our vision of enabling companies to create transparent, resilient, and sustainable supply chains across a massive amount of trading partners. We’re being recognized as a Leader in the <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2023/12/02200664-9f7e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">IDC MarketScape: Worldwide Multi-Enterprise Supply Chain Commerce Network 2023 Vendor Assessment</a>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="why-sap-is-a-leader">Why SAP Is a Leader</h2>
  <p>In an increasingly digitalized world, it is imperative that companies stay connected via a business network. I believe SAP was selected as a Leader because <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-network.html?campaigncode=CRM-Y123-ISM-1980086&#x26;source=blog-glo-SAPLeaderinIDCMarketScape">SAP Business Network</a> – our entry into the Multi-Enterprise Supply Chain Commerce Network space – can successfully drive buyer-supplier collaboration across procurement, supply chain, logistics, and asset management by providing a digital platform for trading partners to collaborate externally and exchange data just as, if not more, efficiently as their own internal processes.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_187994eca96ea26313df6a84f0d5d56cfe3bbffac.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_187994eca96ea26313df6a84f0d5d56cfe3bbffac.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_187994eca96ea26313df6a84f0d5d56cfe3bbffac.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_187994eca96ea26313df6a84f0d5d56cfe3bbffac.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="620" height="615">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>Source: “IDC MarketScape: Worldwide Multi-Enterprise Supply Chain Commerce Network 2023 Vendor Assessment,” by Simon Ellis, December 2023, IDC #US49948423.* Click to enlarge.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The IDC MarketScape report notes these competitive strengths of SAP Business Network:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Depth and breadth</strong> of product features and functionalities, as well as a future road map covering all major B2B collaboration categories (indirect, direct material, MRO logistics, financial, services, and sustainability) and scenarios in an end user, persona-based manner.</li>
    <li><strong>Integration and extensibility capabilities</strong> include integration between SAP ERP, SAP procurement modules, other applications like ERP, SCAM, and customer applications, and technologies such as machine learning, AI, and blockchain through SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP).</li>
    <li><strong>Global adoption and breadth of collaboration</strong> makes SAP among the industry’s largest, highly adopted B2B collaboration platforms enabling trading partners to collaborate in real time. Ongoing efforts to harmonize commerce, asset intelligence, and logistics continue to enhance the power of the connected economy.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>The IDC MarketScape report notes, “Manufacturers and retailers looking for a vendor of both a multi-enterprise network and supply chain procurement application should consider SAP,” citing the “breadth and depth of [its] business network capabilities, strategic road map vision, and unmatched integration with core SAP and non-SAP supply chain and procurement applications,” making SAP a strong choice.</p>
  <h2 id="charting-the-evolution-of-sap-business-network">Charting the Evolution of SAP Business Network</h2>
  <p>I’m so pleased that as a pioneer in business networks, we continue to be recognized for our commitment to executing our vision. As we’ve continued to evolve our road map, I’m reflecting on how far we’ve come and paved the way for the future of intelligent business networks. From the founding of Ariba Supplier Network in 1996 to what we’ve become today, SAP Business Network touches US$4.9 trillion in commerce annually across many business processes and industries and has over 2 million active users on the network.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-business-network-powers-transparency-resiliency-and-sustainability">SAP Business Network powers transparency, resiliency, and sustainability</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-network.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Recent years have shown us that intelligent, digital business networks are essential to supporting an agile supply chain. SAP Business Network is a comprehensive platform that helps connect people, processes, and systems across multiple enterprises, ultimately creating transparent, resilient, and sustainable supply chains that can span the globe and be tailored to each line of business, helping to drive partner collaboration beyond a company’s own four walls and spanning the entire value chain.</p>
  <p>I’m proud to say that SAP Business Network can provide best-in-class supply chain collaboration, helping companies adhere to legal mandates, scale with confidence, and automate repetitive tasks, leaving more time for strategic decision-making informed by patterns gleaned from vast amounts of data. Our vision – what so many talented people at SAP are working towards every day – is to create the world’s best and largest B2B marketplace to help our customers meet their business goals.</p>
  <h2 id="recent-advancements-continue-to-revolutionize-b2b-collaboration">Recent Advancements Continue to Revolutionize B2B Collaboration</h2>
  <p>If you know SAP, you know about our commitment to continuous innovation. In 2023, we announced many exciting innovations around SAP Business Network, including:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Build on artificial intelligence in SAP Business Network.</strong> My colleague Muhammad Alam <a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2023/11/40a14527-977e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html?campaigncode=CRM-Y123-ISM-1980086&#x26;source=blog-glo-SAPLeaderinIDCMarketScape">announced our plans</a> to further integrate generative AI in spend management at SAP Spend Connect Live. Customers can look forward to enriched supplier responses to SAP Business Network Discovery postings, helping to facilitate more transparent communication between buyers and suppliers. Generative AI improvements can give suppliers the ability to generate clear, concise catalog descriptions, as well as summarize common errors for users so buyers can find exactly what they’re looking for.</li>
    <li><strong>Tackle industry-specific challenges with SAP Business Network for Industry.</strong> We’ve combined our more than 50 years of industry knowledge with the power of business networks to help customers address industry-specific supply chain challenges. Take a look at <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-network/industries.html?campaigncode=CRM-Y123-ISM-1980086&#x26;source=blog-glo-SAPLeaderinIDCMarketScape">how companies across industries use SAP Business Network</a> to help predict and respond to disruptions, comply with industry regulations, and meet sustainability goals.</li>
    <li><strong>Learn more with trading partner insights.</strong> Account managers struggle with obtaining comparative measures to assess the performance of trading partners. New KPIs and benchmarks, presented in a streamlined dashboard, can allow suppliers to evaluate customer transaction performance of orders, invoices, and payments with automatically generated KPIs and SAP Business Network community benchmarks. These insights can support collaborative dialogues with customers to help reduce transaction costs and mitigate business risk. <a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2023/05/44712fba-737e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html?campaigncode=CRM-Y123-ISM-1980086&#x26;source=blog-glo-SAPLeaderinIDCMarketScape">Watch the demo to learn more</a>.</li>
    <li><strong>Draw insights from data with component planning collaboration.</strong> With component planning collaboration, buyers and suppliers can view the forecast planning data for a finished good together with its components. Armed with this visibility, buyers and suppliers can respond to material shortages and adjust production accordingly, making supply more predictable. <a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2023/05/585c0fc7-737e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html?campaigncode=CRM-Y123-ISM-1980086&#x26;source=blog-glo-SAPLeaderinIDCMarketScape">Learn more in this demo</a>.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>Stay tuned for more exciting innovations this year. Stay up-to-date about recent and upcoming innovations and explore road maps <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-network/innovations.html?campaigncode=CRM-Y123-ISM-1980086&#x26;source=blog-glo-SAPLeaderinIDCMarketScape">here</a>.</p>
  <h2 id="transforming-the-future-of-business-networks">Transforming the Future of Business Networks</h2>
  <p>I am proud that SAP is being recognized as a leader in delivering solutions that connect people, processes, and systems, enabling trading partners to collaborate effectively. I can’t wait to see our road map continue to come to life as we collaborate with our customers to develop innovations that help them achieve their business objectives by automating tasks, scaling efficiently, and operating sustainably.</p>
  <p>To learn more, visit <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-network.html?campaigncode=CRM-Y123-ISM-1980086&#x26;source=blog-glo-SAPLeaderinIDCMarketScape">the SAP Business Network product page</a> and read the full IDC MarketScape report <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2023/12/02200664-9f7e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">here</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>Tony Harris is senior vice president and chief marketing and solutions officer for SAP Business Network.</p>
        <p>*IDC MarketScape vendor analysis model is designed to provide an overview of the competitive fitness of ICT suppliers in a given market. The research methodology utilizes a rigorous scoring methodology based on both qualitative and quantitative criteria that results in a single graphical illustration of each vendor’s position within a given market. The Capabilities score measures vendor product, go-to-market and business execution in the short-term. The Strategy score measures alignment of vendor strategies with customer requirements in a 3-5-year timeframe. Vendor market share is represented by the size of the circles. Vendor year-over-year growth rate relative to the given market is indicated by a plus, neutral or minus next to the vendor name.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc-marketscape</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network-for-industry</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[IDC MarketScape Positions SAP as a Leader in Cloud-Enabled Sourcing Applications]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/idc-marketscape-sap-a-leader-cloud-enabled-sourcing-applications</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/idc-marketscape-sap-a-leader-cloud-enabled-sourcing-applications</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is once again a Leader in the IDC MarketScape: Worldwide SaaS and Cloud-Enabled Sourcing Applications 2023 Vendor Assessment.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_133a48d9e5374e4e14271c30ea75c355e2eada374.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_133a48d9e5374e4e14271c30ea75c355e2eada374.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_133a48d9e5374e4e14271c30ea75c355e2eada374.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="IDC MarketScape Positions SAP as a Leader in Cloud-Enabled Sourcing Applications" src="./media_133a48d9e5374e4e14271c30ea75c355e2eada374.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="idc-marketscape-positions-sap-as-a-leader-in-cloud-enabled-sourcing-applications">IDC MarketScape Positions SAP as a Leader in Cloud-Enabled Sourcing Applications</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>SAP’s tireless efforts to build solutions that address today’s toughest challenges and deliver real business value is paying big dividends for our customers. Now, we have more recognition to prove it.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="optimize-cost-manage-risk-and-ensure-negotiated-savings-are-realized-with-strategic-sourcing-solutions">Optimize cost, manage risk, and ensure negotiated savings are realized with strategic sourcing solutions</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/spend-management/solutions.html#active_tab_item_1602592051931">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Based on an IDC analysis and customer feedback, SAP has been positioned in the Leaders Category of the <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2023/11/6a569cf4-987e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">IDC MarketScape: Worldwide SaaS and Cloud-Enabled Sourcing Applications 2023 Vendor Assessment</a>.*</p>
  <p>For those of us at SAP who have been working to deliver <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/spend-management/solutions.html#active_tab_item_1602592051931">sourcing applications</a> that help organizations work more strategically and efficiently, this is another milestone as we continue to advance up the leader board. More significantly, it is gratifying to know that this positioning is not just based on the IDC MarketScape’s detailed examination of our solutions. It’s also based on the word of our customers.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <picture>
          <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d697d7aa950dc39987b1ea9b4b23aceb728196db.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
          <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d697d7aa950dc39987b1ea9b4b23aceb728196db.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
          <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1d697d7aa950dc39987b1ea9b4b23aceb728196db.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
          <img loading="lazy" alt="IDC MarketScape Worldwide SaaS and Cloud-Enabled Sourcing Applications, 2023" src="./media_1d697d7aa950dc39987b1ea9b4b23aceb728196db.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="1013">
        </picture>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>IDC MarketScape vendor analysis model is designed to provide an overview of the competitive fitness of ICT suppliers in a given market. The research methodology utilizes a rigorous scoring methodology based on both qualitative and quantitative criteria that results in a single graphical illustration of each vendor’s position within a given market. The Capabilities score measures vendor product, go-to-market and business execution in the short-term. The Strategy score measures alignment of vendor strategies with customer requirements in a 3-5-year timeframe. Vendor market share is represented by the size of the icons.<br><em>Source:</em> <em><a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2023/11/6a569cf4-987e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">IDC MarketScape: Worldwide SaaS and Cloud-Enabled Sourcing Applications 2023 Vendor Assessment</a>, IDC #US51215923e, November 2023</em></p>
  <p>According to the IDC MarketScape’s assessment report, “SAP Ariba is a mature, established, and trusted brand…users expressed that the integration with SAP ERP and SCM products is a compelling feature.”</p>
  <p>The report highlights these SAP strengths:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Integrated sourcing functionality leverages capabilities across spend analytics, supplier identification, SAP Business Network, analytics/reporting dashboards, and contract management to serve as a “force multiplier” and provides a view to total cost impact of sourcing decisions.</li>
    <li>Milestone/project view extends functionality beyond simple sourcing events and provides all impacted stakeholders with the ability to follow progress, achieve milestones, assess the sourcing strategy, and provide input.</li>
    <li>Complex sourcing capabilities are strong, providing the ability to plan and execute large and compliant global sourcing events that come with a myriad of deliverables and complex pricing. Client references noted and appreciated the ability to scale and support sourcing events often involving many thousands of line items.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>The IDC MarketScape report says, “Consider SAP when you need a trusted, enterprise-grade sourcing application that can be utilized for large, complex, and global sourcing activities while also leveraging the capabilities of the full SAP Ariba solutions.”</p>
  <h2 id="continuing-our-commitment-to-customer-focused-innovation">Continuing Our Commitment to Customer-Focused Innovation</h2>
  <p>I believe one of the reasons SAP continues to advance its leadership position is our commitment to steady innovation. However, this is not just innovation for innovation’s sake. We carefully study the day-to-day role that sourcing and procurement professionals play today and, importantly, how that role is evolving. With these insights, we build solutions that are designed to help sourcing and procurement teams play an increasingly valuable role within their organizations.</p>
  <p>In just the past year, we have introduced a slew of innovations:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/spend-management/category-management-software.html">SAP Ariba Category Management</a></strong> empowers category managers to use data insights strategically to help identify trends, develop and implement strategies, and evaluate success relative to tangible business metrics. Just a few weeks ago at SAP Spend Connect, we announced enhancements to SAP Ariba Category Management with the power of generative AI to help procurement professionals build comprehensive and effective category strategies faster. We also highlighted <a href="/2023/09/joule-new-generative-ai-assistant">Joule</a>, which will be embedded across the SAP portfolio and available in SAP Spend Management solutions in 2024. Integration with large language models through SAP Business AI empowers procurement professionals to jump-start category strategy development and planning. Generative AI enables us to enhance our market analysis tool, offering valuable, visual insights into supply and demand, risk, opportunity, and top suppliers. <a href="https://sapvideoa35699dc5.hana.ondemand.com/?entry_id=1_caxgkqyw">Watch a demo here</a>.</li>
    <li>The next evolution of the <strong>guided buying capability</strong> in SAP Ariba solutions provides a personalized buying experience for today’s professional and casual buyers. It leverages AI to offer suggestions for specific work roles, and intelligent recommendations to help weigh the sustainability and environmental impact of a purchase. Much of this functionality is available today with more to come in future releases. <a href="https://sapvideoa35699dc5.hana.ondemand.com/?entry_id=1_ut29oylb">Watch a demo here</a>.</li>
    <li><strong>SAP Spend Control Tower</strong> delivers comprehensive spend analysis capabilities. To make it easier for procurement professionals to make timely, informed decisions, new dashboards in SAP Ariba Sourcing and SAP Ariba Buying embed near real-time insights where they are most useful — within key process workflows. These capabilities are available today and built on a new architecture that helps create the foundation for future innovation. Beginning in the first quarter of 2024, <a href="https://sapvideoa35699dc5.hana.ondemand.com/?entry_id=1_xqw6unwv">SAP Spend Control Tower</a> can help uncover cost-saving opportunities with advanced AI features and the ability to see across all spend — in cloud ERP, SAP Ariba, SAP Fieldglass, and SAP Concur solutions.</li>
    <li>With <strong>risk-aware procurement</strong> with AI-infused risk assessment in source-to-settle solutions, SAP has embedded AI-powered supplier risk assessment capabilities into its source-to-settle solutions to help business users make smarter decisions faster. This can make it possible to assess risk profiles within the sourcing, contracting, and buying solutions as an integral part of these processes to determine third-party risk. Supplier risk assessment capabilities are available today in SAP Ariba Sourcing, SAP Ariba Contracts, and SAP Ariba Buying.</li>
    <li>Supporting the <strong>future of supplier management</strong>, at SAP Spend Connect Live we provided a sneak preview of a feature we refer to as “the new supplier 360,” which can deliver instant access to risk data, AI-powered sustainability information, and operational evaluation to help track metrics like price variance. <a href="https://sapvideoa35699dc5.hana.ondemand.com/?entry_id=1_ai4bz2p8">Watch a demo here</a>.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>Want to read more about these innovations? <a href="/2023/10/procurement-news-sap-spend-connect-live">Check out our announcement from SAP Spend Connect Live 2023</a> that provides additional detail.</p>
  <h2 id="why-sap-is-a-leader">Why SAP is a Leader</h2>
  <p>With our steady stream of innovations designed to help businesses solve their biggest sourcing challenges, I am not surprised that SAP is once again a Leader in the <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2023/11/6a569cf4-987e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">IDC MarketScape: Worldwide SaaS and Cloud-Enabled Sourcing Applications 2023 Vendor Assessment</a>. Of course, we don’t intend to stop here.</p>
  <p>Looking ahead, we know that sourcing professionals are looking for an intuitive user experience that allows them to focus on strategic, value-added tasks. And as we have seen recently, they are eager to use generative AI, analytics, and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/spend-management/innovations.html#ai">practical AI use cases</a> to support them.</p>
  <p>Of course, AI is only as effective as the quality and availability of data. A huge amount of data and transactions run through SAP’s <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/spend-management/solutions.html">systems</a> and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-network.html">business network</a>. This makes us uniquely qualified to help organizations — large and small — access the data they need, interpret it, and take decisive action.</p>
  <p>As we have already shown, SAP is in the best position to deliver the broad-based use cases that businesses will need to stay competitive as conditions evolve.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Baber Farooq is senior vice president and head of Market Strategy for SAP Procurement Solutions.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-sap-news-on-linkedin-for-the-latest-stories">Connect with SAP News on LinkedIn for the latest stories</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news/">Follow now</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><em>*“IDC MarketScape: Worldwide SaaS and Cloud-Enabled Sourcing Applications 2023 Vendor Assessment” November 2023, IDC #US51215923e</em></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc-marketscape</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Why SAP Is a Leader in the IDC MarketScape for Enterprise Treasury and Risk Management Applications]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/sap-leader-idc-marketscape-treasury-risk-management</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/sap-leader-idc-marketscape-treasury-risk-management</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP has been recognized in the 2023 IDC MarketScape: Worldwide SaaS and Cloud-Enabled Enterprise Treasury and Risk Management Applications.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/financial-management</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc-marketscape</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-treasury-and-risk-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Winning Combination: SAP Customers and Our Spend Management Solutions]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/winning-combination-sap-customers-spend-management</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/winning-combination-sap-customers-spend-management</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Our commitment to delivering a complete set of SAP spend management solutions has only grown, as shown by the recognitions we've received.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc-marketscape</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-spend</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-concur</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fieldglass</category>
            <category>topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/trustradius</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP a Leader in Procurement Applications]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/sap-leader-in-procurement-applications</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/sap-leader-in-procurement-applications</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP has been named a Leader in the IDC MarketScape: Worldwide SaaS and Cloud-Enabled Procurement Applications 2023 Vendor Assessment.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc-marketscape</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>topic/spend-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Named a Leader in IDC MarketScapes for Cloud-Enabled Manufacturing and Operational ERP Applications]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/sap-named-leader-idc-marketscapes-cloud-manufacturing-operational-erp</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/sap-named-leader-idc-marketscapes-cloud-manufacturing-operational-erp</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[IDC has positioned SAP as a Leader within the 2022 IDC MarketScape for worldwide SaaS and cloud-enabled operational ERP applications.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/covid-19</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc-marketscape</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Positioned as a Leader in U.S. and European IT Training by IDC MarketScape]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/03/sap-positioned-leader-it-training-idc-marketscape</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/03/sap-positioned-leader-it-training-idc-marketscape</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is positioned as a Leader for IT Training in the U.S. and Europe by IDC MarketScape. Learn more about the reports and SAP Learning.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc-marketscape</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>