<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/product/sap-sustainability-footprint-management/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Putting Sustainability at the Heart of ERP]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sustainability-erp-sap-business-ai-sap-sapphire</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sustainability-erp-sap-business-ai-sap-sapphire</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP’s ERP-centric, cloud-based, AI-enabled approach is redefining how companies manage sustainability. Learn how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_19f549b1c60b71d253752564f5659b7cd5b69ae91.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_19f549b1c60b71d253752564f5659b7cd5b69ae91.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_19f549b1c60b71d253752564f5659b7cd5b69ae91.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Putting Sustainability at the Heart of ERP" src="./media_19f549b1c60b71d253752564f5659b7cd5b69ae91.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="putting-sustainability-at-the-heart-of-erp">Putting Sustainability at the Heart of ERP</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Sustainability has evolved from a boardroom buzzword to a critical driver of business success and strategic differentiation. To thrive, companies are going to need to understand how to operate in a modern, low-carbon, circular economy. SAP solutions will support them by embedding sustainability into every aspect of their operations.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-sapphire-taking-business-to-the-next-level-in-the-era-of-ai">SAP Sapphire: Taking Business to the Next Level in the Era of AI</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/events/sapphire/news-guide.html">Read the news guide</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>At our customer flagship event, <a href="/topics/sap-sapphire">SAP Sapphire</a>, we’re discussing how we support customers with their biggest challenges, looking at future trends, and unveiling the latest product innovations.</p>
  <p>This makes the event the perfect opportunity to highlight how we are redefining the way companies manage sustainability through our ERP-centric, cloud-based, AI-enabled approach.</p>
  <h2 id="erp-centric">ERP-Centric</h2>
  <p>For true business model transformation, sustainability needs to be at the core of how companies operate. At SAP, we integrate sustainability data into cloud ERP business processes, which helps companies connect financial and non-financial information and thus treat carbon like money. This makes all decisions financially <em>and</em> environmentally sound while enabling customers to record real impacts and report audit-ready environmental, social, and governance (ESG) metrics seamlessly.</p>
  <h2 id="cloud-based">Cloud-Based</h2>
  <p>Instant access to fast-evolving innovations is only possible through the cloud. Our modern cloud-based solutions ensure that businesses can quickly adopt new functionality and stay ahead in a rapidly changing environment.</p>
  <h2 id="ai-enabled">AI-Enabled</h2>
  <p>Business AI is revolutionizing the way we approach sustainability. At SAP, AI takes complex sustainability tasks reliant on sustainability data and ERP data and makes them automated and auditable. It enables companies to improve operational efficiency, foster greater transparency around supply chain emissions, design and plan more effectively, and automate time-consuming tasks. SAP Business AI is built on the data and processes that run the business world, including sustainability related information from both inside and outside the company’s walls, making our solutions smarter, faster, and more effective.</p>
  <p>With SAP Business AI, we support our customers’ efforts to optimize for sustainable impact. This year at SAP Sapphire, we are thrilled to announce two new AI-driven sustainability use cases:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Emission Factor Mapping with AI:</strong> Available in SAP Sustainability Footprint Management, this feature enhances the accuracy and speed of carbon footprint calculations through automated, intelligent suggestions. By reducing the manual effort involved in mapping emission factors, businesses can achieve more precise measurements and make informed decisions faster.</li>
    <li><strong>ESG Report Generation with AI:</strong> This capability allows for the automatic generation of ESG reports based on the data within SAP Sustainability Control Tower. This not only streamlines the reporting process but also helps ensure that the data is reliable and actionable, providing a clear picture of a company’s sustainability performance.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>Our comprehensive approach to carbon management is becoming a reality as we introduce new sustainability tracking, monitoring, and reporting features within the SAP cloud ERP portfolio as well as a new solution that will help customers manage sustainability commitments and comply with global regulations.</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Advanced Carbon Calculator Engine:</strong> This powerful tool featured in SAP Sustainability Control Tower and SAP Sustainability Footprint Management integrates ERP data from SAP S/4HANA Cloud and other sources and embeds results back into business processes for informed decision-making. As such, it allows customers to meet Greenhouse Gas Protocol reporting standards, offering advanced, granular calculations of both product and corporate carbon footprints.</li>
    <li><strong>SAP Green Ledger</strong> will be released at the end of 2024. The solution will help customers connect their emissions data and financial data, allowing customers to easily understand the correlation between emissions and finances, model sustainable business scenarios, and then act with decisions that are both financially and environmentally sound.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>At SAP, we believe that the future of business is inextricably linked to sustainability. This is why sustainability is a key pillar of our growth strategy. Businesses must recognize that sustainable practices are not just ethical choices, but strategic financial decisions that drive innovation, reduce costs, and mitigate risks.</p>
  <p>Moreover, sustainable transformation opens up significant economic opportunities. By transforming their operations around sustainability, businesses can create a modern, low-carbon, circular economy that benefits both the environment and their bottom line, enhancing overall resilience.</p>
  <p>This transformation aligns business success with global sustainability goals, paving the way for a more sustainable, valuable, and prosperous future.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Sophia Mendelsohn is chief sustainability and commercial officer at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-news-and-coverage-from-sap-sapphire-in-2024">Get the latest news and coverage from SAP Sapphire in 2024</h3>
        <p><em><a href="/topics/sap-sapphire">Read more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-footprint-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Infuses Business AI Throughout Its Enterprise Cloud Portfolio and Partners with Cutting-Edge AI Leaders to Bring Out Customers’ Best]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-sapphire-news-business-ai-enterprise-cloud-portfolio-cutting-edge-partnerships</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-sapphire-news-business-ai-enterprise-cloud-portfolio-cutting-edge-partnerships</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New SAP Business AI innovations and collaborations with partners are igniting ingenuity. Read the news from SAP Sapphire Orlando in 2024.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18ff27978e1178b1dce994986e74f4cc1f6087f26.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18ff27978e1178b1dce994986e74f4cc1f6087f26.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_18ff27978e1178b1dce994986e74f4cc1f6087f26.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Infuses Business AI Throughout Its Enterprise Cloud Portfolio and Partners with Cutting-Edge AI Leaders to Bring Out Customers’ Best" src="./media_18ff27978e1178b1dce994986e74f4cc1f6087f26.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-infuses-business-ai-throughout-its-enterprise-cloud-portfolio-and-partners-with-cutting-edge-ai-leaders-to-bring-out-customers-best">SAP Infuses Business AI Throughout Its Enterprise Cloud Portfolio and Partners with Cutting-Edge AI Leaders to Bring Out Customers’ Best</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>SAP Business AI Innovations and Collaborations with Partners including Google Cloud, Meta, Microsoft, Mistral AI and NVIDIA Ignite Ingenuity</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <table>
          <thead>
            <tr>
              <th>Text Large</th>
            </tr>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td><strong><em>ORLANDO</em></strong> — At its annual SAP Sapphire conference, SAP unveiled generative AI innovations and partnerships that showcase how the company is taking business to the next level in the era of AI.</td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="taking-business-to-the-next-level-in-the-era-of-ai">Taking Business to the Next Level in the Era of AI</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/events/sapphire/news-guide.html">Read the news guide</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>By infusing Business AI across an enterprise cloud portfolio that powers the world’s most mission-critical processes and partnering with companies pushing the edge of what’s possible with AI, SAP is igniting a new wave of insight and ingenuity in global business.</p>
  <p>“The Business AI innovations we’re announcing at SAP Sapphire in 2024 will redefine the way businesses run,” says Christian Klein, CEO and member of the Executive Board of SAP SE. “Today’s AI announcements and partnerships build on our commitment to deliver revolutionary technology that drives real-world results, helping customers unleash the agility and ingenuity they need to succeed in today’s fast-moving business landscape.”</p>
  <h2 id="ai-that-means-business">AI That Means Business</h2>
  <p>As SAP embeds Business AI across its enterprise solutions, it puts rich insights at users’ fingertips, empowering them to deliver better outcomes and elevate the creative problem-solving humans do best. Examples include AI-generated reports in SAP SuccessFactors solutions that give people managers responsibly sourced insights for compensation-related discussions as well as forecasting capabilities in SAP Sales Cloud solutions that predict combinations of salespeople and products most likely to drive sales. Meanwhile, the SAP Business Technology Platform is adding large language models from Amazon Web Services, Meta and Mistral AI to its generative AI hub. This capability in the SAP AI Core infrastructure makes it easier to build generative AI use cases for SAP applications.</p>
  <p>SAP’s generative AI copilot Joule, which quickly sorts and contextualizes data from multiple systems to advance automation and improve decision-making, is expanding throughout the company’s solution portfolio. Joule launched in <a href="/2023/09/joule-new-generative-ai-assistant">SAP SuccessFactors solutions last fall</a> and is now embedded into SAP S/4HANA Cloud solutions and others including SAP Build and SAP Integration Suite. Further expansion by year-end will include SAP Ariba and SAP Analytics Cloud solutions. At Sapphire, SAP also announced <a href="/">plans to further broaden Joule’s scope</a> by integrating it with Microsoft Copilot to surface even richer insights. This deep, bi-directional integration gives users a unified experience built right into the flow of work, enabling seamless access to information from interactions with business applications in SAP and Microsoft 365.</p>
  <p>Reflecting Business AI’s increasing importance, SAP is redoubling its commitment to the principles of relevant, reliable, and responsible AI it pioneered. At Sapphire, SAP is adopting the 10 guiding principles of the UNESCO Recommendation on the Ethics of Artificial Intelligence, which aim to ensure that AI technologies are developed and used in ways that respect human rights, promote fairness and contribute to sustainable development.</p>
  <h2 id="partnerships-that-scale-innovation">Partnerships That Scale Innovation</h2>
  <p>SAP is partnering with best-in-class technology leaders to push the limits of what generative AI can do at an enterprise level. In addition to our expanded collaborations with <a href="/2024/05/aws-sap-generative-ai-new-innovation">AWS</a> and Microsoft, partnerships with Google Cloud, Meta, Mistral AI and NVIDIA ensure SAP can harness the power of AI-ready technology to innovate at speed and deliver richer real-world results.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Google Cloud</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP and Google Cloud are expanding their partnership, using Business AI to help enterprises better predict and mitigate supply-chain risks to minimize disruptions and maintain optimal inventory levels. The companies will integrate Joule and the SAP Integrated Business Planning for Supply Chain solution with Google Cloud’s Gemini models AI assistant and Google Cloud Cortex Framework’s data foundation.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Meta</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP will leverage Meta Llama 3 to generate scripts that render highly customized analytics applications in SAP Analytics Cloud. Meta’s next-generation AI model excels at language nuances and contextual understanding, making it an ideal candidate for translating enterprise business requirements into tangible outcomes.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Mistral AI</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP will also add <a href="/">new large language models from Mistral AI</a>, a global company headquartered in Paris specializing in generative AI, to the generative AI hub capability in SAP AI Core.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>NVIDIA</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP and NVIDIA Corporation advance a <a href="https://blogs.nvidia.com/blog/sap-sapphire-ai-omniverse/">cross-product partnership</a> to embed cutting-edge technologies into enterprise-ready business applications:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>As SAP trains Joule to serve as an AI assistant for the RISE with SAP solution implementations, NVIDIA’s state-of-the-art AI models sift through SAP consulting assets to provide relevant and precise answers to implementation-related questions;</li>
    <li>As SAP embeds Joule in the ABAP Cloud model to generate ABAP code for SAP developers, NVIDIA’s accelerated infrastructure will run, scale, and manage SAP’s generative AI model for ABAP code generation;</li>
    <li>As SAP infuses generative AI into the SAP Intelligent Product Recommendation solution, NVIDIA Omniverse Cloud APIs enable the simulation of complex manufacturing products and configurations as industrial digital twins.</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="cloud-technology-that-drives-agility-and-sustainability">Cloud Technology That Drives Agility and Sustainability</h2>
  <p>Business success in the era of AI means being in the cloud. SAP is making the move easier than ever with initiatives that help customers find partners with the expertise needed for complex SAP S/4HANA Cloud transformations. Further cloud innovations at SAP Sapphire include features that help the world’s organizations measure, manage and execute their sustainability strategies. SAP Sustainability Control Tower and SAP Sustainability Footprint Management solutions now track carbon footprints at scale and help businesses meet regulatory standards.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><a href="https://www.sap.com/events/sapphire/news-guide.html">Learn more in the 2024 SAP Sapphire News Guide</a>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Visit the <a href="/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-news-and-coverage-from-sap-sapphire-in-2024">Get the latest news and coverage from SAP Sapphire in 2024</h3>
        <p><em><a href="/topics/sap-sapphire">Read more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>About SAP</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As a global leader in enterprise applications and business AI, SAP (NYSE:SAP) stands at the nexus of business and technology. For over 50 years, organizations have trusted SAP to bring out their best by uniting business-critical operations spanning finance, procurement, HR, supply chain, and customer experience. For more information, visit <a href="http://www.sap.com">www.sap.com</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Note to editors:</strong><br>To preview and download broadcast-standard stock footage and press photos digitally, please visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/photos">www.sap.com/photos</a>. On this platform, you can find high resolution material for your media channels.</p>
  <p><strong>For customers interested in learning more about SAP products:</strong><br>Global Customer Center: +49 180 534-34-24<br>United States Only: 1 (800) 872-1SAP (1-800-872-1727)</p>
  <p><strong>For more information, press only:</strong><br>Joellen Perry, +1 (650) 445-6780, <a href="mailto:joellen.perry@sap.com">joellen.perry@sap.com</a> PT<br>Marcus Winkler, +49 6227-767497, <a href="mailto:marcus.winkler@sap.com">marcus.winkler@sap.com</a> CET<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>This document contains forward-looking statements, which are predictions, projections, or other statements about future events. These statements are based on current expectations, forecasts, and assumptions that are subject to risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results and outcomes to materially differ. Additional information regarding these risks and uncertainties may be found in our filings with the Securities and Exchange Commission, including but not limited to the risk factors section of SAP’s 2023 Annual Report on Form 20-F.<br>© 2024 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.<br>Please consider our <a href="https://www.sap.com/corporate/en/legal/privacy.html">privacy policy</a>. If you receive this press release in your e-mail and you wish to unsubscribe to our mailing list please contact <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a> and write Unsubscribe in the subject line.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/abap-cloud</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-sales-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-footprint-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[CP Foods Selects SAP Solutions for Cloud Sustainability]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/cp-foods-selects-sap-solutions-for-cloud-sustainability</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/cp-foods-selects-sap-solutions-for-cloud-sustainability</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[CP Foods has selected SAP software to future-proof its business and use data to make more sustainable decisions. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_183175263685a353d3b61ffbc18dc57a24b395640.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_183175263685a353d3b61ffbc18dc57a24b395640.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_183175263685a353d3b61ffbc18dc57a24b395640.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="CP Foods Selects SAP Solutions for Cloud Sustainability" src="./media_183175263685a353d3b61ffbc18dc57a24b395640.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="cp-foods-selects-sap-solutions-for-cloud-sustainability">CP Foods Selects SAP Solutions for Cloud Sustainability</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF and BANGKOK</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced Charoen Pokphand Foods Public Company Limited (“CP Foods”) has selected multiple SAP solutions to drive further growth and competitive advantage and to ensure the sustainability of its products for the future.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="record-report-and-act-on-your-sustainability-goals-with-sap-software">Record, report and act on your sustainability goals with SAP software</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/sustainability/solutions.html">Learn how</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Catering to more than 4 billion people globally, CP Foods is embarking on its next stage of digital transformation with the RISE with SAP, SAP Sustainability Footprint Management, and SAP Sustainability Control Tower solutions. In addition, the SAP EHS Management, environment management application will be implemented to future-proof its business and to gain strategic insight into the sustainability impact of its products, processes and infrastructure globally. The company is a leading integrated agro-industrial and food business that is one of the world’s largest producers of feed, shrimp, poultry and pork. It has operations in 17 countries and exports to more than 50 countries.</p>
  <h2 id="global-net-zero-ambitions">Global Net-Zero Ambitions</h2>
  <p>In line with CP Foods’ goal of becoming the “Sustainable Kitchen of the World,” CP Foods is the first food processing company in the world with near- and long-term forests, lands and agriculture (FLAG) sustainability targets validated by the Science-Based Targets Initiative (SBTi). CP Foods is looking to realize the company’s <a href="https://www.cpfworldwide.com/en/media-center/oversea-operations-coal-free-to-net-zero">Net Zero goals</a> of reducing 42% of Scope 1 and 2 emissions and 30.3% of Scope 3 emissions by 2030 – and 90% of Scope 1 and 2 emissions and 72% of Scope 3 emissions by 2050. To achieve these goals, the company is implementing SAP Sustainability solutions to record, report and act on real-time sustainability data, driving carbon accounting at both corporate and product levels.</p>
  <p>“Net Zero is the only solution to climate change,” CP Foods CEO Prasit Boondoungpraser said. “It is important to us to understand and reduce our impact on the planet, so we create food that is not only safe and nutritious for people but also green and clean for the earth. Feeding our livestock, farming our food and transporting it to people’s plates incurs emissions we have to be able to record and report. With RISE with SAP and SAP Sustainability solutions, we will have insight into actual emissions automated in real time rather than relying on manual averages, allowing us to make quick, informed and sustainable business decisions for our operations and for the planet.”</p>
  <p>SAP plans to provide a technology foundation that will support CP Foods in complying with forthcoming carbon regulations in various markets, including the EU Carbon Border Adjustment Mechanism (EU C-BAM) and U.S. SEC climate risk disclosures.</p>
  <p>Key to reducing total emissions, CP Foods will focus on supply chain emissions, with its emissions mostly falling under Scope 3. CP Foods will work with the Customer Success organization at SAP, leverage YASH Technologies’ sustainability expertise and build on Amazon Web Services (AWS) to implement SAP Sustainability solutions. Doing so will allow it to record and report on its Scope 1 and 2 emissions in Thailand and select Scope 3 (3.1 and 3.4) for its feed business in Thailand covering both FLAG and non-FLAG emissions. The next phase of implementation will extend in scope to cover operations around the world.</p>
  <h2 id="cloud-sustainability">Cloud Sustainability</h2>
  <p>Paul Marriott, president of SAP Asia Pacific &#x26; Japan, said: “Sustainability is a huge opportunity for businesses across Asia. Using RISE with SAP and our sustainability solutions, CP Foods is getting ahead of forthcoming emissions regulation and future-proofing its business by using data to make more sustainable decisions. It can use those insights to drive more operational efficiencies, optimize supply chains, and differentiate its business against competitors.”</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-our-approach-to-sustainability-and-our-aspirations-for-a-world-with-zero-emissions-zero-waste-and-zero-inequality">Learn more about our approach to sustainability and our aspirations for a world with zero emissions, zero waste and zero inequality</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/sustainability/our-approach.html">Explore our journey</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>About SAP</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As a global leader in enterprise applications and business AI, SAP (NYSE:SAP) stands at the nexus of business and technology. For over 50 years, organizations have trusted SAP to bring out their best by uniting business-critical operations spanning finance, procurement, HR, supply chain, and customer experience. For more information, visit <a href="http://www.sap.com">www.sap.com</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Note to editors:</strong><br>To preview and download broadcast-standard stock footage and press photos digitally, please visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/photos">www.sap.com/photos</a>. On this platform, you can find high resolution material for your media channels.</p>
  <p><strong>For customers interested in learning more about SAP products:</strong><br>Global Customer Center: +49 180 534-34-24<br>United States Only: 1 (800) 872-1SAP (1-800-872-1727)</p>
  <p><strong>For more information, press only:</strong><br>Rizka Laksmi, <a href="mailto:rizka.laksmi@sap.com">rizka.laksmi@sap.com</a>, WIB<br>Lesa Plingen, +49 622 776 9000, <a href="mailto:lesa.plingen@sap.com">lesa.plingen@sap.com</a>, CET<br><a href="mailto:SAP%20Press%20Room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>This document contains forward-looking statements, which are predictions, projections, or other statements about future events. These statements are based on current expectations, forecasts, and assumptions that are subject to risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results and outcomes to materially differ. Additional information regarding these risks and uncertainties may be found in our filings with the Securities and Exchange Commission, including but not limited to the risk factors section of SAP’s 2023 Annual Report on Form 20-F.<br>© 2024 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.<br>Please consider our <a href="https://www.sap.com/corporate/en/legal/privacy.html">privacy policy</a>. If you received this press release in your e-mail and you wish to unsubscribe to our mailing list please contact <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a> and write Unsubscribe in the subject line.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-ehs-management</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-footprint-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Meeting the New SEC Emissions Policies: We Already Have All the Technology We Need]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/new-sec-emissions-policies-sap-technology</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/new-sec-emissions-policies-sap-technology</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New SEC emissions policies require disclosure of Scope 1 and 2 emissions. At SAP, we embrace the SEC’s ruling. Read about why.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-emissions</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-footprint-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[From CSRD Reporting to Sustainable Business Outcomes]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/from-csrd-reporting-to-sustainable-business-outcomes</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/from-csrd-reporting-to-sustainable-business-outcomes</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[By leveraging SAP Sustainability solutions, organizations can move beyond compliance, like CSRD reporting, and operationalize sustainability.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/compliance</category>
            <category>news-tag/esg</category>
            <category>news-tag/green-ledger</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-data-exchange</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-footprint-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-sustainability-solutions</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Accelerating Sustainability Innovation in the Cloud]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/accelerating-sustainability-innovation-in-the-cloud</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/accelerating-sustainability-innovation-in-the-cloud</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With our cloud-driven innovations, we help customers build the foundation for the evolution of their long-term sustainability strategies.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/esg</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-footprint-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How High Tech Helps S.Oleum Deliver ESG Metrics You Can Trust]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/high-tech-helps-s-oleum-deliver-esg-metrics</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/high-tech-helps-s-oleum-deliver-esg-metrics</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[S.Oleum’s data-driven sustainability efforts will generate revenue and sequester carbon. Read how SAP helps lay the foundation for success.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_130d6fab1e2941e378a85881bd255a5fab73223e2.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_130d6fab1e2941e378a85881bd255a5fab73223e2.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_130d6fab1e2941e378a85881bd255a5fab73223e2.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="How High Tech Helps S.Oleum Deliver ESG Metrics You Can Trust" src="./media_130d6fab1e2941e378a85881bd255a5fab73223e2.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="how-high-tech-helps-soleum-deliver-esg-metrics-you-can-trust">How High Tech Helps S.Oleum Deliver ESG Metrics You Can Trust</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>How can a three-year-old agroforestry company produce trustworthy, <a href="/topics/sustainability">sustainable</a> feedstock – raw materials for finished goods, energy, and more – while reducing the amount of carbon in the atmosphere?</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“We do that by using the biodiversity of this region, the Cerrado in Brazil,” Francisco de Blanco, S.Oleum co-founder and CEO, told SAP at the company’s headquarters, an innovative farm just outside João Pinheiro.</p>
  <p>Why the Brazilian outback? This tropical savanna is home to the macaúba, a highly adaptable oil-producing tree with a penchant for scrubbing harmful CO2 from the air. Macaúba fruit yields advanced vegetable oils (AVOs) and high-protein food – and it can be 15 times more productive than soybeans.</p>
  <p>“We are restoring the landscape that was deforested…Macaúba was native here many, many years ago,” Felipe Morbi, S.Oleum co-founder and Agroforestry VP, said. “Now we are bringing back these trees, and also all the other species, to restore this biodiversity.”</p>
  <p>S.Oleum seeks to accomplish this scientifically, using macaúba and other crops in an integrated crop-livestock-forest approach, according to Morbi. The goal is to create working farms that rejuvenate degraded, low-yielding soil – and that sequester into the soil more carbon than they generate.</p>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ba7dafe5dd92eabd85315450bbf0bdc404c57879.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ba7dafe5dd92eabd85315450bbf0bdc404c57879.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1ba7dafe5dd92eabd85315450bbf0bdc404c57879.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="How S.Oleum Will Use High Tech to Get Back to Brazil’s Roots" src="./media_1ba7dafe5dd92eabd85315450bbf0bdc404c57879.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://youtu.be/czukYJD_15c">How S.Oleum Will Use High Tech to Get Back to Brazil’s Roots</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="science-based-approach-to-reforesting-the-cerrado">Science-Based Approach to Reforesting the Cerrado</h2>
  <p>“We are looking for the balance of the system,” Morbi said in a new <a href="https://youtu.be/czukYJD_15c">SAP video</a>. “We will measure the amount of carbon in the soil, the moisture, the biodiversity in terms of the plants we have, and also native animals coming back to the area.”</p>
  <p>Toward that end, S.Oleum is starting small, but aiming big. Most of the current crop grows on a 700-hectare, or more than 1,700-acre, pilot farm. But S.Oleum intends to plant more than 65 million additional macaúba trees by 2029, which would reforest 180,00 hectares – about 444,800 acres – in Brazil’s southeastern state of Minas Gerais.</p>
  <p>Over time, macaúba trees also help improve the nutrient and moisture capacity of the soil, making it easier to grow other crops, according to de Blanco. And S.Oleum increases farm productivity by growing carefully chosen crops in between rows of macaúba trees, such as sunflowers, peanuts, and yucas.</p>
  <p>“If you do it right, agriculture as a system is positive for the environment,” de Blanco said. “Plants that were deforested a few decades ago, they are currently in a poor state because they were depleted by poor management…We believe there are better ways, and that’s what we are pursuing here.”</p>
  <p>An innovative case in point: macaúba trees increase a biome’s carbon sequestration levels. Removing this greenhouse gas helps more than the planet; S.Oleum also generates revenue by selling carbon credits and building trust via its data.</p>
  <h2 id="any-little-bit-of-data">Any Little Bit of Data</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="earth-overshoot-day-2023-reversing-the-clock-for-a-sustainable-future">Earth Overshoot Day 2023: Reversing the Clock for a Sustainable Future</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2023/08/earth-overshoot-day-2023-sustainable-future">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“Any little thing, any generation of data that R&#x26;D is currently developing, is extremely important,” Mirelle Santos, S.Oleum Agroforestry R&#x26;D manager, said. “We want to deploy technologies as dictated by those urgent needs.”</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_117cccc01d32d21d19b8033c668004e09a27b9c1b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_117cccc01d32d21d19b8033c668004e09a27b9c1b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_117cccc01d32d21d19b8033c668004e09a27b9c1b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Macaúba thorns" src="./media_117cccc01d32d21d19b8033c668004e09a27b9c1b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="300" height="225">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p><em>Photo by Derek Klobucher</em></p>
  <p>This could include remote sensing via drones that run fruit-recognition software, according to Santos. This would help S.Oleum gather and compile data quickly, without human error – and without sending workers, who must dress in personal protective equipment (PPE) to defend against snakes, mosquitos, the brutal Cerrado sun (even in winter), and dangerous macaúba thorns, which grow even on seedlings.</p>
  <p>S.Oleum’s intricate business model combines agriculture, forestry, biodiversity, and carbon offsetting – and that leads to a lot of complexity. SAP technology will be an important differentiator for this small enterprise, as well as a foundation for its future growth.</p>
  <p>“We have a big project to run; so, a lot of people, a lot of machines, a lot of suppliers,” Morbi said. “And we need everything in the right moment, in the right way.”</p>
  <h2 id="how-to-best-manage-esg-metrics">How to Best Manage ESG Metrics</h2>
  <p>“SAP is different because it is recognized as one of the most reliable ERP systems on the market, not only based on the technology,” de Blanco said. “Also, because it has well-established and well-defined processes.”</p>
  <p>Standardizing processes was “extremely important” for S.Oleum both internally and to inspire customer, stakeholder, and regulatory confidence, according to de Blanco. SAP will also enable S.Oleum to run its circular enterprise as well as record, report, and act on its sustainability data.</p>
  <p>“We have a very integrated system, and a very circular way to produce things,” de Blanco said. “Finding out where waste is generated – and where it’s being used – is very important to ensure the carbon intensity and the circularity of our systems at our entire site…This is where SAP helps us.”</p>
  <p>SAP S/4HANA, SAP Ariba solutions, SAP Concur solutions, and SAP SuccessFactors solutions will help standardize all of S.Oleum’s processes, which will improve transparency and compliance, according to S.Oleum IT Director Marcio Propp. To help better manage and understand its myriad environmental, social, and governance (ESG) metrics, the company has also begun implementation of <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/sustainability-control-tower.html">SAP Sustainability Control Tower</a> and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/sustainability-footprint-management.html">SAP Sustainability Footprint Management</a>.</p>
  <p>“It is super important that we have a very robust core system in place because it will serve as the basis for all our other processes…and practically all niche applications focused on digital agriculture connect with this core with SAP,” Propp said. “SAP is an agribusiness market standard, and it makes perfect sense for S.Oleum to be part of this ecosystem.”</p>
  <p>That’s a big deal because compliant, transparent ESG metrics are crucial to S.Oleum’s success, according to de Blanco.</p>
  <h2 id="a-matter-of-trust">A Matter of Trust</h2>
  <p>“Somewhere around one-third of our revenues come from carbon credits,” de Blanco said. “This is our, let’s say, core business…to convert sustainability into revenues and financial results.”</p>
  <p>That will require trust. SAP core technologies, such as SAP S/4HANA Cloud and <a href="https://www.sap.com/sustainability.html">SAP Sustainability solutions</a>, will help S.Oleum keep that trust, thanks to a reliable foundation of sustainability data and robust, auditable ESG metrics for reporting.</p>
  <p>“My advice for companies that are starting their sustainability endeavor: do it as quick as you can,” de Blanco said. “And do it attached to science.”</p>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div>For more information on how SAP helps companies record, report, and act on their sustainability goals, visit <a href="https://www.sap.com/sustainability.html">www.sap.com/sustainability</a>.</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>Top photo credit S.Oleum</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/agribusiness</category>
            <category>news-tag/circular-economy</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/esg</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-concur</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-footprint-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-sustainability-solutions</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Decarbonization Through Emission Transparency: Introducing SAP Sustainability Data Exchange]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/introducing-sap-sustainability-data-exchange</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/introducing-sap-sustainability-data-exchange</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The new SAP Sustainability Data Exchange solution is a testament to SAP's commitment to being a champion of a sustainable future.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/green-ledger</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-data-exchange</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-footprint-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[What Gets Measured, Gets Managed: Record, Report, and Act to Decarbonize Using SAP Sustainability Footprint Management]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/record-report-act-sap-sustainability-footprint-management</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/record-report-act-sap-sustainability-footprint-management</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP enables the data visibility and insight needed to decarbonize across value chains with SAP Sustainability Footprint Management.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-accounting</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-emissions</category>
            <category>news-tag/climate-action</category>
            <category>news-tag/decarbonization</category>
            <category>news-tag/green-ledger</category>
            <category>news-tag/greenhouse-gas-emissions</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-footprint-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-sustainability-solutions</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Introduces Transactional Carbon Accounting to Accelerate Climate Action]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/sap-introduces-transactional-carbon-accounting</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/sap-introduces-transactional-carbon-accounting</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is well-positioned deliver high-quality carbon accounting to rapidly scale business decarbonization. Learn about the new SAP solutions.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-accounting</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-emissions</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-footprint</category>
            <category>news-tag/climate-action</category>
            <category>news-tag/decarbonization</category>
            <category>news-tag/net-zero</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-data-exchange</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-footprint-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-sustainability-solutions</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP’s Vision for Future-Proofed Business in the Age of AI Comes to Life: SAP Sapphire in 2023]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/sap-sapphire-future-proofed-business-age-of-ai</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/sap-sapphire-future-proofed-business-age-of-ai</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[At SAP Sapphire in 2023, SAP unveiled sweeping innovations that equip customers to tackle an uncertain future with confidence. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/green-ledger</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-data-exchange</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-footprint-management</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>