<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/industry/telecommunications/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Deutsche Telekom Chooses RISE with SAP in Cloud Transformation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/deutsche-telekom-rise-with-sap-cloud-transformation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/deutsche-telekom-rise-with-sap-cloud-transformation</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Deutsche Telekom, a leading integrated telecommunications companies, has chosen RISE with SAP to accelerate its journey to the cloud.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1700bd00be5fff8c11a0434fa79589819e4d1ada0.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1700bd00be5fff8c11a0434fa79589819e4d1ada0.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1700bd00be5fff8c11a0434fa79589819e4d1ada0.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Deutsche Telekom Chooses RISE with SAP in Cloud Transformation" src="./media_1700bd00be5fff8c11a0434fa79589819e4d1ada0.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="deutsche-telekom-chooses-rise-with-sap-in-cloud-transformation">Deutsche Telekom Chooses RISE with SAP in Cloud Transformation</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced that Deutsche Telekom, one of the world’s leading integrated telecommunications companies, has chosen the RISE with SAP solution to accelerate its journey to the cloud.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="rise-with-sap-improve-compliance-and-build-business-resilience-in-a-managed-cloud-offering">RISE with SAP: Improve compliance and build business resilience in a managed cloud offering</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/rise.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Deutsche Telekom is the first enterprise to implement RISE with SAP through SAP’s recently expanded partnership with <a href="https://www.telekom.com/en/media/media-information/archive/tsi-announces-expanded-partnership-with-sap-1057448">T-Systems as a premium supplier of RISE with SAP</a>, marking a significant milestone in the relationship between SAP and Deutsche Telekom.</p>
  <p>As Europe’s largest telecommunications provider, with more than 252 million mobile customers, 25 million fixed-network lines and 22 million broadband lines, Deutsche Telekom operates in more than 50 countries. Aligned with the company’s vision to be the leading digital telecommunications provider in the world, Deutsche Telekom has chosen RISE with SAP to transform a major part of its ERP landscape to SAP S/4HANA Cloud. As a premium supplier of RISE with SAP, T-Systems will migrate, consolidate and manage more than 300 systems into the public and private cloud using T-Systems’ Future Cloud Infrastructure (FCI) and select hyperscalers. This is designed to enable customers to meet all German and European data protection requirements, as well as to benefit from tailored migration and orchestration of complex landscapes.</p>
  <p>Peter Leukert, chief information officer of Deutsche Telekom, said, “SAP is a trusted and important partner for Deutsche Telekom in both reliably running core business processes and accelerating innovation in the cloud. Through RISE with SAP, we can drive business transformation and take our partnership to new heights. With SAP S/4HANA Cloud, Deutsche Telekom will be able to drive efficiency across key business functions such as logistics, procurement and finance.”</p>
  <p>“Deutsche Telekom’s decision to select RISE with SAP to migrate and streamline more than 300 of their systems to the cloud marks an important milestone in their business transformation and continues a long history of our two companies innovating together for our customers,” said Scott Russell, member of the executive board of SAP SE, customer success. “This investment by Deutsche Telekom will give them new capabilities, drive greater efficiencies, and allow them to access key insights from across their enterprise so they can adjust to changing market conditions and seize new opportunities faster than they could before. We look forward to supporting Deutsche Telekom in this exciting new era of their cloud transformation.”</p>
  <p>As a premium supplier of RISE with SAP, T-Systems offers “<a href="https://www.t-systems.com/us/en/application-services/solutions/sap-solutions/rise-with-sap">Thrive with T-Systems</a>,” a collection of end-to-end transformation services that includes consulting, migration, implementation and operation of RISE with SAP and support for RISE with SAP S/4HANA Cloud Private Edition.</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>About SAP</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP’s strategy is to help every business run as an intelligent, sustainable enterprise. As a market leader in enterprise application software, we help companies of all sizes and in all industries run at their best: SAP customers generate 87% of total global commerce. Our machine learning, Internet of Things (IoT), and advanced analytics technologies help turn customers’ businesses into intelligent enterprises. SAP helps give people and organizations deep business insight and fosters collaboration that helps them stay ahead of their competition. We simplify technology for companies so they can consume our software the way they want – without disruption. Our end-to-end suite of applications and services enables business and public customers across 26 industries globally to operate profitably, adapt continuously, and make a difference. With a global network of customers, partners, employees, and thought leaders, SAP helps the world run better and improve people’s lives. For more information, visit <a href="http://www.sap.com">www.sap.com</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Note to editors:</strong><br>To preview and download broadcast-standard stock footage and press photos digitally, please visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/photos">www.sap.com/photos</a>. On this platform, you can find high resolution material for your media channels.</p>
  <p><strong>For customers interested in learning more about SAP products:</strong><br>Global Customer Center: +49 180 534-34-24<br>United States Only: 1 (800) 872-1SAP (1-800-872-1727)</p>
  <p><strong>For more information, press only:</strong><br>Lesa Plingen, +49 622 776 9000, <a href="mailto:lesa.plingen@sap.com">lesa.plingen@sap.com</a>, CET<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>This document contains forward-looking statements, which are predictions, projections, or other statements about future events. These statements are based on current expectations, forecasts, and assumptions that are subject to risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results and outcomes to materially differ. Additional information regarding these risks and uncertainties may be found in our filings with the Securities and Exchange Commission, including but not limited to the risk factors section of SAP’s 2023 Annual Report on Form 20-F.<br>© 2024 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.<br>Please consider our <a href="https://www.sap.com/corporate/en/legal/privacy.html">privacy policy</a>. If you received this press release in your e-mail and you wish to unsubscribe to our mailing list please contact <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a> and write Unsubscribe in the subject line.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/enterprise-resource-planning</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
            <category>industry/telecommunications</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Scope 3 Emissions in the Telecommunications Industry: Driving Sustainable Transformation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/emissions-in-telecommunications-industry-sustainable-transformation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/emissions-in-telecommunications-industry-sustainable-transformation</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Addressing scope 3 emissions is vital for telecommunications companies to meet climate goals and lead the transition to a sustainable future.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_174e09b00b05a139cf976c0528b18baf650fa1d08.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_174e09b00b05a139cf976c0528b18baf650fa1d08.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_174e09b00b05a139cf976c0528b18baf650fa1d08.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Scope 3 Emissions in the Telecommunications Industry: Driving Sustainable Transformation" src="./media_174e09b00b05a139cf976c0528b18baf650fa1d08.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="scope-3-emissions-in-the-telecommunications-industry-driving-sustainable-transformation">Scope 3 Emissions in the Telecommunications Industry: Driving Sustainable Transformation</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>The telecommunications business has been revolutionary in its ability to connect individuals worldwide. However, this phenomenal growth has left the sector with a significant portion of the world’s emissions. With increasing data demand, telecommunications companies must prioritize decreasing greenhouse gas emissions throughout their value chain.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Scope 3 emissions from activities across suppliers, product lifecycles, and customer usage comprise the overwhelming majority of emissions for telecommunications companies. While progress has been made on scope 1 and 2 emissions, scope 3 emissions remain a blind spot that demands urgent action. Addressing scope 3 emissions is vital for telecommunications companies to meet climate goals and lead the transition to a sustainable digital future.</p>
  <p>According to the <a href="https://www.wri.org/insights/4-charts-explain-greenhouse-gas-emissions-countries-and-sectors">World Resources Institute</a>, the global telecommunications industry emitted 1.7 billion tons of CO2 equivalent in 2019, representing approximately 2% of total global emissions. Telecommunications companies have an outsized opportunity to drive change and reduce emissions given their scale and influence across global supply chains and billions of customers worldwide.</p>
  <p>Now is the time for telecommunications companies to step up with courageous leadership, collective action across the ecosystem, transparency, and a laser focus on reducing scope 3 emissions.</p>
  <h2 id="understanding-scope-3-emissions-in-telecommunications">Understanding Scope 3 Emissions in Telecommunications</h2>
  <p>Scope 3 emissions encompass the vast majority of emissions across the telecommunications value chain. Key sources include:</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="how-sap-helps-businesses-streamline-their-emissions-declarations">How SAP Helps Businesses Streamline Their Emissions Declarations</h3>
        <p><em><a href="/2023/05/sap-ehs-management-streamline-emissions-declarations">Read the feature</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><strong>Supply chain</strong><br>Manufacturing, transport, and disposal of network equipment makes up the largest share, such as 60% of Verizon’s total scope 3</p>
  <p><strong>Product usage</strong><br>Energy consumption of infrastructure, data centers, and devices</p>
  <p><strong>Customers</strong><br>Emissions from using products and services represent over 20% for leading telecommunications companies</p>
  <p>While methodologies vary, standards like the <a href="https://ghgprotocol.org/">Greenhouse Gas (GHG) Protocol</a> enable consistent and transparent scope 3 accounting. Robust data collection and industry alignment will enhance accuracy over time. The urgency of climate action necessitates that telecommunications companies act now to address primary scope 3 hotspots like supply chain and product usage.</p>
  <p>Success requires transparency, cooperation, and immediate commitment to tackle scope 3 emission sources.</p>
  <h2 id="challenges-in-calculating-scope-3-emissions-in-the-telecommunications-industry">Challenges in Calculating Scope 3 Emissions in the Telecommunications Industry</h2>
  <p>Calculating scope 3 emissions poses major challenges for telecommunications companies, including:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Data limitations</strong>: Telecommunications companies lack visibility into supplier and vendor emissions. Greater transparency and coordination are essential.</li>
    <li><strong>Complex value chains</strong>: Varied reporting mechanisms across the vast partner ecosystem create aggregation difficulties.</li>
    <li><strong>Methodology alignment</strong>: Companies must determine boundaries and allocate shared infrastructure emissions while adhering to accounting standards.</li>
    <li><strong>Rapid technology changes</strong>: Emerging solutions like 5G and the Internet of Things (IoT) require continuous emissions monitoring.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>Robust data collection, industry collaboration, and transparency will be vital to overcome these obstacles. Standardized methodologies guided by established protocols will enhance accuracy over time.</p>
  <p>Above all, open cooperation across telecommunications value chains is crucial to drive scope 3 progress. From suppliers to customers, aligning stakeholders to prioritize emissions reductions will accelerate the sustainability shift, despite near-term uncertainty. Telecommunications companies have the scale and influence to lead the way.</p>
  <h2 id="strategies-for-mitigating-scope-3-emissions">Strategies for Mitigating Scope 3 Emissions</h2>
  <p>Telecommunications companies can mitigate scope 3 emissions through:</p>
  <p><strong>Supplier collaboration</strong><br>Joint research and development (R&#x26;D), audits, and incentive programs enable partners to reduce their supply chain footprint. AT&#x26;T uses a sustainability scorecard to motivate action.</p>
  <p><strong>Renewable energy</strong><br>Shifting infrastructure and operations to clean power significantly decreases emissions. BT Group and Telefónica aim for 100% renewable electricity use.</p>
  <p><strong>Eco-design</strong><br>Prioritizing recyclable and energy-efficient materials and manufacturing reduces lifecycle impacts. Vodafone’s Eco Rating drives more sustainable devices.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="achieve-transparency-and-gain-carbon-neutrality-with-sap-sustainability-data-exchange">Achieve transparency and gain carbon neutrality with SAP Sustainability Data Exchange</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/registration/request-demo.html?campaigncode=CRM-YI23-IMM-1939705&#x26;pageTitle=Climate+Action+Solutions&#x26;countryOfOrigin=en_us&#x26;refererPagePath=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.sap.com%2Fsustainability%2Fclimate-action.html&#x26;refererContentPath=%2Fcontent%2Fsapdx%2Flanguages%2Fen_us%2Fsustainability%2Fclimate-action&#x26;navTitle=Request+a+Demo">Demo it</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><strong>Customer engagement</strong><br>Awareness campaigns, energy-saving tips, and green tariffs incentivize sustainable usage. Orange’s set-top box eco-rating nudges consumers.</p>
  <p><strong>Policy and regulation</strong><br>Scope 3 requirements in markets like the EU also drive telecommunications companies to address value chain emissions through mandated reporting and carbon pricing.</p>
  <p>Additionally, telecommunications companies can further engage customers through expanded recycling and take-back programs to optimize device lifecycles. Services like leasing instead of selling phones can incentivize longevity. Features that track energy consumption also enable users to reduce their footprint.</p>
  <p>There are still challenges, but collective effort across the telecommunications ecosystem can drive progress on scope 3 emissions. Engagement and incentives can accelerate emissions reductions across value chains from suppliers to customers. With their global scale, telecommunications companies must lead the way.</p>
  <h2 id="calculating-and-reporting">Calculating and Reporting</h2>
  <p>To enable accurate and consistent scope 3 accounting, telecommunications companies should:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Adopt recognized standards like the GHG Protocol Corporate Value Chain Standard, which provides comprehensive guidance.</li>
    <li>Improve supplier data collection through surveys and supplier engagement platforms.</li>
    <li>Increase transparency by regularly disclosing scope 3 inventories and strategies in sustainability reports.</li>
    <li>Obtain third-party verification for scope 3 emissions data to ensure reliability.</li>
    <li>Collaborate with industry peers and partners to align methodologies and reporting.</li>
    <li>Continuously refine calculations by incorporating improved data sources and emission factors.</li>
    <li>Supplement inventory accounting with scenario modeling to project future emissions.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>While uncertainties remain, standardized and transparent scope 3 reporting is vital to understand emissions baselines, track progress over time, and hold companies accountable. Investors and customers are increasingly demanding credible disclosure.</p>
  <p>Telecommunications companies should lead the drive towards robust scope 3 accounting and reporting across sectors. Their commitment can catalyze broader adoption of carbon transparency.</p>
  <p>Using SAP Sustainability Data Exchange, telecommunications companies can collaborate with partners, enhance awareness and engagement of stakeholders, gain insights, mitigate risks, and seize opportunities to reduce and offset emissions.</p>
  <p>Ultimately, courageous leadership and collective diligence across telecommunications company value chains are imperative to drive progress. Telecommunications companies have the influence to spearhead robust and transparent scope 3 practices across all sectors. But, success hinges on prioritizing partnerships, integrity, and environmental stewardship above all. The moment for action has come.</p>
  <p>For more information on how SAP helps companies record, report, and act on their sustainability goals, visit <a href="https://www.sap.com/sustainability.html">www.sap.com/sustainability</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Venkata Rao is a business transformation expert at SAP.<br>Mohan Shekar is head of Industry Service at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-emissions</category>
            <category>news-tag/climate-action</category>
            <category>news-tag/greenhouse-gas-emissions</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-data-exchange</category>
            <category>industry/telecommunications</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tackling Today’s Billing and Revenue Challenges for Media]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/09/tackling-billing-and-revenue-challenges-for-media</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/09/tackling-billing-and-revenue-challenges-for-media</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Automated, secure, accurate billing processes are a must for today’s media companies. SAP Billing and Revenue Innovation Management can help.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/financial-management</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/quote-to-cash</category>
            <category>news-tag/recurring-revenue-models</category>
            <category>product/sap-billing-and-revenue-innovation-management</category>
            <category>industry/telecommunications</category>
            <category>news-tag/xaas</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Vodafone Is Changing the World of Telecommunications from the Inside Out]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/05/vodafone-group-telecommunications-sap-solutions</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/05/vodafone-group-telecommunications-sap-solutions</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 May 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Vodafone Group created a single digital core for the entire business based on SAP S4/HANA to gain greater consistency everywhere it operates.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16822df66158e2206f5da710120b1243898efd0bf.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16822df66158e2206f5da710120b1243898efd0bf.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_16822df66158e2206f5da710120b1243898efd0bf.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="How Vodafone Is Changing the World of Telecommunications from the Inside Out" src="./media_16822df66158e2206f5da710120b1243898efd0bf.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="how-vodafone-is-changing-the-world-of-telecommunications-from-the-inside-out">How Vodafone Is Changing the World of Telecommunications from the Inside Out</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>It is hard to imagine a technology that has changed the modern world more than the smartphone. Every day, millions of us use a single device to talk with friends, take videos, share photos, check e-mail, get driving directions, or go shopping. It’s been a global revolution.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As one of the world’s largest telecommunications companies, Vodafone Group connects more than 300 million people across the globe. And company leaders fully believe that tomorrow’s communications services will continue to transform our lives in powerful ways.</p>
  <p>Vodafone is already preparing for this future by making significant changes – and it is starting from within.</p>
  <h2 id="looking-for-global-consistency">Looking for Global Consistency</h2>
  <p>“Vodafone has been growing in recent years to strengthen its portfolio of services and expand into new geographies,” says Ignacio Garcia, CIO of Corporate Information Systems at Vodafone Group. But, as Garcia explains, much of this growth has been through acquisitions, resulting in various system landscapes and often inconsistent business practices throughout the group of companies.</p>
  <p>“We needed to operate as a single global organization and drive further innovation across the entire business,” Garcia adds. “To do that, we needed to run our company with a consistent, digital-first focus.” This realization led to big changes at Vodafone.</p>
  <p>The company migrated its complex and disparate enterprise resource planning (ERP) environment to a single digital core based on <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/s4hana-erp.html?btp=e479f1e4-7ee5-4e94-abfc-84a0233a3fb8">SAP S/4HANA</a>. “And we built on this solid foundation with SAP SuccessFactors, SAP Ariba, and SAP Concur solutions,” adds Holger Grewe, head of Corporate Transformation at Vodafone Group.</p>
  <p>Grewe – who has played a key leadership role in this project – points out that Vodafone benefited from some strong relationships along the way. This included implementation support from Accenture, SAP Services and Support, and customer success experts from SAP.</p>
  <p>“This was a massive transformation, covering more than twenty countries,” reports Grewe. “And SAP was by our side throughout the journey, supporting us with a <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/customer-involvement/customer-first.html">Customer First approach</a>.”</p>
  <h2 id="driving-needed-change">Driving Needed Change</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="discover-how-sap-empowers-telecommunications-providers">Discover how SAP empowers telecommunications providers</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/telecommunications.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The impact of the project on Vodafone’s operations has been huge.</p>
  <p>“We now have one data model that is standard across the footprint,” Grewe says. And Vodafone is simplifying the workplace for its more than 100,000 employees by digitizing business areas such as HR, travel and expense, and supply chain.</p>
  <p>Garcia estimates that Vodafone has standardized more than 80% of its core business processes and boosted automation levels to over 60%. “And it’s not the endgame,” remarks a smiling Garcia. “This is just the beginning.”</p>
  <p>In addition, Garcia notes that new capabilities like <a href="https://insights.sap.com/what-is-machine-learning/">machine learning</a> and advanced analytics will help Vodafone develop the next generation of products and services.</p>
  <h2 id="building-a-digital-future-at-vodafone-group">Building a Digital Future at Vodafone Group</h2>
  <p>Innovation will be crucial as <a href="https://www.vodafone.com/our-purpose">Vodafone looks ahead</a> to achieve specific goals for improving lives.</p>
  <p>By 2025, for example, the company wants to:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Connect over 50 million people and their families to mobile money services</li>
    <li>Bring mobile to an additional 20 million women in Africa and Turkey</li>
    <li>Support 10 million young people in learning the digital skills needed to thrive in the digital economy</li>
    <li>Connect 150 million vehicles to <a href="https://insights.sap.com/what-is-iot-internet-of-things/">the Internet of Things (IoT)</a></li>
  </ul>
  <p>Vodafone is confident that today’s transformation will enable the company to build a digital future that works for everyone. “These changes are helping Vodafone work as one company,” Grewe says, “so people around the world will stay better connected.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="test-drive-sap-s4hana-today">Test drive SAP S/4HANA today</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/s4hana-erp.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="to-hear-more-from-ignacio-garcia-and-holger-grewe-about-the-changes-at-vodafone-group-watch-this-video-also-check-out-these-videos-on-vodafones-experience-with-sap-successfactors-sap-concur-and-sap-ariba-solutions-as-well-as-sap-maxattention-services">To hear more from Ignacio Garcia and Holger Grewe about the changes at Vodafone Group, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/intelligent-enterprise.html?campaigncode=CRM-YD21-SOC-CUSTREF&#x26;video=d07a8f9f-df7d-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b">watch this video</a>. Also check out these videos on Vodafone’s experience with <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm.html?campaigncode=CRM-YD21-SOC-CUSTREF%E2%80%A2&#x26;video=ba32689d-df7d-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b">SAP SuccessFactors</a>, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/e-procurement/travel-expense-management.html?campaigncode=CRM-YD21-SOC-CUSTREF&#x26;video=eae78f9f-df7d-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b">SAP Concur</a> and <a href="https://www.ariba.com/?campaigncode=CRM-YD21-SOC-CUSTREF&#x26;video=2c7d909f-df7d-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b">SAP Ariba</a> solutions, as well as <a href="https://www.sap.com/uk/services/premium-engagement/maxattention.html?sort=latest_desc?campaigncode=CRM-YD21-SOC-CUSTREF&#x26;video=84788d9f-df7d-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b">SAP MaxAttention</a> services.</h3>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-concur</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-hana</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/service-industries</category>
            <category>industry/telecommunications</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Entel Charted a Path to Digital Self-Learning Despite Disruption]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/entel-digital-self-learning-sap-successfactors</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/entel-digital-self-learning-sap-successfactors</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Employees at leading Chilean telecommunications company Entel enjoy an enhanced learning experience with SAP SuccessFactors. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16b818302542f7c5bfe597377655d0c473ae578e5.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16b818302542f7c5bfe597377655d0c473ae578e5.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_16b818302542f7c5bfe597377655d0c473ae578e5.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="How Entel Charted a Path to Digital Self-Learning Despite Disruption" src="./media_16b818302542f7c5bfe597377655d0c473ae578e5.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="how-entel-charted-a-path-to-digital-self-learning-despite-disruption">How Entel Charted a Path to Digital Self-Learning Despite Disruption</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="support-continuous-learning-with-a-unified-learning-management-system">Support continuous learning with a unified learning management system</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/corporate-lms.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>The best employees have always had a vested interest in building their skills but precious little time to train. Then the <a href="/covid-19">COVID-19</a> pandemic hit, and a new way of working gave many employees pause – and the chance to think long and hard about their careers. So, Empresa Nacional de Telecomunicaciones S.A., commonly known as Entel, responded to a disrupted workforce and provided these employees with the digital tools to reskill and <a href="https://insights.sap.com/importance-upskilling/">upskill</a>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Today, employees at this leading Chilean telecommunications company enjoy an enhanced learning experience with SAP SuccessFactors solutions. Entel used SAP SuccessFactors solutions to help fully digitalize Entel University, the company’s training program, as the pandemic rocked the lives of workers worldwide. Rather than caving to this disruption, HR leaders at Entel transformed crisis into opportunity and adapted the company’s training formula to the new normal.</p>
  <p>“The COVID-19 pandemic accelerated the process that we had been developing, causing us to completely digitalize our corporate learning plan,” said Angélica Sánchez, organizational development and learning management analyst at Entel. “Today, the focus is to maintain this trend and concentrate our digital offerings, further democratizing knowledge.”</p>
  <p>By providing fully digital learning experiences to a <a href="https://insights.sap.com/connect-remote-workforces-strengthen-corporate-culture/">newly remote workforce</a>, Entel empowered employees to take control of their careers during an increasingly uncertain time. Not only that, but remote e-learning courses helped provide structure to employees’ workdays as they adjusted to working from home.</p>
  <p>Entel adapted learning content to face the pandemic head-on, developing leadership workshops and trainings focused on supporting employees. These included sessions on increasing productivity at home and best practices for remote collaboration, as well as tips for self-care and overcoming anxiety in times of uncertainty.</p>
  <p>“We know that in the current reality, one of the main interests of companies and organizations is to maintain productivity,” said Cristóbal Vergara, a general manager at SAP Chile. “To achieve this, it is relevant to reimagine the processes and invest in distance collaboration tools, technologies to facilitate work, and worker training programs because building a culture of continuous learning reflects that the company is investing in potential and growth.”</p>
  <p>Entel’s digital learning journey began in 2016 when the company implemented a <a href="https://insights.sap.com/what-is-lms/">learning management system (LMS)</a> from SAP SuccessFactors solutions to help enhance Entel University, a largely in-person education center. The company founded Entel University in 2010 with a face-to-face classroom format that proved to be a constant challenge for learners spread across locations. Not only that, but in-person learning also required a large investment in time and money. The digital LMS helped reduce these costs by initiating self-learning processes and bringing content online, and it offered specialized training tailored to the needs of each employee’s role and specialization.</p>
  <p>Then, in the midst of the pandemic, Entel decided to take the plunge and completely digitalize Entel University. It consolidated its entire learning infrastructure on a single platform on SAP SuccessFactors solutions. The solutions helped create a foundation for permanent corporate learning through diverse and dynamic courses that align with the company’s strategy. Employees can easily access topics of interest intuitively organized on one digital experience through their desktop or mobile devices. They can take advantage of a new professional skills program that includes performance management workshops and more. In addition, specialized courses help employees gain new skills in sales, e-commerce, cybersecurity, and customer experience.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="create-a-more-flexible-engaged-workforce-and-a-more-resilient-business">Create a more flexible, engaged workforce and a more resilient business</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>At its core, Entel University promotes a new digital culture that emphasizes self-management and continuous learning. In 2020, 3,098 employees took one or more e-learning courses at Entel University for a total of 6,003 completed remote courses – three times more than all of the courses completed in 2019. Entel University will make it easy for employees to continue learning, even after the pandemic subsides.</p>
  <p>“For Entel, learning management is in constant evolution, mobilizing the capacities that our company requires in its permanent transformation,” said Sanchez. “That is why, within the next 12 years, the main challenge will be to train talent with an emphasis on the development of digital capabilities and a mentality willing to change.”</p>
  <p>To achieve this, the company continues the successful journey it started with SAP SuccessFactors solutions. Entel hopes that its digital training, in addition to future developments in human experience management (HXM), will help reduce employee turnover by improving the overall Entel employee experience.</p>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div>To learn more about how SAP SuccessFactors solutions can help your business provide effective digital enablement for employees, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/corporate-lms.html">visit sap.com/lms</a>.</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div><a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2021/04/21/this-telecommunications-company-charted-a-path-to-digital-self-learning-despite-disruption/?sh=724ec7e6eda5">This story originally appeared on SAP BrandVoice on Forbes</a>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/covid-19</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning-management-system</category>
            <category>industry/telecommunications</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Will Technology Keep Us Together? Ask Vodafone]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/03/technology-together-vodafone-cio-ignacio-garcia</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/03/technology-together-vodafone-cio-ignacio-garcia</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Mar 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Vodafone CIO Ignacio Garcia recently appeared on Getting Real with SAP to discuss leveraging technology to serve customers amid COVID-19.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e5eb9658e7797cedc7b5a1fe87983fdcf92873d7.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e5eb9658e7797cedc7b5a1fe87983fdcf92873d7.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1e5eb9658e7797cedc7b5a1fe87983fdcf92873d7.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Will Technology Keep Us Together? Ask Vodafone" src="./media_1e5eb9658e7797cedc7b5a1fe87983fdcf92873d7.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="will-technology-keep-us-together-ask-vodafone">Will Technology Keep Us Together? Ask Vodafone</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>It is easy to feel isolated these days, so it’s no wonder that we seem to rely on our smartphones more than ever to stay in touch through calls, texts, and social media.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>But the global health crisis has been challenging for everyone – including the companies that have been working hard to keep us connected, like Vodafone Group. Vodafone is a multinational technology communications company that serves more than 300 million mobile customers around the world.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="watch-the-episode-with-vodafone-conquering-the-challenge-head-on-by-doubling-service">Watch the episode with Vodafone: Conquering the Challenge “Head-On” By Doubling Service</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/covid-19/back-to-best.html?video=10d8458c-d17d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="quick-response-to-customers-and-employees">Quick Response to Customers and Employees</h2>
  <p>Ignacio Garcia, CIO of Corporate Information Systems at Vodafone, recently appeared on <em>Getting Real with SAP</em>. There, he discussed how companies are leveraging technology to manage their business and continue to serve customers in the age of <a href="/covid-19">COVID-19</a>.</p>
  <p>“You can imagine what we were thinking: How much extra demand are we going to have?” says Garcia. “We needed to keep our employees safe and make sure we supported our customers in the best possible way.”</p>
  <p>Vodafone was able to do both.</p>
  <p>In short order, the company developed a <a href="https://www.vodafone.com/covid19">five-point plan</a> to help the communities it serves. Keystones of the plan were a commitment to maintaining the quality of service and providing network capacity and network services for critical government functions.</p>
  <p>Vodafone also made sure to quickly address the needs of a global workforce that encompasses more than 100,000 employees. Vodafone offered support for working at home, created richer virtual training opportunities for its people, and adjusted performance goals and objectives to align with new business needs.</p>
  <h2 id="the-right-technology-pays-dividends">The Right Technology Pays Dividends</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="make-your-organization-more-resilient-and-agile-in-todays-challenging-environment-get-back-to-best-with-sap">Make your organization more resilient and agile in today’s challenging environment: Get back to best with SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/covid-19/back-to-best.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Vodafone’s business agility was not merely the result of good luck.</p>
  <p>Less than a year ago, Vodafone completed a massive global rollout of SAP S/4HANA to help improve operational efficiency in business functions such as finance, supply chain, and IT.</p>
  <p>It was an impressive project covering more than 20 countries. And in addition to establishing a single digital core for the company, it included retooling Vodafone’s worldwide HR systems. “Using the power of the technology was fundamental, having a single data model, a single way to optimize and understand the different markets,” says Garcia.</p>
  <h2 id="stay-creative">Stay Creative</h2>
  <p>Vodafone may have been ahead of the curve in its ability to meet the challenges of COVID-19. But many other companies are responding with technology-driven innovation. There has been an incredible degree of creativity in how businesses have reacted.</p>
  <p>Staying connected will only be one of the challenges we face in the days ahead. This is a critical time for all of us – as individuals and as businesses.</p>
  <p>Check out <a href="https://www.sap.com/covid-19/back-to-best.html?video=10d8458c-d17d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff">this episode of <em>Getting Real with SAP</em></a> to learn more.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em><a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2021/03/03/will-technology-keep-us-together-ask-vodafone/?sh=655f126042da">This story originally appeared on SAP BrandVoice on Forbes.</a></em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/back-to-best</category>
            <category>news-tag/covid-19</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/service-industries</category>
            <category>industry/telecommunications</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Tech that Falls from Space]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/the-tech-that-falls-from-space</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/the-tech-that-falls-from-space</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The business of space has evolved substantially in recent years, as private companies have joined the public sector in advancing in the space economy.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_147a59d43b6152fca398b52e2fe5874a2bcee4294.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_147a59d43b6152fca398b52e2fe5874a2bcee4294.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_147a59d43b6152fca398b52e2fe5874a2bcee4294.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="qq" src="./media_147a59d43b6152fca398b52e2fe5874a2bcee4294.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1044">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="the-tech-that-falls-from-space">The Tech that Falls from Space</h1>
        <p>Investments in space R&#x26;D will bring a new wave of advances in data, networking, and resources that benefit life on earth.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>When NASA announced that it was awarding close to US$1 billion in new contracts as part of a project to return astronauts to the moon by 2024, it felt like a headline from the 1960s.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In fact, the American agency’s Artemis project, which tapped space industry players established by Amazon’s Jeff Bezos and Tesla’s Elon Musk for its next phase, is part of a technology-inspired continuum that dates to the start of the space race.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="want-a-quick-overview">Want a quick overview?</h3>
        <p>Learn how innovations on earth are being sourced from the cosmos.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2022/10/e00bfc0a-487e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Read the brief</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Indeed, the results of space research have been the source of numerous technology innovations, many of which we now take for granted. Desensitized by awe-inspiring science fiction CGI, most of us gloss over the true impact of space science that has led to mobile devices and GPS systems that rely on satellite data.</p>
  <p>Digital business leaders have taken notice, however. Record investment in global space ventures, along with ever-increasing revenues generated by the space industry, suggests that space continues to be a key driver of technology and business innovation. Space-based breakthroughs have birthed new technologies and markets, including LEDs and advanced solar technology, anti-icing systems and firefighting gear, improved food safety and water purification, and even enriched baby food and our beloved memory-foam mattresses.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_123637013e3545b6ddc1d7fe52edba70149ee95fd.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_123637013e3545b6ddc1d7fe52edba70149ee95fd.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_123637013e3545b6ddc1d7fe52edba70149ee95fd.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Radio telescopes under Milky Way" src="./media_123637013e3545b6ddc1d7fe52edba70149ee95fd.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>More than 9,000 satellites orbit the Earth, providing a powerful source of Big Data for businesses, governments, and nonprofits and supporting breakthroughs in areas such as climate observation and Earth resource monitoring.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The World Economic Forum’s <em>Global Future Council on Space Technologies</em> <a href="https://www.weforum.org/agenda/2017/06/countdown-what-will-2030s-new-space-economy-look-like/">predicts</a> a new wave of space-enabled innovation by 2030, including downstream applications of observational data that could boost climate resilience, ensure water and food security, and help us monitor or predict the impact of natural disasters. We can also anticipate speedy rocket-propelled trips around the world, affordable broadband for all, more accurate and accelerated supply chains and delivery, and new supplies of vital natural resources.</p>
  <h2 id="to-the-edge--and-beyond-with-many-partners">To the edge – and beyond, with many partners</h2>
  <p>The business of space has evolved substantially in recent years, as private companies have joined the public sector in advancing in the <a href="https://read.oecd-ilibrary.org/economics/oecd-handbook-on-measuring-the-space-economy_9789264169166-en#page22">space economy</a>, which encompasses space research and resulting products and services. According to the U.S. Federal Aviation Administration’s <em>Annual Compendium of Commercial Space Transportation: 2018</em>, the global space industry represents about <a href="https://www.faa.gov/about/office_org/headquarters_offices/ast/media/2018_ast_compendium.pdf">$345 billion</a> in economic activity. Worldwide, private investors poured <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2020/01/14/space-companies-including-spacex-raised-5point8-billion-in-2019.html">$5.8 billion</a> into it in 2019, according to investment company Space Angels.</p>
  <p>To date, the benefits of these investments have been most visible in the global satellite infrastructure.</p>
  <p><a href="https://www.unoosa.org/oosa/osoindex/search-ng.jspx?lf_id=">More than 9,000 satellites</a> orbit the Earth, providing a powerful source of Big Data for businesses, governments, and nonprofits and supporting breakthroughs in areas such as climate observation and Earth resource monitoring. Within a short time, the cost to launch a satellite has dropped thanks to reusable rockets, and it could decrease further as both launch vehicles and satellites become mass produced. As a recent article in the <em>Financial Times</em> noted, satellites that used to require bankrolling by multi-billion dollar companies can now be <a href="https://www.ft.com/content/32d3f95e-f6c1-11e7-8715-e94187b3017e">developed and launched</a> by startups and universities.</p>
  <p>These fleets of <a href="https://brycetech.com/reports/report-documents/Bryce_Smallsats_2020.pdf">smaller, cheaper satellites</a> are poised to transform our view of the planet even further through access to vastly greater volumes of more granular data generated by Internet of Things (IoT) technologies. These <a href="https://www.techopedia.com/definition/6978/edge-device">edge devices</a> – all kinds of networked products, from mobile phones and sensors to smart cars and robots – need satellites to transmit the data that they process, store, and analyze. Advances in data science, artificial intelligence, and computing power will enable us to turn volumes of real-time imaging and data into insight and innovation across industries.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_173567b090446a0e58ead178ba822f1cd750ca5ed.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_173567b090446a0e58ead178ba822f1cd750ca5ed.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_173567b090446a0e58ead178ba822f1cd750ca5ed.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Shooting stars" src="./media_173567b090446a0e58ead178ba822f1cd750ca5ed.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="the-pervasive-value-of-satellite-data">The pervasive value of satellite data</h2>
  <p>Satellite data is already transforming supply chain management with greater transparency. Startup <a href="https://orbitalinsight.com/">Orbital Insight</a> applies machine learning to satellite imaging data to react to supply chain trends, such as helping a wind turbine manufacturer forecast demand and optimize component replacement, or predicting market fluctuations in the oil and gas industry based on images of storage tanks and commodity stockpiles. British food company <a href="https://www.barfoots.com/">Barfoots</a> uses satellites to track the position of its cargo ships and monitor the temperature and humidity of containers to <a href="http://techzulu.com/5-ways-satellites-satellite-companies-making-world-cleaner-place/">reduce</a> food and resource waste. Network builders are looking to <a href="https://siliconcanals.com/news/these-are-the-5-biggest-tech-predictions-for-2020/">low-earth orbit satellites</a> to deliver high-speed broadband connectivity.</p>
  <p>In the realm of food and freshwater supply, the <a href="https://www.usgs.gov/land-resources/nli/landsat">U.S. Landsat Program</a> has long provided remote sensing data to monitor global food and fiber production, crop health, and soil moisture. Now <a href="https://svs.gsfc.nasa.gov/13543">precision farmers</a> are using it to more efficiently manage their land. <a href="https://www.frontiersin.org/articles/10.3389/fenvs.2020.00007/full">Satellites</a> are critical to protecting freshwater ecosystems that underpin Earth’s global water and food security. The <a href="https://www.oceanmind.global/about/">OceanMind</a> technology platform cross-references satellite imaging with fishing vessel databases and oceanographic data to combat the $23.5 billion illegal fishing market using real-time alerts.</p>
  <p>The newest generation of <a href="https://www.scientificamerican.com/article/new-wave-of-mini-satellites-could-boost-climate-research/">small satellites</a> may vastly improve predictions of weather and climate change. Researchers are developing a new satellite, the <a href="https://eospso.nasa.gov/missions/geostationary-carbon-cycle-observatory-evm-2">Geostationary Carbon Cycle Observatory</a>, to track 10 million daily metrics of climate change. Meanwhile, members of a group called the <a href="https://disasterscharter.org/">The International Charter Space and Major Disasters</a> are collaborating to share satellite data to protect people and infrastructure in the face of more frequent and severe natural disasters.</p>
  <h2 id="a-universe-of-possibilities">A universe of possibilities</h2>
  <p>Space exploration stretches our capabilities even further. By pushing the boundaries of what is technically possible, it stimulates ingenuity and gives us new options for supporting life on Earth – or elsewhere, should our planet become <a href="https://futurism.com/the-byte/new-research-human-civilization-collapse-2050">uninhabitable</a>. Today’s digital leaders are banking on expanding their markets beyond Earth, including Google’s $30 million <a href="https://lunar.xprize.org/">Lunar XPrize</a> competition, Amazon CEO Jeff Bezos’s billions invested into space transportation firm <a href="https://www.blueorigin.com/">Blue Origin</a>, and Tesla CEO Elon Musk’s <a href="https://www.spacex.com/">SpaceX</a>.</p>
  <p>The International Space Station has proven the value of space-based research to fields such as the production of high-performance optical fiber and the development of new vaccines. A new wave of space stations and (once they are created) galactic economic development zones will stimulate a range of developments, such as space tourism and space manufacturing. For example, China has plans to test <a href="https://www.space.com/china-space-station-april-launch-will-prepare.html">a new space ship</a> in 2020 that, if successful, would support construction of a new space station.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1394c74547ce4530a38c8a3ae2179ab38947baf77.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1394c74547ce4530a38c8a3ae2179ab38947baf77.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1394c74547ce4530a38c8a3ae2179ab38947baf77.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Aerial view of farmland" src="./media_1394c74547ce4530a38c8a3ae2179ab38947baf77.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1647" height="1120">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="planetary-minerals">Planetary minerals</h2>
  <p>The cosmos may also serve as a new source of vital resources. <a href="https://space.nss.org/space-solar-power-links/">Space-based solar power</a> could help solve our energy and climate change challenges by providing large quantities of power with little environmental impact. The global mining industry, in decline in recent years, may begin extracting resources from asteroids or the moon. Space watchers see a lucrative future, including astrophysicist Neil DeGrasse Tyson, declaring that the first <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/videos/2019-10-22/want-to-be-a-trillionaire-try-space-mining-video">trillionaires</a> will be those who mine asteroids. The government of Luxembourg has launched a <a href="https://space-agency.public.lu/en/news-media/news/2020/luxembourg_becomes_member_isecg.html">Space Resources Initiative</a> to support the peaceful exploration and sustainable utilization of space resources for the benefit of humankind.</p>
  <p>Meanwhile, governments, as well as private companies, are making plans for lunar exploration and development. In 2019, China landed a <a href="https://www.sciencenews.org/article/china-moon-rover-revealed-what-lies-beneath-lunar-farside-surface">lunar rover</a> on the moon’s dark side. <a href="https://www.theguardian.com/science/2020/jan/02/chandrayaan-3-india-unveils-fresh-35m-attempt-to-put-a-rover-on-the-moon">India</a> has plans to land its own moon vehicle after its 2019 effort failed. SpaceX hopes to send a crewed mission to Mars by 2028. And NASA has been developing a new rocket and spacecraft that could take astronauts into deep space to build a <a href="https://www.nasa.gov/feature/nasa-s-lunar-outpost-will-extend-human-presence-in-deep-space/">lunar outpost</a> and eventually travel to Mars, opening up opportunities to explore more distant destinations.</p>
  <p>Whether Musk will meet his goal of reaching the <a href="https://futurism.com/images/invaders-from-earth-how-elon-musk-plans-to-conquer-mars/">Red Planet by 2025</a> – or whether we will want to pull up stakes and <a href="https://futurism.com/adapting-for-survival-on-mars/">live on Mars</a> – are questions for the future. What’s clear is that solving everyday challenges here on Earth requires new solutions today. Breakthrough innovation often requires that we view things from unusual vantage points. Looking down on Earth from space and gazing out into the cosmos provide the ultimate shift of perspective and could give us the insights to go beyond our restricted earthbound thinking.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/business-transformation</category>
            <category>industry/telecommunications</category>
            <category>content-type/trends-predictions</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>