<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/product/sap-intelligent-returns-management/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Power of Personalization in an Increasingly Digital World]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/power-of-personalization-in-increasingly-digital-world</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/power-of-personalization-in-increasingly-digital-world</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Personalization, enabled by SAP solutions, can build relationships, increase customer lifetime value, and enhance customer engagement.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/fashion</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
            <category>product/sap-commerce-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-customer-data-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-emarsys-customer-engagement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-experience-center</category>
            <category>product/sap-intelligent-returns-management</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-retail</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sustainable Retail Business Solutions from SAP]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/01/nrf-2022-sustainable-retail-business-solutions-from-sap</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/01/nrf-2022-sustainable-retail-business-solutions-from-sap</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[During NRF 2022, read how SAP solutions are helping retailers digitally transform and make their businesses sustainable.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a903832003837e34c273cbd6c0ea4f5745d5d107.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a903832003837e34c273cbd6c0ea4f5745d5d107.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1a903832003837e34c273cbd6c0ea4f5745d5d107.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Sustainable Retail Business Solutions from SAP" src="./media_1a903832003837e34c273cbd6c0ea4f5745d5d107.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sustainable-retail-business-solutions-from-sap">Sustainable Retail Business Solutions from SAP</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-sap-at-nrf-2022">Learn more about SAP at NRF 2022</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://events.sap.com/noam/nrf/en/home">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong> — The <a href="https://cdn.nrf.com/sites/default/files/2020-06/RS-118304%20NRF%20Retail%20Impact%20Report%20.pdf">retail industry’s</a> $3.9 trillion contribution to the U.S. annual GDP makes it the nation’s leading industry for private sector employment and uniquely positioned to address climate change.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As recently as the 2021 United Nations Climate Change Conference (COP26) meetings, the <a href="https://nrf.com/blog/retailers-set-science-based-targets-address-climate-change">National Retail Federation (NRF)</a> stated, “Retailers will continue inventing and implementing pragmatic climate change solutions because the needs identified at COP26 demand nothing less.”</p>
  <p>To help retailers digitally transform to make their businesses sustainable, SAP is featuring a number of offerings, including these:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>The new <a href="/2021/07/sap-intelligent-returns-management-consumers-retailers-environment">SAP Intelligent Returns Management solution</a> was built to optimize the returns process for the retail industry. The solution uses routing and dispositioning decisions driven by artificial intelligence (AI) to guide products from customers’ hands to the final dispositioning steps, ultimately maximizing customer experience and company margins while also mitigating waste.</li>
    <li>The recently updated <a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2021/09/a6120d2d-f87d-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">SAP Assortment Planning application</a> now offers advanced category management capabilities. It uses customer data science, assortment strategies, business rules and AI to plan space-aware, localized assortments with a user experience designed for the needs of today’s category manager. Customer-centric, relevant assortments increase customer loyalty, boost profitability and support a more sustainable supply chain.</li>
    <li>The SAP.iO Foundries program is a network of startup companies with integrations to SAP solutions, including:
      <ul>
        <li><strong><a href="https://algramo.com/en">Algramo</a>,</strong> offering a circular platform that encourages consumers to buy in a more convenient, affordable way with zero waste and connects people, brands and retailers in an engaging way to change consumption habits</li>
        <li><strong><a href="https://ecocart.io/business/">EcoCart</a>,</strong> helping thousands of e-commerce brands offer carbon-neutral products</li>
        <li><strong><a href="https://everledger.io/">Everledger</a>,</strong> leveraging blockchain and the Internet of Things to offer transparency into supply chains for clarity on quality, origin, sustainability footprint and compliance standards</li>
        <li><strong><a href="https://evrythng.com/">EVRYTHNG</a>,</strong> helping customers run their businesses differently with real-time data intelligence from each of their products end to end, from factory to consumer and beyond</li>
        <li><strong><a href="https://inspectorio.com/">Inspectorio</a>,</strong> with a dynamic and risk-assessment-based quality compliance program that provides digitalization, automation, transparency and traceability</li>
        <li><strong><a href="https://thelimeloop.com/">LimeLoop</a>,</strong> offering a platform for sustainable shipping including reusable packaging, real-time tracking and predictive analytics</li>
        <li><strong><a href="https://specright.com/">Specright</a>,</strong> providing a purpose-built platform for specification management that fundamentally changes how brands, suppliers, manufacturers and retailers manage data and collaborate to bring products to market</li>
      </ul>
    </li>
  </ul>
  <p>In addition to these offerings, retailers can utilize SAP’s entire portfolio of <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/purpose-and-sustainability.html">sustainable business solutions</a>. Learn more in the blog “<a href="/">SAP Cloud for Sustainable Enterprises: Taking Action Together</a>.”</p>
  <p>SAP’s solutions enable retailers to integrate sustainable business practices smoothly, which is critical to a fast-paced industry such as retail. According to Leslie Hand, IDC Group Vice President, IDC Retail Insights, <a href="https://eur03.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.linkedin.com%2Fcompany%2Fidc_emea%2F&#x26;data=04%7C01%7Cstacy.comes%40sap.com%7C32f20fbd808e403ebab108d9c18832a2%7C42f7676cf455423c82f6dc2d99791af7%7C0%7C0%7C637753612987837002%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJWIjoiMC4wLjAwMDAiLCJQIjoiV2luMzIiLCJBTiI6Ik1haWwiLCJXVCI6Mn0%3D%7C3000&#x26;sdata=Avs0Ujbs1kRZqn0deU53aOOosGrbGrMddrMgbScdhSc%3D&#x26;reserved=0">IDC’s latest research</a> indicates that retail organizations report that, relative to political, social and economic risks, changing environmental targets and regulations will have the greatest impact on their digital transformation and tech investment plans in the next two years. Further, 80% (Asia Pacific) 59% (United States) and 64% (EMEA) of retail organizations agree that their digital technology strategy is an important enabler of their organization’s broader sustainability efforts.*</p>
  <p>For more information about SAP at NRF 2022, Retail’s Big Show, visit <a href="https://events.sap.com/noam/nrf/en/home">sap.com/nrf</a> and follow <a href="https://twitter.com/SAP_Retail">@SAP_Retail</a> on Twitter.</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="http://news.sap.com/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP on Twitter at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Media Contact:</strong> Stacy Ries, SAP Media Relations, +1 (484) 619-0411, <a href="mailto:stacy.ries@sap.com">stacy.ries@sap.com</a>, ET<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p><em>*Source: IDC Retail Core Processes and Applications, May 2021.</em><br>Any statements contained in this document that are not historical facts are forward-looking statements as defined in the U.S. Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995. Words such as “anticipate,” “believe,” “estimate,” “expect,” “forecast,” “intend,” “may,” “plan,” “project,” “predict,” “should” and “will” and similar expressions as they relate to SAP are intended to identify such forward-looking statements. SAP undertakes no obligation to publicly update or revise any forward-looking statements. All forward-looking statements are subject to various risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results to differ materially from expectations. The factors that could affect SAP’s future financial results are discussed more fully in SAP’s filings with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (“SEC”), including SAP’s most recent Annual Report on Form 20-F filed with the SEC. Readers are cautioned not to place undue reliance on these forward-looking statements, which speak only as of their dates.<br>© 2022 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc</category>
            <category>news-tag/nrf</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-assortment-planning</category>
            <category>product/sap-cloud-for-sustainable-enterprises</category>
            <category>product/sap-intelligent-returns-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-io</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Helping Consumers, Retailers, and the Environment]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2021/07/sap-intelligent-returns-management-consumers-retailers-environment</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2021/07/sap-intelligent-returns-management-consumers-retailers-environment</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The new SAP Intelligent Returns Management solution closes the gap between retailers’ front and back offices. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1baefa14c9e60892428339451246c056fcc953f5f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1baefa14c9e60892428339451246c056fcc953f5f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1baefa14c9e60892428339451246c056fcc953f5f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Helping Consumers, Retailers, and the Environment" src="./media_1baefa14c9e60892428339451246c056fcc953f5f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="helping-consumers-retailers-and-the-environment">Helping Consumers, Retailers, and the Environment</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="give-shoppers-and-consumers-the-products-and-personalized-shopping-experiences-they-want-with-sap">Give shoppers and consumers the products and personalized shopping experiences they want with SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/retail.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Our customers face new market conditions, competition and challenges every day, so they rely on us to deliver the technology and solutions to help them survive and thrive in this dynamic and increasingly digital environment. SAP’s deep industry domain knowledge has enabled us to deliver the best and most innovative business process support for our customers for almost 50 years.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>By continuously evolving our enterprise resource planning (ERP) solutions, we are helping our customers modernize business processes and helping them adjust to a new IT reality at the same time. As <a href="/author/thomassaueressig">I’ve said before</a>, this reality combines flexibility, agility, and choice for our customers: Flexibility through a modular yet integrated approach to enterprise software, agility through business processes that can be adapted as needed, and choice for customers to operate their systems on the infrastructure of their choice. And we can certainly add the need for collaborative, networked, and sustainable solutions here.</p>
  <p>One of my favorite examples of how SAP is helping customers adapt and modernize their business processes comes from the retail sector and relates to the impact of the <a href="/covid-19">COVID-19</a> pandemic. E-commerce has surged during the pandemic as consumers faced lockdowns and sought the relative safety of online shopping. This surge in e-commerce has had dramatic implications for traditional retailers that have had to pivot quickly from primarily in-store sales to online platforms but have also had to deal with much higher levels of returns.</p>
  <p>Consumers are more likely to return something when bought online compared to offline purchases. This is particularly true in fashion retail because there is a much higher probability that a particular size doesn’t fit or the color is not quite what the consumer was expecting. Online customers also often bracket-purchase — ordering several similar items or sizes to ensure that one is the right fit and return the others.</p>
  <p>This represents a significant problem for traditional retailers that were not used to dealing with such high levels of returns and that, in the past, often outsourced the handling of returns. Returns — or reverse logistics, as the process is sometimes called — is a costly and time-consuming part of the daily life of the supply chain.</p>
  <p>Companies need to make decisions on where to return the stock, how to handle the stock when returned, and whether the customer will receive a refund or a replacement. Typically, these operations were optimized for time in order to keep customers happy, even if this meant destroying returned goods.</p>
  <p>Retailers know that the return experience can break or build customer loyalty and trust, and that’s why they aim to process returns and provide refunds to customers as quickly as possible. But destroying — and even storing — returned items is potentially bad for the environment and represents a monetary loss. According to UK’s online retail association, <a href="https://www.imrg.org/uploads/media/default/0001/09/aee8f77eb4d47ccae59293c2518ea67641e5a89d.pdf?st">69% of shoppers confirm that the quality of the returns service strongly influences the retailers where they will shop</a>.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="solve-complex-business-challenges-with-greater-ease-and-speed-using-ai-solutions-from-sap">Solve complex business challenges with greater ease and speed using AI solutions from SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Recognizing these problems, SAP has developed an innovative solution that we call <strong>SAP Intelligent Returns Management</strong>, a returns optimization solution that guides products from customers’ hands to the final dispositioning steps, maximizing both the customer experience and company margins. It uses routing and dispositioning decisions driven by artificial intelligence (AI) to maximize our customers’ sales and profits.</p>
  <p>SAP Intelligent Returns Management benefits consumers, retailers, and other stakeholders — and it helps customers operate more sustainably. Consumers benefit because we help our customers make the returns process easy, and that delivers the intended consumer experience. Our retail customers know that brand loyalty is fragile and can be lost quickly if a returns process is anything but straightforward and smooth. They need to optimize their return process to be efficient and ensure a great customer experience. When goods arrive at their return centers, retailers want to be able to make fast decisions about what to do with them: Should they dispose of the goods? Should they do a quality check and re-certify them for sale, or send them to an agent such as outlet or reseller?</p>
  <p>Our solution intelligently recommends return options for consumers optimizing for both the customer experience and the retailer and recommends disposition decisions for warehouse teams to limit value leakage. But it also provides business leaders with newfound visibility into the end-to-end returns process, enabling them to make data-based decisions.</p>
  <p>Particularly, retailers can use the embedded analytics to understand what is selling and what is not. Does a particular item always come back because it does not meet expectations in terms of size or look? Is a particular color not selling or is a style out of fashion? Whatever the reason, they can inform the design team and stem a problem at the source by not offering products that do not meet expectations, and thereby be more sustainable.</p>
  <p>SAP has offered a returns solution in the past, but it was a back-end, logistics solution. Now, with SAP Intelligent Returns Management sitting at the intersection of cloud ERP and SAP’s industry cloud, we have closed the gap between front office and back office. That’s the biggest advantage our solutions bring to fashion retailers and the like.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Thomas Saueressig is a member of the Executive Board of SAP SE for SAP Product Engineering.</em><br><em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/pulse/helping-consumers-retailers-environment-thomas-saueressig/">This story was originally published on LinkedIn</a>.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/blog/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/blog/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/blog/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/blog/article-read-more</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/executive-blog</category>
            <category>news-tag/chasing-zero</category>
            <category>industry/consumer-goods-cpg</category>
            <category>news-tag/economics</category>
            <category>news-tag/enterprise-resource-planning</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
            <category>product/sap-intelligent-returns-management</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>