<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/product-support/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pushing the Boundaries of Procurement Customer Support with Innovations]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/procurement-customer-support-innovations</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/procurement-customer-support-innovations</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In this interview, SAP's Rohan Patel gives insight into how SAP support can benefit procurement customers. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1560e17ebf571c1cad896fad5b3fe9c897622bb2c.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1560e17ebf571c1cad896fad5b3fe9c897622bb2c.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1560e17ebf571c1cad896fad5b3fe9c897622bb2c.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Pushing the Boundaries of Procurement Customer Support with Innovations" src="./media_1560e17ebf571c1cad896fad5b3fe9c897622bb2c.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="pushing-the-boundaries-of-procurement-customer-support-with-innovations">Pushing the Boundaries of Procurement Customer Support with Innovations</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>In today’s environment, customers are reevaluating how they use and source software solutions to run their business. The move from on-premise only solutions to the cloud is SAP’s reality as a cloud vendor.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“Customers undergo a cloud transformation because they want to accelerate their time to realize business value and they want to take advantage of innovations faster,” says Rohan Patel, global vice president, Customer Support and Innovation, Product Support – Procurement, SAP. “That’s what helps them maintain a competitive edge. And they want to do this while decreasing overall cost and minimizing risk.”</p>
  <p>This is where <a href="https://support.sap.com/en/offerings-programs/strategy.html">Real-Time Support</a> from SAP can add real value. In this conversation, Patel gives insight into how SAP support can benefit procurement customers.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Q: How are you supporting procurement customers on their journey to the cloud?</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><strong>A:</strong> Support in the old, on-premise world is what I like to call ‘break-fix’ support. When something failed, the IT department submitted a ticket for support, the problem was fixed, and communication ended until another issue arose. Being a break-fix support provider doesn’t work in the cloud environment. Support requires speed and foresight. Support today identifies problems and optimizes products before customers even notice something’s not working as it should.</p>
  <p>SAP’s strategy is predictive and proactive. We want continuous dialogue with customers to provide insights and guidance that are a value-add so we’re there long before something breaks. Success in the cloud requires adoption outside of the traditional IT environment. Business end users and lines of business, like procurement, supply chain, and HR, expect easy-to-use support portals that are intuitive and quickly anticipate user needs.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-creates-support-programs-to-drive-an-innovative-and-consistent-experience">SAP creates support programs to drive an innovative and consistent experience</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://support.sap.com/en/offerings-programs/strategy.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Can you share some examples of how SAP is using data to enhance predictive support?</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The tools we use not only help us deliver a great experience to our customers, they also continue to improve the SAP solution itself. Consider the cloud health monitoring tools within <a href="https://support.sap.com/en/alm/sap-cloud-alm.html">SAP Cloud ALM</a>, our application lifecycle management solution that helps streamline the way our customers implement and operate their cloud and hybrid environments across the entire business.</p>
  <p>These tools can analyze what’s happening at the customer experience layer – for example, how long it takes a specific page to load, how long a user needs to complete a task, and any delays that could frustrate users, hinder adoption, and slow business outcomes. We act proactively at the engineering and cloud operations layer to help continuously improve that user experience.</p>
  <p>We also use knowledge and data to improve the support experience, such as with <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-network.html">SAP Business Network</a>, which has millions of active trading partners. This business-to-business network of companies connecting, transacting, and partnering with numerous shared processes and information expands the SAP footprint well beyond the four walls of traditional operations.</p>
  <p>Equally important is that our consumers today aren’t just IT support users, but rather work in departments throughout the clients’ operations. We’ve taken steps to help meet the needs of all those different user types. We can provide quick, easy-to-understand guidance and answers to their questions using intuitive, personalized, and real-time channels driven by both humans and artificial intelligence (AI). This recommendation engine can provide guided answers based on who the users are, what they’re doing in the application, or what questions they ask. Users can quickly get useful and relevant content for answering their questions. The data from those guided-answer experiences is then fed into the product road map to help make the entire user experience more optimal and eliminate problems before they happen.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>What have procurement customers seen in 2023 from SAP support?</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Our procurement coverage in 2023 hits two themes: harmonization and Real-Time Support. Let me begin with the harmonization perspective. We’re taking significant steps to create a customer support experience that’s consistent across all SAP solutions – most notably a single entry point to SAP support with <a href="https://me.sap.com/">SAP for Me</a>. SAP Fieldglass solutions went live on SAP for Me case management in March 2023, and SAP Ariba solutions and SAP Business Network will soon follow. The SAP for Me portal can give users the information and answers they need, specific to the solution they’re using. Earlier this year, procurement support went live on <a href="https://community.sap.com/">SAP Community</a>, where our business and IT users can access blog posts, tips, and connect with experts. Even customers and partners can provide an additional layer of insights and guidance, especially to a specific industry.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-real-time-support">Learn more about Real-Time Support</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://support.sap.com/en/offerings-programs/strategy.html">Explore now</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>This year we have been working to bring our Real-Time Support concept to reality for procurement. When I talk about Real-Time Support, I mean support that is always on, continuously evolves, and adapts to customer needs. This can be direct access to support experts for business-critical processes when and where customers need it. It’s the live support channels such as <a href="https://support.sap.com/en/my-support/product-support.html?anchorId=section_519294480">Expert Chat</a>, Ask an Expert Peer, context-sensitive help, <a href="https://support.sap.com/en/my-support/product-support.html?anchorId=section_1255553798">support built into our software</a>, and <a href="/2022/05/artificial-intelligence-future-of-customer-support-experiences">AI-driven self-service access</a> to a vast knowledge base and user community.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>What do you see in the future of support for procurement?</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>I envision a day when customers don’t need to see or hear from us because we’re already working behind the scenes to give our customers a seamless, reliable, and delightful experience. The ultimate vision is preventative support with the help of AI and machine learning – in other words, self-healing IT systems.</p>
  <p>Of course, there will always be times when customers need us. In those times, SAP is prepared to offer as simple of a support experience as possible, such as with <a href="https://support.sap.com/en/my-support/product-support.html?anchorId=section_1255553798">Built-In Support</a> and direct access to experts or a quick call to solve an issue the moment it occurs. We also continuously look to disrupt ourselves by using new technologies such as ChatGPT to enable self-help or self-guidance and provide the best possible customer experience.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>What sets the SAP support experience apart in the industry?</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP mindfully takes steps that help give customers the best support experience possible. We can provide a cohesive array of support channels, self-service tools, and cloud health and integration monitoring. Even with these successes in hand, SAP will continuously push the boundaries of customer support with new innovations, help ensure support interactions are delightful, and offer Real-Time Support that can bring ambition to life.</p>
  <p>Follow Rohan Patel on <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/rohan-patel-1897941/">LinkedIn</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Regina Postman is part of Customer Support and Innovation Communications at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="follow-sap-news-on-linkedin">Follow SAP News on LinkedIn</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news">Connect with us</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/product-support</category>
            <category>news-tag/real-time-support</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fieldglass</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-for-me</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Meeting the Customer in Real Time: Support Whenever They Need It]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/customer-experience-real-time-support</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/customer-experience-real-time-support</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP's Bente Vollan describes the support experience SAP customers can expect with Real-Time Support. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/product-support</category>
            <category>news-tag/real-time-support</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-for-me</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Real-Time Support Channels Take Big Steps Forward in Customer Care]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/real-time-support-big-steps-forward-customer-care</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/real-time-support-big-steps-forward-customer-care</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With Real-Time Support, SAP is moving towards a bidirectional, predictive, and effortless support future. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/built-in-support</category>
            <category>news-tag/expert-chat</category>
            <category>news-tag/product-support</category>
            <category>news-tag/real-time-support</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-for-me</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-support-portal</category>
            <category>news-tag/schedule-a-manager</category>
            <category>news-tag/schedule-an-expert</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enabling a Cloud Mindset Across Barriers Can Revolutionize a Company]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/01/cloud-mindset-revolutionize-a-company</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/01/cloud-mindset-revolutionize-a-company</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Jinan Chaoyixing Catering achieved remarkable results from engaging with Product Support at SAP to make the most of its SAP solutions.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15e2e1c3b07e20b17451f7e237be7ae70c83c6977.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15e2e1c3b07e20b17451f7e237be7ae70c83c6977.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_15e2e1c3b07e20b17451f7e237be7ae70c83c6977.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Enabling a Cloud Mindset Across Barriers Can Revolutionize a Company" src="./media_15e2e1c3b07e20b17451f7e237be7ae70c83c6977.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="enabling-a-cloud-mindset-across-barriers-can-revolutionize-a-company">Enabling a Cloud Mindset Across Barriers Can Revolutionize a Company</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="choose-the-right-next-generation-support-tool-for-your-sap-solutions">Choose the right Next-Generation Support tool for your SAP solutions</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://support.sap.com/en/offerings-programs/strategy.html#section_277629229">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>The Product Support team at SAP provides a wealth of innovative opportunities that allow customers to understand how to make the most of the SAP solutions they are implementing and using. This was on display during a recent engagement with a large and successful catering company in China, Jinan Chaoyixing Catering.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The company, which employs more than 8,000 employees in Jinan – the capital of Shandong province in eastern China – was eager to implement <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/s4hana-erp.html">SAP S/4HANA Cloud</a> to grow into an intelligent catering company able to operate internationally and proudly represent Shandong food culture. However, after going live with SAP S/4HANA Cloud in 2020, and the subsequent exit of its implementation partner from the scene, the business users in China found it difficult to keep up with the quarterly upgrade cycle of the software and began facing issues in areas including finance, sales, and procurement.</p>
  <p>After an on-site visit and extensive conversations between the company and SAP Services and Support, Development, and Customer Engagement &#x26; Experience, close to 30 issues were investigated across all lines of business. It was a huge undertaking. Eventually, a whopping 500 stores were able to benefit from the business process optimization. Here’s a closer look at how the customer was able to achieve such remarkable outcomes.</p>
  <p>It all started with the Development and Support Succeed Together program, sponsored by <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/innovation/labs.html">SAP Labs China</a>, which connects product support and development to deliver customer success and maximize business potential. In this case, the SAP S/4HANA Cloud Product Support team and the SAP S/4HANA Development team in China worked together to get Jinan Chaoyixing Catering the experience and results it needed by arranging a customer site visit.</p>
  <p>By bringing together different perspectives and areas of expertise, the team was able to make great strides during the visit and to arrange several follow-ups to resolve the issues identified on-site. For example, Jinan Chaoyixing Catering’s sales bill of material (BOM) data was stored in an external data system, which could lead to incorrect financial reports due to a missing payment method or other issues. There were many conversations about the difficulty of getting the required information into the financial reports.</p>
  <p>Eventually, the team realized that the external BOM system was the root cause for many of the challenges discussed. The SAP team proposed a dedicated best practices knowledge kit to maintain the sales BOM in SAP S/4HANA Cloud, eliminating this difficulty. Jinan Chaoyixing Catering was excited about the prospect of this best practice and is now exploring how to implement this new best practice scope – one of five best practice scope items introduced for a better system solution adoption, including expanding their business processes to include cost analysis, stock transfer order returns, and sales returns. Both the operating centers and business users were able to benefit from the business process optimization and issue resolution.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-what-product-support-at-sap-has-to-offer">Learn more about what Product Support at SAP has to offer</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://support.sap.com/en/my-support/product-support.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“Through Next-Generation Support we learned a lot about SAP Services and Support offerings, like how to report an incident in an efficient way and how to leverage SAP Help Portal and SAP Community, the real-time channels and advanced tools,” said Donglin Lai, CIO of Jinan Chaoyixing Catering. “The support and development team also gave us a comprehensive introduction to SAP Sales Pipeline Analysis, which brings remarkable value to our operational analysis.”</p>
  <p>In addition to the real business value the customer experienced, its understanding of and appreciation for SAP Services and Support was hugely enhanced. Now that they have been armed with a cloud mindset, the company’s business users are enabled to look for efficient solutions in the future, to imagine what’s possible with SAP S/4HANA Cloud, and to think of new areas of the business that could be positively impacted in the future.</p>
  <p>The future is very much on this customer’s mind. Already, Jinan Chaoyixing Catering is exploring sales and cost analytics to build transparent and timely reporting dashboards and working on merging the financial reporting needs of 15 regional centers. Perhaps most exciting of all, a new, fully automated factory will go live in 2022 and a new supplying company will be established to move the company towards a shared food processing center and other services.</p>
  <p>By engaging deeply with this client, <a href="/topics/support">SAP Services and Support</a> was able not only to solve its immediate issues and create systems for solving other issues in the future, but also to create a meaningful connection with business users to understand their needs, challenges, and ambitions. By adopting a cloud mindset, Jinan Chaoyixing Catering was able to leverage the full potential of SAP S/4HANA Cloud to be prepared to move seamlessly into a digital successful future.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Mohammed Ajouz is senior vice president and global head of Product Support at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/product-support</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-community</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-help-portal</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Automatic Translation: Breaking Down Language Barriers in Technical Support]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/automatic-translation-breaking-down-language-barriers-in-technical-support</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/automatic-translation-breaking-down-language-barriers-in-technical-support</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 11 Oct 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Access to automatic translation enables a support experience that is more accessible, intuitive, and productive for SAP customers worldwide.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/expert-chat</category>
            <category>news-tag/product-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How to Engage with SAP Using Product Support Accreditation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/product-support-accreditation-engage-with-sap</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/product-support-accreditation-engage-with-sap</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The Product Support Accreditation program lead explains how it changes the customer support experience, key benefits, and how to get started.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1130f48f1d4721d82a13f343c0d168b341ecfdc97.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1130f48f1d4721d82a13f343c0d168b341ecfdc97.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1130f48f1d4721d82a13f343c0d168b341ecfdc97.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="How to Engage with SAP Using Product Support Accreditation" src="./media_1130f48f1d4721d82a13f343c0d168b341ecfdc97.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="how-to-engage-with-sap-using-product-support-accreditation">How to Engage with SAP Using Product Support Accreditation</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>The Product Support Accreditation program is designed for SAP users who want to explore the benefits of tools and features from Next-Generation Support and learn how to easily engage with Product Support as well as how to achieve faster, easier closure to technical issues or incidents.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The self-service enablement course takes a little more than one hour to complete and can be accessed by any SAP customer with an S-user.</p>
  <p>Since its 2020 launch, the program has already attracted many customers and partners and has increased its learning content along new launches or extended functionalities and features. Customers and partners may even integrate this program as part of their own enablement trainings.</p>
  <p>How does Product Support Accreditation change the customer support experience, what are the key benefits, and what are the steps to get started? I sat down with Gagandeep Kaur, program lead for the Product Support Accreditation program at SAP, and she shared her experiences on how to best get started, along with insight into new offerings from the program in 2021, and how SAP customers and partners perceive the program.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="keep-your-system-running-at-peak-performance-with-services-and-support-from-sap">Keep your system running at peak performance with services and support from SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/support.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="q-the-product-support-accreditation-program-was-first-launched-in-early-2020-can-you-briefly-describe-what-the-program-is-and-who-benefits-from-it">Q: The Product Support Accreditation program was first launched in early 2020. Can you briefly describe what the program is and who benefits from it?</h3>
  <p><strong>A:</strong> In Product Support we have a variety of great tools to help customers solve their technical issues more efficiently. Live support channels like Expert Chat and Schedule an Expert, the peer-to-peer platform Ask an Expert Peer, or guided help through “support assistant” are well received by users. However, not every user is fully aware of those tools or may not know how to get started. With our Product Support Accreditation program, we wanted to create an easy-to-use, easy-to-consume enablement program that any SAP S-user can access and enroll in at no additional cost.</p>
  <p>Every S-user can benefit from this program at very little effort and at their convenience.</p>
  <h3 id="how-does-it-work-for-an-s-user-who-would-like-to-take-advantage-of-the-program">How does it work for an S-user who would like to take advantage of the program?</h3>
  <p>Very easily! Your <strong>first step</strong> would be to enroll in the program. You can, for example, access the program directly from SAP Support Portal with your S-user and enroll immediately.</p>
  <p>The <strong>second step</strong> would be to make yourself familiar with the learning modules available. You can click through the individual modules and decide in which order you want to start. Let’s say you are interested in using Expert Chat. You could start with the related module and, even if you have not yet completed the learning program, you already know how to make the best use of Expert Chat.</p>
  <p>The <strong>third step</strong> would be to complete all the modules so that you are entitled to get your certificate and badge, which documents the successful completion of all learning modules. If you don’t want to complete them all on the same day, you can stop and continue with a module at your convenience.</p>
  <p>The <strong>fourth step</strong> would be to receive your certificate and badge, which are free to share with your colleagues and peers and even through social media.</p>
  <p>Finally, the <strong>fifth step</strong> would already be the renewal of the program. You can register to receive a reminder e-mail at the beginning each calendar year to consider renewing your accreditation. The renewal is not just repeating the known modules, you will discover new learnings around new tools or improved functionalities.</p>
  <p>That closes the loop and you are up to date around all the helpful tools and features from Next-Generation Support.</p>
  <h3 id="this-sounds-like-an-easy-to-access-and-easy-to-consume-enablement-for-users-who-want-to-make-the-best-out-of-their-engagement-with-sap-do-updates-only-occur-annually-or-will-there-be-updates-throughout-the-year-as-well">This sounds like an easy-to-access and easy-to-consume enablement for users who want to make the best out of their engagement with SAP. Do updates only occur annually or will there be updates throughout the year as well?</h3>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="explore-more-product-support-from-sap">Explore more product support from SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://support.sap.com/en/my-support/product-support.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>I personally value the opportunity to frequently explore the program for new learnings since my last visit. My recommendation to customers is to make use of the annual renewal program so that they get an update at least once a year on improvements or enhancements. Beyond this, they can decide individually if they want to check for any updates over the year. If there is a big change during the year then we might provide a mid-year update and inform program members about the new content available.</p>
  <h3 id="for-updates-during-the-year-and-an-annual-renewal-of-the-accreditation-with-a-renewal-of-the-certificate-and-badge-how-would-these-work-in-regards-to-the-modules-users-take-is-there-a-track-history-or-would-i-have-to-repeat-all-modules-even-without-changes">For updates during the year and an annual renewal of the accreditation with a renewal of the certificate and badge, how would these work in regards to the modules users take? Is there a track history, or would I have to repeat all modules, even without changes?</h3>
  <p>When new content is added to the program you will only be going through the new or updated content in the program. Progress is tracked within your profile. You can of course choose to refresh your memory by watching all the videos, but you won’t need to. You would need to do the final quiz at the end to get the new badge.</p>
  <h3 id="how-about-the-future-of-this-program-can-you-share-what-is-planned-next">How about the future of this program? Can you share what is planned next?</h3>
  <p>The goal of the program is to keep it simple and easy to use. This will remain our focus in the future too. However, we also want to keep growing the learning content along the launches and improved features.</p>
  <p>We will keep growing awareness around the program and to engage even more customers and partners, thus keep growing the community around Product Support Accreditation.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/product-support</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>