<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/industry/insurance/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Insurers Build Success by Digitalizing Vendor Performance Management]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/insurers-digitalizing-vendor-performance-management</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/insurers-digitalizing-vendor-performance-management</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A comprehensive vendor management program, supported by digital technology, can help insurers get value from each supplier.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/insurance</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-for-insurance</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[To Improve Business Results, Insurers Must Modernize External Workforce Management]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/insurers-modernize-external-workforce-management</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/insurers-modernize-external-workforce-management</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The external workforce is a key lever in enabling business performance. Learn why insurers must prioritize external workforce management.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/contingent-workforce-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/external-workforce-management</category>
            <category>industry/insurance</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-for-insurance</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Join Us at the SAP and SAP Fioneer Financial Services Forum]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/06/join-us-sap-and-sap-fioneer-financial-services-forum</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/06/join-us-sap-and-sap-fioneer-financial-services-forum</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The SAP and SAP Fioneer Financial Services Forum brings together the best minds in the finance, banking, and insurance worlds. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/banking</category>
            <category>news-tag/financial-services</category>
            <category>industry/insurance</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fioneer</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Insurance Sessions at SAP Sapphire in 2022]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/04/insurance-sessions-at-sap-sapphire-in-2022</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/04/insurance-sessions-at-sap-sapphire-in-2022</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[insurance sessions at SAP Sapphire will include presentations by industry thought leaders. Get a sampling of some of anticipated sessions.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/insurance</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Insurance Leaders Are Enhancing Agent Experiences for Better Business Outcomes]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/03/insurance-enhancing-agent-experiences</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/03/insurance-enhancing-agent-experiences</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn how the SAP Agent Performance Management solution has helped real businesses better manage agents across the entire agent life cycle.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>industry/insurance</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Why Sustainability Matters for the Insurance Industry]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/02/sustainability-matters-for-insurance-industry</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/02/sustainability-matters-for-insurance-industry</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Stakeholders are pushing for change and demanding accountability when it comes to sustainability and the insurance industry is no exception.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1dc6d64c882367e21343a780f02c2a28f002e2db8.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1dc6d64c882367e21343a780f02c2a28f002e2db8.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1dc6d64c882367e21343a780f02c2a28f002e2db8.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Why Sustainability Matters for the Insurance Industry" src="./media_1dc6d64c882367e21343a780f02c2a28f002e2db8.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="why-sustainability-matters-for-the-insurance-industry">Why Sustainability Matters for the Insurance Industry</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Should the price for an auto insurance policy differ if the vehicle is a conventional gas or diesel engine versus an electric car? What about insurance investor fund allocation – how should companies determine the proportion of green investments within a portfolio? These are just two of the many questions insurers are facing as they grapple with a global shift towards more sustainable business models.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Whether it’s from consumer activism, tighter government regulations, or the need for improved operational resiliency in the face of climate change, companies are taking major strides towards sustainable business models. As <a href="https://www.ey.com/en_us/strategy/why-sustainability-has-become-a-corporate-imperative">EY reports</a>, incorporating sustainability into core business strategies is about more than “doing good” – it’s a smart business strategy. Capital markets are evaluating performance against environmental, social, and governance (ESG) criteria in investment decisions. Companies that fail to consider ESG criteria are at a disadvantage. In fact, <a href="https://www.ey.com/en_us/strategy/why-sustainability-has-become-a-corporate-imperative">90% of global investors</a> will revise their investments if companies do not consider ESG criteria within their business model.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="automate-processes-and-minimize-risk-in-investment-accounting-and-administration-with-sap">Automate processes and minimize risk in investment accounting and administration with SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/10/869aa600-007e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="sustainability-trends-in-the-insurance-industry">Sustainability Trends in the Insurance Industry</h2>
  <p>The United Nations Environment Programme Finance Initiative (UNEP FI) has been launched as a partnership between UNEP and the global financial sector to mobilize private sector finance for sustainable development. UNEP FI works with more than 450 banks, insurers, and investors and over 100 supporting institutions to help create a financial sector that serves people and the planet while delivering positive impacts.</p>
  <p>Regulators are also requiring <a href="/topics/sustainability">sustainability</a> reporting from insurers, and they expect financial flows will be adjusted towards ESG criteria, in accordance with the 2015 Paris Climate Conference. The EU Taxonomy Regulation will require most European financial institutions to outline the environmental sustainability of their economic activities. But the <a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/insurance.html?pdf-asset=b400d5e7-707c-0010-82c7-eda71af511fa&#x26;page=12">shift towards sustainability</a> is not just about ESG criteria, although that’s certainly an important factor. Risks associated with climate change, such as more extreme weather, are also top of mind for insurers.</p>
  <p>Global natural disaster insured losses, the amount insurers are forecast to pay out, is estimated to be as high as US$42 billion for the first half of 2021, according to a <a href="https://www.theguardian.com/business/2021/jul/21/2021s-extreme-weather-leads-to-insurers-biggest-payout-in-10-years">report from the insurer Aon</a>. From the Texas polar vortex to the Canadian heat wave to the extreme flooding in Germany, extreme weather events are costing insurers more than ever – and these climate-related risks are only expected to increase. More than half of U.S. regulators indicate that climate change is likely to have a “high impact or an extremely high impact” on coverage availability and underwriting assumptions, according to the “Insurance Regulator State of Climate Risks Survey” conducted by the <a href="https://www2.deloitte.com/us/en/pages/financial-services/articles/insurance-companies-climate-change-risk.html">Deloitte Center for Financial Services</a>.</p>
  <p>Gone are the days when sustainability was a footnote on an insurance company’s annual report. Today, stakeholders are pushing for change and demanding accountability. Customer preference is driving a shift towards more sustainable products and services. A variety of carrier options in a competitive marketplace means that customers are comfortable walking away from companies that don’t follow sustainable practices. Millennials and Gen Z ­are <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/gregpetro/2021/04/30/gen-z-is-emerging-as-the-sustainability-generation/?sh=676404728699">the most likely to make purchasing decisions based on values and principles</a>. This is the same group insurers are competing to earn loyalty from to build long-term customer relationships.</p>
  <p>The same goes for hiring top talent. In a tight talent market, professionals can afford to be selective about where they work and increasingly opt for companies that align with their values. Improving ESG performance is key to attracting and retaining Millennial and Gen Z employees.</p>
  <h2 id="linking-sustainability-with-business-activity-for-environmental-social-and-economic-impact">Linking Sustainability with Business Activity for Environmental, Social, and Economic Impact</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-how-you-can-become-a-sustainable-intelligent-enterprise">Learn how you can become a sustainable, intelligent enterprise</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/sustainability.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Enterprise solutions from SAP deliver company-wide functionality and industry-specific features designed to help businesses achieve sustainability at scale. <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/sustainability.html">These solutions include</a>:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Climate change solutions:</strong> Lower a business’s environmental impact by minimizing the carbon footprint associated with products and operations.</li>
    <li><strong>Sustainability and ESG reporting solutions:</strong> Connect environmental, social, and financial data holistically to steer businesses toward smarter decision-making.</li>
    <li><strong>Circular economy solutions:</strong> Move to circular processes across a business’s entire supply and value chain.</li>
    <li><strong>Social responsibility solutions:</strong> Enable equality and social equity across a business’s entire workforce and network.</li>
  </ul>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div><a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/insurance.html">Learn more about how SAP can help your organization move towards sustainable solutions that meet the insurance industry’s most pressing needs.</a></div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>Toni Tomic is global head of Insurance at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/insurance</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-for-insurance</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Optimizing Profitability and Finance Practices in a Fast-Changing Insurance Environment]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/01/optimizing-profitability-and-finance-practices-in-insurance-environment</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/01/optimizing-profitability-and-finance-practices-in-insurance-environment</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Insurance organizations and their finance teams need specific tools and capabilities to meet today’s risk and sustainability challenges.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1abb512bbe22bf3c6eb98d112657b83a1a5604e9e.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1abb512bbe22bf3c6eb98d112657b83a1a5604e9e.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1abb512bbe22bf3c6eb98d112657b83a1a5604e9e.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Optimizing Profitability and Finance Practices in a Fast-Changing Insurance Environment" src="./media_1abb512bbe22bf3c6eb98d112657b83a1a5604e9e.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="optimizing-profitability-and-finance-practices-in-a-fast-changing-insurance-environment">Optimizing Profitability and Finance Practices in a Fast-Changing Insurance Environment</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>As insurers make the transition to more sustainable finance and investment practices, empowering insurance finance teams with the tools they need to make better decisions while minimizing risk has never been more urgent.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Yet even as the volume of data grows exponentially across the insurance industry, turning that data into actionable insight remains a challenge. And meeting complex local and international regulations that change constantly still requires a lot of time and effort from insurance finance teams, which further reduces agility and timely insight.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="pursue-new-digital-business-models-with-sap-for-insurance-solutions">Pursue new digital business models with SAP for Insurance solutions</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/insurance.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="improving-insurance-finance-insight-and-process-efficiency">Improving Insurance Finance Insight and Process Efficiency</h2>
  <p>Insurers and their finance teams need specific tools and capabilities to meet today’s risk and sustainability challenges. They need more powerful simulation tools that can help them optimize revenue and cost management across every line of business, channel, policy, and transaction. Finance teams also need to leverage intelligent automation that reduces the cost and effort to complete financial reporting, auditing, and compliance tasks across asset and investment portfolios.</p>
  <h2 id="sap-for-insurance-solutions-can-help">SAP for Insurance Solutions Can Help</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="how-sap-and-northern-trust-meet-the-challenges-of-financial-asset-management-in-the-insurance-industry">How SAP and Northern Trust Meet the Challenges of Financial Asset Management in the Insurance Industry</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/05/sap-and-northern-trust-financial-asset-management">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>By bringing together data across your SAP and third-party system landscape, the <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/08/e4772682-f57d-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">SAP Profitability and Performance Management</a> application empowers teams across your insurance organization to make decisions that can improve profitability, reduce costs, and fully align with core sustainability goals. The application’s scalable, high-speed finance and risk calculation engine combines machine learning with predictive and stochastic financial analysis to deliver powerful simulation capabilities – enabling your people to get more insight out of the information they already have.</p>
  <p>And if you want to bring intelligent automation to your investment practices, subledger accounting, and statutory reporting, the <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/10/869aa600-007e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">SAP Financial Asset Management</a> application can deliver value. It works alongside <a href="/topics/sap-s4hana-2">SAP S/4HANA</a> as well as the SAP ERP application to help take days off closings with automated processes such as calculation of amortization, impairments, and unrealized gains and losses. The application also can streamline compliance reporting with preconfigured content for fast-changing local and international regulations.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong>Want more information? Download our information sheets:</strong></p>
        <p><a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/08/e4772682-f57d-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Empower Your Insurance Employees to Make Profitable and Sustainable Decisions</a><br><a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/10/869aa600-007e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Automate Processes and Minimize Risk in Investment Accounting and Administration</a></p>
        <p><em>Anders Widestrand is senior director, FSI ISV Program and Co-Innovation, Financial Services Ecosystem, at SAP.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/financial-services</category>
            <category>industry/insurance</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-for-insurance</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How SAP and Northern Trust Meet the Challenges of Financial Asset Management in the Insurance Industry]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/05/sap-and-northern-trust-financial-asset-management</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/05/sap-and-northern-trust-financial-asset-management</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Together, SAP and Northern Trust offer advantages to insurers, including helping to ensure compliance with statuary reporting and accounting.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1507f8bf1f49a12a81d5acac32544c7a30d1996cf.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1507f8bf1f49a12a81d5acac32544c7a30d1996cf.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1507f8bf1f49a12a81d5acac32544c7a30d1996cf.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="How SAP and Northern Trust Meet the Challenges of Financial Asset Management in the Insurance Industry" src="./media_1507f8bf1f49a12a81d5acac32544c7a30d1996cf.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="how-sap-and-northern-trust-meet-the-challenges-of-financial-asset-management-in-the-insurance-industry">How SAP and Northern Trust Meet the Challenges of Financial Asset Management in the Insurance Industry</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Over the last decade, <a href="https://insights.sap.com/what-is-digital-transformation/">digital transformation</a> has empowered companies to create new business models, control costs, maintain compliance, and enhance customer loyalty. <a href="/covid-19">COVID-19</a> has accelerated this digital transformation journey, forcing companies to ask themselves, “Are our digital initiatives effective and have they been the right ones?”</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>For Northern Trust, the answer to this question is a resounding “yes,” thanks in part to the strong relationship the company has built with SAP to deliver innovative, scalable systems and business-driven content and services.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="pursue-new-digital-business-models-and-improve-and-protect-your-customers-with-insurance-solutions-from-sap">Pursue new digital business models and improve and protect your customers with insurance solutions from SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/insurance.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="northern-trust-market-leading-approach-to-financial-asset-solutions-for-insurance-companies">Northern Trust: Market-Leading Approach to Financial Asset Solutions for Insurance Companies</h2>
  <p>Named the “Best Custodian” by Private Equity Wire in 2020, Northern Trust serves more than 180 insurance clients worldwide with more than US$1 trillion in assets. The company has been providing financial management solutions to insurance companies for more than 90 years.</p>
  <p>Seven years ago, Northern Trust identified the need for an outsourced investment accounting solution in the marketplace that was robust, scalable, and flexible. In the current low interest environment, insurance companies have had to be creative in how they trade and what they trade. Real-time insight across the entire portfolio is critical to business success. Yet Northern Trust’s clients were struggling to have all their assets on a single platform and instead relied on a patchwork of disparate solutions. Others were going through the process of bringing their derivatives in to see a consolidated view of their true holdings and were struggling to understand their accounting.</p>
  <p>Northern Trust sought a cloud-based, agnostic platform that would allow clients to customize their ledgers, support every type of trading option, allow management of all asset classes from privates to derivatives, and accurately represent their position. The right digital solution would need to solve the challenges caused by extracting accounting data, working with data across the globe, and integrating multiple data platforms – all while providing data in real-time.</p>
  <p>SAP Financial Asset Management works to meet these needs and more, providing a one-of-a-kind investment accounting and analytics services application that marries technology and service. Northern Trust considers the application to be the ironclad calculation engine for everything that happens for its clients’ portfolios. By adding the cloud-based engine for investment accounting and analytics, this gives Northern Trust’s clients the ability to truly “interrogate their data” rather than cobbling together Excel files and PDF files.</p>
  <h2 id="sap-and-northern-trust-innovation-for-insurance-accounting-and-analytics">SAP and Northern Trust: Innovation for Insurance Accounting and Analytics</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="listen-to-the-podcast-on-opensap">Listen to the podcast on openSAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://podcast.opensap.info/industry-insights/2021/04/23/episode-38-sap-and-northern-trust-assurance-in-the-insurance-industry/?campaigncode=CRM-IM21-INS-FITRANS&#x26;source=onlinedisplay-glb-Insurance-ntfam">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Northern Trust started as an SAP customer, operating SAP Financial Asset Management for more than five years before expanding the relationship to help innovate its current business model. Together, the companies work to provide both the market-leading investment accounting platform and robust services. SAP provides the sustainable, scalable application; Northern Trust’s Investment Accounting &#x26; Analytics Service operates on top of SAP Financial Asset Management, providing functional, business-driven content and services to joint customers. It’s a unique relationship that enables exceptional solutions and services to benefit customers that otherwise would not be possible.</p>
  <p>Working together, SAP and Northern Trust offer numerous advantages to insurers, including helping to ensure compliance with statuary reporting for all 50 states and accounting for several bases in parallel, such as US-GAAP and IFRS. The two companies also work to unburden insurers from having to maintain institutional investment management expertise in-house. With Northern Trust’s leadership, insurers can be confident they’re current on rapidly evolving best practices.</p>
  <h2 id="podcast-learn-whats-next-from-the-experts">Podcast: Learn What’s Next from the Experts</h2>
  <p>By 2025, many insurers will be engaging with cross-industry ecosystem providers and defining opportunities beyond managing risk. Solutions like SAP and Northern Trust’s platform and services are essential to help insurers with automation and real-time data insights to embrace the future.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>Learn more on SAP’s <a href="https://podcast.opensap.info/industry-insights/2021/04/23/episode-38-sap-and-northern-trust-assurance-in-the-insurance-industry/">“Industry Insights” podcast</a>,<br>where Josephine Monberg interviews Toni Tomic and<br>Chris Dvorak, head of Insurance Solutions at Northern Trust,<br>on what’s next for this successful pairing.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Toni Tomic is global head of Insurance at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/financial-services</category>
            <category>industry/insurance</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Transforming Operational Excellence for Insurance]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/03/sap-cloud-for-insurance-transforming-operational-excellence</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/03/sap-cloud-for-insurance-transforming-operational-excellence</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[While lowering operating expenses is important, it is just one part of achieving holistic operational excellence. Insurers are also facing pressure from new government regulations ...]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/financial-services</category>
            <category>industry/insurance</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-for-insurance</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>