<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-topic/training/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Game On: Business Builders Prepares Future Business Leaders for a Data-Driven World]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/business-builders-sap-university-alliances</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/business-builders-sap-university-alliances</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Business Builders, built from a partnership between SAP University Alliances and HEC Montréal, is where education meets real-world needs.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-university-alliances</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Powering the AI Revolution with New Learning, Certifications, and Simplified Access to Talent]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/powering-ai-revolution-learning-certifications-talent</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/powering-ai-revolution-learning-certifications-talent</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Bring out your best with new learning opportunities, role-based SAP Certifications, and simplified access to talent. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_158ee9e4c4293f1933f13d07a2fb3eddc96c821de.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_158ee9e4c4293f1933f13d07a2fb3eddc96c821de.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_158ee9e4c4293f1933f13d07a2fb3eddc96c821de.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Powering the AI Revolution with New Learning, Certifications, and Simplified Access to Talent" src="./media_158ee9e4c4293f1933f13d07a2fb3eddc96c821de.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="powering-the-ai-revolution-with-new-learning-certifications-and-simplified-access-to-talent">Powering the AI Revolution with New Learning, Certifications, and Simplified Access to Talent</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Artificial intelligence (AI) is currently forcing the technology industry to undergo <a href="">a paradigm shift</a>, further accelerating the upheaval in business and society. We see AI embedded in tools we have been using for years, and we see software finding its way into every aspect of competition today. Against this background, it comes as no surprise that <a href="https://www2.deloitte.com/us/en/pages/consulting/articles/state-of-ai-2022.html">94% of business leaders see AI as critical to success over the next five years</a>. However, many report the lack of resources and talent to drive competitiveness with these new tools.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="taking-business-to-the-next-level-in-the-era-of-ai">Taking Business to the Next Level in the Era of AI</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/events/sapphire/news-guide.html">Read the news guide</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>To make it easier to develop relevant skills and secure business success in such a volatile environment, <a href="/2022/11/sap-coursera-partnership-digital-skills-underrepresented-groups">we embarked on a journey to upskill millions of people worldwide</a> in search of opportunity. After launching a digital skills initiative for those underserved in tech, forging new partnerships, offering the first role-based certifications to help meet real-life business needs, and making future-focused learning resources available to all, we are now taking our efforts to an even higher level – with more free, self-paced learning and engagement opportunities, new solution demos to experience the latest innovations in SAP Business AI, cloud ERP, and SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP), among others, a full portfolio of role-based certifications and a new certification model, as well as an extended digital skills initiative.</p>
  <h2 id="more-than-250-free-online-courses-now-available-for-all">More Than 250 Free Online Courses Now Available for All</h2>
  <p>From global talent shortages and changing job profiles to the digitalization of entire economies, many organizations see the gaps between skill supply and demand grow wider and wider while searching for ways to adapt to a business landscape where advancements like AI, machine learning, and a new era of Big Data come into play. In this ever-changing atmosphere, tens of thousands of organizations have <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company.html">deployed SAP solutions</a> to support them on their path to bring out their best, leading to skyrocketing demand for SAP talent.</p>
  <p>To help meet the increasing demand, we recently launched more than 50 new free, self-paced learning journeys – many of them touching on AI features embedded in our software – bringing the total number of digital courses on the <a href="https://learning.sap.com/?url_id=text-sapnewscenter-prdteng-Sapphire">SAP Learning site</a> to more than 250. By allowing everyone with an Internet connection to quickly learn a new skill for free, keep up with the latest innovations, and prepare for an in-demand SAP Certification, more professionals can advance in the competitive technology labor market, while customers can draw on a deeper bench of skills to accelerate digital transformation.</p>
  <h2 id="launching-role-based-certifications-for-all-key-roles">Launching Role-Based Certifications for All Key Roles</h2>
  <p>As organizations need to be more adaptive and dynamic, traditional university degrees become less important and skills-based hiring is on the rise when trying to fill positions. In fact, recent reports show that up to <a href="https://www.hiringlab.org/2024/02/27/educational-requirements-job-postings/">52% of job postings</a> in the U.S. in the beginning of the year did not state an educational requirement. Instead, role-based certifications and practical experience have become more determining factors for career paths and hiring.</p>
  <p>Recognizing the advantages role-based certifications can offer both individuals and organizations, we have further enhanced our certification program to better align with real-life business needs, now offering role-based certification for all key roles, including consultants, analysts, and architects. These role-based certifications come with a clear career path for individuals. Together with a <a href="https://learning.sap.com/get-certified?url_id=text-sapnewscenter-prdteng-Sapphire">new model to get and stay certified</a> with continuous assessments, this is our way to help ensure skill sets are sharp, focused on core competencies, and more sustainable and valid for longer periods of time.</p>
  <p>With these enhancements, we believe we have now taken an important next step to support professionals and organizations in the SAP ecosystem to bring out their best with ongoing and up-to-date knowledge of the latest skills, helping to maximize the ROI of SAP software, shorten deployment times, lower costs, speed innovation, and increase employee retention and satisfaction.</p>
  <h2 id="simplified-access-to-pre-trained-sap-talent">Simplified Access to Pre-Trained SAP Talent</h2>
  <p>However, we recognize that many people considered underrepresented in tech still do not have access to future-focused educational resources and with it, fulfilling careers. Launched in late 2022, <a href="https://learning.sap.com/digital-skills?url_id=text-sapnewscenter-prdteng-Sapphire">SAP’s digital skills initiative</a> was intended to equip 10,000 people from underrepresented and underserved groups for a career in the tech industry with free, self-paced learning resources and a free certification exam attempt to obtain an in-demand SAP Certification to show their expertise. Ever since its launch, the initiative has grown – and contributed to <a href="https://community.sap.com/t5/learner-stories/bg-p/learner-stories">amazing success stories</a>.</p>
  <p>Hearing that SAP professionals like <a href="https://community.sap.com/t5/sap-learning-blog-posts/breaking-barriers-and-fighting-sexism-lin-s-journey-from-a-salesgirl-to-an/ba-p/13588835">Lin Fan, a Chinese immigrant to Germany</a>, could overcome gender bias because of our digital skills initiative, makes me proud. “[The digital skills initiative and SAP Certification] indeed opened new doors and helped me get noticed by recruiters,” Fan said. “I got several interviews from major SAP consulting firms shortly after handing in my application. In the interviews, I highlighted what I learned and expressed my confidence in accepting challenges for rolling out SAP S/4HANA. In the end, I got an offer and gladly started a junior role at a consulting firm that actively implements SAP S/4HANA projects.”</p>
  <p>While Fan’s path is inspiring, she is not the only one who turned their life around with the help of SAP. Given the expectation-exceeding demand of now more than 14,500 candidates, we are overwhelmed by the positive uptake of the initiative. One of our recent graduates, <a href="https://community.sap.com/t5/learner-stories/breaking-down-barriers-hear-from-chelcie-scott-how-she-broke-into-tech-with/ba-p/13710541">Chelcie Scott, agreed to tell her story</a> on camera and shared how intimidating the tech industry appeared to the single mother at first. Thanks to her willpower and commitment, plus a little help from the digital skills initiative, she recently got certified and hired by an SAP partner. And as organizations are still struggling to find skilled employees, we have decided to extend SAP’s digital skills initiative, bringing candidates and organizations together. With simplified access to SAP-trained talent, we are helping customers and partners to recruit talent and expand their workforce faster while also allowing for greater diversity and innovation.</p>
  <p>At SAP, we recognize the challenges and opportunities that lie ahead for customers, partners, and individual learners within and outside of the SAP ecosystem. With these enhancements, we have taken the next step to help organizations equip their existing workforce with the right tools and resources to future-proof their skill set while also paving career growth for those who do not have a seat at the table yet but can bring a fresh set of perspectives to it.</p>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1bf4a81f181aead9f58c4d25e211885b7fc5988cc.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1bf4a81f181aead9f58c4d25e211885b7fc5988cc.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1bf4a81f181aead9f58c4d25e211885b7fc5988cc.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Break Down Barriers With the Help of SAP’s Digital Skills Initiative" src="./media_1bf4a81f181aead9f58c4d25e211885b7fc5988cc.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pEsE7dicrc4&#x26;feature=youtu.be">Break Down Barriers With the Help of SAP’s Digital Skills Initiative</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Andre Bechtold is SVP and head of Solution &#x26; Innovation Experience at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-sapphire-in-2024-innovations-to-bring-out-the-best-in-your-business">SAP Sapphire in 2024: Innovations to bring out the best in your business</h3>
        <p><em><a href="/topics/sap-sapphire">Get the latest news and coverage</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills-gap</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Navigating Tax Requirements in the Digital Era: Manage Compliance with Cloud ERP]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/tax-transformation-in-the-digital-era-course</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/tax-transformation-in-the-digital-era-course</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[To help tax professionals prepare for and become valuable members of tax transformation projects, SAP is introducing a new course.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_12d216e0addd5a9233a73cb4294d58a8906d2b314.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_12d216e0addd5a9233a73cb4294d58a8906d2b314.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_12d216e0addd5a9233a73cb4294d58a8906d2b314.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Navigating Tax Requirements in the Digital Era: Manage Compliance with Cloud ERP" src="./media_12d216e0addd5a9233a73cb4294d58a8906d2b314.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="navigating-tax-requirements-in-the-digital-era-manage-compliance-with-cloud-erp">Navigating Tax Requirements in the Digital Era: Manage Compliance with Cloud ERP</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>As businesses adapt to digitalization, they encounter various trends reshaping tax compliance. From emerging business models to governments’ digital initiatives, the tax landscape is undergoing significant transformation.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Authorities are starting to involve themselves in business transactions, disrupting well-established business processes and taking control of the invoicing flow between suppliers and buyers. As a result, they have the data needed to prevent tax evasion and start auditing taxpayers automatically or even auto-populating tax returns moving toward tax bills. Additionally, sustainability efforts and climate change regulations further impact tax regulations.</p>
  <p>Amid these shifts, SAP can provide peace of mind to navigate complexities efficiently. By understanding the evolving tax landscape, businesses can leverage SAP solutions to help streamline compliance processes and drive automation to capitalize on emerging opportunities.</p>
  <p>SAP solutions for global tax management are tailored to help address modern tax challenges. <a href="/topics/erp">SAP S/4HANA Cloud</a> can provide transparency and compliance on a global scale, enabling businesses to embed tax requirements in processes.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="pave-the-way-to-strategic-tax-management-and-automated-compliance-with-sap">Pave the way to strategic tax management and automated compliance with SAP</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/tax-management">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Through localized solutions that offer standardized but flexible business processes, a complete suite of solutions facilitates efficient tax management, from e-invoicing to statutory reporting and overall tax compliance. With SAP technology and expertise, businesses can achieve greater accuracy and agility in tax compliance, paving the way for sustainable growth and competitive advantage.</p>
  <p>To help tax professionals prepare for and become valuable members of tax transformation projects, SAP is introducing a new course: <strong><a href="https://open.sap.com/courses/s4htax-pc">Unlocking Tax Transformation with SAP</a></strong>.</p>
  <p>The course is designed to equip professionals with the knowledge needed to navigate today’s tax landscape and learn new capabilities that can be leveraged as part of SAP S/4HANA-enabled transformations to simplify tax compliance.</p>
  <p>The course offers practical strategies to learn about the different tax types, global developments and their business relevance, and the importance of technology with a focus on SAP S/4HANA and SAP solutions for global tax management. It begins on April 30 and <a href="https://open.sap.com/courses/s4htax-pc">enrollment is now open</a>. By enrolling in this course, tax professionals can gain valuable insights into industry best practices and leverage the latest SAP innovations to help optimize their tax processes.</p>
  <p>In a time of rapid change, SAP supports businesses on their journey to tax compliance and growth. Through collaboration with SAP and a commitment to continuous learning, businesses can navigate the complexities of taxation with confidence and achieve their long-term objectives.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Erika Buson is part of Product Marketing for Global Tax Management and Entity Close at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="follow-and-connect-with-sap-news-on-linkedin">Follow and connect with SAP News on LinkedIn</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news">Stay in touch</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/financial-management</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/financial-services</category>
            <category>news-tag/opensap</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Building a Dynamic Organization with a Skills-Based Approach to Talent]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/building-dynamic-organization-skills-based-approach-to-talent</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/building-dynamic-organization-skills-based-approach-to-talent</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A skills-based approach to talent management can help organizations build a dynamic and resilient workforce. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/recruiting</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-learning</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-opportunity-marketplace</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-recruiting</category>
            <category>news-tag/talent-acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhancing Support Experiences with Support Accreditation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/enhancing-support-experiences-with-support-accreditation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/enhancing-support-experiences-with-support-accreditation</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The Support Accreditation course enables customers and partners to make the best use of SAP's offerings and tools. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c17ed9e9e6e8aba827d32e446eff7f7691e16f08.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c17ed9e9e6e8aba827d32e446eff7f7691e16f08.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1c17ed9e9e6e8aba827d32e446eff7f7691e16f08.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Enhancing Support Experiences with Support Accreditation" src="./media_1c17ed9e9e6e8aba827d32e446eff7f7691e16f08.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="enhancing-support-experiences-with-support-accreditation">Enhancing Support Experiences with Support Accreditation</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>The Support Accreditation course offered by SAP plays a vital role in educating partners, customers, and internal employees about <a href="/topics/support">SAP’s support services</a>. In this interview, Simone Engelhardt, SVP and head of Customer Engagement Support for Customer Services &#x26; Delivery at SAP, discusses the importance of support channels, the 24/7 support structure, service continuity, and best practices for interacting effectively with SAP support teams.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Feedback from participants highlights the training’s success in improving the understanding and utilization of support services. Ongoing updates help ensure the course remains relevant amidst evolving technology and business landscapes, with future developments likely to incorporate advancements in artificial intelligence (AI) and machine learning tools for support services.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Q: Can you provide an overview of the Support Accreditation training and its significance for anyone engaging with SAP’s support processes?</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><strong>Engelhardt:</strong> The Support Accreditation is a vital learning tool for our partners and customers as well as for our employees. It’s an informative course that can familiarize participants with SAP support services and help maximize their support experience. This is a unique opportunity to understand all the tools and resources available when interacting with SAP support and to learn efficient ways of engaging with our teams and resolving issues.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>In situations of urgency or escalation, customers might try to contact someone at SAP they personally know rather than follow the regular process. How does Support Accreditation address such situations and educate participants on the importance of following the proper channels?</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>That’s a great point. In urgent or escalated situations, individuals might feel tempted to bypass the usual channels and seek immediate remedies. However, these uninformed measures can result in delays. The Support Accreditation course emphasizes following the correct SAP support processes, which can ensure their issues are routed to the appropriately skilled support teams, leading to more efficient problem resolution.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Can you shed light on how the Support Accreditation training details the importance of our 24/7 support structure and how customers and partners can take advantage of it?</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The course thoroughly details our 24/7 support structure. We work to ensure that participants understand how, no matter their time zone, they can harness this around-the-clock support. It’s about making sure that our customers and partners know that they always have the backing of SAP, no matter when an issue arises.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-started-with-support-from-sap">Get started with support from SAP</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://learning.sap.com/learning-journey/getting-started-with-support-from-sap-support-accreditation">Explore the Support Accreditation course</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>How can customers and partners ensure that their issues are addressed efficiently even when their primary contacts at SAP are out of office?</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>We indeed cover this crucial aspect. The training delves into detail about the Customer Support organization, which aims to ensure service continuity even if specific account contacts at SAP are unavailable. Our course participants are made aware of the various support structures in place to assist them.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>The Support Accreditation training also covers the etiquette and best practices for interacting with SAP support. Can you talk more about this and why it’s important?</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Interacting with support teams forms a large part of managing SAP services, so etiquette and best practices in this area are covered in our course. We guide learners on the most effective ways to communicate with our teams, provide necessary information, and follow prescribed processes for optimal support assistance.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Do you have any insights related to the feedback from Support Accreditation participants? How has the course improved their understanding and utilization of our support services?</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Feedback from Support Accreditation participants has been overwhelmingly positive. Our learners report significantly improved knowledge about SAP support services and tools, and they’ve been successful in applying this knowledge to engage more effectively with SAP support. This has resulted in smoother, quicker issue resolutions, translating to improved satisfaction and service experiences.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>With technology and business requirements evolving, how will the Support Accreditation course adapt to these changes? What future developments can participants expect?</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The course isn’t static; it evolves with the technology landscape and business requirements. We continually update it to include new tools, offerings, or changes to existing processes. This helps ensure that the Support Accreditation training remains up-to-date and continues to be a valuable resource for our customers and partners. Future developments will certainly involve advancements in AI and machine learning tools in support services, so participants can be well prepared for the future of support services.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Recognized as a Strategic Challenger in 2024 Fosway 9-Grid™ for Learning Systems]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/sap-strategic-challenger-2024-fosway-9-grid-for-learning-systems</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/sap-strategic-challenger-2024-fosway-9-grid-for-learning-systems</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP was recently named a Strategic Challenger in the 2024 Fosway 9-Grid for Learning Systems. Read to learn more about the recognition.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1909b111011bdb2e7f1b173d6614d6bdebec89073.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1909b111011bdb2e7f1b173d6614d6bdebec89073.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1909b111011bdb2e7f1b173d6614d6bdebec89073.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Recognized as a Strategic Challenger in 2024 Fosway 9-Grid™ for Learning Systems" src="./media_1909b111011bdb2e7f1b173d6614d6bdebec89073.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-recognized-as-a-strategic-challenger-in-2024-fosway-9-grid-for-learning-systems">SAP Recognized as a Strategic Challenger in 2024 Fosway 9-Grid™ for Learning Systems</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>SAP was recently named a Strategic Challenger in the <a href="https://www.fosway.com/9-grid-2/learning-systems/">2024 Fosway 9-Grid<sup>TM</sup> for Learning Systems</a>, a multidimensional learning market analysis model. As a Strategic Challenger, SAP is recognized as demonstrating solid performance with solutions that have a rich and broad suite of capability compared to the market.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>With the widened availability of AI, the race for skills is impacting both people and organizations. While people are learning how to use AI to drive more efficiency within their individual roles, organizations are also under pressure to adopt AI technology that can deliver more personalized development opportunities and greater talent intelligence.</p>
  <p>Over the last year, SAP has made significant investments across <a href="http://sap.com/hr">SAP SuccessFactors solutions</a>, specifically in <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/corporate-lms.html">SAP SuccessFactors Learning</a>, to deliver these capabilities.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="boost-employee-skills-while-helping-ensure-compliance-with-sap-successfactors-learning">Boost employee skills while helping ensure compliance with SAP SuccessFactors Learning</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/corporate-lms.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>These investments are part of a broader strategy to help our customers focus on accelerated skills growth and build a <a href="/2023/09/new-integrated-learning-experience-sap-successfactors">future-ready workforce</a>. Recently, we released a redesigned <strong>integrated learning experience</strong> that can deliver an entirely new way for people to experience learning at work. The highly personalized experience can guide the learner to not only accomplish compliance trainings – what they “have to learn” – and organizational goals – what they “need to learn” – but also helps to drive an intrinsic culture of learning around what they “want to learn,” tapping into each individual’s needs, aspirations, interests, or preferences based on their growth profile.</p>
  <p>Furthermore, <strong>the AI-powered</strong> <strong><a href="/2023/10/skills-based-organization-talent-intelligence-hub">talent intelligence hub</a></strong> is now available across all SAP SuccessFactors solutions. It is a framework that helps organizations understand the skills their employees have today, the gaps that exist, and how to close those gaps. With this intelligence, SAP SuccessFactors Learning can continue to deliver even more personalized learning and development recommendations.</p>
  <p>“The level of innovation within the learning systems market continues to accelerate rapidly – specifically around AI and skills,” said David Wilson, founder and CEO of Fosway Group. “As a major vendor in this space, SAP continues to invest significantly in innovating its learning and talent capabilities, reflecting its focus on enhancing the value it delivers to learning buyers as well as its wider HCM audience.”</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d02d983db0796a8aed17039c36d19de9b713748b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d02d983db0796a8aed17039c36d19de9b713748b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1d02d983db0796a8aed17039c36d19de9b713748b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_1d02d983db0796a8aed17039c36d19de9b713748b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="768">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>Source: 2024 Fosway 9-GridTM for Learning Systems. Click to enlarge.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Both multinational and midsize companies leverage <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/corporate-lms.html">SAP SuccessFactors Learning</a>, along with our partner ecosystem, to help drive upskilling and reskilling and create a culture of continuous learning.</p>
  <p><a href="/2023/07/san-pablo-farmacia-employees-brand-ambassadors">San Pablo Farmacia</a>, a Mexico-based pharmacy retail chain, created an intuitive and engaging training experience that employees can consume at their convenience. By integrating the learning solution with other talent management applications, it can design personal training and development plans in line with its growth strategies and the individual needs of the entire workforce. The company delivered certified training to 1,800 employees without the need to transport its people to a training location and take them away from their pharmacy stores.</p>
  <p>Delta is also embracing AI to drive upskilling and personalized development opportunities. “We are incorporating disruptive technologies like our AI-driven skills ontology that automatically incorporates industry trends with embedded intelligence,” said Tim Gregory, managing director of HR Innovation and Workforce Technology at <a href="/2023/10/skills-based-organization-talent-intelligence-hub">Delta</a>. “We can say which skills are most important to Delta Air Lines and the employee can easily combine those with their current capabilities, strengths and styles, and aspirations to create a personal career path. All of the content is based on Delta-specific skills and personalized to each employee’s career goals.”</p>
  <p>Looking ahead, we will continue to deliver more learning-specific enhancements and new AI capabilities throughout 2024 across all SAP SuccessFactors solutions so leaders can hire the best talent and grow their personal skills with individualized plans while building up the compliance and strategic skills needed by the organization.</p>
  <p><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/corporate-lms.html">Learn more about SAP SuccessFactors Learning.</a></p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Vinita Venkatesh is vice president of Product Management for SAP SuccessFactors Learning.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-learning</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP CSR's eBook Celebrates a Year of Global Impact]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/sap-csr-ebook-celebrates-global-impact</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/sap-csr-ebook-celebrates-global-impact</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The impact of SAP CSR in 2023 is a testament to the power of collective action and shared vision. Read to find out how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1aa60aead41f035043e44cbfe1f53c8c65e859485.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1aa60aead41f035043e44cbfe1f53c8c65e859485.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1aa60aead41f035043e44cbfe1f53c8c65e859485.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP CSR’s eBook Celebrates a Year of Global Impact" src="./media_1aa60aead41f035043e44cbfe1f53c8c65e859485.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-csrs-ebook-celebrates-a-year-of-global-impact">SAP CSR’s eBook Celebrates a Year of Global Impact</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Reflecting on the past year, one event stands out vividly in my memory: the Social Enterprises World Forum (SEWF) in Amsterdam, the Netherlands. For those unfamiliar, imagine a global assembly where more than 1,500 entrepreneurs from 82 countries dedicated to societal and environmental missions come together. These enterprises prioritize people and the planet, reinvesting their profits to advance their respective causes. Witnessing the energy and innovation in Amsterdam was a powerful reminder of why SAP has emphasized social entrepreneurship for the second consecutive year.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>It makes me proud to think about the 676 SAP colleagues who, in 2023, participated in our pro bono consulting programs, offering their expertise to these visionary social entrepreneurs. As in previous years, this collaboration has proven mutually beneficial, with 74% of our employees reporting a positive, lasting impact on their careers. Furthermore, 96% of the supported organizations and 77% of their beneficiaries have seen significant improvements. These numbers speak volumes about the shared value of our engagement.</p>
  <p>But the 2023 SEWF wasn’t just a personal highlight; it marked the beginning of another significant milestone. We announced our investment in the <strong>Social Enterprise People and Planet First Verification</strong> with Good Market and SEWF. This initiative aims to set a global standard for recognizing organizations prioritizing social and environmental impacts. Social enterprises can now also identify themselves on SAP Business Network, the world’s largest B2B commerce platform. This breakthrough can make it easier for these businesses to explore new business-to-business opportunities while also helping SAP customers achieve their goals of being more environmentally and socially responsible. Saying it’s a win-win situation is a bit cliché, but in this case it’s actually true.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-is-powering-equitable-access-to-economic-opportunity-education-and-employment-and-the-circular-economy">SAP is powering equitable access to economic opportunity, education and employment, and the circular economy</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/our-values/csr.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Working with SEWF shows how much we believe in working together and driving towards collective impact. I’ve said it before and I’ll say it again: we can’t do this by ourselves. Working with others is the key to driving the kind of systemic change our world needs. This idea is a big part of what we stand for at SAP, and is at the heart of our corporate social responsibility (<a href="/topics/csr">CSR</a>) strategy.</p>
  <p>This idea of working together really comes to life in our collaboration with <strong>UNICEF and Generation Unlimited</strong>. In 2023 – the fourth year of our partnership – we set out to make a real difference by not just developing the skills of young people but also finding jobs in the SAP ecosystem. Launching the SAP Educate to Employ program is a big step in that direction. Helping 25 young people get jobs with SAP in each of our pilot countries – Nigeria, Kenya, South Africa, and the Philippines – might not sound like a lot, but it’s a huge deal for each of those young people. For them, it’s a gateway to a sustainable livelihood, offering them not just gainful employment but a chance to build a career, achieve financial stability, and make meaningful contributions to their communities and the broader world. It’s about unlocking their potential and enabling them to participate in the digital and green economy. By the end of the year, we saw amazing results. While more than 2,500 had already passed the aptitude test, over 1,000 young people in Africa finished our “Boost Your Career with SAP Skills” course and more than 500 got through the first big part of their training.</p>
  <p>But, what’s a year recap without some high-level numbers? Let’s dive into some impressive <strong>numbers from 2023</strong>. More than 20,000 of our SAP colleagues volunteered over 140,000 hours. Our initiatives reached over 2.8 million young people – almost half girls – and supported over 41,000 teachers. Our partner network reached 1 billion people in over 140 countries. These stats are just the tip of the iceberg, showing our big reach and impact together with our partners.</p>
  <p>Building on this, our signature partnerships with Africa Code Week, Meet and Code, and Latin Code Week have always been at the heart of our achievements. As we handed over these initiatives in 2023, we took a moment to reflect and evaluate Africa Code Week and Latin Code Week outcomes more deeply. For instance, by empowering 14.6 million participants with the education, knowledge, and ICT skills needed to participate in the digital future, <strong>Africa Code Week</strong> has increased the likelihood that beneficiaries will realize higher earnings during their working lives. Common Good Marketplace estimates that Africa Code Week catalyzed up to US$1 billion in social value for program participants between 2015 and 2022 based on future increased income.</p>
  <p>As we close the chapter on 2023 and look ahead, the journey we’ve embarked upon at SAP CSR is a testament to the power of collective action and shared vision. The stories, numbers, and outcomes shared in our eBook reflect our commitment to making a meaningful difference. <a href="https://d.dam.sap.com/a/Gnggenc/SAP%20CSR%20in%20Review%202023.pdf?rc=10">Read the full eBook.</a></p>
  <p>Thank you to everyone who has been a part of this journey. Your passion, dedication, and commitment are what drive us forward.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Alexandra van der Ploeg is global head of Corporate Social Responsibility at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="follow-sap-news-on-linkedin-to-stay-up-to-date">Follow SAP News on LinkedIn to stay up-to-date</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news">Connect with us</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>non-sap-event/africa-code week</category>
            <category>news-tag/csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/generation-unlimited</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/social-entrepreneurship</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Learning Services: What Our Customers Really Need]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/learning-services-what-customers-need</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/learning-services-what-customers-need</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learning services and content must be continually kept up-to-date, especially in a cloud world where innovation and flexibility are key.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Equipping the Next Generation of Underrepresented Talent for a Career in Tech]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/equipping-next-generation-underrepresented-talent-tech</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/equipping-next-generation-underrepresented-talent-tech</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP’s digital skills initiative helps prepare underrepresented groups for a career in tech through a free SAP Certification course.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1516454e29028b1edfdf3049f7d0417f3f4530c3f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1516454e29028b1edfdf3049f7d0417f3f4530c3f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1516454e29028b1edfdf3049f7d0417f3f4530c3f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Equipping the Next Generation of Underrepresented Talent for a Career in Tech" src="./media_1516454e29028b1edfdf3049f7d0417f3f4530c3f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="equipping-the-next-generation-of-underrepresented-talent-for-a-career-in-tech">Equipping the Next Generation of Underrepresented Talent for a Career in Tech</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>“I just never saw myself in tech.”</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>This is what I heard during my discussion with the first cohort of SAP’s <a href="https://learning.sap.com/digital-skills">digital</a> <a href="https://learning.sap.com/digital-skills?campaigncode=CRM-YD24-ISM-2422141&#x26;source=blog-glo-Unrepped_Talent">skills</a> <a href="https://learning.sap.com/digital-skills">initiative</a>, a program that helps equip underrepresented and underserved groups for a career in the tech industry through participation in a free SAP Certification course.</p>
  <p>How could it be that in a time when companies need to find talent quickly to fill the need for technically skilled roles – a need that is becoming more urgent by the day – there is an entire population of determined, driven people who feel as though they do not belong in the tech industry?</p>
  <h2 id="the-current-state-of-diversity-in-technology">The Current State of Diversity in Technology</h2>
  <p>The numbers speak volumes: only <a href="https://ncwit.org/resource/bythenumbers/">27% of all computing-related jobs are held by women</a>. Only 3% of those jobs are held by Black women and 1% are held by Latina women. For me, it has always been impossible to ignore the lack of representation in the tech industry. I am acutely aware of when I am the only woman in the room – let alone the only Black woman.</p>
  <p>But this is changing. Companies have begun implementing diversity-forward hiring practices to try to minimize barriers for populations that have historically been overlooked. The percentage of <a href="https://www.naceweb.org/diversity-equity-and-inclusion/individuals-with-disabilities/ready-willing-but-still-underemployed/e619e772-a54b-4df6-858c-9ca50717a5a0">employers with diversity recruiting efforts</a> rose from 56% in 2016 to 88% in 2021. Though there is now targeted backlash, numerous employers remain committed to their diversity, equity, and inclusion (DE&#x26;I) goals for the workforce.</p>
  <p>These initiatives have proven to be important to younger generations. In a few years, millennials and Gen Z will make up the majority of our workforce – and they want to work for companies that align with their values. A 2022 survey from the <a href="https://www.naceweb.org/diversity-equity-and-inclusion/individuals-with-disabilities/ready-willing-but-still-underemployed/835bc35a-e4be-42fb-b838-d06086cb87bc">National Association of Colleges and Employers (NACE)</a> found that 76% of recent graduates indicated that <a href="/topics/diversity-and-inclusion">diversity, equity, and inclusion efforts</a> were “very important” or “extremely important” when considering their future employers.</p>
  <h2 id="helping-underserved-groups-break-into-tech">Helping Underserved Groups Break into Tech</h2>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="accelerate-your-career-with-our-digital-skills-initiative">Accelerate your career with our digital skills initiative</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://learning.sap.com/digital-skills?campaigncode=CRM-YD24-ISM-2422141&#x26;source=blog-glo-Unrepped_Talent">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>If we want diverse workforces, we must support and create targeted channels to source diverse talent. It is imperative that these groups – including women, people of color, veterans, and others – are given the resources to excel in high tech. I have seen firsthand how our digital skills initiative is making an impact on individuals and their communities, working to ensure that talent from all backgrounds can participate in this exciting era of technological innovation. At SAP, we offer training on products like <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/s4hana.html?campaigncode=CRM-YD24-ISM-2422141&#x26;source=blog-glo-Unrepped_Talent">SAP S/4HANA Cloud</a> and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp.html?campaigncode=CRM-YD24-ISM-2422141&#x26;source=blog-glo-Unrepped_Talent">SAP ERP</a>, whether through programs like the digital skills initiative or on <a href="https://learninghub.sap.com/?campaigncode=CRM-YD24-ISM-2422141&#x26;source=blog-glo-Unrepped_Talent">SAP Learning Hub</a>, helping anyone interested in jump-starting their career in tech.</p>
  <p>Without diverse perspectives, we leave out too many pieces of the puzzle to see the big picture. This deficit is particularly obvious in technology, given its influence on everything from how we shop to how we govern. It is unsustainable to expect lasting market viability from products that are developed by and marketed to one type of person. Put simply, employing diverse talent is essential to long-term success.</p>
  <h2 id="how-companies-can-recruit-diverse-talent">How Companies Can Recruit Diverse Talent</h2>
  <p>For companies that are looking for the next pool of employees to solve today’s business challenges, it is time to consider non-traditional avenues of talent, like graduates from SAP’s digital skills initiative. Each cohort comes equipped with SAP Certification, self-motivation, and a strong work ethic. This is a special opportunity to pull from a curated group of strong candidates, not just because of their new skills but because of demonstrated curiosity and drive that is not easy to find.</p>
  <p>SAP makes these trained and certified candidates available to recruiters at no charge. Want to get access to SAP-certified, ready-to-hire talent? Interested in adopting a cohort? <a href="https://learning.sap.com/digital-skills/hire-talent?campaigncode=CRM-YD24-ISM-2422141&#x26;source=blog-glo-Unrepped_Talent">Contact us</a> to see how you can start hiring and get involved.</p>
  <h2 id="register-for-the-digital-skills-initiative-as-a-participant">Register for the Digital Skills Initiative as a Participant</h2>
  <p>If you are interested in expanding your career opportunities by learning in-demand skills and achieving an SAP Certification free of charge, apply for the digital skills initiative using the <a href="https://community.sap.com/t5/beginner-corner-blog-posts/digital-skills-initiative-applicant-guide-for-self-study-candidates/ba-p/273119">applicant guide</a>. This is a fantastic opportunity for those who want to make a career switch to tech.</p>
  <p>To those who never pictured themselves in the tech industry, picture it. There is a place for you. Take this as a sign to invest in yourself and create a new path to success.</p>
  <h2 id="making-an-impact-on-future-generations">Making an Impact on Future Generations</h2>
  <p>When I talked with this first cohort of the digital skills initiative, I saw how they take great pride in their certification. For some, these new skills will prove to be life-changing.</p>
  <p>My goal is to support initiatives that aim to ensure that everyone, from all backgrounds, can pursue their interests in finding a career in tech. When we leave these doors closed, we not only rob those shut out of the opportunity, but all of us from the creativity, perspectives, and outcomes they could deliver.</p>
  <p>I am incredibly proud of SAP’s work in empowering people to pursue a career in technology. I believe that we are developing the future of innovation through programs like the digital skills initiative, and I cannot wait to see how similar programs will evolve in the future.</p>
  <p>If you are an NGO, university, or an SAP partner or customer, contact us at <a href="mailto:partners.digitalskills@sap.com">partners.digitalskills@sap.com</a> to learn more. If you are interested in applying to the digital skills initiative, <a href="https://groups.community.sap.com/t5/beginner-corner-discussions/creating-an-sap-account-and-getting-started-in-the-community/m-p/260744">create an SAP account</a> to start your journey.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Etosha Thurman is chief marketing and solutions officer for Intelligent Spend and Business Network at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>product/sap-learning-hub</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How to Boost Your Cloud Adoption]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/how-to-boost-your-cloud-adoption</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/how-to-boost-your-cloud-adoption</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Preferred Success and SAP Learning Hub can provide the training essential for unlocking the full business value of the cloud.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>product/sap-learning-hub</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-preferred-success</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Offers Professionals New Digital Learning and Certification]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/sap-offers-professionals-new-digital-learning-certification</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/sap-offers-professionals-new-digital-learning-certification</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New digital learning and certification from SAP are helping to meet the dramatically growing demand for skilled IT professionals. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15c26622362450c1931dc209600aa9d2d067dc3ff.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15c26622362450c1931dc209600aa9d2d067dc3ff.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_15c26622362450c1931dc209600aa9d2d067dc3ff.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Offers Professionals New Digital Learning and Certification" src="./media_15c26622362450c1931dc209600aa9d2d067dc3ff.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-offers-professionals-new-digital-learning-and-certification">SAP Offers Professionals New Digital Learning and Certification</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced the launch of a new guided premium learning offering with SAP Learning Hub and an enhanced certification program including a new role-based certification for SAP S/4HANA Cloud implementation consultants.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The demand for skilled IT professionals is expected to grow dramatically – up 23% by 2031 in the United States alone, according to the U.S. Department of Labor. To help meet this demand, the <a href="https://learning.sap.com/certifications/sap-certified-associate-implementation-consultant-sap-s-4hana-cloud-public-edition?url_id=text-sapnewscenter-prdteng">new role-based certification for implementation consultants of SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition</a> <a href="">emphasizes</a> core skills and competencies that can be applied across various cloud solutions from SAP and related versions.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="grow-your-skills-future-proof-your-career-learn-sap-for-free-anywhere-anytime">Grow your skills. Future proof your career. Learn SAP for free, anywhere, anytime.</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://learning.sap.com/">Start now</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“The pace of change and the talent shortage call for a new approach to identifying future-focused skills and roles. Instead of focusing on traditional aspects like degrees, job histories and titles, professional competencies become more important,” says Andre Bechtold, senior vice president and head of solution and innovation experience at SAP. “By transitioning to role-based certifications that focus on core skills and competencies, the skillset of a learner becomes more valuable and gains sustainability and more relevance for longer periods of time.”</p>
  <p>Many organizations rely on SAP solutions and skilled professionals to ensure a smooth and fast transition and drive business success. The enhanced SAP Learning Hub provides access to great content and includes four certification attempts per learner per year. Subscribers can receive expert guidance in digital live sessions, on-demand hands-on practice systems, advanced analytics and learning management functionalities. This new digital premium offering marks a major step in the evolution of the SAP Learning portfolio. To meet the rapid pace of technological innovation and the need to quickly gain new and future-proof skills, SAP continues to help organizations learn and become certified faster to maximize their investment.</p>
  <p>With the need for fast, comprehensive and role-based upskilling, the new certification model will make continuous learning and assessments a priority. Starting in early second quarter, these changes will support customers, partners and individuals in gaining skills across the SAP solutions portfolio and keeping them up to date.</p>
  <p><a href="/">Partners can benefit from further advancements</a>, including a tailored partner experience with curated learning journeys, exclusive access to events and subject matter experts. A subscription to SAP Learning Hub, <a href="">partner</a> edition comes with a significantly reduced price per user per year and offers additional chances to earn certifications, as well as improved analysis and tracking features.</p>
  <p>With the move to the cloud in full swing, the enhanced SAP Learning Hub and new certification program help customers and partners meet the challenges of a tight labor market and necessary workforce transformation. Learn more about <a href="https://www.sap.com/training-certification/learning-hub.html?sort=latest_desc">SAP Learning Hub</a> and the <a href="https://learning.sap.com/staying-certified">new certification program</a>.</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="http://news.sap.com/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Media Contact:</strong><br>Martin Gwisdalla, +49 6227 7-67275, <a href="mailto:martin.gwisdalla@sap.com">martin.gwisdalla@sap.com</a>, ET<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>This document contains forward-looking statements, which are predictions, projections, or other statements about future events. These statements are based on current expectations, forecasts, and assumptions that are subject to risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results and outcomes to materially differ. Additional information regarding these risks and uncertainties may be found in our filings with the Securities and Exchange Commission, including but not limited to the risk factors section of SAP’s 2022 Annual Report on Form 20-F.<br>© 2024 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>product/sap-learning-hub</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Invests in Partner Learning to Boost Availability of SAP Experts]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/sap-invests-in-partner-learning</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/sap-invests-in-partner-learning</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Learning is reimagining partner enablement with SAP Learning Journeys, subject matter experts, and opportunities to earn credentials.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Why It’s Better to Accept Generative AI Sooner, Not Later]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/videos/why-its-better-to-accept-generative-ai-sooner-not-later</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/videos/why-its-better-to-accept-generative-ai-sooner-not-later</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP's Julia White joins experts from Deloitte, BCG, and StartSteps Digital Education to discuss society’s scramble to get the right people into new jobs.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/video</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-education</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>non-sap-event/wef-davos</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The State of Computer Science in the U.S.]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/the-state-of-computer-science-in-the-us</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/the-state-of-computer-science-in-the-us</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Shaina Glass from the Computer Science Teachers Association gives an interview about the state of computer science education in the country.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Support Accreditation: A Consultant’s Hack for Maximizing SAP’s Support Offerings]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/support-accreditation-maximizing-sap-support-offerings</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/support-accreditation-maximizing-sap-support-offerings</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Support Accreditation is a course that enables customers and partners to make the best use of SAP's offerings and tools. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/real-time-support</category>
            <category>product/sap-cloud-alm</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mindfulness: The Surprising Business Model]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/mindfulness-the-surprising-business-model</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/mindfulness-the-surprising-business-model</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Global Mindfulness Practice is bringing its successful formula to customers around the world. Read to learn about SLB's experience.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/mental-health-well-being</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-global-mindfulness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Best Time to Be a Developer Is Now]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/best-time-to-be-a-developer-is-now</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/best-time-to-be-a-developer-is-now</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[There is a skyrocketing demand for developers. Resources for constant career growth and learning are critical. Learn what SAP is offering.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cybersecurity a Top Priority at SAP, Early Talent Program Recognized by U.S. Government]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/cybersecurity-top-priority-sap-global-early-talent-program</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/cybersecurity-top-priority-sap-global-early-talent-program</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The two-year Global Security Early Talent program offers young professionals entry into the cybersecurity space at SAP. Learn more about it.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/cybersecurity</category>
            <category>news-tag/talent-acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Accelerate Your Skills Transformation with the New Integrated Learning Experience for SAP SuccessFactors]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/new-integrated-learning-experience-sap-successfactors</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/new-integrated-learning-experience-sap-successfactors</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The integrated learning experience for SAP SuccessFactors helps to address skills gaps and considers employees' whole self in skills growth.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills-gap</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning-management-system</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-learning</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Career Pathfinding on the AI Frontier: Become the Talent Behind the Tech]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/ai-careers-talent-behind-tech</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/ai-careers-talent-behind-tech</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The landscape of AI careers has exploded, with almost every industry needing people with AI skills at different levels.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/opensap</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Learning to Stay Ahead of the Curve: Why Teams Should Value Low-Code/No-Code Training]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/value-low-code-no-code-training</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/value-low-code-no-code-training</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Providing access to learning and development opportunities like low-code/no-code training opens new workforce opportunities. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/low-code-no-code</category>
            <category>product/sap-build</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Powering Business Transformation with Unprecedented Career Growth for SAP Professionals]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/powering-unprecedented-career-growth-sap-professionals</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/powering-unprecedented-career-growth-sap-professionals</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[We all are facing a changing work environment. Read to learn how SAP Learning supports the career growth of SAP professionals.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-certification</category>
            <category>product/sap-learning-hub</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP’s Vision for Future-Proofed Business in the Age of AI Comes to Life: SAP Sapphire in 2023]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/sap-sapphire-future-proofed-business-age-of-ai</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/sap-sapphire-future-proofed-business-age-of-ai</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[At SAP Sapphire in 2023, SAP unveiled sweeping innovations that equip customers to tackle an uncertain future with confidence. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/green-ledger</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-data-exchange</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-footprint-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Starts Pilot with Accenture and IBM to Co-Validate SAP Expertise for Advanced Professionals]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/accenture-ibm-pilot-co-validate-sap-expertise</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/accenture-ibm-pilot-co-validate-sap-expertise</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A new pilot to co-validate SAP expertise, with first partners Accenture and IBM, is paving the way for career growth and business success.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/accenture</category>
            <category>news-tag/ibm</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-certification</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-partner-connect</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Communicating the True Value of Learning and Development in 2023]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/communicating-value-of-learning-development-2023</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/communicating-value-of-learning-development-2023</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Leaders need to be strategic in providing learning opportunities. Learn why and how leaders and employees can benefit from the investment.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c348ed4ab53e7860823ae46dfe75ba57f60e11e8.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c348ed4ab53e7860823ae46dfe75ba57f60e11e8.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1c348ed4ab53e7860823ae46dfe75ba57f60e11e8.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Communicating the True Value of Learning and Development in 2023" src="./media_1c348ed4ab53e7860823ae46dfe75ba57f60e11e8.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="communicating-the-true-value-of-learning-and-development-in-2023">Communicating the True Value of Learning and Development in 2023</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>As we move quickly into the second quarter of 2023, leaders and workers alike are facing increasing pressure resulting from the current tumultuous economic period. In a business environment where every budget line is being questioned, IT leaders must maintain a strategic lens when providing <a href="/topics/training">learning</a> opportunities for their teams. They must be able to clearly articulate the value of technical training and development opportunities – or risk losing them.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In the midst of this uncertainty, keeping IT workers abreast of innovative technologies and the skills to implement them is a balancing act. To stay at the forefront of industry change, learning must be considered more than a priority – it needs to be a core pillar of every organization. IT upskilling is key in today’s landscape to drive employee satisfaction and organizational success. Here are three of the top reasons to invest in learning and development opportunities and how the benefits can be articulated to leadership to ensure they consider learning a top priority, too.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-digital-skills-you-need-with-sap-learning">Get the digital skills you need with SAP Learning</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://learning.sap.com/digital-skills?url_id=text-sapnewscenter-prdteng-DigitalSkills">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="invest-in-your-employees--and-they-just-might-stick-around">Invest in Your Employees – and They Just Might Stick Around</h2>
  <p>While layoffs seem to be dominating the headlines, employees are quitting their jobs at <a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2023/02/13/business/employee-retention-quitting-companies.html">three times</a> the rate of layoffs. Retaining strong talent remains a competitive pursuit, and organizations are feeling the impacts of this challenge. Now, <a href="http://workplaceintelligence.com/upskilling-study/">64% to 66% of employees</a> would consider leaving their current role because there aren’t enough opportunities for skill development or career advancement. The truth is that adequate training directly impacts retention. An important factor in how employees evaluate their organization is based on the opportunities they’re provided to learn the skills that will catapult them towards reaching their goals. Learning and development opportunities can equip employees with essential leadership skills that can elevate their current position and pave the way for internal advancement.</p>
  <p>By offering learning programs, and therefore showing the workforce that leaders are invested in their growth, executive teams will realize a multitude of benefits. Individuals will feel valued and excited by new challenges and upskilling opportunities, making them more likely to be happy with their current role. Beyond this, they’ll build a workforce that is equipped with the latest knowledge to drive meaningful outcomes for the organization.</p>
  <h2 id="fostering-creativity-innovation-and-curiosity">Fostering Creativity, Innovation, and Curiosity</h2>
  <p>The tech industry is evolving – fast. From generative artificial intelligence (AI) and machine learning to immersive-reality technologies, digital transformation has raised the bar on the skills required of teams today. Inspiring employees to lead innovative strategies can feel daunting when the workforce is not properly equipped with the latest knowledge to take on new initiatives. When employees do not feel prepared, they are less likely to be enthusiastic about taking on new responsibilities or raise their hand to lead a project that is outside of their comfort zone. In fact, <a href="https://www.gartner.com/en/publications/emerging-technology-roadmap-for-large-enterprisesB">64% of IT professionals</a> think the skills shortage is the biggest barrier to the adoption of game-changing technologies.</p>
  <p>To combat this hesitation and encourage workers to tackle new challenges, leaders must recognize that learning and development opportunities enable IT teams to feel prepared and excited to move forward on adopting new workplace technologies. This ultimately increases efficiency and allows more time and space for innovation and creativity.</p>
  <p>Steve Lucas, SAP S/4HANA Cloud application consultant at Sapphire Systems, has seen how learning, for instance with <a href="https://learning.sap.com/?url_id=text-sapnewscenter-prdteng">self-paced SAP Learning Journeys on the SAP Learning site</a>, can drive innovation firsthand. “Earning an SAP Certiﬁcation is important to not just my future but the future of my company. It ensures we’ll both meet our goals and remain at the forefront of SAP’s latest innovations,” he said.</p>
  <h2 id="tackling-the-persistent-skills-gap-challenge">Tackling the Persistent Skills Gap Challenge</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="explore-sap-learning-journeys-and-product-pages">Explore SAP Learning Journeys and product pages</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://learning.sap.com/?url_id=text-sapnewscenter-prdteng">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The skills gap remains top-of-mind for leaders across industries as technical roles continue to evolve and competition for top talent remains high. Due to the speed of innovation, over <a href="https://www.gartner.com/en/newsroom/press-releases/2021-02-03-gartner-hr-research-finds-fifty-eight-percent-of-the-workforce-will-need-new-skill-sets-to-do-their-jobs-successfully">58% of the workforce will need new skill sets</a> to do their jobs successfully in the coming years.</p>
  <p>While some employees may be able to make time outside of work hours for learning and development, many have competing personal priorities – meaning encouraging employees to seek upskilling opportunities outside of their nine-to-five may set them on a path of frustration and burnout. Instead, bring training programs directly to them and build a few uninterrupted hours into their workday so that employees can devote themselves to learning without navigating demanding tasks at the same time. This simple solution can mitigate burnout and ensure everyone is receiving the information they need to be successful in their roles – now and in the future.</p>
  <p>For example, learning programs like <a href="https://learning.sap.com/learning-journey/discover-the-foundations-of-sap-commerce-cloud-and-sap-s-4hana-cloud-integration?url_id=text-sapnewscenter-prdteng">SAP S/4HANA</a> or <a href="https://learning.sap.com/learning-journey/utilize-sap-build-for-low-code-no-code-applications-and-automations-for-citizen-developers?url_id=text-sapnewscenter-prdteng">low-code/no-code</a> basics can quickly and efficiently equip employees with the skills they need by educating them on the latest platforms and technology necessary to keep up with digital transformation efforts. These programs can also level the playing field among teams, increasing workers’ value and purpose within their current role.</p>
  <h2 id="the-return-on-learning-and-development-priceless">The Return on Learning and Development? Priceless.</h2>
  <p>While it’s true that that investing in learning and development is a commitment – both in budget and in resources – the benefits far outweigh the drawbacks. It’s easy to deprioritize learning when the time and money that goes into upskilling can seem like an optional expense, but in today’s workplace culture, it is essential. Companies who invest in learning and development opportunities will reap the benefits almost immediately and will equip their teams for a future of innovation, creativity, and equitable opportunities for growth, ultimately leading to higher retention, empowered employees, and a more secure workforce.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Jan Meyer is head of Learning Systems at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills-gap</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Design a Circular Future with New openSAP Course]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/design-circular-future-opensap-course</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/design-circular-future-opensap-course</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A new openSAP course, Designing a Circular Economy, addresses how we can create the products we need in a circular way.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/circular-economy</category>
            <category>news-tag/opensap</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reskilling for the Green Transition]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/reskilling-for-the-green-transition</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/reskilling-for-the-green-transition</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[An inclusive green transition could create millions of jobs in the next decade but requires significant investments in reskilling.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/climate-action</category>
            <category>news-tag/climate-change</category>
            <category>news-tag/csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/people-sustainability</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Women Can Be the Key to Solving the Global Skills Gap in Tech]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/01/women-key-to-global-digital-skills-gap-in-tech</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/01/women-key-to-global-digital-skills-gap-in-tech</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The global lack of digitally skilled workers is increasing in the tech industry. Learn about SAP's initiative and how women are key.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/coursera</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills-gap</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-certification</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-community</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Industry 4.0 Attracts Workers Whose Entire Lives Are on Their Mobile Device]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/industry-4-0-attracts-workers-whose-entire-lives-are-on-their-mobile-device</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/industry-4-0-attracts-workers-whose-entire-lives-are-on-their-mobile-device</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Manufacturers are transforming factories, hoping next-generation workers come for the cool factor and stay for career-building innovations.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-4-0</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>news-tag/mobile</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Wellstar Health Improves the Employee Experience through Innovative LMS Governance]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/wellstar-health-employee-experience-lms-governance</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/wellstar-health-employee-experience-lms-governance</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Improved governance helped Wellstar Health make the most out of its SAP SuccessFactors Learning solution. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_133c1cc6858830182923838b672bf97c1f0d1448f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_133c1cc6858830182923838b672bf97c1f0d1448f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_133c1cc6858830182923838b672bf97c1f0d1448f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Wellstar Health Improves the Employee Experience through Innovative LMS Governance" src="./media_133c1cc6858830182923838b672bf97c1f0d1448f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="wellstar-health-improves-the-employee-experience-through-innovative-lms-governance">Wellstar Health Improves the Employee Experience through Innovative LMS Governance</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="building-a-lifelong-learning-culture-is-more-important-than-ever">Building a Lifelong Learning Culture Is More Important Than Ever</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2022/10/building-a-lifelong-learning-culture">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Imagine that you’ve just been hired into a new job, but due to training you can’t really start your actual duties for a week and a half. Now add to this the fact that you’re a healthcare worker whose expertise is very much in need. This was the scenario at Wellstar Health System prior to the start of its learning management system (LMS) governance initiative.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As a customer of multiple <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/hxm-suite.html">SAP SuccessFactors solutions</a>, Wellstar is familiar with the power of SAP and knew it could be getting more out of its SAP SuccessFactors Learning solution. Danielle Mecum, manager of Learning Technology at Wellstar, believed that improved governance of the system was part of the road to getting there. “When governance is lacking, the employee experience suffers,” Mecum explained.</p>
  <p>With a nursing background, she knew firsthand the need to get new hires trained properly and quickly, and that reducing the time from hire to actual work was key. She added, “In addition to our non-clinical employees, our medical employees were taking longer to get to the patient floors to start providing care because of how the required onboarding training was organized and set up. There were inaccurate training assignments, courses not marked as required, and, in some cases, no required-by dates.”</p>
  <p>In addition, users said that their learning assignments were too cluttered and disorganized, Mecum explained. And there were instances where new employees would get to a patient floor and realize that they were not able to enter a patient’s chart, for example, because a course hadn’t been assigned to them in the correct sequence.</p>
  <p>The need to get employees onboarded faster could have been enough to justify the governance project, but to add to the complex nature of the project – and completely out of Wellstar’s control – the organization faced the impending deprecation of Flash content and the impacts of the <a href="/topics/covid-19">COVID-19</a> pandemic. To help tackle this challenge, Wellstar decided to work with its customer engagement executive to start a solution adoption engagement. This type of engagement is intended to provide recommendations to a customer to help them create an action plan to optimize their use of their system – in this case <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/corporate-lms.html">SAP SuccessFactors Learning</a>. A recommendation came out of this engagement that confirmed the needed for the governance initiative.</p>
  <p>Mecum’s nursing background helped her understand the urgency of the situation. She and her team looked at the issues already discussed and began to build a governance model. For example, they instituted a content life cycle management process that incorporated a formal method for requesting the creation of new items, curricula, and assignment profiles. In addition, they implemented an ongoing review procedure that included automated notifications to course owners to review material that had reached expiration. Additionally, Wellstar leveraged and configured custom fields within SAP SuccessFactors Learning to track key data and report on it from within the system to ensure compliance with the new governance process.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="foster-continuous-learning-and-reduce-compliance-risk-with-sap-successfactors-learning">Foster continuous learning and reduce compliance risk with SAP SuccessFactors Learning</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/corporate-lms.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Other governance steps included reviewing and consolidating LMS admin roles to ensure the right administrators had the right permissions to perform administrative tasks as appropriate in the system – without giving them freedom to add to the problem at large. A formal process for vetting new LMS administrators was created to ensure they weren’t simply giving just anyone these permissions. “We knew we needed to define what goes into the system, so we could control what comes out. This helps when we need to get rid of old, outdated courses,” Mecum explained.</p>
  <p>These changes, among others, were implemented as part of the governance initiative. The result is that Wellstar is now reaping greater benefits from <a href="/topics/sap-successfactors-learning">SAP SuccessFactors Learning</a> and, most importantly, employees now have an improved experience with the system. Frustration levels are down and new hires are able to start their actual jobs much sooner than before – in three days rather than a week and a half!</p>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/corporate-lms.html">Learn how an LMS can help your organization.</a></div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>Mark Tarallo is a solution marketing fellow for SAP SuccessFactors.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/covid-19</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>industry/healthcare</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning-management-system</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-learning</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>