<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/product/sap-sustainability-data-exchange/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[We Can’t Achieve Net Zero Without the Circular Economy]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/we-cant-achieve-net-zero-without-the-circular-economy</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/we-cant-achieve-net-zero-without-the-circular-economy</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Net zero and the circular economy go hand in hand. Read to learn how businesses, like SAP, and non-corporate bodies can accelerate progress.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/circular-economy</category>
            <category>news-tag/net-zero</category>
            <category>product/sap-green-token</category>
            <category>product/sap-responsible-design-and-production</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-data-exchange</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-sustainability-solutions</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[From CSRD Reporting to Sustainable Business Outcomes]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/from-csrd-reporting-to-sustainable-business-outcomes</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/from-csrd-reporting-to-sustainable-business-outcomes</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[By leveraging SAP Sustainability solutions, organizations can move beyond compliance, like CSRD reporting, and operationalize sustainability.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/compliance</category>
            <category>news-tag/esg</category>
            <category>news-tag/green-ledger</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-data-exchange</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-footprint-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-sustainability-solutions</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Insights from COP28: Harnessing the Power of Business for Climate Action]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/cop28-insights-power-of-business-climate-action</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/cop28-insights-power-of-business-climate-action</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Reflecting on sustainability measures discussed at COP28, we are seeing a shift towards data sharing and a transition to sustainable energy.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/climate-action</category>
            <category>non-sap-event/cop28</category>
            <category>news-tag/net-zero</category>
            <category>news-tag/renewable-energy</category>
            <category>product/sap-green-token</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-data-exchange</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Scope 3 Emissions in the Telecommunications Industry: Driving Sustainable Transformation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/emissions-in-telecommunications-industry-sustainable-transformation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/emissions-in-telecommunications-industry-sustainable-transformation</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Addressing scope 3 emissions is vital for telecommunications companies to meet climate goals and lead the transition to a sustainable future.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_174e09b00b05a139cf976c0528b18baf650fa1d08.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_174e09b00b05a139cf976c0528b18baf650fa1d08.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_174e09b00b05a139cf976c0528b18baf650fa1d08.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Scope 3 Emissions in the Telecommunications Industry: Driving Sustainable Transformation" src="./media_174e09b00b05a139cf976c0528b18baf650fa1d08.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="scope-3-emissions-in-the-telecommunications-industry-driving-sustainable-transformation">Scope 3 Emissions in the Telecommunications Industry: Driving Sustainable Transformation</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>The telecommunications business has been revolutionary in its ability to connect individuals worldwide. However, this phenomenal growth has left the sector with a significant portion of the world’s emissions. With increasing data demand, telecommunications companies must prioritize decreasing greenhouse gas emissions throughout their value chain.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Scope 3 emissions from activities across suppliers, product lifecycles, and customer usage comprise the overwhelming majority of emissions for telecommunications companies. While progress has been made on scope 1 and 2 emissions, scope 3 emissions remain a blind spot that demands urgent action. Addressing scope 3 emissions is vital for telecommunications companies to meet climate goals and lead the transition to a sustainable digital future.</p>
  <p>According to the <a href="https://www.wri.org/insights/4-charts-explain-greenhouse-gas-emissions-countries-and-sectors">World Resources Institute</a>, the global telecommunications industry emitted 1.7 billion tons of CO2 equivalent in 2019, representing approximately 2% of total global emissions. Telecommunications companies have an outsized opportunity to drive change and reduce emissions given their scale and influence across global supply chains and billions of customers worldwide.</p>
  <p>Now is the time for telecommunications companies to step up with courageous leadership, collective action across the ecosystem, transparency, and a laser focus on reducing scope 3 emissions.</p>
  <h2 id="understanding-scope-3-emissions-in-telecommunications">Understanding Scope 3 Emissions in Telecommunications</h2>
  <p>Scope 3 emissions encompass the vast majority of emissions across the telecommunications value chain. Key sources include:</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="how-sap-helps-businesses-streamline-their-emissions-declarations">How SAP Helps Businesses Streamline Their Emissions Declarations</h3>
        <p><em><a href="/2023/05/sap-ehs-management-streamline-emissions-declarations">Read the feature</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><strong>Supply chain</strong><br>Manufacturing, transport, and disposal of network equipment makes up the largest share, such as 60% of Verizon’s total scope 3</p>
  <p><strong>Product usage</strong><br>Energy consumption of infrastructure, data centers, and devices</p>
  <p><strong>Customers</strong><br>Emissions from using products and services represent over 20% for leading telecommunications companies</p>
  <p>While methodologies vary, standards like the <a href="https://ghgprotocol.org/">Greenhouse Gas (GHG) Protocol</a> enable consistent and transparent scope 3 accounting. Robust data collection and industry alignment will enhance accuracy over time. The urgency of climate action necessitates that telecommunications companies act now to address primary scope 3 hotspots like supply chain and product usage.</p>
  <p>Success requires transparency, cooperation, and immediate commitment to tackle scope 3 emission sources.</p>
  <h2 id="challenges-in-calculating-scope-3-emissions-in-the-telecommunications-industry">Challenges in Calculating Scope 3 Emissions in the Telecommunications Industry</h2>
  <p>Calculating scope 3 emissions poses major challenges for telecommunications companies, including:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Data limitations</strong>: Telecommunications companies lack visibility into supplier and vendor emissions. Greater transparency and coordination are essential.</li>
    <li><strong>Complex value chains</strong>: Varied reporting mechanisms across the vast partner ecosystem create aggregation difficulties.</li>
    <li><strong>Methodology alignment</strong>: Companies must determine boundaries and allocate shared infrastructure emissions while adhering to accounting standards.</li>
    <li><strong>Rapid technology changes</strong>: Emerging solutions like 5G and the Internet of Things (IoT) require continuous emissions monitoring.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>Robust data collection, industry collaboration, and transparency will be vital to overcome these obstacles. Standardized methodologies guided by established protocols will enhance accuracy over time.</p>
  <p>Above all, open cooperation across telecommunications value chains is crucial to drive scope 3 progress. From suppliers to customers, aligning stakeholders to prioritize emissions reductions will accelerate the sustainability shift, despite near-term uncertainty. Telecommunications companies have the scale and influence to lead the way.</p>
  <h2 id="strategies-for-mitigating-scope-3-emissions">Strategies for Mitigating Scope 3 Emissions</h2>
  <p>Telecommunications companies can mitigate scope 3 emissions through:</p>
  <p><strong>Supplier collaboration</strong><br>Joint research and development (R&#x26;D), audits, and incentive programs enable partners to reduce their supply chain footprint. AT&#x26;T uses a sustainability scorecard to motivate action.</p>
  <p><strong>Renewable energy</strong><br>Shifting infrastructure and operations to clean power significantly decreases emissions. BT Group and Telefónica aim for 100% renewable electricity use.</p>
  <p><strong>Eco-design</strong><br>Prioritizing recyclable and energy-efficient materials and manufacturing reduces lifecycle impacts. Vodafone’s Eco Rating drives more sustainable devices.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="achieve-transparency-and-gain-carbon-neutrality-with-sap-sustainability-data-exchange">Achieve transparency and gain carbon neutrality with SAP Sustainability Data Exchange</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/registration/request-demo.html?campaigncode=CRM-YI23-IMM-1939705&#x26;pageTitle=Climate+Action+Solutions&#x26;countryOfOrigin=en_us&#x26;refererPagePath=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.sap.com%2Fsustainability%2Fclimate-action.html&#x26;refererContentPath=%2Fcontent%2Fsapdx%2Flanguages%2Fen_us%2Fsustainability%2Fclimate-action&#x26;navTitle=Request+a+Demo">Demo it</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><strong>Customer engagement</strong><br>Awareness campaigns, energy-saving tips, and green tariffs incentivize sustainable usage. Orange’s set-top box eco-rating nudges consumers.</p>
  <p><strong>Policy and regulation</strong><br>Scope 3 requirements in markets like the EU also drive telecommunications companies to address value chain emissions through mandated reporting and carbon pricing.</p>
  <p>Additionally, telecommunications companies can further engage customers through expanded recycling and take-back programs to optimize device lifecycles. Services like leasing instead of selling phones can incentivize longevity. Features that track energy consumption also enable users to reduce their footprint.</p>
  <p>There are still challenges, but collective effort across the telecommunications ecosystem can drive progress on scope 3 emissions. Engagement and incentives can accelerate emissions reductions across value chains from suppliers to customers. With their global scale, telecommunications companies must lead the way.</p>
  <h2 id="calculating-and-reporting">Calculating and Reporting</h2>
  <p>To enable accurate and consistent scope 3 accounting, telecommunications companies should:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Adopt recognized standards like the GHG Protocol Corporate Value Chain Standard, which provides comprehensive guidance.</li>
    <li>Improve supplier data collection through surveys and supplier engagement platforms.</li>
    <li>Increase transparency by regularly disclosing scope 3 inventories and strategies in sustainability reports.</li>
    <li>Obtain third-party verification for scope 3 emissions data to ensure reliability.</li>
    <li>Collaborate with industry peers and partners to align methodologies and reporting.</li>
    <li>Continuously refine calculations by incorporating improved data sources and emission factors.</li>
    <li>Supplement inventory accounting with scenario modeling to project future emissions.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>While uncertainties remain, standardized and transparent scope 3 reporting is vital to understand emissions baselines, track progress over time, and hold companies accountable. Investors and customers are increasingly demanding credible disclosure.</p>
  <p>Telecommunications companies should lead the drive towards robust scope 3 accounting and reporting across sectors. Their commitment can catalyze broader adoption of carbon transparency.</p>
  <p>Using SAP Sustainability Data Exchange, telecommunications companies can collaborate with partners, enhance awareness and engagement of stakeholders, gain insights, mitigate risks, and seize opportunities to reduce and offset emissions.</p>
  <p>Ultimately, courageous leadership and collective diligence across telecommunications company value chains are imperative to drive progress. Telecommunications companies have the influence to spearhead robust and transparent scope 3 practices across all sectors. But, success hinges on prioritizing partnerships, integrity, and environmental stewardship above all. The moment for action has come.</p>
  <p>For more information on how SAP helps companies record, report, and act on their sustainability goals, visit <a href="https://www.sap.com/sustainability.html">www.sap.com/sustainability</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Venkata Rao is a business transformation expert at SAP.<br>Mohan Shekar is head of Industry Service at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-emissions</category>
            <category>news-tag/climate-action</category>
            <category>news-tag/greenhouse-gas-emissions</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-data-exchange</category>
            <category>industry/telecommunications</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Can the Chemicals Industry Capitalize On Carbon Reduction Opportunities?]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/chemicals-industry-sustainability-carbon-reduction-opportunities</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/chemicals-industry-sustainability-carbon-reduction-opportunities</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Companies in the chemicals industry that look to sustainability and carbon reduction will be able to future-proof their business.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10349c35f3512c6fdd74903bfb6f42dba5cc51705.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10349c35f3512c6fdd74903bfb6f42dba5cc51705.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_10349c35f3512c6fdd74903bfb6f42dba5cc51705.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="How Can the Chemicals Industry Capitalize On Carbon Reduction Opportunities?" src="./media_10349c35f3512c6fdd74903bfb6f42dba5cc51705.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="how-can-the-chemicals-industry-capitalize-on-carbon-reduction-opportunities">How Can the Chemicals Industry Capitalize On Carbon Reduction Opportunities?</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>The chemicals industry is a $4 trillion business employing upwards of 20 million people. While a consumer of high volumes of energy and resources, it is also at the forefront of developing energy efficiencies, low carbon and renewable raw materials and fuels, chemical energy storage, and materials from CO2 capture. It is also uniquely positioned to pioneer and promote circular economy models by innovating for the easier reuse and recycling of materials.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>It is simultaneously the third highest contributor to carbon emissions in the industrial sector and the best placed industry to decarbonize products across a multitude of industries.</p>
  <p>As a result of its position high upstream in the supply chain, the chemicals industry can often seem invisible. Its products sit in the value chain of key industries including agriculture, pharmaceuticals, and consumer goods, making up a significant proportion of their Scope 3 emissions. But change is coming that will make companies more accountable for these previously hidden emissions. New legislation such as the European Corporate Sustainability Reporting Directive (CSRD) will reveal the carbon footprint of the chemicals industry as companies with more than 250 employees will be required to report their GHG emissions, including those that lie in Scope 3.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="create-innovative-new-products-increase-agility-and-drive-greener-growth">Create innovative new products, increase agility, and drive greener growth</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/chemicals.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="a-vision-for-the-chemicals-industry">A Vision for the Chemicals Industry</h2>
  <p>In order to meet new legal requirements and identify opportunities for emissions reduction, the chemicals industry needs to look beyond its current tools and collaborations to upgrade the quality of data — based on primary information rather than averages and estimates — and share access to it. Aligning data structures and using the same semantics will encourage competition among suppliers, galvanizing them to manufacture chemical products with ever lower carbon footprints, benefiting all downstream customers as well as the climate. To realize this vision, the solution will receive actual data from suppliers upstream, using a standardized methodology, allowing companies to calculate their own product carbon footprint so it can then be shared with downstream customers. For broad adoption, this carbon data exchange tool needs to be relatively simple while allowing for secure data exchange.</p>
  <p>The automotive industry already has a blueprint that the chemicals industry can adopt. It tracks material flows digitally throughout the entire supply chain. Catena-X allows companies to share standardized emissions data from their supply chain with confidence based on technology that provides an auditable chain of custody. This offers car manufacturers the information they need to make strategic decisions to reduce the carbon footprint of their products, embrace circularity, and increase the adoption of circular business models such as battery recycling. Some of the chemical companies that supply the automotive industry are already involved, such as BASF.</p>
  <p>“As an energy-intensive industry at the beginning of nearly all value chains, the chemical sector plays a key role in reducing global carbon footprint in manufacturing and beyond. Carbon footprint transparency at product level is a fundamental step to achieve this,” said Alessandro Pistillo, director of Digital Strategic Projects at BASF. “BASF is a founding member and very active contributor in global initiatives focused on Scope 3 transparency and product carbon footprint standardization such as Together for Sustainability in the chemical sector, as well as Catena-X and the Global Battery Alliance in the automotive and battery value chain respectively. At the same time, BASF is also a leading member of WBCSD-PACT, whose framework is geared toward ensuring cross-sectoral interoperability.”</p>
  <h2 id="improved-accuracy">Improved Accuracy</h2>
  <p>Historically, industry averages and secondary data have been used to estimate carbon footprints. The cornerstone of the vision for the chemicals industry involves a significant improvement in GHG emissions data, a step that will provide much greater emissions transparency for the industry itself and for its customers. SAP has been working with the World Business Council for Sustainable Development (WBCSD) since 2021 as an innovation partner and has been involved in the Partnership for Carbon Transparency (PACT) initiative, helping to develop the global standards, methodology, and technological infrastructure needed for product-level emission accounting and exchange.</p>
  <h2 id="collaborative-data-exchange">Collaborative Data Exchange</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="record-report-and-act-on-your-sustainability-goals-with-sap">Record, report, and act on your sustainability goals with SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/sustainability.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The desire and the frameworks for the chemicals industry to collaborate already exist. They date back to 1985, with the establishment of the Responsible Care program and the 2011 formation of industry body Together for Sustainability, a worldwide initiative to raise sustainability standards in the chemicals industry’s supply chain. Its members include some of the world’s largest chemical groups, represented by their chief procurement officers. Despite the industry’s ability and willingness to cooperate, and its current pilot IT system for sharing upstream product carbon footprint information, it is still on the cusp of data exchange.</p>
  <p>“Footprint data is there,” said Michael Sambeth, global enterprise architect at SAP. “It can be calculated using out-of-the-box solutions from SAP; now it needs to flow across the supply chain.”</p>
  <p><a href="/topics/catena-x">Catena-X</a> led to the launch of the SAP Sustainability Data Exchange application, which was designed specifically with security in mind, to exchange standardized carbon footprint data along the value chain. SAP Sustainability Data Exchange uses the carbon data standards established by WBCSD PACT. With a high proportion of Together for Sustainability members already using SAP ERP systems, they are well placed to be able to leverage SAP Sustainability Data Exchange to exchange this data with their suppliers and customers while adhering to global standards.</p>
  <h2 id="moving-to-a-green-ledger-approach">Moving to a Green Ledger Approach</h2>
  <p>The chemicals industry is a product of its established supply chains, high-volume activities, cost efficiencies, and scalability. It is highly organized and well versed in creating and following methodologies, but it needs to see the value in primary standardized data — and data sharing — for decarbonization.</p>
  <p>A <a href="/topics/green-ledger">green ledger approach</a> will allow businesses to treat their emissions in the same way as their financials. Carbon accounting makes emission “bookings” part of every business transaction in the same way as financial information. This means that a level of detail and confidence is achieved, allowing companies to look at emissions from any angle — by product, organization, profit center, site, factory, equipment, etc. This granularity is the foundation for planning and steering, which cannot be done using averages or highly aggregated figures.</p>
  <p>The decarbonization of a multitude of industries hinges on the ability of the chemicals industry to successfully standardize and exchange carbon footprint data. Only those chemical companies with sustainability at the core of their strategy and the right tools for high-quality emissions accounting will be able to future-proof their business to remain competitive in the face of the ever-evolving legislative changes created to combat the effects of global warming.</p>
  <p>For more information on how SAP helps companies record, report, and act on their sustainability goals, visit <a href="https://www.sap.com/sustainability.html">www.sap.com/sustainability</a>.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-sap-news-on-linkedin">Connect with SAP News on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/catena-x</category>
            <category>industry/chemicals</category>
            <category>news-tag/green-ledger</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-data-exchange</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Focuses on Key Suppliers to Reduce Carbon Emissions]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/sap-key-suppliers-reduce-carbon-emissions</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/sap-key-suppliers-reduce-carbon-emissions</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP will work with key suppliers to reduce greenhouse gas emissions along the upstream value chain through a supply chain engagement program.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-emissions</category>
            <category>news-tag/net-zero</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-data-exchange</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Decarbonization Through Emission Transparency: Introducing SAP Sustainability Data Exchange]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/introducing-sap-sustainability-data-exchange</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/introducing-sap-sustainability-data-exchange</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The new SAP Sustainability Data Exchange solution is a testament to SAP's commitment to being a champion of a sustainable future.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/green-ledger</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-data-exchange</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-footprint-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Introduces Transactional Carbon Accounting to Accelerate Climate Action]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/sap-introduces-transactional-carbon-accounting</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/sap-introduces-transactional-carbon-accounting</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is well-positioned deliver high-quality carbon accounting to rapidly scale business decarbonization. Learn about the new SAP solutions.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-accounting</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-emissions</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-footprint</category>
            <category>news-tag/climate-action</category>
            <category>news-tag/decarbonization</category>
            <category>news-tag/net-zero</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-data-exchange</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-footprint-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-sustainability-solutions</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP’s Vision for Future-Proofed Business in the Age of AI Comes to Life: SAP Sapphire in 2023]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/sap-sapphire-future-proofed-business-age-of-ai</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/sap-sapphire-future-proofed-business-age-of-ai</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[At SAP Sapphire in 2023, SAP unveiled sweeping innovations that equip customers to tackle an uncertain future with confidence. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/green-ledger</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-data-exchange</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-footprint-management</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>