<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Eastman Energizes HR Reporting to Deliver One-Stop Insights to Leaders]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/eastman-hr-reporting-deliver-insights-to-leaders</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/eastman-hr-reporting-deliver-insights-to-leaders</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Eastman accelerated HR reporting for improved efficiency and insights using story reports in SAP SuccessFactors People Analytics. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>topic/data-analytics</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-preferred-success</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-employee-central</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-people-analytics</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-recruiting</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Coles Reimagines Volume Hiring with AI and Automation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/coles-reimagines-volume-hiring-with-ai-and-automation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/coles-reimagines-volume-hiring-with-ai-and-automation</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Coles uses an AI-powered solution integrated with SAP SuccessFactors to help revolutionize its hiring process and gain speed and efficiency.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_149ed3b06f07dcdc3485b441db14e19620bea42c6.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_149ed3b06f07dcdc3485b441db14e19620bea42c6.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_149ed3b06f07dcdc3485b441db14e19620bea42c6.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Coles Reimagines Volume Hiring with AI and Automation" src="./media_149ed3b06f07dcdc3485b441db14e19620bea42c6.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="coles-reimagines-volume-hiring-with-ai-and-automation">Coles Reimagines Volume Hiring with AI and Automation</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><a href="https://www.colesgroup.com.au/home/">Coles Group</a>, one of Australia’s most trusted and iconic brands, is steadfast in delivering on its purpose to help Australians eat and live better every day. Through its core business as a full-service supermarket retailer, Coles engages with millions of customers every week in its 860 supermarkets throughout Australia. The group’s other areas of business include its Click &#x26; Collect online platform, network of liquor stores, and financial services with nearly 1,000 additional retail outlets.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Guided by the organization’s clear <a href="https://colescareers.com.au/au/en/culture">vision, purpose, and strategy</a>, Coles’ team of 120,000 employees is dedicated to making a difference in the lives of customers and the local communities it serves.</p>
  <p>In fiscal year 2020/21, Coles Group hired nearly 30,000 people to deliver on its business needs. Mike Virgo, head of Talent Acquisition for Coles Group, said this hiring volume was necessary to make sure the company was “positioned well to support our customers.”</p>
  <p>The business environment, however, dramatically shifted as the public health crisis of the pandemic unfolded, resulting in repeated lockdowns and restrictions. As a neighborhood retailer dependent on in-person interaction to deliver most of its services, Coles found its workforce impacted by the pandemic. Faced with supply chain disruptions, panic buying behaviors by consumers, high employee absenteeism, and increased turnover, Coles urgently needed to step up its volume and pace of hiring to support its customers.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="create-ai-powered-experiences-that-drive-real-competitive-advantage-with-sap-successfactors">Create AI-powered experiences that drive real competitive advantage with SAP SuccessFactors</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“Around 2020-2021, we started to experience one of the most significant shifts in the employment market we’d ever seen,” Virgo said in a <a href="https://go3.events.sap.com/successconnect/virtual/2023/reg/flow/sap/sc23/catalog/page/catalog/session/1693098679863001ykJ6">session</a> at <a href="https://www.sap.com/events/successconnect/virtual.html?campaigncode=CRM-YI23-HXM-2055448&#x26;source=text-glo-SAPNews">SuccessConnect Virtual</a>. “It started to create huge challenges for organizations around the world – around how we attract, retain, and hire talent.”</p>
  <h2 id="catalyst-for-change-and-a-new-way-of-working">Catalyst for Change and a New Way of Working</h2>
  <p>To meet pressing business demands, Coles doubled its hiring volume from 30,000 to 60,000 people and increased recruitment advertising spend by a factor of three. Its talent acquisition team grew proportionally to manage the increased workload – but then labored under manual transactional activities that slowed processing times. As a result of the huge strain, variability in the candidate and hiring manager experience became noticeable.</p>
  <p>Due to the volume of work, Coles looked for ways to evolve its system to create more speed, efficiency, and scalability. With a list of criteria, Coles began to review technology solutions on the market to find one that could support its vision for a new way of working. “We wanted to reimagine how we recruit for our stores,” Virgo said. “We needed automation and AI to remove a lot of the manual work in our systems. We wanted to create more consistency and uplift the experiences we were giving our candidates and our hiring managers. And ultimately, [the solution] needed to drive commercial benefit for us.”</p>
  <p>As a key requirement, the new solution needed to integrate with <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/what-is-hxm-suite.html">SAP SuccessFactors Human Experience Management (HXM) Suite</a>. In 2020, as part of an organization-wide <a href="/australia/2021/09/08/how-coles-group-is-transforming-hr-during-the-global-pandemic">digital transformation</a> that introduced SAP S/4HANA and SAP Ariba solutions, Coles modernized its HR and payroll processing, replacing a patchwork of outdated systems with SAP SuccessFactors solutions. It became the first organization in the southern hemisphere to launch all modules of the SAP SuccessFactors portfolio in one go. With all HR processes unified on a single platform, Coles benefits from having a single source of truth for people data that is accurate and available in real time for the entire organization.</p>
  <h2 id="two-way-integration-ensures-single-source-of-truth-in-data">Two-Way Integration Ensures Single Source of Truth in Data</h2>
  <p>To help with the project, Coles chose <a href="https://www.phenom.com/">Phenom</a>, an SAP partner whose AI-powered Intelligent Talent Experience platform provides two-way integration with SAP SuccessFactors solutions. Virgo said the two-way integration “allows us to have a holistic view of the candidates that progress through the process, no matter whether the team is operating in Phenom or SAP SuccessFactors, and it allows SAP SuccessFactors to be our single source of truth.”</p>
  <p>There are several key benefits of Phenom’s solution at Coles. One is candidate attraction and engagement, which is achieved primarily through the Coles career site and chatbot. Another is recruiter automation and interview management, which provides automation and process efficiencies from when a job requisition is created in SAP SuccessFactors solutions and replicated into Phenom until a hiring manager chooses a candidate for the job. Once a candidate is chosen, the two-way integration enables the HR team to access the data in SAP SuccessFactors solutions and complete all compliance aspects, such as working rights, contract generation, and onboarding.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-how-phenom-can-compliment-sap-successfactors-recruiting">Learn how Phenom can compliment SAP SuccessFactors Recruiting</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://store.sap.com/dcp/en/product/display-2001007992_live_v1">Find out</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The Coles team gains additional efficiencies in its onboarding programs through the application of robotic process automation (RPA) powered by two bots that work in the background: <em>Ashbotty</em> processes the working rights and <em>Usain Bot</em> processes onboarding and manages pending recruits. “They take a lot of the transactional, manual work that we used to have team members doing. It can do that quickly, accurately, and it can do that 24/7 – which is particularly important for us as a seven-days-a-week business,” Virgo said.</p>
  <h2 id="ai-powered-experiences-for-candidates-and-recruiters">AI-Powered Experiences for Candidates and Recruiters</h2>
  <p>Coles reimagined the candidate experience to launch a modern, tech-enabled career site – which has been chosen as a two-time winner of Australia’s Best Careers Site. The site includes an AI-powered chatbot to guide candidates as they look for information, search relevant job postings, and submit their applications. It also includes Coles’ Expression of Interest, always-on advertising that drives the growth of its talent pool and advances its talent marketing by reducing the need to advertise every role. A Hosted Apply process, facilitated by integrations with Phenom, presents a consistent candidate experience and increases the conversion rate on applications.</p>
  <p>Phenom AI Scheduling, a key part of Coles’ hiring experience, enables candidates to book themselves an available interview slot and automates the coordination of hiring team calendars. The new solution provides a fully mobile-enabled experience to meet the demands of candidates for an omni-channel, real-time experience where they can learn, read, and apply for jobs where and when they want.</p>
  <p>Inundated by nearly 1 million applications each year to review, Coles also took steps to elevate the recruiter experience and increase the speed and accuracy of candidate screening and job matching. It implemented Phenom Fit Score, an AI-powered feature that assesses a candidate’s suitability for an open role, based on location and optimal travel distances, availability, and working rights; then, assigns a fit score and surfaces the most closely matched candidates to the recruiters. In addition, the new solution empowers in-store managers to collaborate with recruiters to review candidates and make quick hiring decisions with confidence.</p>
  <h2 id="talent-pools-grow-with-improvements-to-hiring-speed-and-efficiency">Talent Pools Grow with Improvements to Hiring Speed and Efficiency</h2>
  <p>With the new augmented solution, Coles is experiencing tangible benefits across multiple categories and key metrics for success: time-to-fill is down six days; time-to-hire is down two days, which is impressive considering candidates can book the in-store interview up to two weeks in advance; and advertising spend is down 50%.</p>
  <p>Most notably for Coles as a people-centric organization is the development of its talent pool, now numbering 2 million potential candidates. It achieves an 85% application conversion rate on up to 1 million applications per year. Through its <a href="https://www.colesgroup.com.au/media-releases/?page=coles-group-ranked-1-for-recruitment-of-aussies-with-disabilities">commitment</a> to be a safe, inclusive, and diverse workplace, Coles has applied the new solution to provide greater accessibility for more diverse candidates, resulting in an increase of 24% more hiring for people who identify as having a disability.</p>
  <p>Virgo said that the talent acquisition team will continue to evolve its solution and assess more opportunities for AI and automation to bring value to the recruitment process. Although these technologies are not cure-alls for every recruitment scenario, they can save recruiting teams precious time and resources to focus on more high-touch interactions further down the recruiting funnel. In sharing lessons learned, Virgo noted, “I think the important call out is the level of automation you can inject in your process will likely diminish as the seniority, complexity, and requirements of your roles increase because they are likely to be more high touch, perhaps need more interpretation or judgment calls from your recruiters to identify who the right talent is for your organization.”</p>
  <p>Watch <a href="https://www.sap.com/events/successconnect/virtual.html?campaigncode=CRM-YI23-HXM-2055448&#x26;source=text-glo-SAPNews">SuccessConnect Virtual</a> on demand.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="follow-sap-news-on-linkedin-to-stay-up-to-date">Follow SAP News on LinkedIn to stay up-to-date</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/automation</category>
            <category>industry/consumer-goods-cpg</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>news-tag/recruiting</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
            <category>sap-event/successconnect</category>
            <category>news-tag/talent-acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ATS Connects HR Processes to Build a Future-Ready Workforce]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/ats-connects-hr-processes-future-ready-workforce</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/ats-connects-hr-processes-future-ready-workforce</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[To modernize its core HR and talent management systems, ATS chose SAP SuccessFactors and its next-generation cloud HR technology. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Realizing Employee Potential with HR Technology]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/realizing-employee-potential-with-hr-technology</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/realizing-employee-potential-with-hr-technology</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[HR leaders can improve employee potential practices and enable unbiased decision-making processes with HR technology. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-opportunity-marketplace</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-performance-goals</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Named a Leader in 2023 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Cloud HCM Suites for 1,000+ Employee Enterprises]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/2023-gartner-mq-cloud-hcm-suites-1000-employee-enterprises</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/2023-gartner-mq-cloud-hcm-suites-1000-employee-enterprises</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is a leader in the Cloud HCM Magic Quadrant for the eight consecutive year as it continues to help drive change within workforces.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-erp-hcm</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-work-zone</category>
            <category>news-tag/ux</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP SuccessFactors Second Half 2023 Release: AI-Driven Innovation to Ignite the Potential in Your Workforce]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/sap-successfactors-second-half-2023-release</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/sap-successfactors-second-half-2023-release</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Our SAP SuccessFactors second half 2023 release is full of AI innovation. Read to learn how we are applying it in our solutions.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-erp-hcm</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-work-zone</category>
            <category>news-tag/ux</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Three Highlights from SuccessConnect 2023]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/three-highlights-from-successconnect-2023</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/three-highlights-from-successconnect-2023</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SuccessConnect 2023 celebrated the HR community, discussed what AI means for the future of work, and shared ideas. Here are the highlights.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_19ceecf9802c64707f3aee1c60f9ef5908b6cd90d.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_19ceecf9802c64707f3aee1c60f9ef5908b6cd90d.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_19ceecf9802c64707f3aee1c60f9ef5908b6cd90d.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Three Highlights from SuccessConnect 2023" src="./media_19ceecf9802c64707f3aee1c60f9ef5908b6cd90d.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="three-highlights-from-successconnect-2023">Three Highlights from SuccessConnect 2023</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Thousands of attendees came to Las Vegas, Nevada, to celebrate the HR community, discuss what artificial intelligence (AI) means for the future of work, and share new ideas for how to ignite the potential within every workforce and business.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Indeed, from the mainstage keynote and breakout sessions to networking with customers and partners, AI was at the center of every conversation. If you weren’t able to attend this year’s event, you can catch the latest product announcements and select content now available <a href="https://go3.events.sap.com/successconnect/virtual/2023/reg/flow/sap/sc23/catalog/page/catalog?tab.sessionplanned=1692641568884001cZ9d">on demand</a>.</p>
  <p>Here are three takeaways from this year’s SuccessConnect.</p>
  <h2 id="the-time-is-now-to-adopt-ai">The Time Is Now to Adopt AI</h2>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="igniting-workforce-potential-with-the-new-sap-successfactors-ai-innovations">Igniting Workforce Potential with the New SAP SuccessFactors AI Innovations</h3>
        <p><em><a href="/2023/10/new-sap-successfactors-ai-innovations-successconnect">Read keynote coverage</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As the pace of technological innovation continues to accelerate, organizations face an incredible opportunity to explore new ways to get work done – ways that take engagement and productivity to new heights for everyone at work. Special guest <a href="https://go3.events.sap.com/successconnect/virtual/2023/reg/flow/sap/sc23/catalog/page/catalog/session/1695684941523001eAp3">Josh Bersin</a>, global industry analyst and CEO of The Josh Bersin Company, discussed the urgent need for companies to get on board with AI, emphasizing how AI can help keep companies ahead of the curve by transforming the employee experience. Bersin also shared ways to increase everyone’s knowledge and confidence when it comes to adopting AI, as well as the real economic benefits organizations can achieve based on early case studies.</p>
  <p>In addition, Julia White, member of the Executive Board of SAP SE and chief marketing and solutions officer, shared what AI means for businesses today and <a href="https://go3.events.sap.com/successconnect/virtual/2023/reg/flow/sap/sc23/catalog/page/catalog/session/1695684941478001eFQ4">how SAP is embedding AI into its cloud HR solutions</a>. She talked about the latest addition to SAP Business AI, <a href="/2023/09/joule-new-generative-ai-assistant">Joule</a> – a natural-language, generative AI copilot designed to help improve the experiences of everyone at work by making it easy for users to find information, get answers to questions, navigate processes, and complete tasks related to HR as well as finance, supply chain, and customer relationship management. She emphasized how Joule, with its AI-powered insight and assistance, can help organizations unlock new levels of performance, productivity, and efficiency.</p>
  <h2 id="talent-intelligence-is-key-to-closing-skills-gaps">Talent Intelligence Is Key to Closing Skills Gaps</h2>
  <p>The power of talent intelligence has far-reaching implications for how organizations can more accurately and efficiently evaluate talent across all levels and address skills gaps. During the event, there was a lot of buzz around the general availability of the <a href="/2023/10/skills-based-organization-talent-intelligence-hub">talent intelligence hub</a>, an AI-powered skills framework that’s built into the foundation of <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/solutions.html?campaigncode=CRM-YI23-HXM-2055448&#x26;source=text-glo-SAPNews">SAP SuccessFactors Human Experience Management (HXM) Suite</a>. Now organizations can have the power and simplicity of a single skills model to fuel everything from recruiting and onboarding to learning and development, as well as performance and succession.</p>
  <p>Sam Passman, vice president, Product Management at SAP SuccessFactors, provided a comprehensive overview of the <a href="https://go3.events.sap.com/successconnect/virtual/2023/reg/flow/sap/sc23/catalog/page/catalog/session/1695684941379001elme">talent intelligence hub</a>, including how organizations can better understand and leverage the skills of their workforce. “An organization that is not focused on skills is going to be left behind,” he said. “Customers often struggle with having visibility into their full skills picture and having employee profile data integrated throughout talent management processes. The talent intelligence hub is how we are making sure our customers can match the right people, doing the right work, at the right time – truly helping them become skills-based organizations.”</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="put-your-people-at-the-center-of-everything-with-sap-successfactors">Put your people at the center of everything with SAP SuccessFactors</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In addition, Tim Gregory, managing director of HR Innovation and Workforce Technology at <a href="https://go3.events.sap.com/successconnect/virtual/2023/reg/flow/sap/sc23/catalog/page/catalog/session/1695684941731001exmK">Delta Air Lines</a>, shared how the company is using SAP SuccessFactors solutions, including the talent intelligence hub, to create personalized career development plans for employees based not only on the skills most important to Delta but also each individual’s capabilities, strengths, and aspirations.</p>
  <p>Other sessions provided tips for becoming a skills-based organization and focused on <a href="https://go3.events.sap.com/successconnect/virtual/2023/reg/flow/sap/sc23/catalog/page/catalog/session/1693098679964001yjIr">how to get ready for the talent intelligence hub</a> and use it to help guide actions across all areas of talent management and development. And, of course, a live demonstration brought the talent intelligence hub to life as part of the <a href="https://go3.events.sap.com/successconnect/virtual/2023/reg/flow/sap/sc23/catalog/page/catalog/session/1692366446499001bBgm">SuccessConnect keynote</a>.</p>
  <h2 id="a-powerful-cloud-foundation-drives-true-hr-transformation">A Powerful Cloud Foundation Drives True HR Transformation</h2>
  <p>Having a cloud-based HR foundation is key for achieving true HR transformation – the kind of transformation that makes data-driven insights, smarter decision-making, automation, and a positive employee experience a reality. At the event, Mihael Sutalo, vice president, People Technology at <a href="https://go3.events.sap.com/successconnect/virtual/2023/reg/flow/sap/sc23/catalog/page/catalog/session/1695672921270001Czuo">Pandora</a>, the world’s leading jewelry brand, shared how the company is digitalizing HR and adopting new technologies to create amazing employee experiences as a unified, global company. “We wanted to scale to future-proof the company, and we believe strongly in the power of the cloud,” he said. He explained how Pandora has successfully moved from a fragmented HR landscape to SAP SuccessFactors HXM Suite, improving the company’s ability to attract and retain top talent.</p>
  <p>Avery Williams, manager of HR Operations Strategy at <a href="https://go3.events.sap.com/successconnect/virtual/2023/reg/flow/sap/sc23/catalog/page/catalog/session/1693098680331001ybtw">Starbucks Corporation</a>, also discussed how the company modernized its core HR technology, service delivery, and employee and partner experience by migrating 250,000 employees and partners from the legacy, on-premise SAP ERP Human Capital Management solution to a new cloud-based platform with <a href="https://go3.events.sap.com/successconnect/virtual/2023/reg/flow/sap/sc23/catalog/page/catalog/session/1695684941222001ejfa">SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central</a>.</p>
  <p>In addition, Todd Asevedo, GVP, chief expert, SAP, shared a host of best practices for how customers can minimize risk and disruption as they <a href="https://go3.events.sap.com/successconnect/virtual/2023/reg/flow/sap/sc23/catalog/page/catalog/session/1693098680290001ycKR">make the move</a> from SAP ERP HCM to the cloud. He also outlined the various deployment options to help organizations understand the transition paths available for a smooth migration.</p>
  <p>Couldn’t attend the in-person event? You can get the best of SuccessConnect wherever you are! Be sure to access the <a href="https://go3.events.sap.com/successconnect/virtual/2023/reg/flow/sap/sc23/catalog/page/catalog?tab.sessionplanned=1692641568884001cZ9d&#x26;search.sessiontype=sessionType_keynote">keynotes</a>, <a href="https://go3.events.sap.com/successconnect/virtual/2023/reg/flow/sap/sc23/catalog/page/catalog?tab.sessionplanned=1692641568884001cZ9d&#x26;search.sessiontype=1693097660680001RkSd&#x26;search.sessiontype=1695686379399001hUNT">customer success stories</a>, and <a href="https://go3.events.sap.com/successconnect/virtual/2023/reg/flow/sap/sc23/catalog/page/catalog?tab.sessionplanned=1692641568884001cZ9d&#x26;search.sessiontype=1679388717208002sub4">expert sessions</a>, including road maps, product demos, and more, all available <a href="https://go3.events.sap.com/successconnect/virtual/2023/reg/flow/sap/sc23/catalog/page/catalog?tab.sessionplanned=1692641568884001cZ9d">on demand</a>. Plus, don’t forget to sign up to stay informed about the <a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/nl/successconnect/index.html">SuccessConnect event in 2024</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Lara Albert is global vice president of Solution Marketing for SAP SuccessFactors.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-sap-news-delivered-right-to-your-inbox">Get the latest SAP news delivered right to your inbox</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/nl/sap-news-center-newsletter/index.html">Sign up now</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-employee-central</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
            <category>sap-event/successconnect</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Igniting Workforce Potential with the New SAP SuccessFactors AI Innovations]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/new-sap-successfactors-ai-innovations-successconnect</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/new-sap-successfactors-ai-innovations-successconnect</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[At SuccessConnect, SAP announced new innovations around AI and talent intelligence to help organizations address their skills gaps.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-opportunity-marketplace</category>
            <category>sap-event/successconnect</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Power a Skills-Based Organization with the Talent Intelligence Hub]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/skills-based-organization-talent-intelligence-hub</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/skills-based-organization-talent-intelligence-hub</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The talent intelligence hub, an AI-powered skills framework built into SAP SuccessFactors HXM Suite, is now generally available. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
            <category>sap-event/successconnect</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Recognized as a Strategic Leader in 2023 Fosway 9-Grid™ for Cloud HR]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/sap-strategic-leader-2023-fosway-9-grid-cloud-hr</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/sap-strategic-leader-2023-fosway-9-grid-cloud-hr</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Fosway named SAP SuccessFactors as a Strategic Leader in its 2023 9-Grid for Cloud HR. Read to learn more about the recognition.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Delivering a People-Centered User Experience with SAP SuccessFactors Solutions]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/delivering-people-centered-ux-with-sap-successfactors</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/delivering-people-centered-ux-with-sap-successfactors</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn about the focus of recent UX innovation and investment at SAP SuccessFactors and why a superior user experience enables efficient work.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-opportunity-marketplace</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-work-zone</category>
            <category>news-tag/ux</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How AI Is Revolutionizing the User Experience for HR]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/hr-flow-of-work-ux-evolution</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/hr-flow-of-work-ux-evolution</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The modern digital shift in UX involves embedding high-value, critical HR tasks directly into applications employees use daily. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11c1aad13f445550b3d2f80df49ae85345a288923.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11c1aad13f445550b3d2f80df49ae85345a288923.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_11c1aad13f445550b3d2f80df49ae85345a288923.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="How AI Is Revolutionizing the User Experience for HR" src="./media_11c1aad13f445550b3d2f80df49ae85345a288923.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="how-ai-is-revolutionizing-the-user-experience-for-hr">How AI Is Revolutionizing the User Experience for HR</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Rapidly evolving technology presents endless possibilities for enhancing the user experience (UX). SAP is seizing this moment to usher in a new era of efficiency, productivity, and engagement for businesses and their employees by integrating HR processes into the flow of work.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="ai-in-hr-cultivate-a-dynamic-inclusive-and-future-ready-workforce">AI in HR: Cultivate a dynamic, inclusive, and future-ready workforce</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence.html#active_tab_item_1680651733277">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>A prime example of this modern digital shift in UX is embedding high-value, critical HR tasks directly into the applications employees use daily. By integrating <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/solutions.html">SAP SuccessFactors Human Experience Management (HXM) Suite</a> with other workplace technology solutions, SAP enables people to perform HR tasks without interrupting their daily work.</p>
  <p>All of us have seen how artificial intelligence (AI) can increase process efficiency and productivity, reduce human errors, and elevate user standards. But UX will change the most as the potential for new AI capabilities and models is expanded to address pressing business needs and employee expectations.</p>
  <h2 id="shaping-the-user-experience-with-a-purpose">Shaping the User Experience with a Purpose</h2>
  <p>Whether predictive, conversational, or generative, advancements in business AI are expected to bring the most significant shift in how people use technology at work.</p>
  <p>By investing in AI to strengthen SAP SuccessFactors HXM Suite, SAP supports how people naturally interact, get work done, and leverage technology in the workplace. And best of all, we are doing it ethically by following our guiding principles to be:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Relevant:</strong> Helping users get greater insights and perform tasks more efficiently with AI designed with business context in mind to enhance the flow of work</li>
    <li><strong>Reliable:</strong> Using AI that is trained on the customer’s industry and company data and accessible in the solutions used each day</li>
    <li><strong>Responsible:</strong> Running responsible AI built on leading ethics and data privacy standards while maintaining full governance and lifecycle management across an entire organization</li>
  </ul>
  <p>By only employing AI technology that meets our stringent standards, we help our customers ensure the delivery of a meaningful and engaging UX for their entire workforce. Doing so allows employees to not only reach their full potential but also feel accomplished, supported, and engaged.</p>
  <p>For instance, HR professionals and their stakeholders are unlocking higher engagement and productivity for their employees, organizations, and businesses through their recruitment and talent development processes. One of the ways this is being accomplished is by unifying SAP SuccessFactors solutions with leading business productivity applications such as Microsoft Teams and further enhancing that integration with AI embedded in SAP SuccessFactors solutions to generate suggestions and recommendations using natural language.</p>
  <p>This business-oriented AI innovation represents some of the fundamental changes SAP is creating to transform how people will experience work in the years to come.</p>
  <h2 id="future-ready-hr-for-a-future-ready-workforce">Future-Ready HR for a Future-Ready Workforce</h2>
  <p>Our AI-enabled use cases for SAP SuccessFactors HXM Suite are exceptional evidence of how HR tasks — from talent acquisition and talent management to core HR processes — can become a natural extension of people’s everyday work experience.</p>
  <p>Consider the value of these scenarios heavily used in the recruiting process:</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Creating Job Descriptions</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Hiring managers and recruiters can fine-tune job descriptions with generative AI within the SAP SuccessFactors Recruiting solution. This allows them to incorporate supplementary content, identify biased language, and help ensure alignment with business requirements. Once the final version is approved by the appropriate hiring manager and assigned recruiter, the job description can be published in SAP SuccessFactors solutions.</p>
  <p>Instead of starting from scratch every time a new position is created or requirements are updated, recruiters and hiring managers can draft job descriptions faster and stay in their normal flow of work. And more importantly, the final content is more meaningful, inclusive, and competitive — attracting a larger pool of qualified and interested candidates.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Interviewing Candidates</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Hiring managers can construct unbiased and more effective interview questions by using AI-generated prompts, creating an exceptional impression on the candidate and leading to the right decision for both parties.</p>
  <p>Recruiters and hiring managers can also provide their assessment of candidates throughout the process through Microsoft Teams, which is then captured by SAP SuccessFactors Recruiting for further evaluation.</p>
  <h2 id="the-right-time-to-ignite-hrs-full-potential">The Right Time to Ignite HR’s Full Potential</h2>
  <p>To learn more about how adding HR processes into the flow of work with business AI can redefine the user experience for your employees, register for <a href="https://go3.events.sap.com/successconnect/virtual/2023/reg/flow/sap/sc23/catalog/page/catalog?tab.sessionplanned=1692641568884001cZ9d">SuccessConnect Virtual</a> to access a variety of breakout sessions, demos, Q&#x26;A sessions and more on this topic, all available on-demand, including:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><a href="https://go3.events.sap.com/successconnect/virtual/2023/reg/flow/sap/sc23/catalog/page/catalog/session/1693098679922001ykzQ">Uncovering the Value and Ethics of AI for Recruiting</a></li>
    <li><a href="https://go3.events.sap.com/successconnect/virtual/2023/reg/flow/sap/sc23/catalog/page/catalog/session/1693931342129001bIIT">How AI Is Revolutionizing the User Experience</a></li>
  </ul>
  <p>Take this opportunity to explore new opportunities to redefine your HR experience — setting the foundation for igniting the potential of your workforce and meeting the demands of a changing world.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>AJ Whalen is a senior director of Solution Marketing at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-recruiting</category>
            <category>news-tag/ux</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Eurobank Achieves Compliance with New Labor Law Supported by Accuracy of SAP SuccessFactors Time Tracking]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/eurobank-labor-law-compliance-sap-successfactors-time-tracking</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/eurobank-labor-law-compliance-sap-successfactors-time-tracking</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Eurobank achieves compliance with Greece’s labor law by using SAP SuccessFactors Time Tracking solution for data on employee working hours.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How the “Broken Rung” Is Impacting Women in the Workplace and How HXM Technology Can Help]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/broken-rung-women-in-workplace-hxm-technology</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/broken-rung-women-in-workplace-hxm-technology</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Organizations are using SAP SuccessFactors solutions to address the "broken rung" and other systemic biases in the workplace.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d46530ef90cfa2cd40a0002001a263d2368e417e.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d46530ef90cfa2cd40a0002001a263d2368e417e.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1d46530ef90cfa2cd40a0002001a263d2368e417e.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="How the “Broken Rung” Is Impacting Women in the Workplace and How HXM Technology Can Help" src="./media_1d46530ef90cfa2cd40a0002001a263d2368e417e.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="how-the-broken-rung-is-impacting-women-in-the-workplace-and-how-hxm-technology-can-help">How the “Broken Rung” Is Impacting Women in the Workplace and How HXM Technology Can Help</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Representation of women in leadership has been increasing in recent years. However, only about 25% of C-suite leaders and 40% of manager-level positions are held by women today. According to psychologists, biased perceptions of women in the workplace may be partially to blame, preventing women from obtaining and being successful in leadership-level roles. The inability to access higher levels of leadership is termed the “broken rung,” and there is still a lot of work to do to repair it.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Recently, a group of psychologists at the annual Society for Industrial &#x26; Organizational Psychology conference met to present emerging research on the broken rung. Caitlynn Sendra, Ph.D., experience product scientist at SAP SuccessFactors, who hosted the session, explained that because of the roles men and women historically held in society, our stereotypes around men and women can carry over into today’s workplace, even if not intentionally. “Men are stereotypically thought to be agentic, direct, and task-focused – traits historically associated with leaders. On the other hand, women are stereotyped to be nurturing, communal, and community-focused,” explained Sendra. Although this has led women to be seen as less leader-like, Sendra presented original research on how this may actually give women leaders an advantage when it comes to influencing organizational culture.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-the-latest-research-from-the-sap-successfactors-growth--insights-team">Read the latest research from the SAP SuccessFactors Growth &#x26; Insights team</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/dg/hr-meta-trends-2023/index.html?campaigncode=CRM-YI23-HXM-2055448&#x26;source=ctabutton-glo-SAPNews">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Throughout the session, the researchers presented data on several different sources of potential bias around women leaders, including 360-degree reviews, “high-potential” programs, and feedback. For example, Dr. Martin Lanik, CEO of Pinsight, demonstrated that men are three times more likely than women to be identified as “high potential.” Additionally, Dr. Stefanie Mockler, co-founder of The Violet Group, showed data indicating that managers tended to “soften” their feedback to women. The message of the session was clear: businesses need to be proactive in removing this bias from people processes in order to level the playing field for women leaders.</p>
  <p>The session ended with a discussion about what <a href="/topics/human-resources">HR</a> leaders can do to help reduce bias towards women leaders. Providing training on bias awareness and reduction was one solution provided by the researchers. HR technology was also called out as a key piece of the puzzle.</p>
  <p>At SAP, we’re working with organizations of all sizes to help drive more equitable and inclusive HR strategies that empower equitable experiences for every employee, including women. With embedded features throughout <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm.html?campaigncode=CRM-YI23-HXM-2055448&#x26;source=text-glo-SAPNews">SAP SuccessFactors Human Experience Management (HXM) Suite</a>, our customers are provided with the tools they need to help detect and prevent unconscious bias while also gaining the insights required to make decisions that can cultivate a diverse and inclusive workforce.</p>
  <p>Here are three examples of how organizations are using SAP SuccessFactors solutions to help solve for the broken rung and other systemic biases in the workplace:</p>
  <h3 id="sanlam">Sanlam</h3>
  <p><a href="https://www.sap.com/asset/dynamic/2022/11/7c370ed5-4e7e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Sanlam</a> is one of the largest financial services groups in South Africa and believes building a diverse, future-ready workforce is key to becoming the unrivaled industry leader in Africa and to strengthening its position abroad. With 105,000 team members, including both permanent employees and contingent staff, Sanlam is committed to ensuring access and opportunity across its total workforce.</p>
  <p>With SAP SuccessFactors solutions, Sanlam is bridging the gap between permanent and contingent workers by providing a consistent experience for all workers. With visibility into the total workforce, management can identify skill gaps and offer all workers development opportunities that match future priorities. And with group-wide analytics, Sanlam’s leadership can set and actively track targets around race, gender, and disability.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="understand-what-your-people-need-how-they-work-and-what-motivates-them">Understand what your people need, how they work, and what motivates them</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm.html">Explore SAP SuccessFactors solutions</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“We have all the information we need at the drop of a hat,” said Ronel Pfotenhauer, SAP SuccessFactors portfolio product owner, Sanlam Life Insurance Limited. “For instance, we can report on the number of Black, African females with five years of experience and an MBA as potential candidates for a leadership role, with SAP SuccessFactors solutions acting as a type of internal recruitment portal.”</p>
  <h3 id="the-university-of-toronto">The University of Toronto</h3>
  <p>The University of Toronto’s mission is to build a community where academic and learning opportunities are given to every member of its community, including 12,000 full-time and 14,000 part-time employees across three campuses. Its recent work on the anti-Black racism task force and similar initiatives to do with anti-semitism and anti-Asian racism demonstrates the organization’s commitment to ensuring the principles of equity, diversity, and inclusion are deeply embedded in the fabric of everything it does.</p>
  <p>With SAP SuccessFactors solutions, the University of Toronto is bringing a consistent look and feel to the employee experience, providing comprehensive learning programs and empowering people leaders to create the conditions for all talent to thrive. <a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2022/12/cc9d1c23-5f7e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Watch this video to see how</a>.</p>
  <h3 id="mod-pizza">MOD Pizza</h3>
  <p><a href="https://www.sap.com/asset/dynamic/2023/07/623a5dca-807e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">MOD Pizza</a> is dedicated to making positive social impacts in the lives of its employees and the communities it serves. The company strives to create a more equitable world full of opportunities for those who face barriers to steady employment, such as people formerly incarcerated as well as individuals with intellectual or developmental disabilities. It calls its community of employees the MOD Squad, and the MOD Squad is 10,000 employees strong and growing along with the company.</p>
  <p>With SAP SuccessFactors solutions, MOD Pizza has redefined the value of HR data, processes, and experiences – putting the MOD Squad at the heart of its business success. All candidates and new hires are provided with a welcoming experience to help them feel supported and prepared. All employees are provided with on-demand digital training to encourage continuous learning and growth. And with multiple touchpoints to gather sentiment feedback, MOD Pizza can quickly identify areas for potential improvement.</p>
  <p>“SAP’s dedication to people sustainability struck a chord with us. This focus continues to show us that SAP solutions are the right choice for MOD Pizza because they’re designed to create a fair future full of opportunities for our employees,” said Tara Gambill, senior director of Enterprise Systems, MOD Pizza LLC.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Carrie Klauss is global director of Solution Marketing at SAP SuccessFactors.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-sap-news-delivered-to-your-inbox-every-week">Get the latest SAP news delivered to your inbox every week</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/nl/sap-news-center-newsletter/index.html">Sign up</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
            <category>news-tag/women-in-leadership</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Versuni Gains Agility with HXM and Connected Cloud ERP as Strong Data Foundation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/versuni-hxm-cloud-erp-strong-data-foundation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/versuni-hxm-cloud-erp-strong-data-foundation</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Versuni achieved a successful HR transformation in 10 months, deploying SAP SuccessFactors solutions in a greenfield implementation.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>industry/consumer-goods-cpg</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>sap-award/sap-innovation-awards</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-employee-central</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-learning</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-work-zone</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Five Things to Look Forward to at SuccessConnect 2023]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/five-things-at-successconnect-2023</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/five-things-at-successconnect-2023</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[At SuccessConnect 2023, we are bringing together our HR community, along with inspiration, ideas, and solutions. Here's what to expect.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
            <category>sap-event/successconnect</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[On-Premise Customers Realizing Benefits of Moving HR to SAP SuccessFactors]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/benefits-moving-on-premise-hr-to-sap-successfactors</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/benefits-moving-on-premise-hr-to-sap-successfactors</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[At SAP SuccessFactors, we continue to make investments to streamline the transition for our on-premise customers with focused initiatives]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1cbfc53de6444e8aa82313cbc8457262f0c9abf49.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1cbfc53de6444e8aa82313cbc8457262f0c9abf49.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1cbfc53de6444e8aa82313cbc8457262f0c9abf49.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="On-Premise Customers Realizing Benefits of Moving HR to SAP SuccessFactors" src="./media_1cbfc53de6444e8aa82313cbc8457262f0c9abf49.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="on-premise-customers-realizing-benefits-of-moving-hr-to-sap-successfactors">On-Premise Customers Realizing Benefits of Moving HR to SAP SuccessFactors</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Organizations are constantly looking for ways to enhance their operational efficiency and provide a better experience for their workforce.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>I spent many years of my career working on SAP ERP Human Capital Management (HCM) on-premise and it is very near and dear to my heart. But, I am also a big believer in using innovative modern technology to help organizations run their business as efficiently as possible and get the most out of their people. We are seeing an increased urgency for customers to transform their HR operations to improve agility and productivity in a constantly changing world.</p>
  <p>For Maryann Abbajay, chief revenue officer at SAP SuccessFactors, the readiness of many of our customers to begin their cloud HR journeys is accelerating. “So far in 2023, we are seeing increased momentum of SAP on-premise customers moving to the cloud. In the first half of the year, we saw well over 100 customers sign up to move their core HCM or payroll to the cloud,” she said. “We’re gearing up to increase this pace in the second half of the year as well.”</p>
  <p>More importantly, a move to the cloud is about achieving success and better business results, which includes large and complex businesses. Here are a few recent examples of customers that are realizing benefits with the move:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><a href="https://www.sap.com/asset/dynamic/2022/11/80daf380-4d7e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Microsoft</a> has been able to create consistent employee experiences worldwide for its 220,000 employees in over 100 countries. With a move to the cloud, it can create jobs much faster and become a more agile business.</li>
    <li><a href="https://www.sap.com/asset/dynamic/2023/04/7a53dae4-6c7e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Purolator</a> has created organizational agility while providing a better experience for employees. The integration of HR and finance is helping the company make better business decisions.</li>
    <li><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/customer-stories/roehm.html">Röhm</a> has been able to standardize its processes leading to significantly reduced HR IT costs. It can now better support and empower employees with a new digital HR experience.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>At SAP SuccessFactors, we continue to make a substantial investment to streamline the transition for our existing customers with focused initiatives. These include the introduction of the SAP Readiness Check tool for SAP SuccessFactors solutions, where we continue to see <a href="https://blogs.sap.com/2023/02/17/sap-readiness-check-for-successfactors-customer-momentum/">increased adoption</a> with nearly 150 customers, including those with over 100,000 employees, running it to help jump-start a move to the cloud.</p>
  <p>We’ve also delivered product investments focused on meeting the business requirements of SAP ERP HCM based upon direct customer feedback. This includes enhancements to <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/employee-central-hris.html">SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central</a>, building a leading <a href="/2022/09/sap-industry-leading-time-management-suite">time management suite</a>, and an emphasis on hybrid customers by building enhanced data and process integrations for a best-in-class experience for customers that continue to use on premise along with SAP SuccessFactors solutions.</p>
  <p>A few years ago, I wrote an article on a dozen improvements in SAP SuccessFactors Human Experience Management (HXM) Suite, which had a direct comparison between on premise and the cloud. It becomes clear that there are a lot of advantages to moving to SAP SuccessFactors solutions, but in 2023 we face a complex economic landscape and many companies are being intentional about where to invest their time and resources.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="simplify-your-move-from-on-premise-hcm-to-the-cloud-with-sap-successfactors">Simplify your move from on-premise HCM to the cloud with SAP SuccessFactors</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/hxm-move.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="building-a-business-case-to-support-moving-hr-to-the-cloud">Building a Business Case to Support Moving HR to the Cloud</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-the-infographic-moving-from-sap-erp-hcm-to-sap-successfactors-solutions">Read the infographic: Moving from SAP ERP HCM to SAP SuccessFactors Solutions</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2023/07/aa55462b-7e7e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html?campaigncode=CRM-YI23-HXM-2053446&#x26;source=text-glo-SAPNews">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>To help customers make the business case, we recently worked with a third-party vendor, Enterprise Strategy Group (ESG) by TechTarget, to analyze the economic benefits of moving from SAP ERP HCM to SAP SuccessFactors HXM Suite. To complete the analysis, ESG conducted multiple customer interviews, used its industry knowledge, leveraged public data, and evaluated SAP SuccessFactors solutions to build a comprehensive model that compared the cost and benefits of HR operations of SAP SuccessFactors solutions versus continued use of SAP ERP HCM.</p>
  <p>The research contained four categories in which customers would expect to see a benefit: improved experience for all employees, more efficient HR and IT operations, improved business agility and enablement, and unique SAP advantages.</p>
  <p>The result of this analysis validated how organizations can realize over 100% ROI through increased organizational efficiency. Learn more: <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/hxm-move.html?pdf-asset=aa55462b-7e7e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b&#x26;page=1&#x26;url_id=ctabutton-us-move-esginfographic">Analyzing the Economic Benefits of Moving from SAP ERP HCM to SAP SuccessFactors HXM Suite.</a></p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Imran Sajid is senior director of HXM Solution Marketing at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-erp-hcm</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP SuccessFactors First Half 2023 Release: Skill-Centric Innovation to Build Your Future-Ready Workforce]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/sap-successfactors-first-half-2023-release</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/sap-successfactors-first-half-2023-release</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With the SAP SuccessFactors first half 2023 release, we continue to deliver on our promise to help build future-ready workforces. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/future-of-work</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-employee-central</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-opportunity-marketplace</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-work-zone</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP SuccessFactors Unlocks Global Innovation Velocity with Next-Generation Cloud Delivery]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/sap-successfactors-next-generation-cloud-delivery</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/sap-successfactors-next-generation-cloud-delivery</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Next-Generation Cloud Delivery creates the foundation for our SAP SuccessFactors innovation road map. Read to learn more about the campaign.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/dynamic-teams</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Great Resignation Points to a Serious Sustainability Issue]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/great-resignation-serious-sustainability-issue</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/great-resignation-serious-sustainability-issue</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The Great Resignation is a sustainability warning to companies that have not focused on culture and leadership for a while. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/people-sustainability</category>
            <category>news-tag/qualtrics</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-workforce-analytics</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP SuccessFactors Second Half 2022 Release: Building a Future-Ready Workforce Today]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/sap-successfactors-second-half-2022-release</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/sap-successfactors-second-half-2022-release</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The SAP SuccessFactors second half 2022 release introduces new innovations around creating an agile and future-ready workforce. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1074c8b37f11498501b456579a1cc6d70dabc96f4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1074c8b37f11498501b456579a1cc6d70dabc96f4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1074c8b37f11498501b456579a1cc6d70dabc96f4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP SuccessFactors Second Half 2022 Release: Building a Future-Ready Workforce Today" src="./media_1074c8b37f11498501b456579a1cc6d70dabc96f4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-successfactors-second-half-2022-release-building-a-future-ready-workforce-today">SAP SuccessFactors Second Half 2022 Release: Building a Future-Ready Workforce Today</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>In today’s business landscape, organizations must equip themselves to respond to workforce opportunities or challenges <em>before</em> they arise. If recent trends have taught us anything, it’s that by the time a business reacts to a market shift, a new one is already occurring. Staying a step ahead of workforce demands is no longer a step ahead – it’s step one.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The SAP SuccessFactors second half 2022 release, which is available for preview today, introduces new innovations focused on empowering organizations to create an agile and future-ready workforce in a rapidly changing workplace as well as further investments for individualized experiences and agile and compliant HR.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="realizing-a-people-centered-future-of-work-through-the-intelligent-enterprise">Realizing a People-Centered Future of Work Through the Intelligent Enterprise</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/06/people-centered-future-of-work-intelligent-enterprise-hxm">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="creating-a-future-ready-workforce">Creating a Future-Ready Workforce</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="change-the-world-of-work-for-good-with-the-next-generation-of-hcm-software-from-sap">Change the world of work for good with the next generation of HCM software from SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In the face of increasingly complex and more urgent transformations, organizations must accelerate their talent development at scale. At the core of such adaptability is an understanding of the skills organizations need to build and grow. As part of our early adopter care program, select customers will have access to skills ontology, growth portfolio, and dynamic teams, which work together to deliver greater intelligence on the skills and capabilities that currently exist and are needed within an organization.</p>
  <p><strong>The skills ontology</strong> is a major advancement for SAP SuccessFactors that’s connected to global skills databases to help ensure that organizations have a comprehensive and up-to-date view of the most important skills for their workforce. It delivers machine learning and artificial intelligence (AI) powered recommendations to employees about relevant and trending skills to prioritize for development.</p>
  <p><strong>The growth portfolio</strong>, also part of the early adopter care program, is how employees can reveal their skills, capabilities, education, language proficiencies, and certifications. In the second half release, this data will connect employees to the most relevant assignments in <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/opportunity-marketplace.html">SAP SuccessFactors Opportunity Marketplace</a>. While the skills ontology gives organizations the ability to align talent development to the ambitions of the organization, the growth portfolio enables employees to align their own talent development to their ambitions.</p>
  <p><strong>Dynamic teams</strong> is also part of the SAP SuccessFactors foundation and available to all customers. Within organizations today, there are countless teams that exist outside of traditional organizational structures – groups of people that work cross-functionally on a project for a certain amount of time. The dynamic teams functionality can provide organizations with visibility into these teams as well as tools to help manage and assemble teams. Team progress can be measured using objectives and key results (OKRs) and employees can find a dynamic team within SAP SuccessFactors Opportunity Marketplace to help learn new skills and continue to grow their career. This transparency within the organization levels the playing field and creates equal opportunity for employees.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11660a4ded960363037d3e57f808136c91669c786.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11660a4ded960363037d3e57f808136c91669c786.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_11660a4ded960363037d3e57f808136c91669c786.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_11660a4ded960363037d3e57f808136c91669c786.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="534">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p><em>Click to enlarge</em></p>
  <p>With richer data and greater talent intelligence, organizations can help ensure that employees are connected to the most relevant talent development opportunities that are aligned to the ambitions of employees and the needs of the organization. Skills ontology, growth portfolio, and dynamic teams provide significant updates to the foundation of <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/hxm-suite.html">SAP SuccessFactors Human Experience Management (HXM) Suite</a> – built into what customers already have instead of requiring an entirely new solution.</p>
  <p>Some more exciting features for our second half 2022 release are around individualized experiences and agile and compliant HR, including:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Chosen name and personal pronouns:</strong> As part of our commitment to diversity, equity, and inclusion, we are taking important steps to help every individual be seen and valued. People can now indicate their chosen name, personal pronouns, and gender directly within the people profile. This information is displayed consistently across SAP SuccessFactors solutions – from recruiting to learning, helping to foster a greater sense of belonging.</li>
    <li><strong>End-to-end visual redesign:</strong> We are enhancing the overall look and feel of SAP SuccessFactors by implementing the Horizon visual theme for SAP Fiori. This new theme enhances consistency while delivering a more informed and streamlined product experience. Employees will find nearly every element of the solution updated with new colors, typography, iconography, layouts, and visual hierarchy focused on intent and success. We remain on track to have every employee-facing SAP SuccessFactors experience unified with the theme by the end of 2023.</li>
    <li><strong>SAP SuccessFactors Work Zone guided onboarding experience:</strong> By bringing together SAP SuccessFactors solutions and third-party integrations, organizations can more efficiently handle an array of complex onboarding processes. This new feature helps ensure that employees receive individualized experiences, even before their first day. Covering key phases of the new hire journey, the guided onboarding experience for <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/workzone-hr.html">SAP SuccessFactors Work Zone</a> helps provide the tools and information employees need, both before and after hiring.</li>
    <li><strong>Cross-system workflow capability:</strong> We are unveiling a new cross-system workflow capability for processes that involve multiple users from multiple systems, such as SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central and the payroll component of SAP ERP Human Capital Management. A guided activity framework for key processes enables our on-premise customers to more rapidly unlock the value of the cloud with SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central and the latest HXM innovations while maintaining and progressively moving on-premise processes to the cloud over time.</li>
    <li><strong>Time management enhancements:</strong> We are continuing to <a href="/2022/09/sap-industry-leading-time-management-suite">enhance our capabilities in time management</a> with the much-anticipated ability to export leave events into calendar applications along with better support for public holidays and handling of grace rules. Time administrators can now copy time-related configuration objects, reducing the need for manual duplication during configuration. In addition, temporary work schedules and absence information on a per day basis will now be available for reporting in SAP SuccessFactors People Analytics.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>All these and many more exciting features will be available in our 2H 2022 release, in preview today and production on Friday, December 9. Please watch our <a href="https://dam.sap.com/mac/app/p/video/asset/preview/KvodB4Q?ltr=a&#x26;rc=10">second half 2022 release highlights video</a> for more information.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Amy Wilson is senior vice president of Products and Design for SAP SuccessFactors.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>news-tag/dynamic-teams</category>
            <category>news-tag/future-of-work</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-erp-hcm</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-opportunity-marketplace</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-work-zone</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Five Highlights from SuccessConnect 2022]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/five-takeaways-from-successconnect-2022</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/five-takeaways-from-successconnect-2022</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SuccessConnect was finally back in person after three years! Here are five key takeaways if you missed the in-person event.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/future-of-work</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
            <category>sap-event/successconnect</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How SAP Has Built an Industry-Leading Time Management Suite One Day at a Time]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/09/sap-industry-leading-time-management-suite</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/09/sap-industry-leading-time-management-suite</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP SuccessFactors has built an intuitive time management solution that uses localization, compliance, and local language. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors-hcm-suite</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-work-zone</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Five Things to Look Forward to at SuccessConnect 2022]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/five-things-look-forward-to-successconnect-2022</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/five-things-look-forward-to-successconnect-2022</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[For new or longtime SAP SuccessFactors customers as well as companies looking to make a move, here’s what to expect at SuccessConnect 2022.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-people-analytics</category>
            <category>sap-event/successconnect</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Great Lakes Cheese Accomplishes Smooth HR Transformation with Change Management Plan]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/06/great-lakes-cheese-hr-transformation-change-management-plan</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/06/great-lakes-cheese-hr-transformation-change-management-plan</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Great Lakes Cheese built a change management plan to empower employees and streamline HR processes with the adoption of SAP SuccessFactors.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/capgemini</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How HR Transformation Is Changing in a New Hybrid Era]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/06/how-hr-transformation-is-changing-hybrid-cloud-era</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/06/how-hr-transformation-is-changing-hybrid-cloud-era</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Many organizations view the cloud as a viable, long-term choice for HR transformation. Learn what deployment option is best for your business.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-hxm-movement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Sanlam Developed a Diverse, Engaged, and Future-Ready Workforce]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/sanlam-diverse-engaged-future-ready-workforce</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/sanlam-diverse-engaged-future-ready-workforce</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Sanlam launched a HR shared services model using SAP solutions to embrace a total workforce management strategy. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/contingent-workforce-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>sap-award/sap-innovation-awards</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
            <category>news-tag/total-workforce-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/well-being-at-work</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Banking On a People-Centric Digital Transformation for Continued Success]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/banco-atlantida-people-centric-digital-transformation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/banco-atlantida-people-centric-digital-transformation</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[During COVID-19, Banco Atlántida digitally transformed so customers could continue to complete their financial activities uninterrupted.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/banking</category>
            <category>news-tag/covid-19</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-employee-central</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Discovery Creates a Culture of People Empowerment]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/04/discovery-creates-culture-of-people-empowerment</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/04/discovery-creates-culture-of-people-empowerment</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Discovery chose SAP SuccessFactors solutions to help bring its operations into the 21st century and develop an even more supportive culture.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>sap-award/sap-innovation-awards</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Kärcher Supports a Growing Workforce by Moving HR to the Cloud]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/02/karcher-moves-workforce-hr-to-cloud</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/02/karcher-moves-workforce-hr-to-cloud</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[To provide the best workplace experience for employees, Kärcher is moving to a cloud-based HR system with SAP SuccessFactors solutions.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>