<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/spotlight-black-businesses/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Black History Month: Reflecting on History and Living Through Historic Times]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/black-history-month-reflecting-history-historic-times</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/black-history-month-reflecting-history-historic-times</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[This Black History Month at SAP, Chief Diversity & Inclusion Officer Judith Williams reflects on both history and these historic times.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_179d8c1738382eb4e544feb1bd1c144d823a2148d.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_179d8c1738382eb4e544feb1bd1c144d823a2148d.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_179d8c1738382eb4e544feb1bd1c144d823a2148d.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Black History Month: Reflecting on History and Living Through Historic Times" src="./media_179d8c1738382eb4e544feb1bd1c144d823a2148d.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="black-history-month-reflecting-on-history-and-living-through-historic-times">Black History Month: Reflecting on History and Living Through Historic Times</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>This year, Black History Month offers the opportunity to not only reflect on significant events and people who are a part of our history, but also acknowledge that we are living through historic times.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>While we can look backward, we can also pause to recognize that history is happening all around us, and consider the contemporary changemakers who will soon be inscribed in the historical record.</p>
  <p>When I wrote about Black History Month last year, I had no idea that a <a href="/covid-19">global pandemic</a> would significantly change the way we live, work, care for our families, and interact with our friends and communities. I was, however, keenly aware that things needed to change for the better for Black people living in America and throughout the world. The effects of long-term institutional and individual discrimination in healthcare, education, and employment persists within our society. Yet we see the persistence and fortitude of Black artists, activists, technologists, politicians, and others to bring attention to and solve these challenges.</p>
  <p>For example, when Dr. Anthony Fauci, the director of the National Institute of Allergy and Infectious Diseases (NIAID) in the U.S., talks about coronavirus vaccine research, he praises the work of a young Black scientist named Dr. Kizzmekia Corbett. Dr. Corbett is the National Institute of Health’s lead scientist on the COVID-19 vaccine from Moderna, arguably one of the most important vaccines of our time. Not only is Dr. Corbett a tremendous role model for young Black people, motivating them to overcome challenges and realize their full potential, but her work also increases confidence in the vaccine and will hopefully improve the health outcomes of Black communities.</p>
  <p>Dr. Corbett’s contribution to modern healthcare reminds us of the role of earlier Black inventors and scientists, such as Garrett Augustus Morgan, the African American inventor of the gas mask and the traffic signal; or Daniel Hale Williams, an American physician and founder of Provident Hospital in Chicago, who is credited with the first successful heart surgery; or more recently, Patricia Bath, an ophthalmologist and laser scientist who was an innovative research scientist and advocate for blindness prevention, treatment, and cure. Bath’s accomplishments include the invention of a new device and technique for cataract surgery known as laserphaco, and the creation of a new discipline known as “community ophthalmology.”</p>
  <p>Today, there are many unsung heroes in our midst, and more and more we are seeing organizations and individuals who are taking action and turning it into political power.</p>
  <p>After Lucy McBath’s son, Jordan Davis, was shot and killed for listening to “loud music” while sitting in the backseat of a friend’s car at a gas station, McBath dedicated her life to preventing other families from experiencing the same pain she did. She left her 30-year career as a flight attendant for Delta Airlines to become the national spokesperson and outreach leader for Everytown for Gun Safety and Moms Demand Action for Gun Sense in America. In 2017, after the mass shooting that killed 17 high school students at Stoneman Douglas High School in Parkland, Florida, McBath knew she had to stand up and run for Congress. Since taking her oath of office, she has identified bipartisan solutions to end gun violence, uplift small businesses, protect and serve U.S. veterans, and lower the cost of healthcare and prescription drugs.</p>
  <p>Stacy Abrams, an American politician, lawyer, and voting rights activist, founded Fair Fight Action to stop voter suppression in Georgia. Her efforts have been widely credited with boosting voter turnout in the state during the 2020 presidential election, where Joe Biden won the state, as well as in Georgia’s 2020-21 U.S. Senate election and special election, which gave Democrats control over the Senate.</p>
  <p>Congresswoman McBath’s and Ms. Abrams’s contributions remind me of the fleeting successes of African American Reconstruction Era politicians. During this era, more than 1,500 African Americans served in political capacities, including five Republican Senators and the U.S. Representatives Benjamin S. Turner (R-AL), Robert DeLarge (R-SC), Josiah Walls (R-FL), Jefferson Long (R-GA), Joseph Rainey, and Robert B. Elliott (R-SC).</p>
  <p>Hiram Revels (R-MS) was the first African American elected to the U.S. Senate. He was born free in North Carolina and attended college in Illinois. Revels worked as a preacher in the Midwest in the 1850s and as a chaplain to a Black regiment in the Union Army before going to Mississippi in 1865 to work for the Freedmen’s Bureau. Blanche Bruce, elected to the Senate in 1875 from Mississippi, had been enslaved but received some education. The background of these men was typical of the leaders that emerged during the Reconstruction.</p>
  <p>In 1967, almost a century after Revels and Bruce served in the U.S. Senate during Reconstruction, Edward Brooke of Massachusetts became the first African American senator elected by popular vote.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="spotlight-black-businesses-explore-the-companies-participating-in-the-initiative">Spotlight Black Businesses: Explore the companies participating in the initiative</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://discover.sap.com/spotlight-black-businesses/en-us/index.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="history-in-the-making-at-sap">History in the Making at SAP</h2>
  <p>The demonstrations and protests that broke out last year are built on the history of African American activism and achievement that has been essential to the success of the U.S. I am proud that SAP was quick to acknowledge the grief and anger that our employees were feeling and to invest in our Black employees and the Black community. SAP has introduced a <a href="https://blogs.sap.com/2021/02/03/closing-the-gap-while-social-distancing/">Pro Bono for Economic Equity program</a> so that employees can share their know-how and expertise to help solve critical business challenges for Black-owned businesses affected by social and racial injustices in the U.S. SAP also launched the <a href="/topics/spotlight-black-businesses">Spotlight Black Businesses</a> program to assist Black-owned businesses that have been impacted by COVID-19 and protests caused by social unrest.</p>
  <p>As a society, we have made progress that will continue to be documented in our history books, but we must also continue to push for greater opportunity in all aspects of our lives. Only then will we be truly equally represented in society and will “Black History” be remembered as our shared history.</p>
  <h2 id="black-history-month-events-at-sap">Black History Month Events at SAP</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="saps-statement-on-taking-action-toward-social-justice">SAP's Statement on Taking Action Toward Social Justice</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2020/06/social-justice-taking-action">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Throughout the month of February, <a href="/2021/02/cameron-champ-driving-change-equality">SAP and pro golfer Cameron Champ are teaming up</a> to “drive change.” Each week, Champ will play in a golf tournament in support of one of the Black-owned businesses featured in the Spotlight Black Businesses initiative. If Champ’s driving distance averages 320 yards during the tournament, SAP and the Cameron Champ Foundation will donate $10,000 to that week’s featured business.</p>
  <p>On February 25, from 4:15-5:15 p.m. ET, the Annual EY-SAP Black History Month Executive Roundtable will hold a “Boardroom Conversation on Inclusion.” The session will be held virtually and will cover how boards are overseeing their companies’ progress on diversity and inclusion, as well as advancing diversity inside the boardroom — what works, what doesn’t.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em><a href="/author/judithwilliams">Judith Williams</a> is head of People Sustainability and chief diversity and inclusion officer at SAP SE</em>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>news-tag/spotlight-black-businesses</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Driving Change On and Off the Golf Course]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/cameron-champ-driving-change-equality</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/cameron-champ-driving-change-equality</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP and its newest golf ambassador, Cameron Champ, are teaming up during Black History Month to “drive change” on and off the golf course.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1450885de8d6014907cdde32170cc1b66ab1dd0b7.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1450885de8d6014907cdde32170cc1b66ab1dd0b7.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1450885de8d6014907cdde32170cc1b66ab1dd0b7.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Driving Change On and Off the Golf Course" src="./media_1450885de8d6014907cdde32170cc1b66ab1dd0b7.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="driving-change-on-and-off-the-golf-course">Driving Change On and Off the Golf Course</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Businesses, communities, and individuals recognize the urgency to not only speak up for social justice but to take actionable steps towards change. Last summer, SAP launched <a href="https://discover.sap.com/spotlight-black-businesses/en-us/index.html">Spotlight Black Businesses</a>, leveraging our platforms to elevate, promote, and support small, Black-owned businesses impacted by the pandemic and social unrest. This year we are building on the <a href="/2020/07/spotlight-black-businesses-new-sap-initiative">Spotlight Black Businesses</a> initiative in honor of Black History Month.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP and SAP’s newest golf ambassador, <strong>Cameron Champ</strong>, are teaming up to “drive change” on and off the golf course. Throughout the month of February, Champ will leverage his distance driving skills and network and SAP will allocate branding space as part of the sponsorship to increase awareness and support for some deserving businesses.</p>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1fd3de776a147d0a32859c88d0575e99b66a5d926.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1fd3de776a147d0a32859c88d0575e99b66a5d926.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1fd3de776a147d0a32859c88d0575e99b66a5d926.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Drive Change: Cameron Champ + SAP" src="./media_1fd3de776a147d0a32859c88d0575e99b66a5d926.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://youtu.be/Fs0I6GnaCSI">Drive Change: Cameron Champ + SAP</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="black-history-month">Black History Month</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="watch-the-blank-canvas-episode-to-learn-more-about-socially-conscious-sports">Watch the Blank Canvas episode to learn more about socially conscious sports</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://insights.sap.com/conversations/blank-canvas-sports-social-issues/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Black History Month, observed each year during the month of February, celebrates the contributions Black people have made to American history and culture and recognizes Black Americans’ struggle for equality. This federally acknowledged observance recognizes the meaningful endeavors of Black Americans and strengthens all Americans’ understanding of the contributions, complexity, and struggles Black people continue to face while shaping our nation’s history.</p>
  <h2 id="a-champion-for-equality">A Champion for Equality</h2>
  <p><a href="https://cameronchamp.com/">Champ</a>, an elite player on the PGA TOUR, seeks to address the underrepresentation of Black people and people of color in the workforce and foster a culture of equality in golf and in society at large. Champ is no stranger to the challenges Black people have faced in America. His late grandfather, Mack Champ, was a phenomenal, self-taught golfer but was never able to do more than caddie because of the color of his skin. He serves as a champion for equality, diversity, and inclusion and recognizes the critical role of the private sector in influencing societal change.</p>
  <p>Powered by SAP, Champ’s participation in three upcoming golf tournaments – the Waste Management Phoenix Open, Genesis Invitational, and WGC Championship – will give him the opportunity to raise money for four Black-owned businesses close to his heart. Each week Champ will play in support of one of the businesses, and if his driving distance averages 320 yards during the tournament SAP will donate US$10,000 to that week’s business.</p>
  <p>“SAP proudly supports Cameron Champ’s commitment to driving equality and transforming the lives of underserved and underrepresented communities,” shares Judith Williams, head of People Sustainability, senior vice president, and chief diversity and inclusion officer at SAP. “Our shared values guide this collaboration and provide a channel through which SAP can strengthen our commitment to social justice and our continued effort toward realizing a future where everyone is equal.”</p>
  <p>Be sure to cheer on Cameron Champ as he “drives change” and advances equality in the golf community and beyond.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Dan Fleetwood is vice president of Global Sponsorships at SAP.</em><br><em>Janis Fratamico is global head of Brand Experience at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-sponsorships</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-sports</category>
            <category>news-tag/spotlight-black-businesses</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>