<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/digital-skills/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Powering the AI Revolution with New Learning, Certifications, and Simplified Access to Talent]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/powering-ai-revolution-learning-certifications-talent</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/powering-ai-revolution-learning-certifications-talent</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Bring out your best with new learning opportunities, role-based SAP Certifications, and simplified access to talent. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_158ee9e4c4293f1933f13d07a2fb3eddc96c821de.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_158ee9e4c4293f1933f13d07a2fb3eddc96c821de.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_158ee9e4c4293f1933f13d07a2fb3eddc96c821de.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Powering the AI Revolution with New Learning, Certifications, and Simplified Access to Talent" src="./media_158ee9e4c4293f1933f13d07a2fb3eddc96c821de.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="powering-the-ai-revolution-with-new-learning-certifications-and-simplified-access-to-talent">Powering the AI Revolution with New Learning, Certifications, and Simplified Access to Talent</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Artificial intelligence (AI) is currently forcing the technology industry to undergo <a href="">a paradigm shift</a>, further accelerating the upheaval in business and society. We see AI embedded in tools we have been using for years, and we see software finding its way into every aspect of competition today. Against this background, it comes as no surprise that <a href="https://www2.deloitte.com/us/en/pages/consulting/articles/state-of-ai-2022.html">94% of business leaders see AI as critical to success over the next five years</a>. However, many report the lack of resources and talent to drive competitiveness with these new tools.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="taking-business-to-the-next-level-in-the-era-of-ai">Taking Business to the Next Level in the Era of AI</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/events/sapphire/news-guide.html">Read the news guide</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>To make it easier to develop relevant skills and secure business success in such a volatile environment, <a href="/2022/11/sap-coursera-partnership-digital-skills-underrepresented-groups">we embarked on a journey to upskill millions of people worldwide</a> in search of opportunity. After launching a digital skills initiative for those underserved in tech, forging new partnerships, offering the first role-based certifications to help meet real-life business needs, and making future-focused learning resources available to all, we are now taking our efforts to an even higher level – with more free, self-paced learning and engagement opportunities, new solution demos to experience the latest innovations in SAP Business AI, cloud ERP, and SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP), among others, a full portfolio of role-based certifications and a new certification model, as well as an extended digital skills initiative.</p>
  <h2 id="more-than-250-free-online-courses-now-available-for-all">More Than 250 Free Online Courses Now Available for All</h2>
  <p>From global talent shortages and changing job profiles to the digitalization of entire economies, many organizations see the gaps between skill supply and demand grow wider and wider while searching for ways to adapt to a business landscape where advancements like AI, machine learning, and a new era of Big Data come into play. In this ever-changing atmosphere, tens of thousands of organizations have <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company.html">deployed SAP solutions</a> to support them on their path to bring out their best, leading to skyrocketing demand for SAP talent.</p>
  <p>To help meet the increasing demand, we recently launched more than 50 new free, self-paced learning journeys – many of them touching on AI features embedded in our software – bringing the total number of digital courses on the <a href="https://learning.sap.com/?url_id=text-sapnewscenter-prdteng-Sapphire">SAP Learning site</a> to more than 250. By allowing everyone with an Internet connection to quickly learn a new skill for free, keep up with the latest innovations, and prepare for an in-demand SAP Certification, more professionals can advance in the competitive technology labor market, while customers can draw on a deeper bench of skills to accelerate digital transformation.</p>
  <h2 id="launching-role-based-certifications-for-all-key-roles">Launching Role-Based Certifications for All Key Roles</h2>
  <p>As organizations need to be more adaptive and dynamic, traditional university degrees become less important and skills-based hiring is on the rise when trying to fill positions. In fact, recent reports show that up to <a href="https://www.hiringlab.org/2024/02/27/educational-requirements-job-postings/">52% of job postings</a> in the U.S. in the beginning of the year did not state an educational requirement. Instead, role-based certifications and practical experience have become more determining factors for career paths and hiring.</p>
  <p>Recognizing the advantages role-based certifications can offer both individuals and organizations, we have further enhanced our certification program to better align with real-life business needs, now offering role-based certification for all key roles, including consultants, analysts, and architects. These role-based certifications come with a clear career path for individuals. Together with a <a href="https://learning.sap.com/get-certified?url_id=text-sapnewscenter-prdteng-Sapphire">new model to get and stay certified</a> with continuous assessments, this is our way to help ensure skill sets are sharp, focused on core competencies, and more sustainable and valid for longer periods of time.</p>
  <p>With these enhancements, we believe we have now taken an important next step to support professionals and organizations in the SAP ecosystem to bring out their best with ongoing and up-to-date knowledge of the latest skills, helping to maximize the ROI of SAP software, shorten deployment times, lower costs, speed innovation, and increase employee retention and satisfaction.</p>
  <h2 id="simplified-access-to-pre-trained-sap-talent">Simplified Access to Pre-Trained SAP Talent</h2>
  <p>However, we recognize that many people considered underrepresented in tech still do not have access to future-focused educational resources and with it, fulfilling careers. Launched in late 2022, <a href="https://learning.sap.com/digital-skills?url_id=text-sapnewscenter-prdteng-Sapphire">SAP’s digital skills initiative</a> was intended to equip 10,000 people from underrepresented and underserved groups for a career in the tech industry with free, self-paced learning resources and a free certification exam attempt to obtain an in-demand SAP Certification to show their expertise. Ever since its launch, the initiative has grown – and contributed to <a href="https://community.sap.com/t5/learner-stories/bg-p/learner-stories">amazing success stories</a>.</p>
  <p>Hearing that SAP professionals like <a href="https://community.sap.com/t5/sap-learning-blog-posts/breaking-barriers-and-fighting-sexism-lin-s-journey-from-a-salesgirl-to-an/ba-p/13588835">Lin Fan, a Chinese immigrant to Germany</a>, could overcome gender bias because of our digital skills initiative, makes me proud. “[The digital skills initiative and SAP Certification] indeed opened new doors and helped me get noticed by recruiters,” Fan said. “I got several interviews from major SAP consulting firms shortly after handing in my application. In the interviews, I highlighted what I learned and expressed my confidence in accepting challenges for rolling out SAP S/4HANA. In the end, I got an offer and gladly started a junior role at a consulting firm that actively implements SAP S/4HANA projects.”</p>
  <p>While Fan’s path is inspiring, she is not the only one who turned their life around with the help of SAP. Given the expectation-exceeding demand of now more than 14,500 candidates, we are overwhelmed by the positive uptake of the initiative. One of our recent graduates, <a href="https://community.sap.com/t5/learner-stories/breaking-down-barriers-hear-from-chelcie-scott-how-she-broke-into-tech-with/ba-p/13710541">Chelcie Scott, agreed to tell her story</a> on camera and shared how intimidating the tech industry appeared to the single mother at first. Thanks to her willpower and commitment, plus a little help from the digital skills initiative, she recently got certified and hired by an SAP partner. And as organizations are still struggling to find skilled employees, we have decided to extend SAP’s digital skills initiative, bringing candidates and organizations together. With simplified access to SAP-trained talent, we are helping customers and partners to recruit talent and expand their workforce faster while also allowing for greater diversity and innovation.</p>
  <p>At SAP, we recognize the challenges and opportunities that lie ahead for customers, partners, and individual learners within and outside of the SAP ecosystem. With these enhancements, we have taken the next step to help organizations equip their existing workforce with the right tools and resources to future-proof their skill set while also paving career growth for those who do not have a seat at the table yet but can bring a fresh set of perspectives to it.</p>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1bf4a81f181aead9f58c4d25e211885b7fc5988cc.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1bf4a81f181aead9f58c4d25e211885b7fc5988cc.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1bf4a81f181aead9f58c4d25e211885b7fc5988cc.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Break Down Barriers With the Help of SAP’s Digital Skills Initiative" src="./media_1bf4a81f181aead9f58c4d25e211885b7fc5988cc.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pEsE7dicrc4&#x26;feature=youtu.be">Break Down Barriers With the Help of SAP’s Digital Skills Initiative</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Andre Bechtold is SVP and head of Solution &#x26; Innovation Experience at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-sapphire-in-2024-innovations-to-bring-out-the-best-in-your-business">SAP Sapphire in 2024: Innovations to bring out the best in your business</h3>
        <p><em><a href="/topics/sap-sapphire">Get the latest news and coverage</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills-gap</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Equipping the Next Generation of Underrepresented Talent for a Career in Tech]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/equipping-next-generation-underrepresented-talent-tech</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/equipping-next-generation-underrepresented-talent-tech</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP’s digital skills initiative helps prepare underrepresented groups for a career in tech through a free SAP Certification course.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1516454e29028b1edfdf3049f7d0417f3f4530c3f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1516454e29028b1edfdf3049f7d0417f3f4530c3f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1516454e29028b1edfdf3049f7d0417f3f4530c3f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Equipping the Next Generation of Underrepresented Talent for a Career in Tech" src="./media_1516454e29028b1edfdf3049f7d0417f3f4530c3f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="equipping-the-next-generation-of-underrepresented-talent-for-a-career-in-tech">Equipping the Next Generation of Underrepresented Talent for a Career in Tech</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>“I just never saw myself in tech.”</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>This is what I heard during my discussion with the first cohort of SAP’s <a href="https://learning.sap.com/digital-skills">digital</a> <a href="https://learning.sap.com/digital-skills?campaigncode=CRM-YD24-ISM-2422141&#x26;source=blog-glo-Unrepped_Talent">skills</a> <a href="https://learning.sap.com/digital-skills">initiative</a>, a program that helps equip underrepresented and underserved groups for a career in the tech industry through participation in a free SAP Certification course.</p>
  <p>How could it be that in a time when companies need to find talent quickly to fill the need for technically skilled roles – a need that is becoming more urgent by the day – there is an entire population of determined, driven people who feel as though they do not belong in the tech industry?</p>
  <h2 id="the-current-state-of-diversity-in-technology">The Current State of Diversity in Technology</h2>
  <p>The numbers speak volumes: only <a href="https://ncwit.org/resource/bythenumbers/">27% of all computing-related jobs are held by women</a>. Only 3% of those jobs are held by Black women and 1% are held by Latina women. For me, it has always been impossible to ignore the lack of representation in the tech industry. I am acutely aware of when I am the only woman in the room – let alone the only Black woman.</p>
  <p>But this is changing. Companies have begun implementing diversity-forward hiring practices to try to minimize barriers for populations that have historically been overlooked. The percentage of <a href="https://www.naceweb.org/diversity-equity-and-inclusion/individuals-with-disabilities/ready-willing-but-still-underemployed/e619e772-a54b-4df6-858c-9ca50717a5a0">employers with diversity recruiting efforts</a> rose from 56% in 2016 to 88% in 2021. Though there is now targeted backlash, numerous employers remain committed to their diversity, equity, and inclusion (DE&#x26;I) goals for the workforce.</p>
  <p>These initiatives have proven to be important to younger generations. In a few years, millennials and Gen Z will make up the majority of our workforce – and they want to work for companies that align with their values. A 2022 survey from the <a href="https://www.naceweb.org/diversity-equity-and-inclusion/individuals-with-disabilities/ready-willing-but-still-underemployed/835bc35a-e4be-42fb-b838-d06086cb87bc">National Association of Colleges and Employers (NACE)</a> found that 76% of recent graduates indicated that <a href="/topics/diversity-and-inclusion">diversity, equity, and inclusion efforts</a> were “very important” or “extremely important” when considering their future employers.</p>
  <h2 id="helping-underserved-groups-break-into-tech">Helping Underserved Groups Break into Tech</h2>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="accelerate-your-career-with-our-digital-skills-initiative">Accelerate your career with our digital skills initiative</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://learning.sap.com/digital-skills?campaigncode=CRM-YD24-ISM-2422141&#x26;source=blog-glo-Unrepped_Talent">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>If we want diverse workforces, we must support and create targeted channels to source diverse talent. It is imperative that these groups – including women, people of color, veterans, and others – are given the resources to excel in high tech. I have seen firsthand how our digital skills initiative is making an impact on individuals and their communities, working to ensure that talent from all backgrounds can participate in this exciting era of technological innovation. At SAP, we offer training on products like <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/s4hana.html?campaigncode=CRM-YD24-ISM-2422141&#x26;source=blog-glo-Unrepped_Talent">SAP S/4HANA Cloud</a> and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp.html?campaigncode=CRM-YD24-ISM-2422141&#x26;source=blog-glo-Unrepped_Talent">SAP ERP</a>, whether through programs like the digital skills initiative or on <a href="https://learninghub.sap.com/?campaigncode=CRM-YD24-ISM-2422141&#x26;source=blog-glo-Unrepped_Talent">SAP Learning Hub</a>, helping anyone interested in jump-starting their career in tech.</p>
  <p>Without diverse perspectives, we leave out too many pieces of the puzzle to see the big picture. This deficit is particularly obvious in technology, given its influence on everything from how we shop to how we govern. It is unsustainable to expect lasting market viability from products that are developed by and marketed to one type of person. Put simply, employing diverse talent is essential to long-term success.</p>
  <h2 id="how-companies-can-recruit-diverse-talent">How Companies Can Recruit Diverse Talent</h2>
  <p>For companies that are looking for the next pool of employees to solve today’s business challenges, it is time to consider non-traditional avenues of talent, like graduates from SAP’s digital skills initiative. Each cohort comes equipped with SAP Certification, self-motivation, and a strong work ethic. This is a special opportunity to pull from a curated group of strong candidates, not just because of their new skills but because of demonstrated curiosity and drive that is not easy to find.</p>
  <p>SAP makes these trained and certified candidates available to recruiters at no charge. Want to get access to SAP-certified, ready-to-hire talent? Interested in adopting a cohort? <a href="https://learning.sap.com/digital-skills/hire-talent?campaigncode=CRM-YD24-ISM-2422141&#x26;source=blog-glo-Unrepped_Talent">Contact us</a> to see how you can start hiring and get involved.</p>
  <h2 id="register-for-the-digital-skills-initiative-as-a-participant">Register for the Digital Skills Initiative as a Participant</h2>
  <p>If you are interested in expanding your career opportunities by learning in-demand skills and achieving an SAP Certification free of charge, apply for the digital skills initiative using the <a href="https://community.sap.com/t5/beginner-corner-blog-posts/digital-skills-initiative-applicant-guide-for-self-study-candidates/ba-p/273119">applicant guide</a>. This is a fantastic opportunity for those who want to make a career switch to tech.</p>
  <p>To those who never pictured themselves in the tech industry, picture it. There is a place for you. Take this as a sign to invest in yourself and create a new path to success.</p>
  <h2 id="making-an-impact-on-future-generations">Making an Impact on Future Generations</h2>
  <p>When I talked with this first cohort of the digital skills initiative, I saw how they take great pride in their certification. For some, these new skills will prove to be life-changing.</p>
  <p>My goal is to support initiatives that aim to ensure that everyone, from all backgrounds, can pursue their interests in finding a career in tech. When we leave these doors closed, we not only rob those shut out of the opportunity, but all of us from the creativity, perspectives, and outcomes they could deliver.</p>
  <p>I am incredibly proud of SAP’s work in empowering people to pursue a career in technology. I believe that we are developing the future of innovation through programs like the digital skills initiative, and I cannot wait to see how similar programs will evolve in the future.</p>
  <p>If you are an NGO, university, or an SAP partner or customer, contact us at <a href="mailto:partners.digitalskills@sap.com">partners.digitalskills@sap.com</a> to learn more. If you are interested in applying to the digital skills initiative, <a href="https://groups.community.sap.com/t5/beginner-corner-discussions/creating-an-sap-account-and-getting-started-in-the-community/m-p/260744">create an SAP account</a> to start your journey.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Etosha Thurman is chief marketing and solutions officer for Intelligent Spend and Business Network at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>product/sap-learning-hub</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Why It’s Better to Accept Generative AI Sooner, Not Later]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/videos/why-its-better-to-accept-generative-ai-sooner-not-later</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/videos/why-its-better-to-accept-generative-ai-sooner-not-later</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP's Julia White joins experts from Deloitte, BCG, and StartSteps Digital Education to discuss society’s scramble to get the right people into new jobs.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/video</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-education</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>non-sap-event/wef-davos</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Accelerate Your Skills Transformation with the New Integrated Learning Experience for SAP SuccessFactors]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/new-integrated-learning-experience-sap-successfactors</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/new-integrated-learning-experience-sap-successfactors</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The integrated learning experience for SAP SuccessFactors helps to address skills gaps and considers employees' whole self in skills growth.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills-gap</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning-management-system</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-learning</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Learning to Stay Ahead of the Curve: Why Teams Should Value Low-Code/No-Code Training]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/value-low-code-no-code-training</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/value-low-code-no-code-training</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Providing access to learning and development opportunities like low-code/no-code training opens new workforce opportunities. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/low-code-no-code</category>
            <category>product/sap-build</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Helping SAP Partner Delaware Meet Its Recruiting Needs]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/06/partner-talent-initiative-delaware-recruiting-needs</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/06/partner-talent-initiative-delaware-recruiting-needs</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The Partner Talent Initiative helped Delaware UK find, recruit, and retain knowledgeable, skilled individuals to bolster its success.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>news-tag/talent-acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Powering Business Transformation with Unprecedented Career Growth for SAP Professionals]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/powering-unprecedented-career-growth-sap-professionals</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/powering-unprecedented-career-growth-sap-professionals</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[We all are facing a changing work environment. Read to learn how SAP Learning supports the career growth of SAP professionals.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-certification</category>
            <category>product/sap-learning-hub</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Communicating the True Value of Learning and Development in 2023]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/communicating-value-of-learning-development-2023</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/communicating-value-of-learning-development-2023</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Leaders need to be strategic in providing learning opportunities. Learn why and how leaders and employees can benefit from the investment.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c348ed4ab53e7860823ae46dfe75ba57f60e11e8.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c348ed4ab53e7860823ae46dfe75ba57f60e11e8.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1c348ed4ab53e7860823ae46dfe75ba57f60e11e8.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Communicating the True Value of Learning and Development in 2023" src="./media_1c348ed4ab53e7860823ae46dfe75ba57f60e11e8.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="communicating-the-true-value-of-learning-and-development-in-2023">Communicating the True Value of Learning and Development in 2023</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>As we move quickly into the second quarter of 2023, leaders and workers alike are facing increasing pressure resulting from the current tumultuous economic period. In a business environment where every budget line is being questioned, IT leaders must maintain a strategic lens when providing <a href="/topics/training">learning</a> opportunities for their teams. They must be able to clearly articulate the value of technical training and development opportunities – or risk losing them.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In the midst of this uncertainty, keeping IT workers abreast of innovative technologies and the skills to implement them is a balancing act. To stay at the forefront of industry change, learning must be considered more than a priority – it needs to be a core pillar of every organization. IT upskilling is key in today’s landscape to drive employee satisfaction and organizational success. Here are three of the top reasons to invest in learning and development opportunities and how the benefits can be articulated to leadership to ensure they consider learning a top priority, too.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-digital-skills-you-need-with-sap-learning">Get the digital skills you need with SAP Learning</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://learning.sap.com/digital-skills?url_id=text-sapnewscenter-prdteng-DigitalSkills">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="invest-in-your-employees--and-they-just-might-stick-around">Invest in Your Employees – and They Just Might Stick Around</h2>
  <p>While layoffs seem to be dominating the headlines, employees are quitting their jobs at <a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2023/02/13/business/employee-retention-quitting-companies.html">three times</a> the rate of layoffs. Retaining strong talent remains a competitive pursuit, and organizations are feeling the impacts of this challenge. Now, <a href="http://workplaceintelligence.com/upskilling-study/">64% to 66% of employees</a> would consider leaving their current role because there aren’t enough opportunities for skill development or career advancement. The truth is that adequate training directly impacts retention. An important factor in how employees evaluate their organization is based on the opportunities they’re provided to learn the skills that will catapult them towards reaching their goals. Learning and development opportunities can equip employees with essential leadership skills that can elevate their current position and pave the way for internal advancement.</p>
  <p>By offering learning programs, and therefore showing the workforce that leaders are invested in their growth, executive teams will realize a multitude of benefits. Individuals will feel valued and excited by new challenges and upskilling opportunities, making them more likely to be happy with their current role. Beyond this, they’ll build a workforce that is equipped with the latest knowledge to drive meaningful outcomes for the organization.</p>
  <h2 id="fostering-creativity-innovation-and-curiosity">Fostering Creativity, Innovation, and Curiosity</h2>
  <p>The tech industry is evolving – fast. From generative artificial intelligence (AI) and machine learning to immersive-reality technologies, digital transformation has raised the bar on the skills required of teams today. Inspiring employees to lead innovative strategies can feel daunting when the workforce is not properly equipped with the latest knowledge to take on new initiatives. When employees do not feel prepared, they are less likely to be enthusiastic about taking on new responsibilities or raise their hand to lead a project that is outside of their comfort zone. In fact, <a href="https://www.gartner.com/en/publications/emerging-technology-roadmap-for-large-enterprisesB">64% of IT professionals</a> think the skills shortage is the biggest barrier to the adoption of game-changing technologies.</p>
  <p>To combat this hesitation and encourage workers to tackle new challenges, leaders must recognize that learning and development opportunities enable IT teams to feel prepared and excited to move forward on adopting new workplace technologies. This ultimately increases efficiency and allows more time and space for innovation and creativity.</p>
  <p>Steve Lucas, SAP S/4HANA Cloud application consultant at Sapphire Systems, has seen how learning, for instance with <a href="https://learning.sap.com/?url_id=text-sapnewscenter-prdteng">self-paced SAP Learning Journeys on the SAP Learning site</a>, can drive innovation firsthand. “Earning an SAP Certiﬁcation is important to not just my future but the future of my company. It ensures we’ll both meet our goals and remain at the forefront of SAP’s latest innovations,” he said.</p>
  <h2 id="tackling-the-persistent-skills-gap-challenge">Tackling the Persistent Skills Gap Challenge</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="explore-sap-learning-journeys-and-product-pages">Explore SAP Learning Journeys and product pages</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://learning.sap.com/?url_id=text-sapnewscenter-prdteng">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The skills gap remains top-of-mind for leaders across industries as technical roles continue to evolve and competition for top talent remains high. Due to the speed of innovation, over <a href="https://www.gartner.com/en/newsroom/press-releases/2021-02-03-gartner-hr-research-finds-fifty-eight-percent-of-the-workforce-will-need-new-skill-sets-to-do-their-jobs-successfully">58% of the workforce will need new skill sets</a> to do their jobs successfully in the coming years.</p>
  <p>While some employees may be able to make time outside of work hours for learning and development, many have competing personal priorities – meaning encouraging employees to seek upskilling opportunities outside of their nine-to-five may set them on a path of frustration and burnout. Instead, bring training programs directly to them and build a few uninterrupted hours into their workday so that employees can devote themselves to learning without navigating demanding tasks at the same time. This simple solution can mitigate burnout and ensure everyone is receiving the information they need to be successful in their roles – now and in the future.</p>
  <p>For example, learning programs like <a href="https://learning.sap.com/learning-journey/discover-the-foundations-of-sap-commerce-cloud-and-sap-s-4hana-cloud-integration?url_id=text-sapnewscenter-prdteng">SAP S/4HANA</a> or <a href="https://learning.sap.com/learning-journey/utilize-sap-build-for-low-code-no-code-applications-and-automations-for-citizen-developers?url_id=text-sapnewscenter-prdteng">low-code/no-code</a> basics can quickly and efficiently equip employees with the skills they need by educating them on the latest platforms and technology necessary to keep up with digital transformation efforts. These programs can also level the playing field among teams, increasing workers’ value and purpose within their current role.</p>
  <h2 id="the-return-on-learning-and-development-priceless">The Return on Learning and Development? Priceless.</h2>
  <p>While it’s true that that investing in learning and development is a commitment – both in budget and in resources – the benefits far outweigh the drawbacks. It’s easy to deprioritize learning when the time and money that goes into upskilling can seem like an optional expense, but in today’s workplace culture, it is essential. Companies who invest in learning and development opportunities will reap the benefits almost immediately and will equip their teams for a future of innovation, creativity, and equitable opportunities for growth, ultimately leading to higher retention, empowered employees, and a more secure workforce.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Jan Meyer is head of Learning Systems at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills-gap</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Vodafone Builds Its Future-Ready Workforce on Cloud HR Foundations]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/vodafone-builds-cloud-hr-foundations</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/vodafone-builds-cloud-hr-foundations</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Vodafone Group Plc implements SAP SuccessFactors solutions as its cloud HR foundation for improved efficiency and employee engagement.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fieldglass</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-learning</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-work-zone</category>
            <category>sap-event/successconnect</category>
            <category>news-tag/total-workforce-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP CSR Launches Third Edition of eBook, Celebrating a Year of Global Impact]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/sap-csr-launches-ebook-third-edition</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/sap-csr-launches-ebook-third-edition</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Corporate Social Responsibility (SAP CSR) launched the third edition of its annual eBook, "Helping the World Run Better – Together."]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-social-sabbatical</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Women Can Be the Key to Solving the Global Skills Gap in Tech]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/01/women-key-to-global-digital-skills-gap-in-tech</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/01/women-key-to-global-digital-skills-gap-in-tech</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The global lack of digitally skilled workers is increasing in the tech industry. Learn about SAP's initiative and how women are key.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/coursera</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills-gap</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-certification</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-community</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ENGAGE.EU Think Tank: Students Talk Robust Supply Chains]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/engage-eu-think-tank-students-talk-robust-supply-chains</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/engage-eu-think-tank-students-talk-robust-supply-chains</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[At the ENGAGE.EU Think Tank at the University of Mannheim, SAP CFO Luka Mucic and others talked about disruptive supply chains.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-university-alliances</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Great Resignation Points to a Serious Sustainability Issue]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/great-resignation-serious-sustainability-issue</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/great-resignation-serious-sustainability-issue</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The Great Resignation is a sustainability warning to companies that have not focused on culture and leadership for a while. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/people-sustainability</category>
            <category>news-tag/qualtrics</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-workforce-analytics</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Three Steps to Prioritize Digital Skills for Sustainable Growth]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/three-steps-prioritize-digital-skills</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/three-steps-prioritize-digital-skills</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Businesses must have enough people with the right skills, at the right time, to help them accelerate their digital transformation.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/covid-19</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/people-sustainability</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Industry 4.0 Attracts Workers Whose Entire Lives Are on Their Mobile Device]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/industry-4-0-attracts-workers-whose-entire-lives-are-on-their-mobile-device</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/industry-4-0-attracts-workers-whose-entire-lives-are-on-their-mobile-device</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Manufacturers are transforming factories, hoping next-generation workers come for the cool factor and stay for career-building innovations.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-4-0</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>news-tag/mobile</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Pledges to Equip Underrepresented Groups with Digital Skills, Announces Partnership with Coursera to Reach Millions of Learners Worldwide]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/sap-coursera-partnership-digital-skills-underrepresented-groups</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/sap-coursera-partnership-digital-skills-underrepresented-groups</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A Coursera partnership and global skills initiative are part of SAP's efforts to grow a more diverse ecosystem of tech professionals.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/sap-teched</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/coursera</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Code Unnati: Inspiring Bright Futures through Digital Inclusion]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/code-unnati-digital-inclusion</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/code-unnati-digital-inclusion</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Code Unnati aims to impart digital literacy among adolescents, citizens, and children as well as employable IT skills among youth. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-education</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/redefining-youth</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[German Chancellor Olaf Scholz Says Innovation Creates Hope for Society]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/german-chancellor-olaf-scholz-innovation-creates-hope</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/german-chancellor-olaf-scholz-innovation-creates-hope</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[German Chancellor Olaf Scholz attended an event celebrating SAP's 50th anniversary, where he spoke on the potential of the digital economy.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-education</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A New Chapter for SAP Learning: Empowering Careers and Cultivating Skills for the Future]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/sap-learning-site-empowering-careers-cultivating-skills</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/sap-learning-site-empowering-careers-cultivating-skills</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The new SAP Learning site takes a new approach to delivering a digitally native and learner-focused experience. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1eb3d5dcede4d7060d6b549750fd52d6f37f7ecb4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1eb3d5dcede4d7060d6b549750fd52d6f37f7ecb4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1eb3d5dcede4d7060d6b549750fd52d6f37f7ecb4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="A New Chapter for SAP Learning: Empowering Careers and Cultivating Skills for the Future" src="./media_1eb3d5dcede4d7060d6b549750fd52d6f37f7ecb4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="a-new-chapter-for-sap-learning-empowering-careers-and-cultivating-skills-for-the-future">A New Chapter for SAP Learning: Empowering Careers and Cultivating Skills for the Future</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>We talk about it regularly: in the next decade, more than a billion workers will require reskilling. At the core of this tectonic shift in work is the integration of software-enabled innovation into every business process. SAP is the backbone of this change – it’s why we see massive demand for SAP skills across our customer environments and partner ecosystem. Those who can leverage SAP to deliver flexibility and harness opportunity are the instigators of innovation.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>At SAP, we know that it’s a big responsibility to ensure that this knowledge is pervasive. That’s why we also recognize the need to simplify the act of reskilling. Our increasingly busy schedules and the fast pace of our day-to-day work often pull us away from learning. It’s not easy to find time to sharpen our skills and learn new ones.</p>
  <p>So, when you do make time to focus on your learning, the process of finding the right material should be simple and streamlined – and the content comprehensive. At SAP Learning, we’ve reinforced our commitment to removing barriers to learning by making it simpler to discover our content and easier to navigate our platforms.</p>
  <p>Because success is rooted in learning, it’s critical to have all the support you need right at your fingertips to move forward easily and consistently.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="turn-learning-into-achieving-with-sap-learning">Turn learning into achieving with SAP Learning</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="http://www.sap.com/training">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="empowering-the-individual-learner">Empowering the Individual Learner</h2>
  <p>Today’s learners demand a personalized experience to cultivate their skills. Almost every individual with an Internet connection has been introduced to the ease of consumer-grade applications – and we know that learning content competes with every distraction. To that end, it is critical to create engaging content and offer enjoyable experiences that empower individuals at every stage of their career and learning journey. Therefore, SAP Learning is taking a new approach to delivering a digitally native and learner-focused experience.</p>
  <p>As part of our ongoing and reimagined commitment to enhancing learning opportunities, we’ve launched an all-new <a href="https://learning.sap.com/">SAP Learning site</a> that includes a comprehensive array of learning content available in various formats – from expert-led sessions and hands-on training to microlearning videos. By opening the door to accessible opportunities for everyone to upskill, reskill, and validate SAP skills, we are focusing squarely on the success of <a href="/2021/10/preparing-partners-for-their-future-with-sap-learning">our ecosystem</a> and meeting our learners where they are. After all, learning should make your life easier, not more complicated.
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c5eff5fc2c74c83179837e7d0dbeefd83957434d.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c5eff5fc2c74c83179837e7d0dbeefd83957434d.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1c5eff5fc2c74c83179837e7d0dbeefd83957434d.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="New SAP Learning site" src="./media_1c5eff5fc2c74c83179837e7d0dbeefd83957434d.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="733">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p>We’re proud of the progress we’re making. We also look forward to hearing more feedback from our community so we can bring continuous improvement to our operations.</p>
  <h2 id="equipping-for-the-needs-of-tomorrow">Equipping for the Needs of Tomorrow</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-launches-free-student-offering-sap-learning-hub-edition-for-sap-next-gen">SAP Launches Free Student Offering: SAP Learning Hub, Edition for SAP Next-Gen</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/05/launch-sap-learning-hub-edition-for-sap-next-gen">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Designed to be simple and intuitive to navigate, the <a href="https://learning.sap.com/">SAP Learning site</a> will become the one-stop-shop that brings together the expansive portfolio of well-established SAP learning offerings. With <a href="/topics/sap-teched">our SAP TechEd releases</a>, learners in development roles as well as future developers can quickly start and gain SAP skills in core innovation areas and prepare for an <a href="https://learning.sap.com/certification?url_id=text-sapnewscenter-prdteng-Certification">SAP Certification</a> at no cost. The site features access to various free content for upskilling with <a href="https://learning.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform?url_id=text-sapnewscenter-prdteng-BTP">SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP)</a>, including a brand-new learning journey focused on <a href="https://learning.sap.com/learning-journey/utilize-sap-build-for-low-code-no-code-applications-and-automations-for-citizen-developers?url_id=text-sapnewscenter-prdteng-LCNC">how to develop low-code/no-code applications</a>.</p>
  <p>We’re also partnering with <a href="https://www.placement.com/">Placement</a>, a career coaching service provider, so that the first 1,000 developers who complete a certification exam on SAP BTP through the new site will receive a voucher for services like résumé review, LinkedIn screening, and career coaching. And now through November 2022, all registered learners on the SAP Learning site can utilize select services from Placement as well as enjoy access to Placement’s Job Board at a discounted price.</p>
  <p>Looking to the future, the site will continue to support all learners’ career development and accelerate broader organizational transformations by extending the scope to include all free SAP Learning content. For more details, watch the <a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2021/11/8008e636-047e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">video</a> or check out the <a href="https://learning.sap.com/">new site</a> on your own.</p>
  <p>It’s never been easier to get started building and achieving SAP skills – and it’s only the beginning for this new chapter of SAP Learning.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Max Wessel is EVP and chief learning officer at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-more-news-and-coverage-from-sap-teched">Read more news and coverage from SAP TechEd</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/topics/sap-teched">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/sap-teched</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Booting Up for the Future with Brooks Crossing Innovation Lab]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/brooks-crossing-innovation-lab-learning-digital-skills</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/brooks-crossing-innovation-lab-learning-digital-skills</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Nov 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A new program with Brooks Crossing Innovation Lab furthers SAP's commitment to preparing youth for success in a digital world.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14233399a10f4a2a7bfd4dbc3c97eb61be96447d1.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14233399a10f4a2a7bfd4dbc3c97eb61be96447d1.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_14233399a10f4a2a7bfd4dbc3c97eb61be96447d1.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Booting Up for the Future with Brooks Crossing Innovation Lab" src="./media_14233399a10f4a2a7bfd4dbc3c97eb61be96447d1.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="booting-up-for-the-future-with-brooks-crossing-innovation-lab">Booting Up for the Future with Brooks Crossing Innovation Lab</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-young-thinkers-enabling-youth-to-shape-the-world">SAP Young Thinkers: Enabling youth to shape the world</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/innovation/next-gen-innovation-platform/young-thinkers.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Our youth may be poised to shape tomorrow’s world, but we have to let them do it. That’s why at SAP, we’re committed to putting children in position for success now, devoting time, resources, and energy to education that will empower them later.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Today, we are furthering that commitment through a new program with Brooks Crossing Innovation Lab. The Newport News, Va.-based after-school instructional hub is dedicated to learning driven by science, technology, engineering, and mathematics (STEM) and grounded in team building and collaboration. At the lab, students of all ages, abilities, and disciplines learn valuable skills by designing creative solutions to real-world problems.</p>
  <p>“SAP’s support for Brooks Crossing Innovation Lab will not only boost a love for learning,” said Mia Joe, the lab’s director, “it will also make a generational impact on workforce development by providing more access to specialized educational resources and more opportunity for children during early and impressionable developmental stages.”</p>
  <p>The alliance is yet another logical outgrowth of <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/innovation/next-gen-innovation-platform/young-thinkers.html">SAP Young Thinkers</a>, a community for youth all over the world who are passionate about innovation and technology — and who want to influence the way our digital world will take shape. SAP works with colleagues, ambassadors, and a global network of diverse institutions to provide students with the opportunity to learn and practice their skills every day, all around the world.</p>
  <p>At <a href="https://www.nnva.gov/2509/Innovation-Lab">Brooks Crossing Innovation Lab</a> — the result of a collaboration among Newport News Shipbuilding, Old Dominion University, and the City of Newport News — SAP’s participation will lead to:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Integration of SAP Young Thinkers learning modules that encourage creative learning and social innovation</li>
    <li>Professionals from all participating organizations teaching workshops for K-12 and adult learners</li>
    <li>Increased collaboration on curriculum offerings and industry-led design thinking activities</li>
  </ul>
  <p>The program officially got rolling with a kick-off event in Newport News last month, highlighting a day in the life of the lab’s students and allowing them to create a game that was presented to SAP executives.</p>
  <p>“Meeting the instructor and the kids in this program was a powerful testament to the good that can be accomplished in our community,” said SAP Regulated Industries Chief Operating Officer Scott Thatcher. “The night was energetic and engaging, and it was thrilling to see the kids so locked in.”</p>
  <p>This is only the beginning of the relationship between SAP and Brooks Crossing Innovation Lab, but Thatcher is eagerly anticipating the children’s continued growth, whether it be in coding skills or social skills.</p>
  <p>“It was incredible getting to meet the people directly involved in this initiative and to see those in the community show up and invest of themselves,” he said. “This is going to have a real lifelong impact on these kids and their confidence, and I can’t wait to watch it happen.”</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Meet Africa Code Week’s Youth Ambassador]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/africa-code-week-youth-ambassador</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/africa-code-week-youth-ambassador</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Africa Code Week’s 2021 Youth Ambassador is 17-year-old Nigerian student Victory Yinka-Banjo, who is eager to empower young African minds.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1da3fe95137eee9f68d07672d3baa31b3eaaada98.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1da3fe95137eee9f68d07672d3baa31b3eaaada98.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1da3fe95137eee9f68d07672d3baa31b3eaaada98.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Meet Africa Code Week’s Youth Ambassador" src="./media_1da3fe95137eee9f68d07672d3baa31b3eaaada98.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="meet-africa-code-weeks-youth-ambassador">Meet Africa Code Week’s Youth Ambassador</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Speaking to Victory Yinka-Banjo is like drinking a fizzy drink; she bubbles with ideas and confidence. It’s no wonder that this 17-year-old Nigerian was chosen to be this year’s youth ambassador for Africa Code Week, the continent’s biggest digital skills youth initiative.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Even at her young age, Victory is no stranger to publicity. Earlier this year, she was offered 19 full scholarships to study at North American universities (She ended up picking MIT). But hers is no rags-to-riches story. The eldest daughter of two smart parents, a university lecturer mother and a father who works in procurement and supply chain management, Victory has always pushed herself to the limit. “My mother taught me how to hustle, and without this scholarship I could never have afforded to study in the U.S.,” she points out.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-africa-code-week">Learn more about Africa Code Week</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://africacodeweek.org/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="youth-ambassador-and-it-role-model-for-girls">Youth Ambassador and IT Role Model for Girls</h2>
  <p>Victory is looking forward to getting involved in this year’s <a href="https://africacodeweek.org/">Africa Code Week</a>, of which she is the official youth ambassador. Girls in science, technology, engineering, and mathematics (STEM) have traditionally lagged behind boys, which is why SAP and Camden Education Trust, the founders of Africa Code Week, are on a mission to make a difference – one African community at a time. Now in its seventh year, the program was proud to report 47% female participation in 2020. The event, which includes the popular AfriCANCode Challenge, has an enormous reach of 54 countries, with millions of children and youth participating. Last year, the program completely shifted to the exciting online world due to <a href="/covid-19">COVID-19</a>.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f25f5e30155c3b5c3c58d16be04bb33c57c10f19.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f25f5e30155c3b5c3c58d16be04bb33c57c10f19.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1f25f5e30155c3b5c3c58d16be04bb33c57c10f19.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Victory Yinka-Banjo headshot" src="./media_1f25f5e30155c3b5c3c58d16be04bb33c57c10f19.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="241" height="300">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p><em>Victory Yinka-Banjo</em></p>
  <p>“I participate in digital youth skills initiatives like Africa Code Week because I am passionate about empowering young people in underserved communities,” she says. Last year, she created an educational video encouraging children to learn computer programming with Scratch, MIT’s free online learning tool for coding. “Scratch is how I was introduced to coding,” she says, mentioning all its various applications that make it fun for kids, from interactive stories and games to animations. Scratch forms an integral part of Africa Code Week, encouraging teachers and African governments to see how easy it is to get kids into coding and fast-track them to the 21<sup>st</sup> century. To date, nine countries have adopted coding as a school subject thanks to the ongoing awareness, support, and contributions from the Africa Code Week program.</p>
  <p>A proud, female code representative, Victory wears many hats and keeps herself busy with multiple projects. In addition to Africa Code Week, she is actively involved with <a href="https://coderina.org/">Coderina</a>, a nonprofit organization that promotes ICT development, youth innovation, and entrepreneurship across Africa.</p>
  <p>“My first introduction to Coderina was during the pandemic last year. I helped facilitate the Lifelong Learning Program (LLP) sessions where young people were able to learn from a virtual space about everything digital skills related, from coding to 3D printing. I also taught a class during this period on design thinking and innovation. This year, I was a coach to the First Lego League (FLL) team comprising of a group of girls in secondary school in Nigeria. FLL is an exciting international robotics competition that is largely driven by Coderina.”</p>
  <h2 id="passionate-about-finding-solutions">Passionate About Finding Solutions</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="advancing-digital-skills-when-needed-most">Advancing Digital Skills When Needed Most</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/08/advancing-digital-skills-when-needed-most-sap-young-professionals-program">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>When asked what she likes about coding, Victory is unequivocal: she wants to find solutions. “I love the challenge of being given a problem and using technology to find a way to solve it,” she says. In 2019, she was part of the winning African team in the global mobile app building competition, Technovation. “The problem we had to solve was double parking, which is common in Nigeria,” she explains. “We developed an app that uses location sensors to enable your phone to pick up whenever another car parks you in, so you can step outside and speak to the owner or can communicate with the owner via instant messaging on the app.”</p>
  <p>It is this same passion for solving problems that has made her pursue a career in computer science and molecular biology. “There are so many different applications of these novel, overlapping fields, from aspects of synthetic biology to RNA sequencing in bioinformatics,” she says. Some of the questions that interest her are whether DNA can be used to store digital data and what machine learning tools can be used to model a vaccine to tackle the next variant of the coronavirus.</p>
  <p>One thing she’s sure about is that she doesn’t want to be put in a box. “Too many young people are fixated about their future career, wanting to become a doctor, engineer, or lawyer,” she says. “So many things are unconventional now. Rather than having a fixed profession, I want to say, ‘I do computational biology and it allows me to proffer solutions to this and that.’” Having a problem-solving mindset will elevate young Africans to be the change they want to see in the world, she believes – with a little bit of help from technology, of course.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Adam Hunter is EMEA communications lead for SAP CSR.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>non-sap-event/africa-code week</category>
            <category>news-tag/csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Advancing Digital Skills When Needed Most]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/advancing-digital-skills-when-needed-most-sap-young-professionals-program</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/advancing-digital-skills-when-needed-most-sap-young-professionals-program</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[During COVID-19, the SAP Young Professionals program went virtual, attracting recent graduates who might not have been able to attend in-person.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills-gap</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[De-Coding the Classroom]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/science-on-stage-de-code-the-classroom</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/science-on-stage-de-code-the-classroom</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 02 Aug 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Supported by SAP, the European Code Leaguge and Science on Stage enable more students to gain digital skills needed for a challenging future.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10ef344527722252b1347bd697f9b1d41b88e24d6.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10ef344527722252b1347bd697f9b1d41b88e24d6.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_10ef344527722252b1347bd697f9b1d41b88e24d6.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="De-Coding the Classroom" src="./media_10ef344527722252b1347bd697f9b1d41b88e24d6.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="de-coding-the-classroom">De-Coding the Classroom</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Teachers, along with their students, are shaping the future of education with Science on Stage’s European Code League. Meet this year’s inspiring 2021 winner.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In the 1940s, Nobel Prize-winning Hungarian biochemist Albert Szent-Gyoergyi wrote: “The future will be like the schools are today.” In 2021, these words still ring true, even more so for the winners of the European Code League competition, Dr. Corina Toma and Mihaela Giurgea, along with their students from Tiberiu Popoviciu High School of Computer Science in Romania. Second and third place went to teams from Turkey and Greece.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="in-a-post-pandemic-world-youth-take-center-stage-and-lead">In a Post-Pandemic World, Youth Take Center Stage and Lead</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/07/possibilists-study-youth-lead-post-pandemic-world">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="change-is-the-only-constant-but-changemakers-are-ever-changing">Change Is the Only Constant, but Changemakers Are Ever Changing</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-more-sap4good-stories">Read more SAP4Good stories</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/topics/sap4good">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The <a href="/covid-19">pandemic</a> has been quite a revelation in this aspect, with unexpected and seemingly limitless opportunities presenting themselves and youth grabbing them with both hands.</p>
  <p>According to a report by the World Economic Forum, around 65% of children who start primary school today will work in professions that do not even exist yet: their future lies in the hands of educators. To date, Science on Stage reaches about 100,000 teachers and teacher trainers in over 30 countries, providing a necessary network to exchange ideas and to scale them across Europe. And with 79% of participating teachers implementing the teaching ideas they’ve seen at Science on Stage festivals over the years, European Code League has proven that it’s possible for teachers and students to work together — even in the midst of a pandemic — to create inspiring, real-world science, technology, engineering, and mathematics (STEM) projects.</p>
  <p>Organized by Science on Stage with the support of the SAP Corporate Social Responsibility (SAP CSR) team in Middle Eastern Europe, the European Code League is a competition to which teacher-student teams with innovative coding projects can apply. It was launched in 2020 as a follow up to Science on Stage’s <a href="https://www.science-on-stage.eu/project/coding-stem-education">successful coding project for STEM education</a>.</p>
  <p>“Science on Stage gave me the opportunity to find new ways to motivate my students to learn physics using ICT,” says Dr. Toma, who became a teacher after 10 years working as a physicist. “Physics is everywhere and happens at any time. In the classroom, I am at home. I like to talk with my students and explain all kinds of topics.”</p>
  <p>Science on Stage Europe is a network for STEM teachers focusing on the exchange of best practice teaching ideas. The ultimate goal is to improve STEM teaching by supporting educators in their professional development and growth.</p>
  <p>“Teachers are often the ideas, the starting point. Students who finish high school do not know what their role in the world will be,” Dr Toma adds. “These projects show how important it is to code, and also to learn STEM subjects like mathematics, physics, chemistry, and biology.”</p>
  <p>CaeliBox, the winning coding project, used sensors to measure different air parameters such as concentration of CO2, humidity, pressure, temperature, noise, and other noxious substances in the studennts’ town. The data was transferred to a server so the students could access and work with it at any time.</p>
  <p>“My town in Romania used to be small but now it is very big. As a result, the air is polluted because we have so many cars. CaeliBox is a useful device for STEM education and our students were happy to combine coding with physics and technology,” explains Dr. Toma, who adds that she faced many challenges trying to complete the project, from broken sensors to realizing they needed more space and swapping out their Arduino Uno for an Arduino Mega.</p>
  <p>For Dr. Toma, Science on Stage is far more than a networking opportunity for teachers, it’s a community of like-minded educators: “At first, I saw that the education in Romania is very different from other countries, but then I realized that as teachers we have the same goals and can make the same activities. Science on Stage is a community to challenge our ideas and to understand that we are in the same place. SAP can be very proud for supporting STEM teaching training in Europe.”</p>
  <p>There is no one way to make the world a better place. By helping discover and promote innovative teaching concepts among Europe’s science teachers, Science on Stage and the European Code League enable more students to gain the digital skills they need for a challenging future and encourage them to consider a career in science, ICT or engineering to help the positively change the world.</p>
  <p>In a world shaped increasingly by technology and digitalization, teachers make the difference and the youth of today have so many more opportunities to learn and be the change.</p>
  <p>The 12th European Science on Stage festival takes place March 24-27, 2022, in Prague, Czech Republic. Stay tuned to see amazing youth in action, redefining how a career in science, ICT, or engineering can help make a positive change in the world.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>SAP is committed to helping the world run better and improve people’s lives, with youth playing a critical role. Join us in sharing good news by tagging your stories of inspirational youth or your actions inspiring youth with @SAP4Good on <a href="https://www.instagram.com/sap4good/">Instagram</a>, <a href="https://twitter.com/sap4good">Twitter</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/sap4good">Facebook</a>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning-for-life</category>
            <category>news-tag/redefining-youth</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Meet and Code Celebrates Five Years of Coding Impact]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/meet-and-code-five-years-impact</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/meet-and-code-five-years-impact</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jul 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Five years after its founding, Meet and Code continues to empower youth to shape their digital future through coding. Learn how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/un-sdgs</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enabling an Innovative, Agile Culture with SAP Innovate to Win]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/sap-innovate-to-win-agile-culture</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/sap-innovate-to-win-agile-culture</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Newly expanded, the SAP Innovate to Win program helps customers build an internal culture around innovative and agility. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_185769a8bf884145887bfdb3c5602151d7f6c78db.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_185769a8bf884145887bfdb3c5602151d7f6c78db.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_185769a8bf884145887bfdb3c5602151d7f6c78db.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Enabling an Innovative, Agile Culture with SAP Innovate to Win" src="./media_185769a8bf884145887bfdb3c5602151d7f6c78db.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="enabling-an-innovative-agile-culture-with-sap-innovate-to-win">Enabling an Innovative, Agile Culture with SAP Innovate to Win</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>To become an intelligent enterprise in our increasingly digitized and rapidly evolving world, it is crucial to foster an engaged workforce that prioritizes innovation and agility. Employers foresee skills such as problem-solving, critical thinking, creativity, flexibility, and active learning increasing in demand moving forward, according to the World Economic Forum’s recent <a href="https://www.weforum.org/reports/the-future-of-jobs-report-2020">Future of Jobs Report</a>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP is committed to setting individuals and teams up for success by creating opportunities to develop and hone new capabilities and ways of thinking. As part of this mission, we’ve expanded <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/05/4a102369-e17d-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html?source=social-Global-SAPEDU-TWITTER-MarketingCampaign-Training_Enablement-unspecified-spr-4846849072&#x26;campaigncode=CRM-WX20-EDU-SOC">SAP Innovate to Win</a>, a service designed to help customers get enabled on innovation frameworks and mindsets and apply these to build an internal culture around innovative and agility.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="turn-learning-into-achieving-with-sap-training-and-adoption">Turn learning into achieving with SAP Training and Adoption</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/training-certification.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="empowering-new-ways-of-thinking">Empowering New Ways of Thinking</h2>
  <p>Available for companies of all sizes and from all industries, SAP Innovate to Win is an innovation enablement and coaching service that helps companies to tackle their individual business challenges. We piloted the program in the Middle East and North Africa region, and have now expanded to support enterprises around the globe with virtual, in-person, and hybrid format options.</p>
  <p>The customized service enables teams within organizations to adopt Design Thinking — defined by <a href="https://hpi.de/en/school-of-design-thinking/design-thinking/what-is-design-thinking.html">The HPI School of Design Thinking (HPI D-School)</a> as a human-centered, iterative, team-based mindset that leads to breakthrough innovations — and to build digital prototypes using SAP technologies. It also uniquely includes Business Model Innovation, Blue Ocean strategy, positive psychology, and creative coaching.</p>
  <p>The standard program is delivered in seven different modules over the course of six weeks. With an emphasis on learning by doing, users complete field work in between each module to apply their learnings. This culminates in the final module when they then pitch the concepts they’ve developed to be utilized in real-world situations. SAP also creates a “maturity assessment,” or checklist, to help teams stay on track to achieve their objectives.</p>
  <h2 id="supporting-it-and-business-professionals">Supporting IT and Business Professionals</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-more-detail-on-the-innovation-enablement-and-coaching-service-with-sap-innovate-to-win">Get more detail on the innovation enablement and coaching service with SAP Innovate to Win</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/05/4a102369-e17d-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html?source=social-Global-SAPEDU-TWITTER-MarketingCampaign-Training_Enablement-unspecified-spr-4846849072&#x26;campaigncode=CRM-WX20-EDU-SOC">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP Innovate to Win is also designed for different types of professionals. First, the programming can be geared to people specializing in IT who want to collaborate more efficiently with the business side of an organization. With SAP Innovate to Win, IT professionals are better equipped to communicate with different kinds of teams and move from conversations centered on tech requirements to those focused on outcomes.</p>
  <p>On the other hand, business professionals can leverage SAP Innovate to Win to build digital skills and IT-inspired mindsets. In doing so, both business and IT teams can speak the same language to foster an innovation culture across the broader company.</p>
  <h2 id="propelling-future-success">Propelling Future Success</h2>
  <p>As the <a href="https://hbr.org/2020/01/the-transformer-clo">Harvard Business Review</a> described, to achieve learning goals, there is now a greater focus on developing growth mindsets and capabilities, rather than role-specific training. With the coaching from SAP Innovate to Win, teams are prepared — and empowered — to creatively explore solutions to unique business challenges that arise down the line.</p>
  <p>We continue to see customers benefit from a personalized SAP Innovate to Win curriculum. Vicky Hasioti, SAP Innovate to Win program director, noted: “Through SAP Innovate to Win, we have already supported our customers to create more than 250 low-fidelity prototypes for new solutions and road maps in an effort to solve business challenges and improve their companies’ business models.”</p>
  <p>In one example, in the United Arab Emirates, Dubai Future Foundation utilized SAP Innovate to Win in a series of workshops. Yaqoob Al-Zaabi from the Strategy Department at Dubai Future Foundation said, “It’s been a surprisingly great experience! It really helped me think in ways that I have never thought before. It also gave me a sense of self-confidence to express myself and give feedback. The content was very clear and everything had a practical aspect and purpose which gave me actionable skills that I can take with me into my job.”</p>
  <p>With the expansion of SAP Innovate to Win, SAP will support more customers around the world in their journeys to cultivate thriving innovation cultures that ultimately generate greater value for stakeholders in the future.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning-for-life</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-training-and-adoption</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Getting Ahead of the Skills Curve]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/getting-ahead-skills-curve</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/getting-ahead-skills-curve</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Businesses can get ahead of the skills curve by aligning strategic workforce planning and business strategy. Read to learn more!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1be3fe31204da0bc2c881ee5a27f5a8d1f0bd6231.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1be3fe31204da0bc2c881ee5a27f5a8d1f0bd6231.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1be3fe31204da0bc2c881ee5a27f5a8d1f0bd6231.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Getting Ahead of the Skills Curve" src="./media_1be3fe31204da0bc2c881ee5a27f5a8d1f0bd6231.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="getting-ahead-of-the-skills-curve">Getting Ahead of the Skills Curve</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>What’s the uber skill? The ability to constantly learn, evolve, update, or even un-learn relevant skills. Today, training workforces to acquire that mindset of continuous learning is everything. We spoke with Stefan Haenisch, senior vice president of SAP Learning Strategic Initiatives at SAP, to dive deeper into his perspective, especially as he comes out of the World Economic Forum’s summer event, <a href="https://www.weforum.org/events/the-jobs-reset-summit-2021">The Jobs Reset Summit</a>, and recently published an <a href="https://www.weforum.org/agenda/2021/05/back-to-school-4-lessons-in-workforce-skilling/">article</a> for WEF about the critical lessons in workforce skilling and lifelong learning.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-the-skills-you-need-anytime-anywhere-with-sap-learning-hub">Learn the skills you need anytime, anywhere with SAP Learning Hub</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://learninghub.sap.com/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="q-in-your-article-for-the-world-economic-forum-you-discuss-the-importance-of-connecting-business-strategy-to-workforce-skills-can-you-share-what-this-looks-like-and-why-its-so-essential">Q: In your article for the World Economic Forum, you discuss the importance of connecting business strategy to workforce skills. Can you share what this looks like and why it’s so essential?</h3>
  <p><strong>A:</strong> Every company plots out its business strategy. But how often does it think about how this relates and aligns with its people strategy and strategic workforce planning and skill building?</p>
  <p>For example, if our strategy is to use <a href="https://insights.sap.com/what-is-artificial-intelligence/">artificial intelligence (AI)</a> to make our products smarter, we must simultaneously be asking ourselves how we can <a href="https://insights.sap.com/importance-upskilling/">upskill the workforce</a> on the required skills to drive this vision.</p>
  <p>Skill training shouldn’t be an afterthought. Instead, by connecting skills and strategy from the very beginning, companies can proactively adapt and more effectively position themselves for long-term success.</p>
  <h3 id="how-does-an-organization-develop-skills-for-the-future-when-things-are-changing-so-frequently-and-we-cant-possibly-know-what-the-world-will-look-like-in-the-next-couple-of-years">How does an organization develop skills for the future when things are changing so frequently and we can’t possibly know what the world will look like in the next couple of years?</h3>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="how-to-upskill-staff-from-strategy-to-practical-steps">How to Upskill Staff: From Strategy to Practical Steps</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://insights.sap.com/how-to-upskill-guide/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As we saw with <a href="http://news.sap.com/covid-19">the global pandemic</a>, things may go differently than predicted. Companies must embrace ambiguity and disruption when it comes to skills for the future. A recent article in the <a href="https://hbr.org/2020/01/the-transformer-clo">Harvard Business Review</a> noted, “If you focus on building individual micro skills, you may be missing the bigger picture.” Indeed, there are ‘expiration dates’ on technical skills as innovation emerges, so companies must establish a culture that encourages agility and experimentation in the workforce – and, not least, motivates continuous learning – in order to yield sustainable success. Soft skills like dealing with uncertainty, staying curious, as well as embracing and tolerating ambiguity are the foundation of employees being ready for the future. They can then quickly and continuously keep up the relevant hard skills.</p>
  <p><a href="https://www2.deloitte.com/content/dam/Deloitte/global/Documents/HumanCapital/gx-the-future-of-work-post-covid-19-poc.pdf">A recent report from Deloitte</a> asserts that the <a href="https://insights.sap.com/what-is-future-of-work/">future of work</a> in our technology-driven world is about “creating an environment where organizations can optimize human potential” and “empowering workers with agency and choice over what they do, unleashing their interests and passions.” What this means is that the ultimate skill is being able to continuously learn in a constantly changing business environment. Fostering agile, innovative mindsets and curiosity throughout the workforce – promoting not only the <em>need</em> to learn, but the <em>want</em> to learn – helps companies to think big and earn a competitive edge.</p>
  <h3 id="how-do-offerings-at-sap-help-support-strategic-workforce-planning-and-continuous-learning">How do offerings at SAP help support strategic workforce planning and continuous learning?</h3>
  <p>At SAP, we value ongoing learning as part of the foundation for success. In the fast-moving tech sector where skill demand changes faster than in other industries, we’re constantly evolving our learning offerings to support the hard and soft skills needed to help people stay competitive.</p>
  <p>Inside SAP, for example, we look at a long and successful track record in deploying skills management to effective resource management in our consulting business and are now evolving this to support dynamic and forward-looking workforce planning and development.</p>
  <p>Our customers can benefit from our experience as we are incorporating the best practices we learned in people and skills management into our SAP SuccessFactors solutions. When it comes to helping our customers and partners build and sustain SAP product skills, our digital learning offerings, <a href="https://open.sap.com/">openSAP</a> and <a href="https://learninghub.sap.com/">SAP Learning Hub</a>, work to provide easy-to-use, engaging content for learners to explore, build, and maintain relevant skills. Additionally, we help support career planning around the skills that learners are honing, working to provide the right learning journey targeted to each learner’s goals.</p>
  <p>Our mission is to create learning and development opportunity for all across the SAP ecosystem. We aim to empower everyone to successfully build SAP software skills using future-oriented content delivered in different formats to fit individual ways of learning. By better aligning strategic workforce planning and business strategy at the onset, as well as becoming laser-focused on a workplace culture that values agility and curiosity, businesses can get ahead of the skills curve.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning-for-life</category>
            <category>news-tag/opensap</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-certification</category>
            <category>product/sap-learning-hub</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-training-and-adoption</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Learning With SAP: What's New and What's to Come]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/06/learning-with-sap-new-to-come</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/06/learning-with-sap-new-to-come</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[What's new and next for learning with SAP? Chief Learning Officer Max Wessel discusses SAP's work to accelerate digital skills of the future.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning-for-life</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-certification</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-training-and-adoption</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Plan to Revitalize Rural China]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/sap-technology-rural-revitalization</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/sap-technology-rural-revitalization</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Rural revitalization is essential to achieving sustainable living conditions. Learn how SAP technology is supporting efforts in China.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b462a712635d83f691e764a6a4a2df3720b72f94.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b462a712635d83f691e764a6a4a2df3720b72f94.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1b462a712635d83f691e764a6a4a2df3720b72f94.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="A Plan to Revitalize Rural China" src="./media_1b462a712635d83f691e764a6a4a2df3720b72f94.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="a-plan-to-revitalize-rural-china">A Plan to Revitalize Rural China</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>When Li Jie left his rural village in 2014 to begin a new life in Chengdu, a sprawling city of 16 million and the largest in Sichuan province, he could never have dreamed he would find prosperity by returning home as a farmer.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Back then there was very little reason to look back. <a href="https://www.chinadaily.com.cn/a/202011/18/WS5fb46f72a31024ad0ba94c6a.html">Poverty has hindered the development of rural Sichuan for decades</a>, but through government initiatives and entrepreneurial spirit, <a href="https://news.cgtn.com/news/2020-11-17/All-counties-in-China-s-Sichuan-have-cast-off-poverty-official--Vu8dJvYuAw/index.html">extreme poverty has largely been eradicated</a>.</p>
  <p>Since 2015, Li has maintained orchards full of blooming dragon fruit plants, one of <a href="https://www.novotaste.com/chinese-dragon-fruit-price-shows-upward-trend-fresh-plaza/">China’s most popular fruits</a>. An annual yield nearly 30,000 kilograms per acre has helped earn Li the honor of “top return entrepreneur” in Sichuan in 2020.</p>
  <p>Supported by SAP, he is now learning to apply new technologies in combination with trickle irrigation to achieve even greater yields at less cost.</p>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_146943e1f30b7292c3c02c8612334dd3a379bcdd4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_146943e1f30b7292c3c02c8612334dd3a379bcdd4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_146943e1f30b7292c3c02c8612334dd3a379bcdd4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Rural Revitalization: China’s New Strategy To Lift Millions Out of Poverty With the Help of Tech" src="./media_146943e1f30b7292c3c02c8612334dd3a379bcdd4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=a0TzuN738HU">Rural Revitalization: China’s New Strategy To Lift Millions Out of Poverty With the Help of Tech</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Li Jie’s story is an integral part of China’s transformation to economic superpower and its negative impact on rural areas. Four decades of strong growth and increases in per capita income have <a href="https://www.ifad.org/">lifted more than 800 million people out of poverty</a> and improved food security, nutrition, and human development.</p>
  <p>But there has been a palpable drain on rural towns, whose populations are projected to drop from 40% of China’s total population today to 31% by 2030. If not checked, this trend is predicted to have a <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/pulse/poverty-alleviation-rural-revitalization-post-2020-china-marchisio/?trk=public_profile_article_view">dramatic effect on the supporting capacity and social stability of rural areas</a>, according to Matteo Marchisio, head of East Asia Regional Hub at the International Fund for Agricultural Development.</p>
  <h2 id="urban-rural-divide-is-global">Urban-Rural Divide Is Global</h2>
  <p>The worldwide exodus from rural areas to cities is not new and it is not limited to China. The world’s rural citizens currently <a href="https://data.worldbank.org/indicator/SP.RUR.TOTL.ZS">make up 45% of the global population</a> but bear a disproportionate burden of poverty, malnutrition, and poor quality of life. This is why <a href="https://www.ifpri.org/blog/global-rural-crisis-rural-revitalization-solution">policy experts worldwide are calling for a system-wide transformation</a> to make rural areas more attractive to young people.</p>
  <p>Rebalancing initiatives, referred to as “rural revitalization,” are essential to achieving sustainable living conditions for all, concluded a <a href="https://doi.org/10.2499/9780896293502">recent report from the International Food Policy Research Institute</a>. “Policies, institutions, and investments that take advantage of new opportunities and technologies, increase access to basic services, create more and better rural jobs, foster gender equality, and restore the environment can make rural areas vibrant and healthy places to live and work,” the report stated.</p>
  <h2 id="sap-introduces-the-leader-plan">SAP Introduces The Leader Plan</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="with-indoor-farming-ever-is-revolutionizing-the-food-chain">With Indoor Farming, &#x26;ever Is Revolutionizing the Food Chain</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2020/04/indoor-farming-ever-revolutionize-food-chain">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Dragon fruit farmer Li Jie is at the forefront of an emerging trend in China, as more and more young people are attracted by government-sponsored incentives to move back to their rural communities and start new livelihoods as farmers. According to China’s Ministry of Agriculture and Rural Affairs, 7.5 million young people returned to rural areas in 2019.</p>
  <p>Since 2017, SAP has been supporting China’s “rural renaissance” by providing digital skills training and mentorship to these returning workers. Under the title “The Leader Plan,” SAP partnered in 2019 with <a href="http://en.youcheng.org/index/index/index.html">YouChange Foundation</a>, <a href="http://www.charityalliance.org.cn/English/index.jhtml">China Charity Alliance</a>, and <a href="https://www.tsinghua.edu.cn/en/index.htm">Tsinghua University</a> to launch the new initiative. SAP provides funding and volunteer expertise to develop learning courses that are delivered online. By 2023, SAP aims to train 50,000 rural entrepreneurs across 30 provinces.</p>
  <p>After moving back to his village, Li took online courses which focused on the industrialization and commercialization of agriculture. With his new knowledge and skills, Li plans to build intelligent greenhouses and manage the temperature in them automatically.</p>
  <p>Now in its third year, online courses have reached more than 43,000 learners. SAP has also supported Tsinghua University in conducting an “Elite Camp” courses and mentoring for entrepreneurs. “We’ve had great impact with The Leader Plan, and I look forward to more success in the future,” said Mark Gibbs, president SAP Greater China.</p>
  <h2 id="next-steps-for-the-leader-plan">Next Steps for The Leader Plan</h2>
  <p><a href="/2020/08/industry-in-china-smarter-faster-more-resilient-ai-machine-learnings">In the future</a>, SAP in China will explore how digital farming technology and information systems can help agricultural productivity in rural China. This includes the use of e-commerce, Internet of Things (IoT), data analytics and other technologies that support the entrepreneurs’ ambitions of improved productivity and commercialization. Employee volunteers will contribute their expertise to the program, and other opportunities such as the <a href="https://www.sap.com/dmc/exp/2017_03_46558/enUS/index.html">SAP Social Sabbatical</a> program will be explored to train rural entrepreneurs with the skills they need to grow their businesses sustainably.</p>
  <p><em>Top image via video.</em></p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/agribusiness</category>
            <category>news-tag/china</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>