<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-topic/investor-relations/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Enters into Agreement to Acquire WalkMe, Driving Business Transformation by Enhancing the Customer Experience and Enriching SAP Business AI Offerings]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-enters-agreement-to-acquire-walkme</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-enters-agreement-to-acquire-walkme</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is entering into an agreement to acquire WalkMe, a leader in digital adoption platforms. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17c02c58752a8aaaec6051673cfe2308da8b06446.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17c02c58752a8aaaec6051673cfe2308da8b06446.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_17c02c58752a8aaaec6051673cfe2308da8b06446.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Enters into Agreement to Acquire WalkMe, Driving Business Transformation by Enhancing the Customer Experience and Enriching SAP Business AI Offerings" src="./media_17c02c58752a8aaaec6051673cfe2308da8b06446.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-enters-into-agreement-to-acquire-walkme-driving-business-transformation-by-enhancing-the-customer-experience-and-enriching-sap-business-ai-offerings">SAP Enters into Agreement to Acquire WalkMe, Driving Business Transformation by Enhancing the Customer Experience and Enriching SAP Business AI Offerings</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) and WalkMe Ltd. (NASDAQ: WKME) announced today that the companies have entered into a definitive agreement under which SAP will acquire WalkMe, a leader in digital adoption platforms (DAPs).</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>WalkMe’s solutions help organizations navigate constant technology change by providing users with advanced guidance and automation features that enable them to execute workflows seamlessly across any number of applications. This results in higher adoption of the underlying application and as such drives value realization.</p>
  <p>The Executive and Supervisory Boards of SAP SE and the board of directors of WalkMe have approved the transaction for US $14.00 per share in an all-cash transaction, representing an equity value of approximately US $1.5 billion. The offer price represents a 45% premium to WalkMe’s closing share price on June 4, 2024.</p>
  <p>The envisioned combination complements SAP’s Business Transformation Management portfolio around SAP Signavio and SAP LeanIX solutions to help customers on their transformation journeys.</p>
  <p>“Applications, processes, data and people are the four key elements of a successful business transformation,” said Christian Klein, CEO and member of the Executive Board of SAP SE. “By acquiring WalkMe, we are doubling down on the support we provide our end users, helping them to quickly adopt new solutions and features to get the maximum value out of their IT investments.”</p>
  <h2 id="walkme-focus-on-analyzing-adoption-and-business-transformation">WalkMe: Focus on Analyzing Adoption and Business Transformation</h2>
  <p>“We are thrilled to join forces with SAP. This acquisition marks a significant milestone in our journey, providing us with the resources and customer base necessary to enhance our product offerings and expand our market reach,” said Dan Adika, CEO of WalkMe. “By leveraging SAP’s extensive ecosystem, we are poised to unlock substantial growth opportunities and deliver even greater value to our customers. Together, we look forward to a future filled with innovation and exceptional service.”</p>
  <p>WalkMe helps organizations boost enterprise productivity and lower risk by enabling consistent, effective and efficient use of software and the workflows it enables. Its DAP works on top of an organization’s application landscape, detects where people encounter friction and provides the tailored support and automation they need to complete the job to be done, right in the flow of work, across any application. Importantly, WalkMe will continue to fully support non-SAP applications.</p>
  <p>Soon, WalkMe will launch the WalkMe<sup>X</sup> copilot, which will use WalkMe’s contextual awareness and AI to suggest the best next step for any workflow, anywhere. WalkMe<sup>X</sup> has the capability to always be on, serving as an overlay to any application, including copilots from different vendors that companies use in their landscapes. Integrating the strength of WalkMe’s adoption capabilities with SAP’s copilot Joule will boost AI assistant and productivity gains for all SAP customers. Additionally, integrating distinctive e-learning features in the SAP Enable Now solution with WalkMe will form the center of SAP’s people-centric transformation approach going forward.</p>
  <p>The acquisition is subject to customary closing conditions, including the receipt of WalkMe shareholder approval and necessary regulatory clearances, and is expected to close in the third quarter of 2024. The impact of the transaction on SAP’s non-IFRS earnings per share for fiscal 2024 is expected to be immaterial.</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>About WalkMe</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>WalkMe (NASDAQ: WKME), headquartered in Tel Aviv, Israel, pioneered DAP innovations and solutions so companies can effectively navigate the constant change brought on by technology. With WalkMe, organizations drive enterprise productivity and reduce risk by ensuring consistent, responsible, and efficient adoption of software and the workflows it powers. Our AI-driven platform sits on top of an organization’s tech stack, identifies where people experience friction, and delivers the personalized guidance and automation needed to get the job done, right in the flow of work. Customers like IBM, Nestle, ThermoFisher Scientific, and the U.S. Dept. of Defense trust WalkMe to create the people-centric experiences required to boost the effectiveness of their workflows and maximize software ROI.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>About SAP</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As a global leader in enterprise applications and business AI, SAP (NYSE:SAP) stands at the nexus of business and technology. For over 50 years, organizations have trusted SAP to bring out their best by uniting business-critical operations spanning finance, procurement, HR, supply chain, and customer experience. For more information, visit <a href="http://www.sap.com">www.sap.com</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Note to editors:</strong><br>To preview and download broadcast-standard stock footage and press photos digitally, please visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/photos">www.sap.com/photos</a>. On this platform, you can find high resolution material for your media channels.</p>
  <p><strong>For customers interested in learning more about SAP products:</strong><br>Global Customer Center: +49 180 534-34-24<br>United States Only: 1 (800) 872-1SAP (1-800-872-1727)</p>
  <p><strong>For more information, financial community only:</strong><br>Anthony Coletta, +49 6227-7-60437, <a href="mailto:investor@sap.com">investor@sap.com</a>, CEST</p>
  <p><strong>For more information, press only:</strong><br>Joellen Perry, +1 650-445-6780, <a href="mailto:joellen.perry@sap.com">joellen.perry@sap.com</a>, PT<br>Daniel Reinhardt, +49 6227-7-40201, <a href="mailto:daniel.reinhardt@sap.com">daniel.reinhardt@sap.com</a>, CEST<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p><strong>For WalkMe Investor Relations:</strong><br>John Streppa, <a href="mailto:investors@walkme.com">investors@walkme.com</a></p>
  <p><strong>Additional Important Information and Where to Find It</strong> In connection with the proposed transaction, WalkMe will prepare a proxy statement to be delivered to its shareholders and furnished to the Securities and Exchange Commission (the “SEC”). INVESTORS AND SECURITY HOLDERS ARE STRONGLY ADVISED TO READ THE PROXY STATEMENT WHEN IT BECOMES AVAILABLE AND OTHER RELEVANT DOCUMENTS FILED OR FURNISHED TO THE SEC IN CONNECTION WITH THE PROPOSED TRANSACTION OR INCORPORATED BY REFERENCE THEREIN, BECAUSE THE PROXY STATEMENT AND SUCH OTHER RELEVANT DOCUMENTS WILL CONTAIN IMPORTANT INFORMATION ABOUT THE PROPOSED TRANSACTION AND THE PARTIES TO THE PROPOSED TRANSACTION. This press release is not a substitute for the proxy statement or any other document that may be filed or furnished by WalkMe with the SEC.</p>
  <p>The proxy statement and other related documents filed or furnished to the SEC regarding the proposed transaction may be obtained for free from the SEC’s website (<a href="http://www.sec.gov/">www.sec.gov</a>), WalkMe’s website at <a href="http://www.walkme.com">www.walkme.com</a> or by directing such request to WalkMe’s Investor Relations.</p>
  <p><strong>Forward-Looking Statements</strong><br>This press release contains “forward-looking statements” within the meaning of the “safe harbor” provisions of the Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995 and other applicable securities laws. All statements other than statements of historical fact, including statements regarding the proposed acquisition of WalkMe by SAP, the expected timing for completing the proposed transaction and the terms thereof, future financial and operating results, benefits and synergies of the transaction, future opportunities for the combined businesses and any other statements regarding events or developments that may occur in the future, may be “forward-looking statements” for purposes of federal and state securities laws. These forward-looking statements involve a number of risks and uncertainties that could significantly affect the financial or operating results of SAP, WalkMe or the combined company. Words such as “expects,” “anticipates,” “intends,” “plans,” “believes,” “estimates,” “predicts,” “seeks,” “targets,” “would,” “will,” “should,” “may” and variations of such words and similar expressions are intended to identify such forward-looking statements. Such statements are based on management’s expectations as of the date they are first made, are not guarantees of future performance and involve certain risks, uncertainties and assumptions that are difficult to predict. Neither SAP nor WalkMe can give any assurances that the expectations in such forward-looking statements will be attained and, therefore, actual outcomes and results may differ materially from what is expressed or forecasted in such forward-looking statements. For example, these forward-looking statements could be affected by factors including, without limitation, risks associated with the ability to consummate the proposed transaction, the satisfaction of the conditions to the consummation of the proposed transaction, including the receipt of certain regulatory approvals, and the timing of the closing of the proposed transaction; the occurrence of any event, change or other circumstance that could give rise to the termination of the proposed transaction; the potential that WalkMe shareholders may not approve the transaction; the ability to successfully integrate operations and employees; the ability to realize anticipated benefits and synergies of the proposed transaction as rapidly or to the extent anticipated by financial analysts or investors; the potential impact of the announcement of the proposed transaction on operating results, business generally and business relationships, including with employees, customers, suppliers and competitors; unanticipated restructuring costs may be incurred or undisclosed liabilities assumed; actual or threatened legal proceedings that have been or may be instituted against SAP or WalkMe in connection with the proposed transaction or otherwise; the ability and costs related to retaining key personnel and clients; risks related to diverting management’s attention from ongoing business operations; delays, challenges, costs, fees, expenses and charges related to the proposed transaction; actions by competitors; general adverse economic, political, social and security conditions in the regions and industries in which SAP and WalkMe operate, including relating to Israel’s ongoing war with Hamas and other terrorist organizations in the Middle East and general hostilities; exposure to inflation, currency rate and interest rate fluctuations and risks associated with doing business locally and internationally, as well as fluctuations in the market price of SAP and WalkMe’s traded securities; natural catastrophes, any pandemic, epidemic or outbreak of infectious disease, warfare, protests and riots, and terrorist attacks; and those additional risks and factors discussed in reports filed or furnished with the SEC by SAP and WalkMe, including SAP’s and WalkMe’s most recent Annual Reports on Form 20-F and in any subsequent reports on Form 6-K, each of which is on file with or furnished to the SEC and available at the SEC’s website at <a href="http://www.sec.gov/">www.sec.gov</a>. Reports filed or furnished with the SEC by SAP are also available on SAP’s website at <a href="http://www.sap.com/investors/en.html">www.sap.com/investors</a> and by WalkMe on WalkMe’s website at <a href="http://www.walkme.com">www.walkme.com</a>. Moreover, other risks and uncertainties of which SAP or WalkMe are not currently aware or may not currently consider material may also affect each of the companies’ forward-looking statements and may cause actual results and the timing of events to differ materially from those anticipated. The forward-looking statements made in this press release are made only as of the date hereof or as of the dates indicated in the forward-looking statements, even if they are subsequently made available by SAP or WalkMe on their respective websites or otherwise. Neither SAP nor WalkMe undertakes any obligation to update or supplement any forward-looking statements to reflect actual results, new information, future events, changes in its expectations or other circumstances that exist after the date as of which the forward-looking statements were made.</p>
  <p>© 2024 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE and affiliated entities in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p>Please consider our <a href="https://www.sap.com/corporate/en/legal/privacy.html">privacy policy</a>. If you receive this press release in your e-mail and you wish to unsubscribe to our mailing list please contact <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a> and write Unsubscribe in the subject line.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/investor-relations</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>product/sap-leanix</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-signavio</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Announces Adjustments to Dividend Policy]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-announces-adjustments-to-dividend-policy</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-announces-adjustments-to-dividend-policy</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP SE (NYSE: SAP) announced today that it is adjusting its dividend policy effective immediately.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b78a97bfc4812eee4dd40bb498139fcb007af75c.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b78a97bfc4812eee4dd40bb498139fcb007af75c.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1b78a97bfc4812eee4dd40bb498139fcb007af75c.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Announces Adjustments to Dividend Policy" src="./media_1b78a97bfc4812eee4dd40bb498139fcb007af75c.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-announces-adjustments-to-dividend-policy">SAP Announces Adjustments to Dividend Policy</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) announced today that it is adjusting its dividend policy effective immediately.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The new policy is to pay a dividend amounting to at least 40% of the SAP Group’s non-IFRS profit after tax from continuing operations (previously: at least 40% of the group’s IFRS profit after tax).</p>
  <p>This change is intended to reduce volatility in the dividend payout ratio and ensure close alignment between dividend payout and financial performance.</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Investor Relations Contacts:</strong><br>Anthony Coletta +49 (6227) 7-60437, <a href="investor@sap.com">investor@sap.com</a>, CEST</p>
  <p><strong>Media Contacts:</strong><br>Joellen Perry, +1 (626) 265-0370, <a href="mailto:joellen.perry@sap.com">joellen.perry@sap.com</a>, PT<br>Daniel Reinhardt, SAP, +49 6227-7-40201, <a href="mailto:daniel.reinhardt@sap.com">daniel.reinhardt@sap.com</a>, CEST<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>This document contains forward-looking statements, which are predictions, projections, or other statements about future events. These statements are based on current expectations, forecasts, and assumptions that are subject to risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results and outcomes to materially differ. Additional information regarding these risks and uncertainties may be found in our filings with the Securities and Exchange Commission, including but not limited to the risk factors section of SAP’s 2023 Annual Report on Form 20-F.<br>© 2024 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/investor-relations</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Alexandra Steiger to Join SAP as Global Head of Investor Relations]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/alexandra-steiger-to-join-global-head-sap-investor-relations</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/alexandra-steiger-to-join-global-head-sap-investor-relations</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Alexandra Steiger will join SAP as global head of Investor Relations on July 1, reporting to SAP Executive Board Member and CFO Dominik Asam.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_12c0f62a0c1bea8cebafaf88b1a2478cf4d11b899.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_12c0f62a0c1bea8cebafaf88b1a2478cf4d11b899.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_12c0f62a0c1bea8cebafaf88b1a2478cf4d11b899.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Alexandra Steiger to Join SAP as Global Head of Investor Relations" src="./media_12c0f62a0c1bea8cebafaf88b1a2478cf4d11b899.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="alexandra-steiger-to-join-sap-as-global-head-of-investor-relations">Alexandra Steiger to Join SAP as Global Head of Investor Relations</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced that Alexandra Steiger will join SAP as new global head of Investor Relations on July 1, 2024, reporting to Dominik Asam, member of the Executive Board and CFO of SAP SE.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>With over a decade of experience in the finance industry, Steiger has held roles at renowned institutions such as Goldman Sachs and UBS. She currently serves as executive director within Global Investment Research at Goldman Sachs, focusing on the U.S. Internet sector, including companies such as Alphabet, Meta and Amazon.</p>
  <p>“I am very happy Alexandra is joining SAP,” said Asam. “We will benefit from her leadership and the wealth of expertise she brings from her previous responsibilities. In her new role, she can build on the strong foundation laid by Anthony Coletta and the entire Investor Relations team.”</p>
  <p>Prior to her assignment at Goldman Sachs, Steiger was an executive director within UBS Equity Research, covering select U.S. Internet and Interactive Entertainment companies. She received a bachelor’s degree in International Business Administration from the University of Maastricht and a master’s degree in International Management CEMS from the Erasmus University Rotterdam and University of St. Gallen.</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="http://news.sap.com/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Media Contacts:</strong><br>Joellen Perry, +1 (626) 265-0370, <a href="mailto:joellen.perry@sap.com">joellen.perry@sap.com</a>, PT<br>Daniel Reinhardt, SAP, +49 6227-7-40201, <a href="mailto:daniel.reinhardt@sap.com">daniel.reinhardt@sap.com</a>, CET<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>Top image courtesy of SAP employee Laurentia-Iulia Pavel</p>
  <p>This document contains forward-looking statements, which are predictions, projections, or other statements about future events. These statements are based on current expectations, forecasts, and assumptions that are subject to risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results and outcomes to materially differ. Additional information regarding these risks and uncertainties may be found in our filings with the Securities and Exchange Commission, including but not limited to the risk factors section of SAP’s 2023 Annual Report on Form 20-F.<br>© 2024 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/investor-relations</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>news-tag/investor-relations</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pekka Ala-Pietilä Elected Chairman of SAP Supervisory Board — Strong Shareholder Support]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/pekka-ala-pietila-elected-chairman-sap-supervisory-board-2024-agm</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/pekka-ala-pietila-elected-chairman-sap-supervisory-board-2024-agm</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[At SAP's Annual General Meeting, Pekka Ala-Pietilä was elected as a new member of the company’s Supervisory Board. Read the 2024 AGM news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_199662acda1c93822a3bb96f83087091d36c8067e.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_199662acda1c93822a3bb96f83087091d36c8067e.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_199662acda1c93822a3bb96f83087091d36c8067e.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Pekka Ala-Pietilä Elected Chairman of SAP Supervisory Board — Strong Shareholder Support" src="./media_199662acda1c93822a3bb96f83087091d36c8067e.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="pekka-ala-pietilä-elected-chairman-of-sap-supervisory-board--strong-shareholder-support">Pekka Ala-Pietilä Elected Chairman of SAP Supervisory Board — Strong Shareholder Support</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>MANNHEIM</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced that at the company’s Annual General Meeting of Shareholders (AGM), Pekka Ala-Pietilä (67) was elected as a new member of the company’s Supervisory Board. Ala-Pietilä’s election was supported by 95.50% of shareholders. Subsequently, Ala-Pietilä was also elected the new Chairman of the SAP Supervisory Board, completing the handover from former Chairman of the Board, Prof. Dr. h. c. mult. Hasso Plattner.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“I am happy to pass the baton to Pekka Ala Pietilä to accompany SAP’s ongoing successful transformation,” said Plattner. “Pekka profoundly understands SAP and the technology industry and will strongly support the company in expanding its leadership in cloud ERP and business AI.”</p>
  <p>Ala-Pietilä added, “I am grateful to the SAP shareholders and Supervisory Board for the opportunity to rejoin Europe’s most important software company and I’m looking forward to help SAP broaden this strong position.”</p>
  <p>As announced in 2023, SAP Co-Founder and former Chairman of the Board Hasso Plattner left the SAP Supervisory Board after the 2024 AGM.</p>
  <p>During Plattner’s tenure as Chairman of the Supervisory Board (May 2003 to May 2024), SAP’s market capitalization increased from c. €30 billion to c. €200 billion, making SAP Germany’s most valuable listed company. Plattner’s innovative and competitive spirit has been a foundation of SAP’s success for more than 50 years, from the company’s first pioneering innovations in ERP to its strategic shift as an enterprise cloud and business AI leader. He will continue to serve as an advisor to SAP, ensuring his knowledge and experience remain available to the company.</p>
  <p>Aicha Evans (55), Gerhard Oswald (70) and Dr. Friederik Rotsch (51) were re-elected as members of the Supervisory Board with 93.39%, 89.82% and 92.45% of the vote respectively. Prof. Dr. Ralf Herbrich (50) was elected with 99.29% of the vote as successor to Punit Renjen, who left the SAP Supervisory Board at the end of the 2024 AGM.</p>
  <p>The AGM also supported all other proposals of the Executive Board and Supervisory Board. That included approving the actions of the Executive Board and Supervisory Board for fiscal 2023, 99.51% and 99.44% support respectively, and approving the adaptation of the compensation of the Chairman of the Supervisory Board. An overview of the resolutions of the Annual General Meetings 2024 and of previous years can be found <a href="https://www.sap.com/investors/en/calendar/agm.html">here</a>.</p>
  <p>For 2023, SAP shareholders will receive a dividend of €2.20 per share. This is an increase of €0.15, or seven percent compared to the dividend paid for 2022. The total payout to shareholders will thus amount to around €2.6 billion. The dividend is expected to be paid out from May 21, 2024.</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-financial-news-and-information-about-sap-and-company-performance">Get the latest financial news and information about SAP and company performance</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/investors/en.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>About SAP</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As a global leader in enterprise applications and business AI, SAP (NYSE: SAP) stands at the nexus of business and technology. For over 50 years, organizations have trusted SAP to bring out their best by uniting business-critical operations spanning finance, procurement, HR, supply chain, and customer experience. For more information, visit <a href="https://www.sap.com.">www.sap.com.</a></p>
  <p><strong>Note to editors:</strong><br>To preview and download broadcast-standard stock footage and press photos digitally, please visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/photos">www.sap.com/photos</a>. On this platform, you can find high resolution material for your media channels. To view video stories on diverse topics, visit <a href="http://www.sap-tv.com">www.sap-tv.com</a>. From this site, you can embed videos into your own Web pages, share video via email links, and subscribe to RSS feeds from SAP TV.</p>
  <p><strong>For customers interested in learning more about SAP products:</strong><br>Global Customer Center: +49 180 534-34-24<br>United States Only: 1 (800) 872-1SAP (1-800-872-1727)</p>
  <p><strong>For more information, financial community only:</strong><br>Anthony Coletta, +49 6227-7-60437, <a href="mailto:investor@sap.com">investor@sap.com</a>, CET</p>
  <p><strong>For more information, press only:</strong><br>Joellen Perry, +1 (650) 445-6780, <a href="mailto:joellen.perry@sap.com">joellen.perry@sap.com</a>, PT<br>Daniel Reinhardt, +49 6227-7-40201, <a href="mailto:daniel.reinhardt@sap.com">daniel.reinhardt@sap.com</a>, CET<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>This document contains forward-looking statements, which are predictions, projections, or other statements about future events. These statements are based on current expectations, forecasts, and assumptions that are subject to risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results and outcomes to materially differ. Additional information regarding these risks and uncertainties may be found in our filings with the Securities and Exchange Commission, including but not limited to the risk factors section of SAP’s 2023 Annual Report on Form 20-F.<br>© 2024 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/investor-relations</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/annual-general-meeting</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Information About Upcoming Merger of Hybris Gesellschaft mit beschränkter Haftung into SAP SE]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/information-about-upcoming-merger-of-hybris-gesellschaft-mit-beschraenkter-haftung-into-sap-se</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/information-about-upcoming-merger-of-hybris-gesellschaft-mit-beschraenkter-haftung-into-sap-se</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[0]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15b655c0ab7d21f5ade2aaaa7940105f194180d83.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15b655c0ab7d21f5ade2aaaa7940105f194180d83.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_15b655c0ab7d21f5ade2aaaa7940105f194180d83.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Information About Upcoming Merger of Hybris Gesellschaft mit beschränkter Haftung into SAP SE" src="./media_15b655c0ab7d21f5ade2aaaa7940105f194180d83.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="information-about-upcoming-merger-of-hybris-gesellschaft-mit-beschränkter-haftung-into-sap-se">Information About Upcoming Merger of Hybris Gesellschaft mit beschränkter Haftung into SAP SE</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Publication of SAP SE, Walldorf,<br>pursuant to Sec. 62 para. 3 sent. 2 half sent. 1 UmwG<br><br>– Information about upcoming merger –</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <ol>
    <li>It is intended to merge Hybris Gesellschaft mit beschränkter Haftung (local court of München, HRB 124384) as transferring company in the course of a simplified group merger into SAP SE as acquiring company. Therefore, the assets of Hybris Gesellschaft mit beschränkter Haftung in its entirety together with all rights and obligations are transferred to SAP SE with effectiveness as of 1 January 2024, 0:00 a.m. (“effective merger date”). From the effective merger date to the date of the expiry of Hybris Gesellschaft mit beschränkter Haftung pursuant to Sec. 20 para. 1 No.2 UmwG<br>all acts and businesses undertaken by Hybris Gesellschaft mit beschränkter Haftung shall be deemed to have been undertaken for the account of SAP SE.</li>
    <li>SAP SE is the sole shareholder of Hybris Gesellschaft mit beschränkter Haftung. A merger resolution of the acquiring company SAP SE is not necessary pursuant to Sec. 62 para. 1 sent. 1 UmwG. A resolution of the general meeting of Shareholders of SAP SE on the approval of the merger agreement is also not required because SAP SE as the acquiring company holds the share capital of Hybris Gesellschaft mit beschränkter Haftung in full. Since SAP SE holds all shares in Hybris Gesellschaft mit beschränkter Haftung, the preparation of a merger report, a merger audit and an audit report is not required pursuant to Secs. 8 para. 3 sent. 3 no. 1 a), 9 para. 2, 12 para. 3, 60 UmwG.</li>
    <li>The stakeholders of SAP SE with a combined holding of one-twentieth of the share capital of the company are herewith advised of their right to request the convention of a general meeting to decide on the approval of the merger (Sec. 62 para. 2 sent. 1, para. 3 sent. 3 UmwG).</li>
    <li>A resolution of the shareholder’s meeting of Hybris Gesellschaft mit beschränkter Haftung on the approval of the merger agreement is not required pursuant to section 62 para. 4 sent. 1 UmwG because SAP SE is the sole shareholder of Hybris Gesellschaft mit beschränkter Haftung.</li>
    <li>As of the date of this announcement, the following documents can be assessed by the links below:
      <ol>
        <li><a href="https://www.sap.com/docs/download/investors/2024/hybris-gmbh/hybris-merger-agreement-draft.pdf">The draft merger agreement between SAP SE and Hybris Gesellschaft mit beschränkter Haftung</a>.</li>
        <li>The annual financial statements and, where required, the annual reports of the companies who are parties to the merger for the fiscal years 2021, 2022, 2023:</li>
        <li><a href="https://www.sap.com/docs/download/investors/2021/sap-2021-rechnungslegung-hgb.pdf">2021 SAP SE Statutory Financial Statements and Review of Operations (HGB)</a><br><a href="https://www.sap.com/docs/download/investors/2022/sap-2022-rechnungslegung-hgb.pdf">2022 SAP SE Statutory Financial Statements and Review of Operations (HGB)</a><br><a href="https://www.sap.com/docs/download/investors/2023/sap-2023-rechnungslegung-hgb.pdf">2023 SAP SE Statutory Financial Statements and Review of Operations (HGB)</a><br><a href="https://www.sap.com/docs/download/investors/2024/hybris-gmbh/hybris-gmbh-jahresabschluss-2021-signed.pdf">2021 Hybris Gesellschaft mit beschränkter Haftung Financial Statements</a><br><a href="https://www.sap.com/docs/download/investors/2024/hybris-gmbh/hybris-gmbh-jahresabschluss-2022-signed.pdf">2022 Hybris Gesellschaft mit beschränkter Haftung Financial Statements</a><br><a href="https://www.sap.com/docs/download/investors/2024/hybris-gmbh/hybris-gmbh-jahresabschluss-2023-signed.pdf">2023 Hybris Gesellschaft mit beschränkter Haftung Financial Statements</a></li>
      </ol>
    </li>
  </ol>
  <p><strong>SAP SE, April 26, 2024</strong></p>
  <p><strong><em>The Board of Directors</em></strong></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/investor-relations</category>
            <category>content-type/statement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-investor-relations</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Announces Q1 2024 Results]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-announces-q1-2024-results</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-announces-q1-2024-results</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP has announced Q1 2024 financial results, with unabated growth momentum of the cloud ERP suite. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/investor-relations</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/earnings</category>
            <category>news-tag/investor-relations</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-investor-relations</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Chief Investor Relations Officer to Leave End of June]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/sap-chief-investor-relations-officer-anthony-coletta-to-leave-end-of-june</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/sap-chief-investor-relations-officer-anthony-coletta-to-leave-end-of-june</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Anthony Coletta will remain in his current role until the end of June 2024; the company is in the process of finding a successor.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/investor-relations</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>news-tag/investor-relations</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-investor-relations</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Releases Integrated Report 2023 and Files Annual Report 2023 on Form 20-F with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/sap-releases-integrated-report-2023-and-files-annual-report-2023-on-form-20-f</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/sap-releases-integrated-report-2023-and-files-annual-report-2023-on-form-20-f</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP SE today announced that it has filed the SAP Annual Report on Form 20-F as well as the 2023 SAP Integrated Report. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/investor-relations</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/investor-relations</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-investor-relations</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Proposes Dividend of €2.20 per Share and Announces Candidates for Shareholder Representative Elections]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/sap-proposes-dividend-and-announces-candidates-for-shareholder-representative-elections</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/sap-proposes-dividend-and-announces-candidates-for-shareholder-representative-elections</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP believes that its shareholders should benefit appropriately from the profit the Company made in 2023. The Company’s dividend policy is to pay a dividend ...]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1006f89343a6bddbfaa0b7d16f4c78618586e373b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1006f89343a6bddbfaa0b7d16f4c78618586e373b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1006f89343a6bddbfaa0b7d16f4c78618586e373b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Proposes Dividend of €2.20 per Share and Announces Candidates for Shareholder Representative Elections" src="./media_1006f89343a6bddbfaa0b7d16f4c78618586e373b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="196" height="130">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-proposes-dividend-of-220-per-share-and-announces-candidates-for-shareholder-representative-elections">SAP Proposes Dividend of €2.20 per Share and Announces Candidates for Shareholder Representative Elections</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong> — The Supervisory Board and Executive Board of <a href="http://www.sap.com">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) recommend that shareholders approve a dividend of €2.20 per share for fiscal year 2023. If approved by shareholders and assuming the same level of treasury shares as at December 31, 2023, the total amount distributed in dividends would be approximately €2.568 billion (2022: €2.393 billion), representing a pay-out ratio of 43.1% (2022: 139.6%).</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP believes that its shareholders should benefit appropriately from the profit the Company made in 2023. The Company’s dividend policy is to pay a dividend totaling 40% or more of profit after tax.</p>
  <p>The following dates are relevant for the dividend payment:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Record date for dividend payment: May 15, 2024</li>
    <li>Ex-dividend date: May 16, 2024</li>
    <li>Payment date: May 21, 2024</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="elections-of-shareholder-representatives-to-the-sap-supervisory-board">Elections of Shareholder Representatives to the SAP Supervisory Board</h2>
  <p>As announced on February 11, 2024, the <a href="/2024/02/pekka-ala-pietila-proposed-by-sap-supervisory-board-as-designated-successor-to-chairman-hasso-plattner">Supervisory Board has nominated Pekka Ala-Pietilä</a> to stand for election at the 2024 Annual General Meeting of Shareholders (AGM) as shareholder representative on the SAP Supervisory Board.</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Dr. h. c. mult. Pekka Ala-Pietilä</strong> (67), Helsinki, Finland, Chairman of the Board of Directors of Sanoma Corporation, Helsinki, Finland. In case of election, his term would expire in 2026. The Supervisory Board intends to elect him as chair.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>Further, the Supervisory Board is announcing the nomination of the following candidate to stand for election:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Prof. Dr. Ralf Herbrich</strong> (49), Falkensee, Germany, Managing director, professor for artificial intelligence and sustainability, Hasso Plattner Institute for Digital Engineering gGmbH, Potsdam, Germany. In case of election, his term would expire in 2028.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>Additionally, three candidates have been nominated to stand for re-election:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Aicha Evans</strong> (54), Los Gatos, CA, USA, Chief Executive Officer and member of the Board of Directors, Zoox, Inc., Foster City, California, USA. In case of re-election, her term would expire in 2028.</li>
    <li><strong>Gerhard Oswald</strong> (70), Walldorf, Germany, Managing director, Oswald Consulting GmbH, Walldorf, Germany; Associate lecturer, Technical University of Munich, Munich, Germany. In case of re-election, his term would expire in 2026.</li>
    <li><strong>Dr. Friederike Rotsch</strong> (51), Königstein im Taunus, Germany, Group General Counsel, Deutsche Bank AG, Frankfurt, Germany. In case of re-election, her term would expire in 2028 and she would continue in the role of Lead Independent Director (LID).</li>
  </ul>
  <p>These nominations are in alignment with the Profile of Skills and Expertise, the Supervisory Board’s Diversity Policy, and the objectives set by the Supervisory Board for its own composition.</p>
  <p><strong>Note to holders of SAP ADRs (American Depositary Receipts):</strong><br>One SAP ADR represents one SAP SE share. The final dividend amount per ADR is dependent upon the euro/US dollar exchange rate. Since SAP SE pays cash dividends on the ordinary shares in euro, the exchange rate fluctuations will affect the US dollar amounts received by holders of ADRs. The final dividend payment by SAP SE to the depositary bank is scheduled for May 21, 2024. The depositary bank will then convert the dividend payment from euro into US dollars as promptly as practicable.</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>About SAP</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP’s strategy is to help every business run as an intelligent, sustainable enterprise. As a market leader in enterprise application software, we help companies of all sizes and in all industries run at their best: SAP customers generate 87% of total global commerce. Our machine learning, Internet of Things (IoT), and advanced analytics technologies help turn customers’ businesses into intelligent enterprises. SAP helps give people and organizations deep business insight and fosters collaboration that helps them stay ahead of their competition. We simplify technology for companies so they can consume our software the way they want – without disruption. Our end-to-end suite of applications and services enables business and public customers across 26 industries globally to operate profitably, adapt continuously, and make a difference. With a global network of customers, partners, employees, and thought leaders, SAP helps the world run better and improve people’s lives. For more information, visit <a href="http://www.sap.com">www.sap.com</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Note to editors:</strong><br>To preview and download broadcast-standard stock footage and press photos digitally, please visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/photos">www.sap.com/photos</a>. On this platform, you can find high resolution material for your media channels.</p>
  <p><strong>For customers interested in learning more about SAP products:</strong><br>Global Customer Center: +49 180 534-34-24<br>United States Only: 1 (800) 872-1SAP (1-800-872-1727)</p>
  <p><strong>For more information, financial community only:</strong><br>Anthony Coletta, +49 (6227) 7-60437, <a href="mailto:investor@sap.com">investor@sap.com</a>, CET<br>Follow SAP Investor Relations on <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-investor-relations">LinkedIn</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>For more information, press only:</strong><br>Joellen Perry, +1 (650) 445-6780, <a href="mailto:joellen.perry@sap.com">joellen.perry@sap.com</a>, PT<br>Daniel Reinhardt, +49 (6227) 7-40201, <a href="mailto:daniel.reinhardt@sap.com">daniel.reinhardt@sap.com</a>, CET<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>This document contains forward-looking statements, which are predictions, projections, or other statements about future events. These statements are based on current expectations, forecasts, and assumptions that are subject to risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results and outcomes to materially differ. Additional information regarding these risks and uncertainties may be found in our filings with the Securities and Exchange Commission, including but not limited to the risk factors section of SAP’s 2022 Annual Report on Form 20-F.<br>© 2024 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/investor-relations</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pekka Ala-Pietilä Proposed by SAP Supervisory Board as Designated Successor to Chairman Hasso Plattner]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/pekka-ala-pietila-proposed-by-sap-supervisory-board-as-designated-successor-to-chairman-hasso-plattner</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/pekka-ala-pietila-proposed-by-sap-supervisory-board-as-designated-successor-to-chairman-hasso-plattner</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Pekka Ala-Pietilä has been nominated to stand for election as a new member of the Supervisory Board and successor to Hasso Plattner.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/investor-relations</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/investor-relations</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-investor-relations</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Announces Q4 and FY 2023 Results]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/sap-announces-q4-and-fy-2023-results</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/sap-announces-q4-and-fy-2023-results</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP SE announced today its financial results for the fourth quarter and fiscal year ended December 31, 2023.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1984fd48fa7c554f5d115cbe32c6e61bafdde4738.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1984fd48fa7c554f5d115cbe32c6e61bafdde4738.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1984fd48fa7c554f5d115cbe32c6e61bafdde4738.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Announces Q4 and FY 2023 Results" src="./media_1984fd48fa7c554f5d115cbe32c6e61bafdde4738.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-announces-q4-and-fy-2023-results">SAP Announces Q4 and FY 2023 Results</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> announced today its financial results for the fourth quarter and fiscal year ended December 31, 2023.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <ul>
    <li>SAP exceeds non-IFRS operating profit and cash flow outlook for FY 2023</li>
    <li>Cloud revenue up 20% and up 23% at constant currencies for FY 2023, underpinned by 25% cloud revenue growth at constant currencies in the fourth quarter</li>
    <li>Current cloud backlog of €13.7 billion, up 25% and up 27% at constant currencies</li>
    <li>IFRS cloud gross profit up 23%, non-IFRS cloud gross profit up 23% and up 27% at constant currencies in FY 2023</li>
    <li>IFRS operating profit down 5%, non-IFRS operating profit up 9% and up 13% at constant currencies in FY 2023</li>
    <li>2024 outlook anticipates accelerating cloud revenue growth</li>
    <li>Planned transformation program including restructuring in 2024 reflects focus on scalability of operations and Business AI</li>
    <li>2025 non-IFRS operating profit and free cash flow ambition updated to reflect updated non-IFRS definition as well as approximately half a billion Euro of incremental efficiency gains from the program</li>
  </ul>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div>SAP has delivered: We met or exceeded our outlook for 2023 in all key metrics. Based on a stellar order entry, our current cloud backlog expanded by 27% – an all-time high. We are confident about the company’s prospects in 2024. From this position of strength, SAP is opening the next chapter: with the planned transformation program, we are intensifying the shift of investments to strategic growth areas, above all Business AI. Going forward, this will empower us to keep leading with innovation while increasing the scalability of the operating model.</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>Christian Klein, CEO</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div>2023 was a year of inflection. We kept our promise and achieved double-digit non-IFRS operating profit growth despite an adverse macro environment. In 2024, we will focus on putting the right gradient of earnings growth in place to deliver on our raised ambition for 2025 and sustain growth and financial performance beyond.</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>Dominik Asam, CFO</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="https://www.sap.com/docs/download/investors/2023/sap-2023-q4-statement.pdf">Read the Quarterly Statement</a></p>
  <p><strong>Press Contacts:</strong><br>Joellen Perry, +1 (650) 445-6780, <a href="mailto:joellen.perry@sap.com">joellen.perry@sap.com</a>, PT<br>Daniel Reinhardt, +49 (6227) 7-40201, <a href="mailto:daniel.reinhardt@sap.com">daniel.reinhardt@sap.com</a>, CET</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/investor-relations</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/earnings</category>
            <category>news-tag/investor-relations</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-investor-relations</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Updates Its Ambition 2025 and Announces Transformation Program for 2024]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/sap-updates-its-ambition-2025-and-announces-transformation-program-for-2024</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/sap-updates-its-ambition-2025-and-announces-transformation-program-for-2024</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP SE (NYSE: SAP) announces plans to implement a company-wide transformation program including restructuring for 2024. In addition, SAP is updating its ambition for 2025. ...]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/investor-relations</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/investor-relations</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP to Release Fourth Quarter and Year-End 2023 Results]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/sap-to-release-fourth-quarter-and-year-end-2023-results</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/sap-to-release-fourth-quarter-and-year-end-2023-results</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP SE (NYSE: SAP) will release its results for the fourth quarter of 2023 and 2023 year-end results on Wednesday, January 24.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/investor-relations</category>
            <category>content-type/statement</category>
            <category>news-tag/earnings</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP to Update Financial Reporting and Receivables Financing Practices in 2024]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/sap-update-financial-reporting-and-receivables-financing-practices</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/sap-update-financial-reporting-and-receivables-financing-practices</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[WALLDORF — SAP updated its reporting and receivables financing practices, effective January 1, 2024. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b78a97bfc4812eee4dd40bb498139fcb007af75c.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b78a97bfc4812eee4dd40bb498139fcb007af75c.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1b78a97bfc4812eee4dd40bb498139fcb007af75c.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP to Update Financial Reporting and Receivables Financing Practices in 2024" src="./media_1b78a97bfc4812eee4dd40bb498139fcb007af75c.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-to-update-financial-reporting-and-receivables-financing-practices-in-2024">SAP to Update Financial Reporting and Receivables Financing Practices in 2024</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced updates to its reporting and receivables financing practices, which will become effective January 1, 2024.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The updates mainly include:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>The inclusion of share-based compensation (SBC) expenses in non-IFRS results,</li>
    <li>The exclusion of gains/losses from equity investments, mainly driven by SAPPHIRE Ventures, from non-IFRS results,</li>
    <li>The general shift of gains/losses even on smaller divestitures to non-operating income/expense,</li>
    <li>The discontinuation of the company’s receivables financing program (“SAP triggered financing”).</li>
  </ul>
  <p>The updates will be reflected for the first time in SAP’s Q1 2024 results, which will be reported on April 22, 2024. While the updates will not impact Q4/FY 2023 results, which will be reported January 24, they will be reflected in SAP’s outlook for 2024 as well as potential updates to its Financial Ambition 2025.</p>
  <p>“By implementing these updates, we hope to further increase the transparency of our operating results, while at the same time reducing short-term noise and volatility,“ said Dominik Asam, CFO and member of the Executive Board of SAP. “Including share-based compensation in our adjusted earnings may be interpreted as a disadvantage in comparison with some of our peers. But we believe recognizing share-based compensation as a genuine expense of running a business is long overdue. We are also convinced that appropriately reflecting it in steering and the incentivization of management will ultimately add economic value.”</p>
  <p>Reflecting the company’s increasing focus on cross- and upselling its broader cloud solution portfolio, SAP also announced its intent to replace the current “SAP S/4HANA Cloud” revenue and current cloud backlog disclosure with a more broadly defined “Cloud ERP Suite” revenue disclosure in 2024.</p>
  <p>Additional background on the announced updates, including a replay of an analyst and investor call hosted by Dominik Asam on Monday, December 18, can be found at SAP’s investor relations website at <a href="https://www.sap.com/investor">www.sap.com/investor</a>.</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="http://news.sap.com/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Media Contact:</strong><br>Joellen Perry, SAP, +1-626-265-0370, <a href="mailto:joellen.perry@sap.com">joellen.perry@sap.com</a>, PT<br>Daniel Reinhardt, SAP, +49-6227-7-40201, <a href="mailto:daniel.reinhardt@sap.com">daniel.reinhardt@sap.com</a>, CET<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-us-on-linkedin-for-the-latest-news-and-updates">Connect with us on LinkedIn for the latest news and updates</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news/posts/?feedView=all">Follow SAP News</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>This document contains forward-looking statements, which are predictions, projections, or other statements about future events. These statements are based on current expectations, forecasts, and assumptions that are subject to risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results and outcomes to materially differ. Additional information regarding these risks and uncertainties may be found in our filings with the Securities and Exchange Commission, including but not limited to the risk factors section of SAP’s 2022 Annual Report on Form 20-F.<br>© 2023 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/investor-relations</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>news-tag/investor-relations</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-investor-relations</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Completes Acquisition of LeanIX]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/sap-completes-acquisition-of-leanix</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/sap-completes-acquisition-of-leanix</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP has completed the acquisition of LeanIX, a market leader for enterprise architecture management (EAM). Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/investor-relations</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>product/sap-leanix</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Announces Q3 2023 Results]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/sap-announces-q3-2023-results</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/sap-announces-q3-2023-results</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP SE (NYSE: SAP) today announced its financial results for the third quarter ended September 30, 2023.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/investor-relations</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/earnings</category>
            <category>news-tag/investor-relations</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-investor-relations</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Announces Updated Timing of Third and Fourth Quarters 2023 Earnings Releases and Financial Analyst Calls]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/sap-announces-updated-timing-of-earnings-releases-and-financial-analyst-calls</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/sap-announces-updated-timing-of-earnings-releases-and-financial-analyst-calls</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP SE (NYSE: SAP) today announced the following schedule for the regular release of financial information for the third and fourth quarters 2023:]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/investor-relations</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/earnings</category>
            <category>news-tag/investor-relations</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-investor-relations</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP to Acquire LeanIX, Delivering Customers a Comprehensive Solution Suite for Continuous Business Transformation and a Foundation for AI-Enabled Process Optimization]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/sap-to-acquire-leanix</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/sap-to-acquire-leanix</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Together SAP and LeanIX will offer a first-of-its-kind transformation suite to provide holistic support to customers. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/investor-relations</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/enterprise-architecture-management</category>
            <category>product/sap-leanix</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-signavio</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Announces Q2 2023 Results]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/sap-announces-q2-2023-results</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/sap-announces-q2-2023-results</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP SE (NYSE: SAP) today announced its financial results for the second quarter ended June 30, 2023.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/investor-relations</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/earnings</category>
            <category>news-tag/investor-relations</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-investor-relations</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP's Credit Rating Upgraded to A+ by Standard and Poor's]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/sap-credit-rating-upgraded</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/sap-credit-rating-upgraded</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP SE was informed that Standard and Poor’s (S&P) upgraded SAP’s credit rating to A+ from A. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/investor-relations</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-investor-relations</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Information About Upcoming Merger of SAP Portals Europe GmbH into SAP SE]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/06/information-about-upcoming-merger-of-sap-portals-europe-gmbh-into-sap-se</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/06/information-about-upcoming-merger-of-sap-portals-europe-gmbh-into-sap-se</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[0]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/investor-relations</category>
            <category>content-type/statement</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Completes Sale of Its Stake in Qualtrics as Silver Lake and CPP Investments Complete Qualtrics Acquisition]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/06/sap-completes-sale-of-its-stake-in-qualtrics-as-silver-lake-and-cpp-investments-complete-qualtrics-acquisition</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/06/sap-completes-sale-of-its-stake-in-qualtrics-as-silver-lake-and-cpp-investments-complete-qualtrics-acquisition</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP SE (NYSE: SAP), today announced that Silver Lake Management, the global leader in technology investing, and its co-investors along with the Canada Pension Plan ...]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/investor-relations</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-investor-relations</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Announces Updated Time of Second Quarter 2023 Earnings Release and Financial Analyst Call]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/06/sap-announces-updated-time-of-second-quarter-2023-earnings-release</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/06/sap-announces-updated-time-of-second-quarter-2023-earnings-release</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP SE (NYSE: SAP) today announced that it will publish its regular earnings release for the second quarter 2023 at 6:00 p.m. CEST / 5:00 ...]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/investor-relations</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/earnings</category>
            <category>news-tag/investor-relations</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-investor-relations</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Updates Mid-Term Financial Ambition 2025 and Announces Share Repurchase Program of up to €5 Billion]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/sap-updates-mid-term-financial-ambition-2025</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/sap-updates-mid-term-financial-ambition-2025</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP has announced an update of its mid-term financial Ambition 2025 as well as a new share repurchase program of up to €5 billion.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/investor-relations</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/investor-relations</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-investor-relations</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Punit Renjen Elected to SAP Supervisory Board With Strong Shareholder Support; Named Deputy Chairperson]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/punit-renjen-elected-to-sap-supervisory-board-named-deputy-chairperson</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/punit-renjen-elected-to-sap-supervisory-board-named-deputy-chairperson</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Punit Renjen has been elected as a new member of the SAP Supervisory Board. Renjen’s election was supported by 99.21% of the shareholders.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/investor-relations</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/annual-general-meeting</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Announces Q1 2023 Results]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/sap-announces-q1-2023-results</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/sap-announces-q1-2023-results</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP SE (NYSE: SAP) today announced its financial results for the first quarter ended March 31, 2023.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/investor-relations</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/earnings</category>
            <category>news-tag/investor-relations</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-investor-relations</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP to Release First Quarter 2023 Results]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/sap-to-release-q1-2023-results</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/sap-to-release-q1-2023-results</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP will release its Q1 2023 results on Friday, April 21.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/investor-relations</category>
            <category>content-type/statement</category>
            <category>news-tag/earnings</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Finalized New Sustainability-Linked Revolving Credit Facility of €3 Billion]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/sap-finalized-new-sustainability-linked-revolving-credit-facility</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/sap-finalized-new-sustainability-linked-revolving-credit-facility</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[WALLDORF — SAP SE (NYSE: SAP) signed new €3 billion sustainability-linked revolving credit facility]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/investor-relations</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/investor-relations</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-investor-relations</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Agrees to Sell Its Stake in Qualtrics as Part of Qualtrics Acquisition by Silver Lake and CPP Investments]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/sap-agrees-to-sell-its-stake-in-qualtrics</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/sap-agrees-to-sell-its-stake-in-qualtrics</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP SE (NYSE: SAP), today announced it has agreed to sell all of its 423 million shares of Qualtrics International Inc. as part of the ...]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/investor-relations</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/experience-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/qualtrics</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Releases Integrated Report 2022 and Files Annual Report 2022 on Form 20-F with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/sap-releases-integrated-report-2022-and-files-annual-report-2022-on-form-20-f</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/sap-releases-integrated-report-2022-and-files-annual-report-2022-on-form-20-f</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP SE (NYSE: SAP) today announced that it has filed the SAP Annual Report on Form 20-F for the year ended December 31, 2022, with ...]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/investor-relations</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/investor-relations</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-investor-relations</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>