<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/forrester/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Master Data Governance Named a Leader in 2023 Master Data Management Analyst Report]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/sap-master-data-governance-leader-forrester</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/sap-master-data-governance-leader-forrester</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Master Data Governance has been named a Leader in The Forrester Wave™: Master Data Management, Q2 2023 report. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/forrester</category>
            <category>news-tag/master-data-management</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-master-data-governance</category>
            <category>news-tag/the-forrester-wave</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Preferred Success: Where the Benefits of Cloud Adoption Outweigh the Costs]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/sap-preferred-success-benefits-cloud-adoption-outweigh-costs</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/sap-preferred-success-benefits-cloud-adoption-outweigh-costs</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A Forrester study show that SAP Preferred Success allows customers to gain an advantage from their cloud investment. Read to find out how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/forrester</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-preferred-success</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Forrester Consulting Study Shows How SAP MaxAttention Supported Better, Faster Cloud Adoption]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/forrester-consulting-study-sap-maxattention-supported-cloud-adoption</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/forrester-consulting-study-sap-maxattention-supported-cloud-adoption</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The Forrester study concluded that SAP MaxAttention delivered an impressive three-year financial impact throughout the cloud journey.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/forrester</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-maxattention</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Named a Leader in Delivering Translytical Data Platforms in Forrester Wave Evaluation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/translytical-data-platforms-forrester-wave-sap-a-leader</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/translytical-data-platforms-forrester-wave-sap-a-leader</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is a leader in The Forrester Wave: Translytical Data Platforms 2022 for the product vision and planned enhancements criteria.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/data-analytics</category>
            <category>news-tag/database-and-data-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/forrester</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Digital Innovations Behind the Booming Life Sciences Industry]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/digital-innovations-life-sciences-industry</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/digital-innovations-life-sciences-industry</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The pandemic has irrevocably disrupted the life sciences industry, revealing a new vision for innovation from cloud-based collaboration.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/covid-19</category>
            <category>news-tag/forrester</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>industry/healthcare</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>industry/life-sciences</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Named a Leader Among Digital Operations Platforms for Manufacturing and Distribution and Digital Operations Platforms for Services]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/09/sap-a-leader-digital-operations-platforms-manufacturing-distribution-services</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/09/sap-a-leader-digital-operations-platforms-manufacturing-distribution-services</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Forrester has named SAP a Leader in “digital operations platforms for both manufacturing and distribution as well as services. Learn why.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/forrester</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Named a Leader among Enterprise Data Fabric Solutions by Forrester Research, Inc.]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/06/sap-leader-enterprise-data-fabric-solutions-forrester-research</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/06/sap-leader-enterprise-data-fabric-solutions-forrester-research</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Forrester Research, Inc., has recognized SAP in "The Forrester Wave: Enterprise Data Fabric, Q2 2022" report. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/database-and-data-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/forrester</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-data-intelligence</category>
            <category>product/sap-data-intelligence-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Preventing Cybercrime with a Solid Security Culture]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/03/preventing-cybercrime-solid-security-culture</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/03/preventing-cybercrime-solid-security-culture</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Building a security culture with shared responsibility and accountability company-wide is the best defense against cybercrime. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ed0db808ab7bc42e8ffe4aeb17d137cd686d0b64.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ed0db808ab7bc42e8ffe4aeb17d137cd686d0b64.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1ed0db808ab7bc42e8ffe4aeb17d137cd686d0b64.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Preventing Cybercrime with a Solid Security Culture" src="./media_1ed0db808ab7bc42e8ffe4aeb17d137cd686d0b64.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="preventing-cybercrime-with-a-solid-security-culture">Preventing Cybercrime with a Solid Security Culture</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Cybercrime is not inevitable. With a <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/trust-center/security.html?pdf-asset=c8573354-f87d-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b&#x26;page=1">security culture</a>, meaning a rigorous, people-first risk management strategy, organizations can muster the vigilance to head off threats.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In the wake of <a href="https://www.scientificamerican.com/article/the-log4j-software-flaw-is-christmas-come-early-for-cybercriminals/">Log4j</a> vulnerabilities, massive breaches like <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/thomasbrewster/2021/02/03/severe-solarwinds-vulnerabilities-allow-hackers-to-take-over-servers-update-now/?sh=4966e1ae687c">SolarWinds</a>, and the <a href="https://www.cnn.com/2021/12/18/business/cream-cheese-cyberattack-schreiber-foods/index.html">cream cheese shortage</a> during the 2021 holiday season, organizations are changing up security strategies to mitigate <a href="https://cybersecurityventures.com/cybercrime-damages-6-trillion-by-2021/">cybercrime</a> damages that are predicted to total US$10.5 trillion annually by 2025.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="explore-the-security-culture-toolkit">Explore the Security Culture Toolkit</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/trust-center/security.html?pdf-asset=c8573354-f87d-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b&#x26;page=1">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="security-cultures-prioritize-new-business-practices">Security Cultures Prioritize New Business Practices</h2>
  <p>As every company becomes technology-driven, risks are escalating, pushing security much closer to the top of business priorities. <a href="https://www.gartner.com/en/articles/the-top-8-cybersecurity-predictions-for-2021-2022">Gartner</a> researchers said that by 2025, 70% of CEOs will mandate a culture of organizational resilience to survive coinciding threats from cybercrime, severe weather events, civil unrest, and political instabilities. Meanwhile, security cultures will have changed numerous business practices. By next year, <a href="https://www.idc.com/getdoc.jsp?containerId=US47193621">IDC</a> analysts said that 80% of organizations faced with complex global regulations will increase security compliance automation investments by 25% to consistently meet policies and regulations. In the same time frame, IDC predicted 25% of G2000 public cloud customers will subscribe to integrated risk management and cyber-insurance policies through shared fate/risk programs to protect against sophisticated cyberattacks.</p>
  <h2 id="make-security-a-company-wide-responsibility">Make Security a Company-Wide Responsibility</h2>
  <p>Security and risk leaders who responded to a recent Gartner <a href="https://www.gartner.com/smarterwithgartner/develop-a-security-strategy-for-cyber-physical-systems/">survey</a> ranked the Internet of Things (IoT) and cyber-physical systems as their top concerns for the next three to five years. <a href="https://www.gartner.com/en/information-technology/trends/the-it-roadmap-for-cybersecurity">Gartner</a> analysts predicted that by 2023, 75% of organizations will restructure risk and security governance to address the widespread adoption of advanced technologies, an increase from less than 15% today.</p>
  <p>In a world where just about every organization is in the computer industry, embedded secure practices across the organization are table stakes. For example, SAP follows the NIST (National Institute of Technology in North America) cybersecurity framework, a holistic security strategy based on repeatable processes. This approach harmonizes controlled security company-wide, including product development and operations.</p>
  <p>“Security has always been our number one concern,” said Tim McKnight, executive vice president and chief security officer at SAP. “With the acceleration of digitalization, organizations have embarked on a massive cloud-based computing transformation that extends to security. We’ve undergone a multi-year security transformation backed by the commitment of our Executive Board and real-time input from customers.”</p>
  <p>A security culture comes down to a shared vision that’s carried out by leaders who make security a priority and teams who participate in ongoing trainings that celebrate success and learn from failures. People in any sector can take a page out of the software applications industry playbook.</p>
  <p>“We’ve set cybersecurity goals for all of our executives,” said McKnight. “We present these measures to the Board on a regular basis, reviewing progress against security initiatives. With open conversations around security, we reinforce priorities while driving accountability from each department. Whether you’re an executive, team lead, or individual contributor, you need to understand your role in driving a security culture with a security-first mentality. After all, the vast majority of security incidents are the result of human error.”</p>
  <h2 id="dont-let-other-business-demands-supersede-security-resources">Don’t Let Other Business Demands Supersede Security Resources</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="secure-your-intelligent-enterprise-with-sap">Secure your intelligent enterprise with SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/trust-center/security.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>While just-in-time supply chains boost business agility in a <a href="/topics/covid-19">post-pandemic</a> environment, having more partners also increases risk. <a href="https://www.forrester.com/predictions/">Forrester</a> researchers predicted that 60% of security incidents will involve third parties in 2022. Maybe that’s why <a href="https://www.idc.com/getdoc.jsp?containerId=US47193621">IDC</a> researchers said that by next year, 55% of organizations will allocate half of their security budgets to cross-technology ecosystems and platforms designed for rapid consumption and unified security capabilities to drive agile innovation.</p>
  <p>Companies need to allocate sufficient resources to prioritize security across the entire product life cycle, from development through go-live and support. With intelligent capabilities from artificial intelligence (AI), machine learning, robotic process automation (RPA), and other technologies, products and services increasingly require advanced security measures.</p>
  <p>“An effective culture makes security everyone’s responsibility,” said Wiebke Thelo, senior vice president and head of SAP Quality, Application Security, and Production. “For example, business information security officers at SAP report directly into business unit leaders. They work together, making sure that security is embedded into product design, development, and operation.”</p>
  <h2 id="educate-employees-now-for-a-trusted-future">Educate Employees Now for a Trusted Future</h2>
  <p><a href="https://www.idc.com/getdoc.jsp?containerId=US48154621&#x26;pageType=PRINTFRIENDLY">IDC</a> research showed that close to 25% of organizations report ransomware infections weekly. Human judgment is core to preventing these incidents. However, <a href="https://www.forrester.com/blogs/predictions-2022-continued-uncertainty-forces-attention-on-securing-relationships/">Forrester</a> analysts warned about the “security brain drain” as one in 10 experienced professionals have exited the industry during the past year. These analysts advised security executives to address burnout and team culture problems and use succession planning to build a pipeline of security leaders.</p>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div><a href="/2022/02/sap-teams-with-hbcus-next-generation-cybersecurity">SAP Teams Up with HBCUs to Attract Talent to the Cybersecurity Curriculum</a></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/2022/02/sap-teams-with-hbcus-next-generation-cybersecurity/embed/#?secret=KrZWqWNpab#?secret=TP1q2sHDbR">“SAP Teams Up with HBCUs to Attract Talent to the Cybersecurity Curriculum” — SAP News Center</a></p>
  <p>“A security culture requires significant learning and development, which is why we’ve professionalized security,” said McKnight. “The human element is critical – we position people first, process second, and technology third. We start with our people and make sure they have the skills they need.”</p>
  <p>As remote working, just-in-time supply chains, and tech innovations continue, companies have to think and act faster than the criminals. There’s never a good time for a cyberattack. Just ask the people who suffered through the cream cheese shortage. Criminals don’t take holidays and a security culture is the best protection.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Follow me @smgaler</em><br><em><a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2022/01/20/preventing-the-next-log4j-with-a-solid-security-culture/?sh=297049942c43">This also appeared on SAP BrandVoice on Forbes.</a></em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/financial-management</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/cybersecurity</category>
            <category>news-tag/forrester</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Retail Trends 2022: In Search of the Ultimate Customer Experience]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/03/retail-trends-2022</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/03/retail-trends-2022</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[What retail trends can we expect in 2022? The right combination of digital and physical CX, sustainability, and great employee experiences.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/forrester</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Workforce Trends 2022: How Companies Are Building Digital Dream Teams]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/02/workforce-trends-2022</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/02/workforce-trends-2022</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Analysts identify incoming workforce trends, revealing how employers are revamping HCM norms to improve the employee experience. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e7a28fd0b82c4064c764164f31084da5ca03f255.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e7a28fd0b82c4064c764164f31084da5ca03f255.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1e7a28fd0b82c4064c764164f31084da5ca03f255.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Workforce Trends 2022: How Companies Are Building Digital Dream Teams" src="./media_1e7a28fd0b82c4064c764164f31084da5ca03f255.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="workforce-trends-2022-how-companies-are-building-digital-dream-teams">Workforce Trends 2022: How Companies Are Building Digital Dream Teams</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>While employees have their say about where, when, and how they want to work, company leaders are just as busy creating the post-pandemic workplace.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>From work anywhere flexibility to technology-driven individual and team augmentation, these are some of the top workforce predictions about how companies can craft the ideal employee experience (EX) for increasingly digitalized, sustainable business models.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="put-employees-at-the-heart-of-everything-you-do-with-sap-successfactors-software">Put employees at the heart of everything you do with SAP SuccessFactors software</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="hybrid-work-upheaves-workplace-norms">Hybrid Work Upheaves Workplace Norms</h2>
  <p>Conversations about remote versus on-site work erroneously position these decisions as an either/or choice. <a href="https://www.forrester.com/blogs/future-of-work-predictions-2022-eu/">Forrester</a> data revealed that in Europe, “skilled employees will force employers to grant them greater flexibility – or leave.”</p>
  <p>Similarly, <a href="https://www.forrester.com/blogs/predictions-2022/">Forrester</a> Analyst Sharyn Leaver predicted that 60% of organizations will shift to a hybrid model in 2022, but one-third will fail in their first attempt at anywhere work. It’s not enough to simply announce flexible work anywhere policies. Organizations also have to restructure expectations around meetings, job roles, and promotion opportunities so they no longer reflect face-to-face experiences. And don’t even consider demanding that everyone return to the office. Forrester warns that the 30% of companies expected to mandate fully in-office work will experience monthly employee quit rates as high as 2.5% “until executives feel the pain and finally commit to making hybrid work…work.”</p>
  <p>Worker location is a business decision predicated on productivity realities as well as competitive market demands. In a recent <a href="https://www.gartner.com/en/webinars/4003227/5-digital-dexterity-enablers-to-support-a-hybrid-workforce">Gartner</a> survey, 64% of workers said they would only consider a new position or job if it allowed for flexible hours. In fact, they cited having flexible work hours as the main reason for their increased productivity.</p>
  <p>Another major issue is upskilling managers. <a href="https://www.gartner.com/en/articles/you-ll-be-breaking-up-with-bad-customers-and-9-other-predictions-for-2022-and-beyond">Gartner</a> analysts predicted that by 2024, 30% of corporate teams will be without a boss due to the agile and hybrid nature of work. They reasoned that agility, by definition, requires “an environment of trust that doesn’t lend itself to traditional hierarchies.” Many managers lack the skills to manage employees in remote or hybrid situations, and only 47% of employees believed their manager capable of leading the team to future success.</p>
  <p>“Managers are on the ground every day, coaching and inspiring their people, driving execution, and ensuring transformation efforts are successful,” said Jill Popelka, president of <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm.html">SAP SuccessFactors</a>. “As workplace and business needs continue to shift, we will need strong, people-focused managers leading the way. Their development must be a top priority for organizations and is critical to business success.”</p>
  <h2 id="technology-changes-the-employee-experience">Technology Changes the Employee Experience</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="five-workplace-norms-innovative-hxm-leaders-are-replacing-right-now">Five Workplace Norms Innovative HXM Leaders Are Replacing Right Now</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/11/five-workplace-norms-innovative-hxm-leaders-are-replacing">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As digitalization transforms business models, it also changes how work gets done. <a href="https://www.idc.com/getdoc.jsp?containerId=US47290521">IDC</a> analysts said by next year, 60% of G2000 businesses will deploy artificial intelligence (AI)- and machine learning-enabled platforms to support the entire employee life cycle experience from onboarding through retirement.</p>
  <p>Digital intelligence will permeate the workplace with profound consequences. <a href="https://www.idc.com/getdoc.jsp?containerId=US47290521">IDC</a> predicted that 70% of connected workers in task-based roles will use intelligence embedded in adaptive digital workspaces from anywhere to engage clients and colleagues and drive enterprise productivity by 2023. These <a href="https://www.idc.com/getdoc.jsp?containerId=US48360721">analysts</a> said that “companies with cross functional leadership – a digital dream team – will enjoy faster rates of innovation, higher market share gains, and greater operational efficiencies than their contemporaries by 2025.”</p>
  <p>Data-driven businesses also need to give employees the right information, recognizing those who apply data across their decision-making. <a href="https://www.idc.com/getdoc.jsp?containerId=US47913321">IDC</a> researchers warned that the lack of a “meritocracy-based data culture” will erode trust in management, reducing employee satisfaction and increasing turnover in two-thirds of midsize to large enterprises by 2024, exacerbating skills gaps.</p>
  <p><a href="https://www.forrester.com/predictions/">Forrester</a> was most optimistic about the combined value of people and technology. It predicted leading organizations will “unlock the creativity of their employees and surround them with intelligent technologies such as automation and prediction engines that focus on outcomes, not just financial results.” This heralds a new era of transformation featuring “human-centered technology initiatives” that connect customer experience (CX) and EX “to drive competitive advantage and deliver a 3% to 5% net gain in productivity.”</p>
  <p>These researchers also predicted a <a href="https://www.forrester.com/blogs/nomorejobs/">“no more jobs”</a> framework where “employees will become more peripatetic, taking their skills to contribute to project-based work and swarm teams, rather than sitting still in a fixed role…The world of no more jobs employs a dynamic mix of full-time employees, internal and external talent marketplaces, on-demand and contingent labor, and bots.”</p>
  <h2 id="sustainable-recruitment-and-business-performance-metrics">Sustainable Recruitment and Business Performance Metrics</h2>
  <p>As employees raise their voices for corporate accountability across a range of diversity, equity, and inclusion (DEI) topics, leading organizations have no choice but to respond. <a href="https://www.idc.com/getdoc.jsp?containerId=US47290521">IDC</a> predicted that 70% of enterprise businesses will have extensively invested in DEI data, tools, and benchmarking by 2024 to define recruitment and human capital strategies. These <a href="https://www.idc.com/getdoc.jsp?containerId=US48300021">researchers</a> predicted two-thirds of organizations worldwide will track their DEI performance using ESG (environmental, social, and corporate governance) metrics and KPIs in the same time frame.</p>
  <p>DEI isn’t just about metrics. Instead of focusing on corporate culture and a shared mission during a disruption, like <a href="/topics/covid-19">COVID-19</a>, <a href="https://www.gartner.com/smarterwithgartner/3-lessons-to-sustain-workforce-resilience-through-disruption">Gartner</a> analysts advised HR to give employees a personal sense of purpose, writing that, “when employees believe that their work is personally relevant, there is a 26% increase in the likelihood of sustained workforce health.”</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Follow me @smgaler.</em><br><em><a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2022/01/18/workforce-trends-2022-how-companies-are-building-digital-dream-teams/?sh=27a661e84394">This also appeared on SAP BrandVoice on Forbes.</a></em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/forrester</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Consumer Products Trends 2022: Can Your Brand Deliver Instant Happiness and Comfort?]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/02/consumer-products-cpg-trends-2022</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/02/consumer-products-cpg-trends-2022</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Leading CPG brands package up superior customer experiences using tech innovation and sustainable business strategies to transform industries.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d70b1fb78d02205a4c7b6a0a2b435d4d5e086f4f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d70b1fb78d02205a4c7b6a0a2b435d4d5e086f4f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1d70b1fb78d02205a4c7b6a0a2b435d4d5e086f4f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Consumer Products Trends 2022: Can Your Brand Deliver Instant Happiness and Comfort?" src="./media_1d70b1fb78d02205a4c7b6a0a2b435d4d5e086f4f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="consumer-products-trends-2022-can-your-brand-deliver-instant-happiness-and-comfort">Consumer Products Trends 2022: Can Your Brand Deliver Instant Happiness and Comfort?</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Underneath all the visionary aspirations for digital transformation, consumer packaged goods (<a href="/topics/cpg">CPG</a>) brands are grappling with a triumvirate challenge: how to balance bottom- and top-line business demands with sustainable practices that will take them into the future.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“CPG companies are moving systems to the cloud to gain business agility by connecting data to actions company-wide,” said Stuart Wilkinson, industry director of CPG and Life Sciences at SAP. “They want best practices to standardize business processes because that’s how they’ll achieve operational excellence, increasing efficiencies that lower costs. With centralized data visibility, they can measure, monitor, and reduce the environmental impact of their product supply chain from sourcing through distribution and after.”</p>
  <p>Here’s a quick roundup of some of the latest industry analyst predictions for the consumer products industry.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="with-sap-solutions-deliver-personalization-with-a-purpose">With SAP solutions, deliver personalization with a purpose</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="http://www.sap.com/industries/consumer-goods-cpg.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="intelligent-data-sharing-and-protection">Intelligent Data Sharing and Protection</h2>
  <p>Personalization may be the watchword for CPG companies aiming to delight their customers, but it’s fraught with land mines. For example, <a href="https://www.idc.com/getdoc.jsp?containerId=US48297321">IDC</a> analysts predicted 35% of brands will openly incentivize consumers to share personal data in exchange for cash rewards, services, and exclusive experiences by 2024. Yet <a href="https://www.gartner.com/en/articles/you-ll-be-breaking-up-with-bad-customers-and-9-other-predictions-for-2022-and-beyond">Gartner</a> analysts predicted that 40% of consumers in the same time frame will trick behavior tracking metrics to intentionally devalue the personal data collected about them, making it difficult to monetize. It’s not surprising that <a href="https://www.idc.com/getdoc.jsp?containerId=US48300021">IDC</a> analysts expected companies to extend their data privacy initiatives to surpass compliance requirements, with 60% of enterprises establishing KPIs regarding the ethical use of data by 2023.</p>
  <p>These challenges are important for consumer brands companies regardless of where they are on the value chain. <a href="https://cache.webcasts.com/content/citr003/1494846/content/fc92275950c5a6a53c52ee6105409576a5a0a524/pdf/secured/IDC_Future_of_Digital_Innovation_Futurescape_2022_Draft2.pdf">IDC</a> researchers forecast that as early as next year, traditional distribution models will crumble as 20% of businesses in some sectors use technology to go direct to customers, seeking to improve customer satisfaction and product development.</p>
  <p>“Consumer brand awareness and selling is nontraditional territory for CPG companies,” said Wilkinson. “Organizations are scrambling to attract employees with B2C skills in the middle of a worker shortage, making cultural shifts along with new technologies to capture these new opportunities.”</p>
  <p>In fact, <a href="https://www.gartner.com/en/webinars/4007946/the-future-of-cloud-prepare-for-2025">Gartner</a> analysts position cloud as the key driver for business innovation across all industries. As cloud-based platforms become the norm, industry networks will be instrumental for every sector. <a href="https://www.idc.com/getdoc.jsp?containerId=US47219421">IDC</a> predicted that by 2024, 40% of manufacturers will share data in their ecosystems (partners, customers, suppliers), improving OEE (operational equipment efficiency) of their factory operations, on average, by 10%.</p>
  <h2 id="go-digital-with-cx-no-more-excuses">Go Digital with CX: No More Excuses</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="ai-trends-2022-spare-us-the-hype-we-want-business-results">AI Trends 2022: Spare Us the Hype, We Want Business Results</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2022/01/ai-trends-2022-spare-us-the-hype-we-want-business-results">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>According to some analysts, customers will reward brands that relieve their stress. <a href="https://www.forrester.com/blogs/predictions-2022-consumer-behavior/">Forrester</a> researchers predicted that, “In 2022, consumers will turn to uplifting, pleasing products and experiences that offer reprieve from the fatigue of ongoing uncertainty.” If these analysts are correct, this could be a boon for “physical goods that spark joy – from comfort food to at-home spa kits,” as well as “experiential consumption, like prioritizing time for personal care or IRL face time with friends and family.”</p>
  <p>Customers definitely have little patience for anything less than stellar experiences. <a href="https://www.forrester.com/predictions/">Forrester</a> found that about six in 10 U.S. and UK consumers believed companies “should have figured out how to handle <a href="/topics/covid-19">pandemic-related disruption</a> by now.” These <a href="https://www.forrester.com/predictions/">analysts</a> saw brands investing in “the commerce building blocks of their experience architectures; order management, payments, and inventory control will make every touch a shoppable moment; investments in immersive experiences will turn browsing into virtual inhabiting; and subscription billing will make loyalty a business model pivot.”</p>
  <p>Gaining insights from connected data makes the biggest business difference. By 2024, <a href="https://www.idc.com/getdoc.jsp?containerId=US48297321">IDC</a> forecasted 30% of Fortune 2000 companies will deploy next-best action across their omni-channel environment, driving demand for customer data platforms, omni-channel management, and customer service solutions.</p>
  <h2 id="sustainable-business-is-a-priority">Sustainable Business Is a Priority</h2>
  <p>It’s impossible to separate the intertwined strands of customer experience, tech innovation, and sustainable business, especially when it comes to supply chains.</p>
  <p><a href="https://www.idc.com/getdoc.jsp?containerId=US48298220">IDC</a> analysts predicted that by 2023, 50% of all supply chain forecasts will be automated through artificial intelligence (AI), improving accuracy by five percentage points. <a href="https://www.gartner.com/en/articles/gartner-predicts-the-future-of-supply-chain-technology">Gartner</a> analysts said 50% of global product-centric enterprises will have invested in real-time transportation visibility platforms by 2023. By the following year, IDC researchers saw 70% of manufacturers in global supply chains improving long-term supply chain profitability with investments in software tools to support sustainability and circular economy business models.</p>
  <p>To improve delivery speed, agility, and visibility for B2B and B2C customers, <a href="https://www.idc.com/getdoc.jsp?containerId=US48298220">IDC</a> analysts said 35% of manufacturers will invest in order management software by 2024, resulting in a 25% improvement in OTIF (on-time, in-full) fulfillment. By 2025, <a href="https://www.idc.com/getdoc.jsp?containerId=US48298220">IDC</a> researchers predicted that 40% of G2000 organizations will invest in supply chain systems to increase information and inventory velocity to improve last-mile delivery efficiency and boost customer experience.</p>
  <p>What’s striking about these predictions is that they’re expected to radically change the CPG sector in just a couple of years. The future has never been more transformational.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Follow me @smgaler.</em><br><em><a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2022/01/11/consumer-products-trends-2022-can-your-brand-deliver-instant-happiness-and-comfort/?sh=2e30f5f5421b">This also appeared on SAP BrandVoice on Forbes.</a></em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/consumer-goods-cpg</category>
            <category>news-tag/forrester</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[AI Trends 2022: Spare Us the Hype, We Want Business Results]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/01/ai-trends-2022-spare-us-the-hype-we-want-business-results</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/01/ai-trends-2022-spare-us-the-hype-we-want-business-results</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The latest industry analyst predictions on AI trends show how smart, creative, and sincere artificial intelligence will become. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c8d8a4bb0d40b93cde54c85cab62756d51ea01fc.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c8d8a4bb0d40b93cde54c85cab62756d51ea01fc.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1c8d8a4bb0d40b93cde54c85cab62756d51ea01fc.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="AI Trends 2022: Spare Us the Hype, We Want Business Results" src="./media_1c8d8a4bb0d40b93cde54c85cab62756d51ea01fc.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="ai-trends-2022-spare-us-the-hype-we-want-business-results">AI Trends 2022: Spare Us the Hype, We Want Business Results</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>If you thought judgment, ethics, and even creativity were the unique purview of humans, think again.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The latest industry analyst predictions about artificial intelligence (AI) are out, and they’re certain to oust a ton of assumptions we’ve made to date. Read on to find out just how smart, creative, and sincere AI will become during the next few years.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="find-out-more-about-intelligent-technologies-from-sap">Find out more about intelligent technologies from SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/intelligent-technologies.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="creative-machines-are-the-future">Creative Machines Are the Future</h2>
  <p>Noting that South Africa granted the first patent to a creative AI system in 2021, <a href="https://www.forrester.com/predictions/">Forrester</a> researchers predicted creative AI systems will win dozens of patents in 2022. They were quick to point out that “AI will not own the products in the traditional sense – the developers of the AI systems…will still enjoy commercial benefits. But companies will experiment with creative AI, knowing that these innovations may be legally protected.”</p>
  <p><a href="https://www.forrester.com/blogs/meet-the-new-demand-for-creativity-with-ai/">Forrester</a> Analyst Diego Lo Giudice looked ahead to “AI 2.0,” which he saw fueling the development of new creative business applications, exceeding basic expectations of AI to free up workers for greater creativity. He predicted that AI would connect business processes across silos to boost business creativity and wrote that “AI’s new business models can optimize the convergence of the digital world with the physical world and drive the ‘anything as a digital service’ trend. The impact on customer experience could be huge.”</p>
  <h2 id="explainable-ai-is-not-your-typical-it-project">Explainable AI Is Not Your Typical IT Project</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="explore-the-entire-sap-institute-for-digital-government-research-series">Explore the entire SAP Institute for Digital Government research series</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://discover.sap.com/sap-institute-digital-gov/en-us/publications.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Explainability and ethics were among the most widely discussed AI-related issues. <a href="https://www.forrester.com/blogs/predictions-for-2022-successfully-riding-the-next-wave-of-ai/">Forrester</a> Analyst Srividya Sridharan saw the market for responsible AI solutions doubling as industries adopt “responsible AI solutions that help companies turn AI principles such as fairness and transparency into consistent practices.” And for those who fear these algorithms will run amok, <a href="https://www.idc.com/getdoc.jsp?containerId=US47913321">IDC</a> analysts predicted that by 2025, to reduce reputational risks, 40% of G2000 companies will be forced to redesign their approaches to algorithmic decision-making, providing better human oversight and explainability.</p>
  <p>AI explainability is one of topics that Ian Ryan is exploring as global head of the SAP Institute for Digital Government. It’s part of a research series for the Australian public sector on the value and impact of technologies for employees, citizens, and society at large. Ryan said that AI can help deliver citizen services with that coveted Amazon-like experience, provided organizations set value-based, measurable objectives.</p>
  <p>“Applications of AI consist of the person using it, the AI model itself, and the information that comes from reality; these three pieces have to be in sync, targeted towards driving a particular outcome,” said Ryan. “You need to train the AI model continuously, keeping it updated so it can support workers as situations evolve, engineering out any bias while preserving data protection.”</p>
  <p>For business value, AI algorithms cannot function as an inscrutable black box or operate autonomously. Ryan said organizations need to build explainability into complex AI models and involve targeted employees in AI model development.</p>
  <p>“AI supports employees by taking tasks away, allowing people to be more productive and focus on high-value activities,” he said. “Al can access huge amounts of seemingly disconnected data from different places and identify patterns in seconds, far faster than humans. Explainability provides the transparency people can trust, so they’ll share their data knowing the organization will protect it and deliver value.”</p>
  <p>Indeed, <a href="https://www.gartner.com/en/information-technology/insights/top-technology-trends">Gartner</a> analysts warned that while AI will help companies emerge from the <a href="/covid-19">pandemic</a> in a strong position, merely adopting AI won’t be enough. Companies need to operationalize updates to AI models, “using integrated data and model and development pipelines to deliver consistent business value from AI. It combines automated update pipelines with strong AI governance.”</p>
  <h2 id="ai-becomes-ubiquitous">AI Becomes Ubiquitous</h2>
  <p>Numerous analyst predictions tout the benefits of AI in strengthening human decisions. <a href="https://www.idc.com/getdoc.jsp?containerId=US48298421">IDC</a> researchers said that 85% of enterprises will combine human expertise with AI, machine learning, natural language processing, and pattern recognition to augment foresight across the organization, making workers 25% more productive and effective by 2026. <a href="https://www.idc.com/getdoc.jsp?containerId=US47913321">IDC</a> researchers saw 30% of organizations using forms of behavioral economics and AI- and machine learning-driven insights to nudge employees’ actions, leading to a 60% increase in desired outcomes by 2026.</p>
  <p>More near term, <a href="https://www.forrester.com/blogs/predictions-for-2022-successfully-riding-the-next-wave-of-ai/">Sridharan</a> expected traditional businesses will take a page out of digital-native practices during the pandemic with an AI-first approach to platform and digital transformation. He said that “the more AI inside, the more enterprises can shrink the latency between insights, decisions, and results.”</p>
  <p>Unlike many previous innovations, AI is not an isolated technology that organizations can surgically apply and wait for the magic to happen. AI is an extraordinarily powerful technology with profound ramifications for organizations and people as they discover its true business potential.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Follow me @smgaler.</em><br><em><a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2021/12/08/ai-trends-2022-spare-us-the-hype-we-want-business-results/?sh=11dd0d96601a">This blog also appeared on SAP BrandVoice on Forbes.</a></em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/forrester</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-anz</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Five Ways Automated Application Testing Adds Value to Your Business]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/01/automated-application-testing-value</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/01/automated-application-testing-value</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Automating application testing can drive faster releases and dramatically lower the cost of moving to intelligent technology. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_123215a77c3416cd8a7197078f3bb8bac897e7a3a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_123215a77c3416cd8a7197078f3bb8bac897e7a3a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_123215a77c3416cd8a7197078f3bb8bac897e7a3a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Five Ways Automated Application Testing Adds Value to Your Business" src="./media_123215a77c3416cd8a7197078f3bb8bac897e7a3a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="five-ways-automated-application-testing-adds-value-to-your-business">Five Ways Automated Application Testing Adds Value to Your Business</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Even though manual application testing is the norm in most IT environments, it can add unnecessary risks, delays, and complexities to long-term digital transformation plans. Once automated, this task can drive faster application releases and dramatically lower the cost of moving to intelligent technology.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Application testing is one of those tasks that IT organizations know they cannot do without but wish it consumed less of their time, budget, and resources. With limited visibility into test conditions, upcoming software release cycles, and overly broad scopes, teams constantly react to bug-laden user experiences, delays to user productivity, poor integration, and excessive hypercare to address production errors.</p>
  <p>Some organizations, however, are rising above these challenges by automating application testing. According to the commissioned Forrester Consulting study, “<a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/12/b22fb2ba-0a7e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">The Total Economic Impact™ of SAP Application Testing Solutions by Tricentis</a>,” automation accelerates application delivery as much as four times — with fewer errors, less risk, and higher time to value.</p>
  <p>Forrester also noted that scaling automation across the application life cycle with technology, such as <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/enterprise-continuous-testing.html">SAP application testing solutions by Tricentis</a>, can yield a <strong>334% return on investment (ROI)</strong> and organizational benefits totaling upward of US$7.8 million over three years. And more importantly, the intelligent nature of automated testing produces a wide variety of benefits that can energize a future of meaningful digital transformation.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="enable-digital-transformation-and-intelligent-operations-by-reducing-business-risk-associated-with-application-changes">Enable digital transformation and intelligent operations by reducing business risk associated with application changes</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/enterprise-continuous-testing.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="benefit-1-84-reduction-in-test-scoping">Benefit 1) 84% Reduction in Test Scoping</h2>
  <p>By leveraging change impact analytics, organizations can determine the conditions that should be tested to reduce errors and those that do not carry that risk. As a result, the number of conditions that need to be tested for a single application can be reduced by 84%, compared to manual testing methods.</p>
  <p>An ERP principal test manager who participated in the Forrester study remarked how an automated testing solution enabled the identification of programs impacted by any given change. Instead of running all conditions to mitigate all risks, the organization only works on approximately 20% of the initial scope.</p>
  <h2 id="benefit-2-78-fewer-production-errors">Benefit 2) 78% Fewer Production Errors</h2>
  <p>With a narrower testing scope, organizations can also decrease errors and bugs in an application moved to production — from an average of 1.5 to 0.3 per project. And for users, their application experience can become one that enhances their productivity as quickly as their first interaction.</p>
  <p>By reducing the risk of incidents that made it into the application during development and in production, IT teams can positively impact employees’ everyday work experiences. Workplace frustration declines, workloads are lower, and the need for hypercare is minimized.</p>
  <h2 id="benefit-3-25-lower-testing-costs">Benefit 3) 25% Lower Testing Costs</h2>
  <p>Even if 70% of their testing processes are automated, moving closer toward full automation can prompt a 25% savings in testing-time costs. For some teams, that is an equivalent of 10,000 person-hours that can be reallocated to more strategic projects. And the impact is even more significant within six months, when a team moves from a 100% manual testing model to an enterprise continuous testing solution that enables 50% automation.</p>
  <p>Additionally, the use of embedded machine learning in application testing solutions can establish self-healing test cases, lowering test costs even further.</p>
  <h2 id="benefit-4-67-faster-time-to-application-release">Benefit 4) 67% Faster Time-to-Application Release</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="download-the-study-here">Download the study here</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/registration/protected/default-overlay.html?gated_asset_path=%2F%2Fwww.sap.com%2Fdocuments%2F2021%2F12%2Fb22fb2ba-0a7e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.rc.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The added effect of automation that is difficult to miss is the opportunity to accelerate the time needed to test all relevant conditions, improving release rates by 300%. In the past, IT organizations may have gone live with new applications every six months with manual processes. Now, they can release new features, applications, and mobile apps in a matter of two months or four more times annually.</p>
  <p>This advantage opens the door to an improved transition to intelligent solutions and platforms, such as <a href="/topics/sap-s4hana-cloud">SAP S/4HANA Cloud</a>. Organizations can migrate faster and at a lower cost with automated testing than manual methods.</p>
  <h2 id="benefit-5-12-to-25-times-more-performance-testing">Benefit 5) 12 to 25 Times More Performance Testing</h2>
  <p>Just think of the possibilities when performance testing goes from 20 person days to one hour. When automation reduces the time required by 99%, IT teams can conduct performance testing once or twice a week — instead of quarterly — to help ensure updates and added features function as designed.</p>
  <p>In one of Forrester’s interviews with study participants, an IT services test manager noted how the gains achieved through automation go beyond just faster application delivery. Since users only need to verify that they have the capabilities necessary to get work done, his team can now confidently skip manual regression testing.</p>
  <h2 id="automated-testing-drives-better-business-outcomes">Automated Testing Drives Better Business Outcomes</h2>
  <p>These outcomes of automated application testing put application developers and the rest of the IT organization in an enviable position in their company’s digital transformation journey. They are not only delivering applications that improve process efficiency and business productivity, but are also empowering the entire workforce to adapt and respond to changes in highly engaging, purpose-driven, and strategic ways.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>Explore the calculated cost savings and business benefits of SAP application testing solutions by Tricentis, which support application testing automation. Read the Forrester Consulting study, “<a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/12/b22fb2ba-0a7e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">The Total Economic Impact of SAP Application Testing Solutions by Tricentis</a>,” commissioned by SAP and Tricentis.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/application-lifecycle-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/forrester</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Named a Leader in “Master Data Management” by Independent Research Firm]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/sap-a-leader-forrester-wave-master-data-management</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/sap-a-leader-forrester-wave-master-data-management</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP has been positioned as a Leader in The Forrester Wave: Master Data Management, Q4 2021. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1cfc99e7852a08ae4b9ae0ca5ec80f8611ead6f3b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1cfc99e7852a08ae4b9ae0ca5ec80f8611ead6f3b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1cfc99e7852a08ae4b9ae0ca5ec80f8611ead6f3b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Named a Leader in “Master Data Management” by Independent Research Firm" src="./media_1cfc99e7852a08ae4b9ae0ca5ec80f8611ead6f3b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-named-a-leader-in-master-data-management-by-independent-research-firm">SAP Named a Leader in “Master Data Management” by Independent Research Firm</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-master-data-governance-improve-the-quality-and-consistency-of-information-across-your-organization">SAP Master Data Governance: Improve the quality and consistency of information across your organization</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/master-data-governance.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced it has been positioned as a Leader in “<a href="https://reprints2.forrester.com/#/assets/2/702/RES176577/report">The Forrester Wave™: Master Data Management, Q4 2021</a>.”</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Forrester Research Inc., a leading global research and advisory firm, researched, analyzed and scored 15 vendors and named SAP a Leader. The report analyzed the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/master-data-governance.html">SAP Master Data Governance</a> application and noted its “good multidomain MDM capabilities at scale” as well as its “prebuilt data models, business rules, workflows, and user interfaces to support MDM deployments.” The 24 scoring criteria employed by Forrester Research covered three categories: Current Offering, Strategy and Market Presence.</p>
  <p>The report states that SAP “supports a multidomain MDM solution for on-premises, private, and public cloud deployment with quality, stewardship, and governance capabilities” and “focuses on extending the cloud services, increasing automation and intelligence, and delivering more integrated data management solutions.”</p>
  <p>The Forrester report points out that “reference customers mainly had positive feedback on SAP [Master Data Governance],” with one customer pointing out, “SAP [Master Data Governance] implementation brought us greater government control and streamlined efficiency.”</p>
  <p>“In our digital economy, having correct, comprehensive and timely views of data is paramount to success,” said Dr. Andreas Doehrn, head of Master Data Management Engineering, SAP. “SAP Master Data Governance improves the quality and consistency of information by consolidating and centrally governing the master data lifecycle. We believe Forrester’s recognition of SAP as a Leader in this evaluation is testament to our robust data solutions and the benefit we bring to our customers.”</p>
  <p>As part of <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">SAP Business Technology Platform</a>, SAP Master Data Governance allows businesses to create a single source of truth by uniting SAP and third-party data sources and mass processing additional bulk updates on large volumes of data. Customers can establish a cohesive and harmonized master data management strategy across domains to simplify enterprise data management, increase data accuracy and reduce total cost of ownership.</p>
  <p>To learn more about SAP’s ranking, <a href="https://reprints2.forrester.com/#/assets/2/702/RES176577/report">read the full report here</a>.</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="http://news.sap.com/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP on Twitter at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Media Contact:</strong><br>Julia Fargel, +1 (650) 276-8964, <a href="mailto:julia.fargel@sap.com">julia.fargel@sap.com</a>, PT<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>Any statements contained in this document that are not historical facts are forward-looking statements as defined in the U.S. Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995. Words such as “anticipate,” “believe,” “estimate,” “expect,” “forecast,” “intend,” “may,” “plan,” “project,” “predict,” “should” and “will” and similar expressions as they relate to SAP are intended to identify such forward-looking statements. SAP undertakes no obligation to publicly update or revise any forward-looking statements. All forward-looking statements are subject to various risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results to differ materially from expectations. The factors that could affect SAP’s future financial results are discussed more fully in SAP’s filings with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (“SEC”), including SAP’s most recent Annual Report on Form 20-F filed with the SEC. Readers are cautioned not to place undue reliance on these forward-looking statements, which speak only as of their dates.<br>© 2021 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>news-tag/forrester</category>
            <category>news-tag/master-data-management</category>
            <category>product/sap-master-data-governance</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Named a Leader in Learning and Experience Platforms by Independent Research Firm]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/sap-a-leader-in-learning-management-systems-and-experience-platforms</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/sap-a-leader-in-learning-management-systems-and-experience-platforms</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is a Leader in The Forrester Wave: Learning Management Systems and Experience Platforms, Q4 2021. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_194e78d92ffd98985530dbcdfc49016d6dfbd6f72.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_194e78d92ffd98985530dbcdfc49016d6dfbd6f72.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_194e78d92ffd98985530dbcdfc49016d6dfbd6f72.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Named a Leader in Learning and Experience Platforms by Independent Research Firm" src="./media_194e78d92ffd98985530dbcdfc49016d6dfbd6f72.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-named-a-leader-in-learning-and-experience-platforms-by-independent-research-firm">SAP Named a Leader in Learning and Experience Platforms by Independent Research Firm</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="put-employees-at-the-heart-of-everything-you-do-with-sap-successfactors-software">Put employees at the heart of everything you do with SAP SuccessFactors software</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced that it has been positioned as a Leader in “The Forrester Wave™: Learning Management Systems and Experience Platforms, Q4 2021” report.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Forrester Research Inc. researched, analyzed and scored 10 vendors across 28 criteria and ranked SAP a Leader based on its current offering, strategy and market presence. SAP was noted as ranking highest in the market presence and strategy categories.</p>
  <p>According to the report: “[<a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm.html">SAP] SuccessFactors</a> is a powerhouse from a resources perspective. In-house research capabilities drive its vision and strategy, and it brings a balanced focus to offering in-suite capabilities and integration beyond [human capital management] into business at all levels.… <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/corporate-lms.html">SAP SuccessFactors</a> has a rich set of capabilities to support learners, administrators, and facilitators. [It] is a strong fit for enterprise buyers looking for a solution that connects learning to business outcomes, provides robust integration, and has a strategy grounded in learning science.”</p>
  <p>“Learning is a critical differentiator for businesses as they transform for the future,” said SAP SuccessFactors President Jill Popelka. “It’s no longer limited to compliance training. Today, our customers are using SAP SuccessFactors learning solutions to help their employees build new skills and capabilities, adjust to changing regulations and demands, and discover new career paths. By helping people learn in a way that is consumable and aligned to their interests, organizations can help them develop a career that is personally fulfilling while also benefitting the business.”</p>
  <p>SAP has continued to build on how it supports organizations with learning. In October, SAP announced the new <a href="/2021/10/sap-successfactors-opportunity-marketplace-drives-internal-mobility-and-upskilling-to-help-organizations-future-proof-their-business">SAP SuccessFactors Opportunity Marketplace</a> solution, which connects workers with individualized recommendations to promote their growth and development, including learning activities as well as mentors and short-term assignments. It is generally available on November 19.</p>
  <p><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/corporate-lms.html">Learn more about SAP’s leadership in learning and download a complimentary report</a>.</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="http://news.sap.com/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP on Twitter at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Media Contact:</strong> Samantha Yerks, +1 (914) 918-6087, <a href="mailto:samantha.yerks@sap.com">samantha.yerks@sap.com</a>, ET<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>Any statements contained in this document that are not historical facts are forward-looking statements as defined in the U.S. Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995. Words such as “anticipate,” “believe,” “estimate,” “expect,” “forecast,” “intend,” “may,” “plan,” “project,” “predict,” “should” and “will” and similar expressions as they relate to SAP are intended to identify such forward-looking statements. SAP undertakes no obligation to publicly update or revise any forward-looking statements. All forward-looking statements are subject to various risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results to differ materially from expectations. The factors that could affect SAP’s future financial results are discussed more fully in SAP’s filings with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (“SEC”), including SAP’s most recent Annual Report on Form 20-F filed with the SEC. Readers are cautioned not to place undue reliance on these forward-looking statements, which speak only as of their dates.<br>© 2021 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>news-tag/forrester</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Custom Guidance: The Secret to High-Value Transformation in the Cloud]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/custom-guidance-cloud-transformation-sap-preferred-success</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/custom-guidance-cloud-transformation-sap-preferred-success</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A Forrester study revealed the business benefits in the cloud that are enabled by SAP Preferred Success. Read about the highlights.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1fe50fe3db75fc6d5437a22dc37e75d23a81dacf4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1fe50fe3db75fc6d5437a22dc37e75d23a81dacf4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1fe50fe3db75fc6d5437a22dc37e75d23a81dacf4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Custom Guidance: The Secret to High-Value Transformation in the Cloud" src="./media_1fe50fe3db75fc6d5437a22dc37e75d23a81dacf4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="custom-guidance-the-secret-to-high-value-transformation-in-the-cloud">Custom Guidance: The Secret to High-Value Transformation in the Cloud</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Cloud technology may drive fast and agile change, but technical unknowns and strategic misdirection can lessen the impact of any degree of success. So how can businesses get on the right path to high-value transformation? The answer is proactive, ongoing, and personalized guidance, according to a study conducted by Forrester Consulting.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>When looking to the cloud to improve operational efficiencies, reduce costs, and meet customer demand with flexibility and speed, companies throw open the doors to a world of opportunities. But first, they need to become familiar with the landscape and available resources, discover capabilities that can benefit them most, and know how to scale the technology to fuel long-term, sustainable growth.</p>
  <p>Unfortunately, most internal IT organizations are too lean to manage it all. They do not have the time and budget needed to scrutinize road map strategies for the cloud and concentrate on continuous improvement after an initial implementation.</p>
  <p>The Forrester Consulting study commissioned by SAP, “<a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/07/aed54c54-ee7d-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">The Total Economic Impact™ of SAP Preferred Success</a>,” presents a solution to this common dilemma. In its assessment of the <a href="https://www.sap.com/services/support-plans/preferred-success-cloud.html">SAP Preferred Success</a> offering, the third-party global market research company revealed that access to success resources and customized guidance can yield a 380% ROI in cloud technology investments over three years.</p>
  <h2 id="fostering-adoption-and-optimization-for-long-term-growth">Fostering Adoption and Optimization for Long-Term Growth</h2>
  <p>To evaluate the potential economic impact of continuous cloud services, Forrester surveyed four companies actively using SAP Preferred Success. The participants’ experiences were then aggregated to create a single composite organization to determine the offering’s total economic impact (TEI).</p>
  <p>In this TEI study, Forrester emphasized how SAP Preferred Success helps SAP customers adopt, consume, and operate cloud solutions with greater ease, speed, and strategic value. Over a three-year period, this kind of guidance was shown to impact how businesses can quickly transform to meet the needs of a dynamic marketplace in four fundamental ways.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-preferred-success-prescriptive-guidance-for-a-world-of-uncertainty">SAP Preferred Success: Prescriptive Guidance for a World of Uncertainty</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2020/04/sap-preferred-success-prescriptive-guidance">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="shrink-implementation-time-by-two-months">1. Shrink Implementation Time by Two Months</h3>
  <p>With the assistance of customer success managers (CSMs), in-depth training materials, and support tools, surveyed businesses cited that their implementations and updates were completed faster and with lower risk. The more familiar they became with the cloud landscape and best-practice methodologies, the more confident their organizations were in supporting a cloud-based IT model. For example, deployment impediments and bugs were detected and addressed proactively, cloud investments were safeguarded, and technologies and capabilities that provide relevant benefits were chosen quickly without the fear of missing opportunities.</p>
  <h3 id="accelerate-time-to-value-with-faster-releases">2. Accelerate Time to Value with Faster Releases</h3>
  <p>The exercise of researching answers to new questions can delay planning by approximately 30%, pushing out the delivery of the solution and realization of its value. Businesses that leverage SAP Preferred Success during planning, deployment, and release preparation can add two more months of additional benefits each year after the initial implementation. Furthermore, those gains can be achieved without disrupting the everyday work experiences of internal teams.</p>
  <h3 id="facilitate-innovation-with-collaboration-and-insight">3. Facilitate Innovation with Collaboration and Insight</h3>
  <p>Interviewed organizations mentioned their interactions with customer communities and access to in-depth training materials through regular strategic reviews and ongoing informal exchanges with CSMs. They viewed this experience as a turning point in their ability to focus on their business priorities and identify opportunities to improve processes and implement new enhancements. Plus, based on Forrester’s calculation, gains in process optimization could raise productivity by, on average, 30% when the time saved is reinvested in constructive work.</p>
  <h3 id="resolve-incidents-faster-and-more-productively">4. Resolve Incidents Faster and More Productively</h3>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-resources-you-need-to-be-successful-in-the-cloud">Get the resources you need to be successful in the cloud</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/services/support-plans/preferred-success-cloud.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>With access to a dedicated CSM from SAP Preferred Success as a point of contact, interviewees from this TEI study reported resolving issues more quickly. Incidents that they raised were prioritized in SAP’s system to meet enhanced service-level agreements, supported by the CSM acting as their advocate, and connected to relevant experts to expedite resolution. This support reduced priority one and priority two incidents by half in the third year after the initial implementation while accelerating priority two incident resolution times by at least 40% and reducing effort by 30%.</p>
  <h2 id="creating-a-low-risk-flexible-foundation-for-transformation">Creating a Low-Risk, Flexible Foundation for Transformation</h2>
  <p>SAP Preferred Success is a premium add-on to SAP Enterprise Support, cloud editions. In an earlier <a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/dg/tei-on-sap-enterprise-support/index.html">TEI study covering the SAP Enterprise Support offering</a>, Forrester revealed that surveyed businesses felt they were well-equipped to move from on-premise solutions to the cloud smoothly. The offering’s prescriptive guidance enabled organizations to implement cloud solutions from SAP and find new ways to safeguard processes, optimize operations, and unlock innovations through continuous enhancements.</p>
  <p>But as Forrester emphasized in this TEI study on SAP Preferred Success, businesses that are unfamiliar with cloud solutions may want personalized assistance and advice on how to adopt, consume, and operate the technology. This is where an add-on, particularly SAP Preferred Success, can be helpful.</p>
  <p>SAP Preferred Success supports a combination of outcomes that can be critical for companies looking to transition and evolve with cloud technology. But more importantly, those advantages create an environment that empowers organizations to transform at their pace and toward their vision with less risk and greater flexibility.</p>
  <p>How can SAP Preferred Success help amplify your potential in the cloud? Find out by reading the full economic impact study by Forrester, “<a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/07/aed54c54-ee7d-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">The Total Economic Impact™ of SAP Preferred Success</a>.”</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Lisa Spangler is global vice president and chief product owner for SAP Preferred Success at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/forrester</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-enterprise-support</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-preferred-success</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Economic Impact of Proactive Planning and Readiness on Cloud-Based Innovation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/economic-impact-sap-enterprise-support-cloud-editions</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/economic-impact-sap-enterprise-support-cloud-editions</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A Forrester study shows that SAP Enterprise Support, cloud editions advance customers' overall journey to the cloud. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1fdc6152b9ae2eba1b41f327fb2674c16f9b4bd76.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1fdc6152b9ae2eba1b41f327fb2674c16f9b4bd76.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1fdc6152b9ae2eba1b41f327fb2674c16f9b4bd76.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="The Economic Impact of Proactive Planning and Readiness on Cloud-Based Innovation" src="./media_1fdc6152b9ae2eba1b41f327fb2674c16f9b4bd76.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="the-economic-impact-of-proactive-planning-and-readiness-on-cloud-based-innovation">The Economic Impact of Proactive Planning and Readiness on Cloud-Based Innovation</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>The cloud is increasingly becoming a choice that is catalyzing innovation and digital transformation for organizations worldwide. Yet, most companies are only beginning to realize the cloud’s vast potential for deployment scale, process efficiency, workforce productivity, and development speed – opening them up to the possibility of enabling long-term, sustainable business growth.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>At a time when businesses are working diligently to rejuvenate themselves by pioneering new business models, products, services, and experiences, operations optimization and continuous enhancement have never been more critical. However, services that support these needs are often overlooked when purchasing cloud subscriptions.</p>
  <p>Are businesses making a significant mistake by delaying proactive planning and readiness support services for another day or skipping them all together? The Forrester Consulting study commissioned by SAP, “<a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/dg/tei-on-sap-enterprise-support/index.html">The Total Economic Impact™ of SAP Enterprise Support, Cloud Editions</a>,” indicated the answer is a resounding “yes” in its analysis of <a href="https://www.sap.com/services/support-plans/enterprise.html">SAP Enterprise Support, cloud editions</a> – revealing a 30% higher process optimization rate over three years.</p>
  <h2 id="revealing-the-full-potential-of-the-cloud">Revealing the Full Potential of the Cloud</h2>
  <p>To better understand the benefits and costs associated with support services, Forrester interviewed five businesses that are using or have used any element from the cloud editions of the SAP Enterprise Support offering. The third-party global market research company engaged in an unbiased survey of the participants’ experiences and aggregated their insights into a single composite organization to calculate quantitative benefits.</p>
  <p>The TEI study highlighted how SAP Enterprise Support, cloud editions enable SAP customers to move from on-premise solutions to the cloud more smoothly. The offering gave prescriptive guidance to the surveyed businesses as they implemented cloud solutions from SAP and searched for ways to enable their business, safeguard their processes, optimize operations, and unlock innovations through continuous enhancements.</p>
  <p>How does this experience impact the way SAP customers advance their overall digital transformation journey in the cloud over a three-year period? Here are key insights that Forrester uncovered in its research.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-proactive-support-you-need-to-succeed-with-sap-enterprise-support">Get the proactive support you need to succeed with SAP Enterprise Support</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://support.sap.com/en/offerings-programs/enterprise-support.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="benefit-1-reduced-implementation-costs-by-27">Benefit #1: Reduced Implementation Costs by 27%</h3>
  <p>By working with a team of SAP experts and support specialists, the surveyed businesses felt more prepared to adopt the cloud and have confidence in their investment. The more informed they were about the capabilities of the cloud solutions, the more capable they were in assuring user readiness, accelerating adoption, and managing expanding use. In addition, emerging risks could be mitigated to safeguard the performance of their internal and partner project teams in realizing the value of their cloud solutions.</p>
  <h3 id="benefit-2-derived-20-more-efficiency-in-internal-it-teams">Benefit #2: Derived 20% More Efficiency in Internal IT Teams</h3>
  <p>When organizations understand the value of the technologies they choose to purchase, they are more likely to embrace best practices that drive greater efficiency. The companies surveyed by Forrester are no exception to this rule. By leveraging SAP Enterprise Support, cloud editions, research participants could manage IT incidents more effectively and perform application support activities with well-defined service-level agreements.</p>
  <h3 id="benefit-3-released-preparations-with-25-less-effort">Benefit #3: Released Preparations with 25% Less Effort</h3>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="why-now-is-the-time-to-differentiate-with-sap-services-and-support">Why Now Is the Time to Differentiate with SAP Services and Support</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/06/differentiate-with-sap-services-and-support">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP customers interviewed for Forrester’s research mentioned having access to enablement materials through SAP Enterprise Support, cloud editions. This allowed them to quickly adapt existing processes to meet changing market needs. As a result, organizations, on average, avoided two weeks of additional effort for each new release of a cloud solution.</p>
  <h2 id="setting-the-foundation-for-fast-time-to-value">Setting the Foundation for Fast Time to Value</h2>
  <p>Perhaps one of the most exciting findings in Forrester’s research is how the combination of reduced cost, greater efficiency, and less effort to prepare for new releases accelerates the overall time to value of cloud solutions. This impact of SAP Enterprise Support, cloud editions is particularly critical for companies that demand more frequent innovation cycles and faster realization of expected outcomes.</p>
  <p>One of the project managers interviewed by Forrester for this TEI study shared that the offering enabled an oil and gas company to launch its move to the cloud two months earlier than expected in an already aggressive timeline. Other interview participants indicated the same experience, in which, on average, SAP Enterprise Support, cloud editions helped deliver initiatives nearly one month earlier for a six-month deployment.</p>
  <p>Could your business gain the same advantage in your move to the cloud? Find out by reading the full economic impact study from Forrester, “<a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/dg/tei-on-sap-enterprise-support/index.html">The Total Economic Impact™ of SAP Enterprise Support, Cloud Editions</a>.”</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Keith Lamont is vice president of Customer Engagement and Experience at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/forrester</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-enterprise-support</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP HANA Named a Leader in “Multimodel Data Platforms” by Independent Research Firm]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/sap-hana-a-leader-multimodel-data-platforms</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/sap-hana-a-leader-multimodel-data-platforms</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is a Leader in “The Forrester Wave™: Multimodel Data Platforms, Q3 2021,” a report that analyzed SAP HANA. Get the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ba8832b9396a43ef35f521bcc608647c3423ebd9.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ba8832b9396a43ef35f521bcc608647c3423ebd9.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1ba8832b9396a43ef35f521bcc608647c3423ebd9.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP HANA Named a Leader in “Multimodel Data Platforms” by Independent Research Firm" src="./media_1ba8832b9396a43ef35f521bcc608647c3423ebd9.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-hana-named-a-leader-in-multimodel-data-platforms-by-independent-research-firm">SAP HANA Named a Leader in “Multimodel Data Platforms” by Independent Research Firm</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-multimodel-processing">Learn more about multimodel processing</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hana/features/multi-model.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced it has been positioned as a Leader in “The Forrester Wave™: Multimodel Data Platforms, Q3 2021.”</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Forrester Research Inc., a leading global research and advisory firm, researched, analyzed and scored 15 vendors and named SAP a Leader. The report analyzed <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hana.html">SAP HANA</a> and noted its “outstanding support for transactions, queries, analytics, and search across hybrid and multi-cloud environments….” The 26 scoring criteria employed by Forrester Research covered three categories: Current Offering, Strategy and Market Presence. SAP scored five out of five in 17 of the 26 evaluation criteria.</p>
  <p>The report states that SAP “leverages a mature in-memory platform to support any multimodel workload” and “has a solid vision that focuses on the distributed SAP HANA multimodel data platform for unified data and analytics for any cloud, supporting all data and all workloads and leveraging advanced AI/ML and self-service capabilities.”</p>
  <p>The Forrester report points out that “reference customers spoke highly about the performance, versatility, all-in-one integrated development environment, and platform flexibility.” The report vendor profile concludes that “SAP is a good fit for applications that need high-performance, low-latency access to multimodel data to support various workloads.”</p>
  <p>“As businesses continue evolving and adapting to market conditions, they are benefiting from SAP HANA and SAP HANA Cloud by harnessing its multimodel data types within a single database platform, helping guide their future to more predictable outcomes,” said SAP HANA Database &#x26; Analytics President Irfan Khan. “We believe Forrester’s recognition of SAP as a Leader in this evaluation is testament to our robust data solutions and the benefit we bring to our customers.”</p>
  <p>An integral part of <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">SAP Business Technology Platform</a>, SAP HANA and SAP HANA Cloud allow businesses to leverage SAP’s single, unified multimodel database that stores, processes and analyzes geospatial, graph, JavaScript Object Notation (JSON) documents and more data types into one solution. Customers can access real-time advanced analytics and gain situational awareness by analyzing data in context, so they have the opportunity to respond to critical situations faster.</p>
  <p>Learn more about <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hana/features/multi-model.html">smart multimodel processing in SAP HANA</a> and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hana/cloud.html">SAP HANA Cloud</a>. To learn more about SAP’s ranking, <a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/dg/forresterwave-mmdp/index.html">read the full report here</a> and <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/pulse/sap-hana-leader-according-forrester-multimodel-data-platforms-khan/?trackingId=F5ktixHJRDWRyLef5Q4LlA%3D%3D">executive blog here</a>.</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="http://news.sap.com/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP on Twitter at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Media Contacts:</strong> Scott Malinowski, +1 (617) 538-6297, <a href="mailto:scott.malinowski@sap.com">scott.malinowski@sap.com</a> ET<br>Julia Fargel, +1 (650) 276-8964, <a href="mailto:julia.fargel@sap.com">julia.fargel@sap.com</a>, PT<br><a href="mailto:SAP%20Press%20Room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>Any statements contained in this document that are not historical facts are forward-looking statements as defined in the U.S. Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995. Words such as “anticipate,” “believe,” “estimate,” “expect,” “forecast,” “intend,” “may,” “plan,” “project,” “predict,” “should” and “will” and similar expressions as they relate to SAP are intended to identify such forward-looking statements. SAP undertakes no obligation to publicly update or revise any forward-looking statements. All forward-looking statements are subject to various risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results to differ materially from expectations. The factors that could affect SAP’s future financial results are discussed more fully in SAP’s filings with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (“SEC”), including SAP’s most recent Annual Report on Form 20-F filed with the SEC. Readers are cautioned not to place undue reliance on these forward-looking statements, which speak only as of their dates.<br>© 2021 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>news-tag/forrester</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-hana</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Four Most Important 2021 Digital Automation Trends]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/four-digital-automation-trends</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/four-digital-automation-trends</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Industry analysts share four of the most important predictions about digital automation trends as we head into a post-pandemic world.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15665aa91089fbe4c28e35ccb8180bc8c7e54cdbb.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15665aa91089fbe4c28e35ccb8180bc8c7e54cdbb.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_15665aa91089fbe4c28e35ccb8180bc8c7e54cdbb.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="The Four Most Important 2021 Digital Automation Trends" src="./media_15665aa91089fbe4c28e35ccb8180bc8c7e54cdbb.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="the-four-most-important-2021-digital-automation-trends">The Four Most Important 2021 Digital Automation Trends</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>The <a href="/covid-19">pandemic</a> turned decades of accepted business principles upside down. Leaders now know everything has to be digital because it’s the only way to future-proof the business. These are some of the most important predictions about digital transformation as we head into a post-pandemic world.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="make-your-organization-more-resilient-and-agile-in-todays-challenging-environment-get-back-to-best-with-sap">Make your organization more resilient and agile in today’s challenging environment: Get back to best with SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/covid-19/back-to-best.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="pragmatism-rules-the-day">Pragmatism Rules the Day</h2>
  <p>Innovation for its own sake is so early aughts. While the pandemic is a force factor for sweeping digital transformation, make no mistake, this is about pragmatic innovation from edge to core.</p>
  <p><a href="https://www.idc.com/getdoc.jsp?containerId=US46990220&#x26;pageType=PRINTFRIENDLY">IDC</a> predicted that by 2022, 70% of all organizations will have accelerated use of digital technologies, transforming existing business processes to drive customer engagement, employee productivity, and business resiliency. Two years later, <a href="https://www.idc.com/getdoc.jsp?containerId=US46990220&#x26;pageType=PRINTFRIENDLY">IDC</a> predicted that 75% of organizations will have comprehensive digital transformation implementation roadmaps, compared to 27% today, resulting in true transformation across all facets of business and society.</p>
  <p>In just three years, <a href="https://www.gartner.com/smarterwithgartner/gartner-top-strategic-technology-trends-for-2021/">Gartner</a> predicted organizations will lower operational costs by 30% by combining hyperautomation technologies (see the next paragraph) with redesigned operational processes.</p>
  <h2 id="no-tech-innovation-is-an-island">No Tech Innovation Is an Island</h2>
  <p>Market interest is high in artificial intelligence (AI), the Internet of Things (IoT), machine learning, digital twins, and robotic process automation (RPA). But these capabilities cannot deliver business results if they are kept in silos. Companies getting the most value are combining the right capabilities together to solve specific problems and uncover opportunities. Gartner called this hyperautomation.</p>
  <p>In fact, <a href="https://www.gartner.com/en/webinars/3991832/the-gartner-2021-predictions-accelerate-results-beyond-rpa-to-hy">Gartner</a> researchers said that “hyperautomation is not about technology. It’s a process that never ends… a disciplined approach organizations use to rapidly identify, vet, and automate as many business and IT processes as possible…they’re not just buying one technology…they’re buying multiple technology that [they] need to architect together.”</p>
  <p><a href="https://go.forrester.com/predictions/">Forrester</a> predicted that “leading CIOs will embrace cloud-first and platform strategies for speed and adaptiveness, eschewing stovepipes for end-to-end solutions.” Further out, <a href="https://goto.webcasts.com/viewer/event.jsp?ei=1365187&#x26;tp_key=a61cd14533">IDC</a> saw 30% of cities using automation from the combination of IoT, AI, and digital twins to blend the physical and digital and improve the remote management of critical infrastructure and digital services by 2025.</p>
  <h2 id="humans-plus-machines-are-the-norm">Humans Plus Machines Are the Norm</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="rise-with-sap-take-control-of-your-business-transformation-journey">RISE with SAP: Take control of your business transformation journey</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/rise.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>I’m hoping this decade will finally put an end to last century either-or debates pitting humans against machines. The highest performing organizations will understand how to seamlessly embed digital technologies to boost human productivity.</p>
  <p>One of the assumptions behind <a href="https://www.gartner.com/en/webinars/3991832/the-gartner-2021-predictions-accelerate-results-beyond-rpa-to-hy">Gartner’s</a> latest predictions was that “everything that can and should be automated will be automated. Everything else must be augmented.” In its vision, machines will automate 80% of processes, serving up information to help people make decisions.</p>
  <p>Most analysts agreed these change weren’t destined for the far off future. <a href="https://go.forrester.com/predictions/">Forrester</a> predicted new forms of automation will support one out of every four remote workers directly or indirectly by the end of this year. These analysts predicted many organizations will invest in conversational AI, machine learning, and hardware advances to help remote workers perform tasks that were “previously done in the office or that held higher labor costs, such as employee self-service, customer service support, and document extraction.”</p>
  <p>By next year, <a href="https://www.idc.com/getdoc.jsp?containerId=US46972220">IDC</a> predicted 65% of CIOs will digitally empower and enable frontline workers with data, AI, and security to extend productivity, adaptability, and decision making in the face of rapid changes. Within two years after that, <a href="https://www.idc.com/getdoc.jsp?containerId=US46917020&#x26;pageType=PRINTFRIENDLY">IDC</a> predicted 50% of knowledge workers will regularly interact with their own AI-enhanced robot assistant, which will help identify and prioritize tasks, collect information, and automate repetitive work.</p>
  <h2 id="industry-leaders-coalesce-into-innovation-powerhouses">Industry Leaders Coalesce into Innovation Powerhouses</h2>
  <p>Some analysts predicted more M&#x26;A activity as larger software and other vendors snap up smaller startups in important areas like AI and RPA. That’s because technologies need to be on the same cloud-based platform to deliver quality, consistent data, powering valuable business insights.</p>
  <p>For example, driven by the goal to embed intelligence in products and services, <a href="https://www.idc.com/getdoc.jsp?containerId=US47396021">IDC</a> predicted that one quarter of Global 2000 companies will acquire at least one AI software startup to ensure ownership of differentiated skills and intellectual property (IP) by 2023.</p>
  <p>According to <a href="https://www.gartner.com/en/webinars/3991832/the-gartner-2021-predictions-accelerate-results-beyond-rpa-to-hy">Gartner</a> analysts, business demands for integrated data will make it far more difficult for companies to survive as standalone tech players. They predicted that by 2024, one or more technology mega-vendors will build or acquire targeted hyperautomation technologies, rendering 60% of the standalone RPA market offerings redundant.</p>
  <p>Integration isn’t limited to acquisitions. Deeply collaborative business, including <a href="/2020/11/creating-network-of-networks">business networks</a>, is on the rise, morphing into what IDC researchers called “digital innovation factories.” By next year, <a href="https://www.idc.com/getdoc.jsp?containerId=US47019920&#x26;pageType=PRINTFRIENDLY">IDC</a> analysts expected 40% of market-leading IT and OT vendors will “form strategic partnerships to deliver a holistic solution; this will reduce integration and deployment costs by 20%.” Further out, these analysts predicted by 2025, driven by volatile global conditions, 75% of business leaders will use digital platforms and ecosystem capabilities to adapt their value chains to new markets, industries, and ecosystems.</p>
  <h2 id="resistance-to-digital-transformation-is-futile">Resistance to Digital Transformation Is Futile</h2>
  <p>What struck me about so many of these and other predictions was the immediacy. Most are expected to happen within the next few years, if not sooner. Digital native companies were already there, and those that haven’t transitioned will get there, hopefully soon enough.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Follow me: @smgaler</em><br><em><a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2021/02/16/the-four-most-important-digital-automation-trends-circa-2021/?sh=543c1ccb3e74">This article originally appeared on SAP BrandVoice on Forbes</a></em>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/forrester</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How to Build Brand Trust in a Polarized World]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/how-to-build-brand-trust-polarized-world</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/how-to-build-brand-trust-polarized-world</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn about the challenges and opportunities facing companies intent on building brand trust in a dynamically fractious world.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/forrester</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Responsible Businesses Put Trust, Ethics, and Sustainability First]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/people-first-trends-responsible-businesses</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/people-first-trends-responsible-businesses</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Among digital growth predictions is a wave of people-first trends. Learn why businesses are putting trust, ethics, and sustainability first.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/forrester</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>