<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/integration/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP TechEd in 2023: That’s a Wrap!]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/sap-teched-2023-wrap-up</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/sap-teched-2023-wrap-up</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Last week at SAP TechEd, SAP announced new SAP BTP innovations that help organizations and developers bring their ideas to life. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1877c9283a8cddb4da2df0b65c45dc5a6351a2863.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1877c9283a8cddb4da2df0b65c45dc5a6351a2863.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1877c9283a8cddb4da2df0b65c45dc5a6351a2863.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP TechEd in 2023: That’s a Wrap!" src="./media_1877c9283a8cddb4da2df0b65c45dc5a6351a2863.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-teched-in-2023-thats-a-wrap">SAP TechEd in 2023: That’s a Wrap!</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>SAP’s mission is to make the world run better and improve people’s lives. As we work to fulfill this purpose each day, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform.html">SAP Business Technology Platform</a> (SAP BTP) serves as the unified platform that enables our customers to accelerate their innovation with application development, integration, automation, data and analytics, and AI capabilities.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="enterprise-innovation-in-the-age-of-ai">Enterprise Innovation in the Age of AI</h3>
        <p><em><a href="">Read the news guide</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Last week at <a href="https://www.sap.com/events/teched/bangalore.html">SAP TechEd</a>, we announced new SAP BTP innovations that help organizations and developers bring their ideas to life.</p>
  <p>Thank you to everyone who attended the event virtually and in person at Bangalore. For those who couldn’t attend live, I recommend reading the <a href="https://www.sap.com/events/teched/news-guide.html">SAP TechEd news guide</a>, checking out the full list of <a href="https://go3.events.sap.com/sapteched/virtual/2023/reg/flow/sap/sapteched23/catalog/page/catalog?tab.sessionplanned=1602215152230002KZab">on-demand sessions</a>, and watching the <a href="https://go3.events.sap.com/sapteched/virtual/2023/reg/flow/sap/sapteched23/catalog/page/catalog/session/1692373933108001qRNV">executive keynote</a>, delivered by SAP CTO Juergen Mueller.</p>
  <p>Here are some of the key announcements we made.</p>
  <h2 id="turning-every-developer-into-an-ai-developer">Turning Every Developer into an AI Developer</h2>
  <p>Developers are essential to the modern world we live in, driving innovation and transformation forward across every industry. To help improve their productivity, we announced <a href="/2023/11/sap-teched-2023-sap-build-code-supercharge-developer-productivity">SAP Build Code</a>, a generative AI-powered application development solution, built on SAP BTP and optimized for Java and JavaScript development. It delivers a turn-key environment for coding, testing, integrations, and application lifecycle management.</p>
  <p>SAP Build Code has embedded generative AI capabilities with <a href="/2023/09/joule-new-generative-ai-assistant">Joule</a> to enable code generation to streamline application development. It also enables fusion development so developers can build rapidly, integrate seamlessly, and collaborate effectively with other developers and business experts. SAP Build Code complements <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/low-code.html">SAP Build</a>, our low-code solution that provides a unified environment to create and enhance enterprise applications, automate processes, and design business sites with drag-and-drop simplicity. <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/developer-tools.html">Learn more here</a>.</p>
  <h2 id="generative-ai-for-everyone">Generative AI for Everyone</h2>
  <p>More than ever before, companies are seeking to unleash the power of AI in their applications and processes. We are thrilled to unveil <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence.html">AI Foundation on SAP BTP</a>, a one-stop shop for developers to build and extend applications powered by AI and generative AI on SAP BTP. With AI Foundation, developers gain access to everything they need to quickly embed business-ready AI into their applications, leveraging the same powerful technology SAP development teams use today. This includes AI services, generative AI management, AI workload management, access to business data and context, and lifecycle management based on SAP AI Core, SAP AI Launchpad, and SAP HANA Cloud. <a href="https://sap.com/joule">Learn more here</a>.</p>
  <p>Later this quarter, AI Foundation will include a new generative AI hub capability in SAP AI Core for accessing a broad range of large language models (LLMs) from third-party providers. With the hub, developers will be able to use tooling for prompt engineering and experimentation to accelerate generative AI application development.</p>
  <h2 id="ai-powered-business-data">AI-Powered Business Data</h2>
  <p>SAP believes every data professional should have seamless and scalable access to mission-critical business data. To this end, we’ve announced new innovations that empower developers to build intelligent data applications with SAP HANA Cloud but also brings new capabilities that not only enhance the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/datasphere/features.html#business-data-fabric">business data fabric</a> with SAP Datasphere.</p>
  <p>Good data is the foundation of good AI, and SAP HANA Cloud continues to pioneer innovation in the data space by adding new vector database features to its multi-model offerings at no additional cost. Vector datastores manage unstructured data — such as text, images, or audio — to provide long-term memory and better context to AI models. This makes it easy to find and retrieve similar objects quickly. For example, users can search for suppliers based on the language in their contracts to examine payment history and trace individual orders. These powerful new vector database features enhance interactions between LLMs and an organization’s mission-critical data. The innovation puts SAP developers at the forefront of delivering radically new levels of data insight within a secure, private framework that uses industry-specific customer data to reduce hallucinations.</p>
  <p>New semantic onboarding capabilities within <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/datasphere.html">SAP Datasphere</a> enable customers to deliver business-ready data products at an accelerated pace. With the powerful semantic layer, organizations can build data products that maintain business context and application logic and forego the time-consuming tasks of extracting business data, creating data pipelines and rebuilding data context that was lost. <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/datasphere/guided-experience.html">Learn more here</a>.</p>
  <h2 id="enterprise-automation">Enterprise Automation</h2>
  <p>Integrating, analyzing, and automating end-to-end business processes is critical in today’s digital landscape. To help customers stay ahead of the competition, SAP offers <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/enterprise-automation.html?pdf-asset=d237f8b9-7e7e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b&#x26;page=1">enterprise automation</a>, one solution that combines the value of <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/integration-suite.html">SAP Integration Suite</a>, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-process-transformation.html">SAP Signavio</a>, and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/low-code.html">SAP Build</a>. At SAP TechEd, we previewed new generative AI capabilities to simplify creating processes and integrations and to recommend pre-built content. Deeper integrations across the three technologies helps companies easily mine non-SAP processes to better analyze, integrate, automate, and monitor business processes across their environment. <a href="https://blogs.sap.com/2023/05/17/introducing-new-capabilities-for-enterprise-automation/">Learn more here</a>.</p>
  <p>See you at SAP TechEd in 2024!</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>JG Chirapurath is chief marketing and solutions officer for SAP BTP and Artificial Intelligence at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-news-coverage-and-stories-from-sap-teched-in-2023">Get the latest news, coverage, and stories from SAP TechEd in 2023</h3>
        <p><em><a href="/topics/sap-teched">Read more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-teched</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/application-development</category>
            <category>news-tag/automation</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/integration</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Integration Is Key to Business Success]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/integration-key-business-success</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/integration-key-business-success</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Choosing the right enterprise-grade integration solution is critical to creating a path to accelerated connectivity and innovation.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/integration</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-integration-suite</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Named a Leader in 2023 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Integration Platform as a Service, Worldwide]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/01/2023-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-ipaas-sap-a-leader</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/01/2023-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-ipaas-sap-a-leader</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Gartner has recognized SAP as a Leader in the 2023 Magic Quadrant for iPaaS, Worldwide for the third time in a row. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/enterprise-integration</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/integration</category>
            <category>news-tag/magic-quadrant</category>
            <category>product/sap-integration-suite</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Task Center: Click, Read, Approve, Repeat!]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/sap-task-center-click-read-approve-repeat</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/sap-task-center-click-read-approve-repeat</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The newly released SAP Task Center on SAP Business Technology Platform supports customers in managing their approval workflows in one place.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_142fe5998aba6eb8edf61f49ee9ebee985a843c87.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_142fe5998aba6eb8edf61f49ee9ebee985a843c87.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_142fe5998aba6eb8edf61f49ee9ebee985a843c87.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Task Center: Click, Read, Approve, Repeat!" src="./media_142fe5998aba6eb8edf61f49ee9ebee985a843c87.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-task-center-click-read-approve-repeat">SAP Task Center: Click, Read, Approve, Repeat!</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>In highly dynamic work environments, the pace of work keeps increasing continuously. As roles and responsibilities grow, it can be challenging to stay on top of mounting numbers of approval workflows, even more so with tasks and approval items scattered across systems.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Especially for cross-functional roles, taking broad workflow approval action across the solution portfolio to realize value quickly and efficiently can be difficult at times. Think of a spend manager for example: working in this area, employees need to oversee expenditure across various solutions like SAP SuccessFactors, SAP Fieldglass, and SAP S/4HANA.</p>
  <p>With <strong>SAP Task Center</strong> we provide a new, unified inbox for approvals across multiple applications with a seamless and integrated user experience. Approval items from multiple SAP solutions are gathered in one list and ready to be processed in just one click. Users can:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Approve tasks quickly and efficiently</li>
    <li>Reduce time spent navigating through various systems to manage approvals</li>
    <li>Work off just one approval list</li>
    <li>Improve quality and consistency of approvals for business-critical items</li>
    <li>Minimize cost of implementation by automated setup</li>
  </ul>
  <p>SAP Task Center provides approvers with a streamlined application and a people-centric user experience across devices to meet their flexible work styles. The unified inbox offers a smart, unified, and actionable approval application — in both mobile and a web environment.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="watch-the-video-sap-task-center">Watch the video: SAP Task Center</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://sapvideoa35699dc5.hana.ondemand.com/?entry_id=1_iwzvmsgg">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="sap-task-center-under-the-hood">SAP Task Center: Under the Hood</h2>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14eaed573d5e38062c014d94930b571b43f479b61.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14eaed573d5e38062c014d94930b571b43f479b61.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_14eaed573d5e38062c014d94930b571b43f479b61.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Graphic: SAP Task Center and SAP BTP" src="./media_14eaed573d5e38062c014d94930b571b43f479b61.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1599" height="2180">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p><em>Click to enlarge</em></p>
  <p>SAP Task Center combines multiple powerful capabilities from <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">SAP Business Technology Platform</a> (SAP BTP), like standardized APIs and a consistent security and identity management. Based on SAP Launchpad, it aims to provide a single point to access all assigned workflow tasks across SAP solutions to improve approval time and quality.</p>
  <p>All assigned tasks can be easily accessed, searched, sorted, and filtered in the respective app, based on predefined criteria. With this, end users can either directly process and approve approvals in the unified inbox application, or can navigate to the task details of the integrated SAP solution — like SAP SuccessFactors, SAP S/4HANA Cloud and on premise, SAP Fieldglass — in case of more complex approval workflows.</p>
  <h2 id="approve-tasks-anywhere-and-any-time-on-sap-mobile-start">Approve Tasks Anywhere and Any Time on SAP Mobile Start</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-business-technology-platform-accelerate-business-outcomes-with-integration-data-to-value-and-extensibility">SAP Business Technology Platform: Accelerate business outcomes with integration, data to value, and extensibility</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16b423ed18aa1c964ad5890a075983b5c493624b3.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16b423ed18aa1c964ad5890a075983b5c493624b3.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_16b423ed18aa1c964ad5890a075983b5c493624b3.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Task Center and SAP Mobile Start" src="./media_16b423ed18aa1c964ad5890a075983b5c493624b3.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3660" height="3400">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p><em>Click to enlarge</em></p>
  <p>In addition to the web application, SAP Task Center is also available within the <a href="/2021/08/sap-mobile-start-launch">SAP Mobile Start</a> app.</p>
  <p>SAP Mobile Start is a native app that serves as the mobile entry point to SAP’s business applications and content, providing users with a consumer-grade experience. Thoughtfully predefined content for typical persona and industry roles allows users to execute mobile-enabled business processes.</p>
  <h2 id="get-started">Get Started</h2>
  <p>SAP Business Technology Platform is the ultimate foundation to intelligently connect people, things, and businesses. To get started with the SAP Task Center requires a consumption-based commercial model in your SAP BTP global account (<a href="https://discovery-center.cloud.sap/serviceCatalog/sap-task-center?licenseModel=cpea&#x26;tab=service_plan&#x26;region=all">SAP Cloud Platform Enterprise Agreement or Pay-As-You-Go for SAP BTP</a>).</p>
  <p>In addition, you can access the unified inbox on your mobile devices through SAP Mobile Start , available for iOS on the <a href="https://apps.apple.com/de/app/sap-mobile-start/id1540195902?l=en">App Store</a>. More details on how to get started with SAP Mobile Start <a href="https://blogs.sap.com/2021/09/03/three-scenarios-on-how-you-can-get-started-on-sap-mobile-start/">are available here</a>.</p>
  <p>SAP Task Center is integrated into SAP S/4HANA, SAP S/4HANA Cloud, SAP Fieldglass, and SAP SuccessFactors solutions. Further SAP solutions, such as SAP Ariba and SAP Concur, are planned to be supported beginning in the first quarter of 2022. Related details can be accessed in the <a href="https://roadmaps.sap.com/board?SQ=INTG_WRF&#x26;range=CURRENT-LAST#Q4%202021">SAP Road Map Explorer</a>.</p>
  <p>SAP Task Center realizes an overarching one workflow inbox across end-to-end processes, as outlined in <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2020/02/520ea921-847d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff.html">SAP’s Integration Strategy paper</a>.</p>
  <p>Over the last 18 months, many more integration innovations have been delivered. Our commitment remains unchanged: we support every customer in their journey to run as an intelligent enterprise.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong>Learn More</strong></p>
        <ul>
          <li><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/intelligent-enterprise.html?url_id=ctabutton-glo-icon-ie">Intelligent Enterprise</a> area on sap.com</li>
          <li><a href="https://community.sap.com/topics/integration-strategy">SAP Community: SAP’s Integration Strategy</a></li>
          <li>SAP Community: <a href="https://blogs.sap.com/?p=1447613">Handling tasks in an efficient, integrated and harmonized way using SAP Task Center</a></li>
          <li>SAP Community: <a href="https://blogs.sap.com/2021/12/01/sap-task-center-is-now-available-in-sap-mobile-start/">SAP Task Center is now available in SAP Mobile Start</a></li>
          <li>SAP Task Center on the <a href="https://help.sap.com/viewer/product/TASK_CENTER/Cloud/en-US">SAP Help Portal</a></li>
        </ul>
        <p><em>Dr. Michael Ameling is senior vice president and head of Intelligent Enterprise and Cross Architecture, Technology &#x26; Innovation, SAP.</em><br><em>Dr. Philipp Herzig is senior vice president and head of Intelligent Enterprise and Cross Architecture, SAP Product Engineering.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/integration</category>
            <category>news-tag/mobile</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>