<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/industry/life-sciences/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Celebrates Healthcare and Life Sciences Industry Heroes]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-celebrates-innovation-life-sciences-healthcare</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-celebrates-innovation-life-sciences-healthcare</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[At the SAP Innovation Days for Life Sciences & Healthcare, healthcare and life sciences heroes are being celebrated for their innovation.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11a28e0140b4548307544da21ffb5966dc472b880.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11a28e0140b4548307544da21ffb5966dc472b880.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_11a28e0140b4548307544da21ffb5966dc472b880.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Celebrates Healthcare and Life Sciences Industry Heroes" src="./media_11a28e0140b4548307544da21ffb5966dc472b880.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-celebrates-healthcare-and-life-sciences-industry-heroes">SAP Celebrates Healthcare and Life Sciences Industry Heroes</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>In the rapidly evolving landscape of life sciences and healthcare, a new breed of heroes has emerged – visionaries that are revolutionizing the industries through innovative SAP technology. From the adoption of artificial intelligence (AI) for drug discovery to building an intuitive mobile app to help Parkinson’s disease patients track symptoms, technology plays a pivotal role in creating a healthier world.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="bring-life-saving-medications-to-market-faster-and-improve-patient-outcomes-with-sap-technology">Bring life-saving medications to market faster and improve patient outcomes with SAP technology</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/life-sciences-healthcare.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>With the integration of cutting-edge technologies, organizations can leverage data-driven insights to make informed decisions, accelerate time-to-market for new treatments, and ultimately improve patient care. Life sciences and healthcare companies are at the forefront of innovation and competitive advantage by embracing changing industry trends and harnessing technology’s power.</p>
  <p>The SAP Industry Heroes program was launched in 2023 to celebrate companies that leverage technology to transform their business in innovative ways. Healthcare and life sciences heroes have harnessed the power of technology to transform the traditional patient paradigm into an adaptive, customer-centric frontier.</p>
  <h2 id="astellas">Astellas</h2>
  <p>Astellas Pharma Inc. is a leading pharmaceutical company dedicated to advancing healthcare through innovative therapies and cutting-edge research. Focusing on addressing unmet medical needs, Astellas develops and markets a wide range of healthcare solutions across various therapeutic areas, striving to improve the health and well-being of patients globally. With RISE with SAP and SAP SuccessFactors solutions, Astellas is building an internal environment that will leverage globally integrated data to unlock the organization’s full potential.</p>
  <h2 id="dxc-technology">DXC Technology</h2>
  <p>DXC Technology is a global IT services and solutions company known for its expertise in digital transformation, enterprise applications, cloud computing, and cybersecurity. With a focus on enabling clients to thrive in the digital era, DXC offers a wide range of technology and advisory services tailored to meet the diverse needs of businesses across industries. A mobile app built on the SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP) and SAP Business AI is enabling individuals with Parkinson’s disease to keep clinicians informed about their symptoms, accompanied by a clinician dashboard – and generative AI query extensions are also in development. The innovative solution aims to improve the quality of life for these patients and their caregivers and marks a huge step forward in using AI to support clinical decisions.</p>
  <h2 id="gilead-sciences">Gilead Sciences</h2>
  <p>Gilead Sciences, Inc. is a biopharmaceutical company that has pursued and achieved breakthroughs in medicine for more than three decades, with the goal of creating a healthier world for all people. The company is committed to advancing innovative medicines to prevent and treat life-threatening diseases, including HIV, viral hepatitis, COVID-19, and cancer. Gilead operates in more than 35 countries worldwide, with headquarters in Foster City, California.</p>
  <p>Gilead’s digital transformation journey includes a bold migration to SAP S/4HANA with segmentation and SAP Ariba and continues to expand its reach with <a href="/topics/business-technology-platform">SAP BTP</a> and cutting-edge solutions such as SAP Intelligent Clinical Supply Management, SAP Cell and Gene Therapy Orchestration, and SAP Batch Release Hub for Life Sciences.</p>
  <p>Most notably, Gilead and SAP are co-innovating on SAP Batch Release Hub for Life Sciences. This groundbreaking add-on will support continued compliance with regulatory standards across regions and jurisdictions with emphasis on highest quality and safety standards for Gilead’s products, further safeguarding patient wellbeing across the globe. Integrating SAP Ariba solutions, including SAP Business Network, Gilead aims to create a globally interconnected platform, enhancing collaboration between suppliers and buyers while optimizing its global procurement operations.</p>
  <p>Additionally, SAP and Gilead are collaborating on co-innovating jurisdiction control checks using SAP Batch Release Hub for Life Sciences. The add-on will perform control checks on manufactured batches of pharmaceutical products, helping life science organizations to maintain compliance with regulatory standards across multiple regions and jurisdictions. This safeguard checklist will further support the quality and safety of products.</p>
  <p>SAP celebrates these organizations’ outstanding efforts, collaboration, and dedication to driving successful business outcomes with technology. The innovations streamline research processes, enhance efficiency, and improve patient care, ultimately revolutionizing how healthcare and life sciences companies operate.</p>
  <p>SAP Innovation Days for Life Sciences &#x26; Healthcare are taking place in Palo Alto, California, from April 24- 25, 2024, and Newton Square, Pennsylvania, from April 29-30, 2024, celebrating industry heroes and bringing attendees together to discuss leveraging technology to drive business outcomes. Get more information on the events <a href="https://events.sap.com/noam/life-sciences-and-healthcare-innovation-and-discovery-days-us-24/en/home">here</a>.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/healthcare</category>
            <category>industry/life-sciences</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[RISE with SAP Accelerates Biotech Innovation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/rise-with-sap-accelerates-innovation-stemcell</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/rise-with-sap-accelerates-innovation-stemcell</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[STEMCELL Technologies is digitally transforming to speed up advanced healthcare discoveries, bringing hope to patients and their families.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/digitalization</category>
            <category>industry/healthcare</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>industry/life-sciences</category>
            <category>news-tag/research-development</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Roche Connects Asset Data to Contextualize and Improve Every Decision]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/roche-asset-data-contextualize-improve-decisions</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/roche-asset-data-contextualize-improve-decisions</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Pharmaceutical company Roche has been improving its asset management and maintenance processes with the help of SAP solutions.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f4368188f69034eaee3b53188d1e3cd047f4908b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f4368188f69034eaee3b53188d1e3cd047f4908b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1f4368188f69034eaee3b53188d1e3cd047f4908b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Roche Connects Asset Data to Contextualize and Improve Every Decision" src="./media_1f4368188f69034eaee3b53188d1e3cd047f4908b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="roche-connects-asset-data-to-contextualize-and-improve-every-decision">Roche Connects Asset Data to Contextualize and Improve Every Decision</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>In a recent webinar, Iago Accioli, project manager of Assets at Roche, discussed how the pharmaceutical company has been improving its asset management and maintenance processes from a broader supply chain perspective.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="https://www.roche.com/about/">Roche</a> is one of the world’s largest biotech companies, a leading provider of in-vitro diagnostics and a global supplier of transformative, innovative solutions across major disease areas.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="find-a-balance-between-performance-cost-and-risk-with-sap-asset-performance-management">Find a balance between performance, cost, and risk with SAP Asset Performance Management</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/apm.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="cost-as-a-main-driver-for-asset-intensive-organizations">Cost as a Main Driver for Asset-Intensive Organizations</h2>
  <p>“As a pharmaceutical company, Roche was founded more than 100 years ago in Basel, Switzerland, with both pharma and diagnostics divisions. We are in the middle of an <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/s4hana.html">SAP S/4HANA</a> journey with the goal to harmonize business processes on all sites and divisions around the world,” said Accioli.</p>
  <p>To <a href="/topics/asset-management">manage assets</a> under volatile conditions effectively, just like other asset-intensive organizations, Roche focuses on <strong>reducing maintenance cost</strong> and <strong>increasing asset reliability</strong>, which are key to its customers and patients.</p>
  <p>The challenge is “the handover from original manufacturer to engineering to maintenance and how to interact with each other,” explained Accioli. “We resolve this with these business process harmonization initiatives.”</p>
  <h2 id="risk-resilience-as-an-investment-for-the-future">Risk Resilience as an Investment for the Future</h2>
  <p>SAP suggests three strategies to help companies manage their business holistically, including cost, speed, profit, customer service, and risk:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Connecting supply chains</strong> to the entire business so that information insight flows go quickly from operations to manufacturing, design, and into the business to respond to disruptions</li>
    <li><strong>Contextualizing information</strong> during the work process to equip users with technology to get real-time insights and make decisions during the business process to increase impact</li>
    <li><strong>Collaborating externally</strong> with suppliers, asset operators, OEMs, and logistics providers to ensure that information is flowing beyond the internal network to set up a risk-resilient business while mitigating risk</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="closing-the-loop-between-strategy-and-execution">Closing the Loop Between Strategy and Execution</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="watch-a-video-to-learn-more-about-enterprise-asset-management">Watch a video to learn more about enterprise asset management</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2020/10/9870e39a-b97d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Managing costs and increasing equipment reliability is a major factor and closing the loop between asset strategy and maintenance execution, such as to make assets more reliable and connected to maintenance execution considering different asset type, is a big opportunity.</p>
  <p>“Five to 10 years ago, reliability engineering became a shining topic at Roche, and we discussed where to start, how much we spend on maintenance, what our most important assets were, and where we should spend more energy and money. We standardized processes to classify our equipment into different asset criticalities – high, medium, and low – and, based on each category, we established a maintenance strategy,” explained Accioli.</p>
  <p>“Afterwards, we looked for a tool that would best suit Roche given the amount of data. Now we have an asset and maintenance strategy in place that is reflected in our system. In 2019, we started harmonizing our processes and were pleased that SAP solutions could support us,” he continued.</p>
  <p>In particular, Roche looked to:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/asset-strategy-performance.html">SAP Asset Strategy and Performance Management</a>, which helps with performing criticality evaluations directly in the SAP system instead of spreadsheets. With criticality results reflected in the system, the maintenance strategy can result in preventive maintenance plans. “Roche is in the middle of the journey. No sites are live yet,” said Accioli. Roche is also enabling access to its service providers to get design insights and improve collaboration.</li>
    <li><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/asset-manager.html">SAP Service and Asset Manager</a>, which enables maintenance plans and work orders to be accessible to maintenance technicians so that they can make instant material reservations and get access to maintenance manuals on mobile devices.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>“I expect a significant <strong>decrease of maintenance execution</strong> as we can plan our work better thanks to a mobile-supported solution,” said Accioli. “The experience with the solution is quite good.”</p>
  <p>Roche was already using SAP at different sites with its own work order types and data model, but it was not automated and connected.</p>
  <p>“We also intend to migrate to <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/apm.html">SAP Asset Performance Management</a>, a successor cloud-based application, where Roche’s enhancement ideas have been incorporated,” explained the manager.</p>
  <h2 id="connected-asset-data-helps-contextualize-business-decisions">Connected Asset Data Helps Contextualize Business Decisions</h2>
  <p>For contextualizing every business process through the eyes of maintenance, it is necessary to converge enterprise IT data with equipment and sensor data to run analyses based on algorithms and machine learning technology. Accioli explained: “Being able to schedule maintenance activities is a substantial improvement for maintenance organizations. To monitor both targets and results, we are using <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/cloud-analytics/features.html">SAP Analytics Cloud</a>, which has many good capabilities. We are developing maintenance KPIs with the insights we get from artificial intelligence (AI) and rolling these back into the asset strategy and reliability process. These are particularly good tools.”</p>
  <h2 id="effective-collaboration-across-the-ecosystem-to-build-a-collaborative-supply-chain">Effective Collaboration Across the Ecosystem to Build a Collaborative Supply Chain</h2>
  <p>“For Roche, sharing information and effective collaboration with asset providers and across our ecosystem is particularly important. Vendors and different equipment suppliers must exchange and collaborate on asset data. Operators and service providers should be able to use the network but also manage the work order process,” said Accioli.</p>
  <p>To summarize, the key benefits of SAP Asset Strategy and Performance Management and SAP Service and Asset Manager Accioli sees are:</p>
  <p><strong>SAP Asset Strategy and Performance Management:</strong></p>
  <ul>
    <li>Defining which maintenance strategy applies to which classification of equipment</li>
    <li>Maintaining assessments in the system</li>
    <li>Generating criticality based on assessments</li>
    <li>Reflecting reliability-centered maintenance in the system, including decision trees and supportive templates</li>
  </ul>
  <p><strong>SAP Service and Asset Manager:</strong></p>
  <ul>
    <li>Being a digitized, automated, paperless solution</li>
    <li>Being able to work offline</li>
    <li>Having all maintenance data at hand in one place</li>
  </ul>
  <p>Listen to the webinar recording <a href="https://event.on24.com/eventRegistration/console/apollox/mainEvent?&#x26;eventid=4174635&#x26;sessionid=1&#x26;username=&#x26;partnerref=&#x26;format=fhvideo1&#x26;mobile=&#x26;flashsupportedmobiledevice=&#x26;helpcenter=&#x26;key=56D188F6DDC0731803732D04D9287E5F&#x26;newConsole=true&#x26;nxChe=true&#x26;newTabCon=true&#x26;consoleEarEventConsole=false&#x26;text_language_id=en&#x26;playerwidth=748&#x26;playerheight=526&#x26;eventuserid=616413864&#x26;contenttype=A&#x26;mediametricsessionid=533671932&#x26;mediametricid=5886174&#x26;usercd=616413864&#x26;mode=launch">here</a>. In addition, watch this <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/asset-management-eam.html?video=9870e39a-b97d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff">overview video</a> to learn how to maximize asset health and performance with SAP Intelligent Asset Management solutions and read what <a href="https://www.sap.com/asset/dynamic/2022/09/77fdedf5-7bbb-4ed6-bc18-1d3febe209ca.html">benefits other enterprises achieved</a>. To know more about the role of service and asset management in your industry, <a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/dg/idc-info-brief-on-service-excellence/index.html">download this complimentary paper from IDC</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Karin Fent is senior director of Global Customer Success Digital Supply Chain at SAP.</em><br><em>Top photo credit: Roche</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/asset-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/enterprise-asset-management</category>
            <category>industry/life-sciences</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP S/4HANA Cloud Is Digital Foundation for Lifesaving Medicines of the Future]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/06/sap-s4hana-cloud-digital-foundation-zymeworks</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/06/sap-s4hana-cloud-digital-foundation-zymeworks</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Biotech innovator Zymeworks builds a foundation for fast growth with SAP solutions, gaining industry best practices with less customization.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>industry/healthcare</category>
            <category>industry/life-sciences</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-concur</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Business Network for Industry Helps Meet Unique Business Needs]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/sap-business-network-for-industry-meet-unique-business-needs</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/sap-business-network-for-industry-meet-unique-business-needs</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Every industry faces challenges that a one-size-fits-all approach can't address. That's where SAP Business Network for Industry can help.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1859392f911d9814db661b8bac76fdce9ce2568e6.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1859392f911d9814db661b8bac76fdce9ce2568e6.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1859392f911d9814db661b8bac76fdce9ce2568e6.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Business Network for Industry Helps Meet Unique Business Needs" src="./media_1859392f911d9814db661b8bac76fdce9ce2568e6.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-business-network-for-industry-helps-meet-unique-business-needs">SAP Business Network for Industry Helps Meet Unique Business Needs</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Companies have been forced to reevaluate the fundamentals of their supply chains over the past several years, often completely overhauling their processes to meet shifting demands. Some of the most significant challenges businesses are facing include skilled labor shortages, shipping and logistics issues, and evolving environmental, social, and governance (ESG) regulations.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The reactive, ad-hoc approach that companies have taken to tackle disruption has resulted in mismatched supply chain processes that offer little visibility and don’t keep up with the speed of change. Companies rely on convoluted, manual communication methods between suppliers and buyers. E-mails and calls get lost in the shuffle of vacations and holidays, making critical collaboration untraceable and delayed.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-the-sap-sapphire-news-guide-tackle-the-future-with-confidence">Read the SAP Sapphire News Guide: Tackle the Future with Confidence</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/events/sapphire/news-guide.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="sap-business-network-is-an-industry-ready-digital-network-of-suppliers-and-buyers">SAP Business Network Is an Industry-Ready Digital Network of Suppliers and Buyers</h2>
  <p>Businesses need a collaborative, many-to-many platform to drive transparent, resilient, and sustainable supply chains. That’s where <a href="/topics/business-network">SAP Business Network</a> comes in: a multi-enterprise collaboration network, built for industry, that helps companies execute their vision and meet growth targets by connecting with trading partners seamlessly.</p>
  <p>Only SAP Business Network provides collaboration across a broad range of processes, including indirect and direct procurement, supply chain, logistics, asset collaboration, finance, and talent.</p>
  <p>But each industry faces unique challenges that can’t always be addressed with a one-size-fits-all approach. For this reason, we are introducing SAP Business Network for Industry with an initial focus on the <strong>consumer products</strong>, <strong>life sciences</strong>, <strong>high tech</strong>, and <strong>industrial manufacturing</strong> industries. This includes:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>A portfolio of SAP Business Network capabilities that address industry needs</li>
    <li>A new SAP Business Network Industry Advisory Board to guide our product and road map strategy</li>
    <li>New SAP Business Network for Supply Chain industry services accelerators for select industries to help customers fast-track their implementation and post go-live success</li>
  </ul>
  <p>With SAP’s more than 50 years of industry expertise and industry process excellence embedded in our technology, we know better than anyone how to help customers tackle their specific challenges.</p>
  <h2 id="capabilities-designed-to-meet-industry-needs">Capabilities Designed to Meet Industry Needs</h2>
  <p>As we work to help companies tackle challenges with supply chain transparency, resiliency, and sustainability, we’ve engaged directly with customers to improve existing functionalities and develop new capabilities for SAP Business Network.</p>
  <p>We developed capabilities including contract manufacturing, planning and forecasting, quality collaboration, stock transfers, support for supplier-managed inventory, material traceability, and track and trace. Several of these capabilities were developed alongside customers to answer unique industry challenges in a variety of industries, including consumer products, high tech, industrial manufacturing, and life sciences. While these and other innovations were originally created to address a specific industry need, many of them can be applied cross-industry to help businesses increase visibility, mitigate risks, and operate more efficiently.</p>
  <p>Working with our customers has helped evolve SAP Business Network into the well-rounded, comprehensive solution it is today. It has been amazing to see the innovations that have come out of these relationships with customers, and their stories and successes have truly inspired me. To build on what we’ve accomplished so far, we’re strengthening the way we collaborate with customers and helping accelerate implementation with new industry-specific use cases.</p>
  <h2 id="continuing-the-tradition-of-customer-collaboration">Continuing the Tradition of Customer Collaboration</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="press-release-saps-vision-for-future-proofed-business-in-the-age-of-ai-comes-to-life">Press Release: SAP’s Vision for Future-Proofed Business in the Age of AI Comes to Life</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2023/05/sap-sapphire-future-proofed-business-age-of-ai">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>To continue the tradition of working with our customers to enhance and extend our product capabilities, we’re introducing the SAP Business Network Industry Advisory Board. This select group of industry leaders will provide strategic direction for our product and road map, making sure we’re meeting the needs of our customers and helping their businesses grow. I’m eager to see the exciting new ideas and developments that will come out of this collaborative forum of industry experts.</p>
  <h2 id="expedite-time-to-value-with-industry-services-accelerators-for-sap-business-network-for-supply-chain">Expedite Time to Value with Industry Services Accelerators for SAP Business Network for Supply Chain</h2>
  <p>For customers beginning their journey with SAP Business Network for Supply Chain in particular, we’re introducing new industry services accelerators from our SAP Business Network Services team to help expedite time to value and achieve success.</p>
  <p>These industry services accelerators support critical supply chain business processes in the consumer products, high tech, industrial manufacturing, and life sciences industries. With prepackaged industry use cases and capabilities, implementation best practices, and dedicated post go-live support, industry services accelerators are based on SAP’s knowledge and expertise with SAP Business Network for Supply Chain. Industry services accelerators can be delivered in collaboration with partners.</p>
  <h2 id="stay-tuned-for-more">Stay Tuned for More</h2>
  <p>Other additions to SAP Business Network include new supplier innovations that will help support supplier adoption, focusing on creating an easier integration process to reduce friction and help grow your business to achieve maximum value.</p>
  <p>To learn more, visit <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-network.html?campaigncode=CRM-YI23-ISM-1982254&#x26;source=blog-glo-blog">SAP Business Network for Industry on sap.com</a>. Here, we’ll keep you up-to-date on all of the exciting innovations happening and share resources to help you tailor your SAP Business Network experience.</p>
  <p>And, don’t miss learning more about SAP Business Network and how SAP can help solve the unique business challenges of your industry at <a href="https://www.sap.com/events/spend-connect-live.html">SAP Spend Connect Live in Vienna</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Val Blatt is global head for SAP Business Network Customer Success &#x26; Go-to-Market at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-more-news-and-coverage-from-sap-sapphire">Read more news and coverage from SAP Sapphire</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/topics/sap-sapphire">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/consumer-goods-cpg</category>
            <category>industry/high-tech</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>industry/life-sciences</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network-for-industry</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Optimizing the Clinical Supply Chain Process to Improve Lives]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/optimizing-clinical-supply-chain-process-to-improve-lives</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/optimizing-clinical-supply-chain-process-to-improve-lives</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With SAP Intelligent Clinical Supply Management, customers can track a clinical trial all the way from study initiation to final shipment.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/life-sciences</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[In Life Sciences and Healthcare, SAP’s Industry Cloud Is Key to Innovation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/life-sciences-healthcare-sap-industry-cloud</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/life-sciences-healthcare-sap-industry-cloud</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP’s industry cloud is helping life sciences and healthcare customers preserve and improve human health one innovation at a time.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/healthcare</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>industry/life-sciences</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[GC Biopharma: Flexible and Integrated HR Portal Improves User Experience]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/gc-biopharma-hr-portal-improves-user-experience</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/gc-biopharma-hr-portal-improves-user-experience</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Pharmaceuticals company GC Biopharma transforms HR with SAP SuccessFactors Work Zone and SAP BTP. Read to learn how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>industry/life-sciences</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-apphaus</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-work-zone</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pharmaceutical Manufacturers Fight Fake Drugs with Intelligent Supply Chains]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/pharmaceutical-manufacturers-drug-supply-chains</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/pharmaceutical-manufacturers-drug-supply-chains</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Investing in intelligent supply chain solutions can enable resilience and prevent counterfeit drugs in the life sciences industry. Learn how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digitalization</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>industry/life-sciences</category>
            <category>product/sap-information-collaboration-hub-for-life-sciences</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-store</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Digital Innovations Behind the Booming Life Sciences Industry]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/digital-innovations-life-sciences-industry</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/digital-innovations-life-sciences-industry</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The pandemic has irrevocably disrupted the life sciences industry, revealing a new vision for innovation from cloud-based collaboration.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/covid-19</category>
            <category>news-tag/forrester</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>industry/healthcare</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>industry/life-sciences</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[California’s Low-Cost Insulin Is Symptom of Lifesaving Innovations to Come]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/life-sciences-innovations-to-come</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/life-sciences-innovations-to-come</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Life sciences leaders are connecting data and people to find for more cost-effective disease prevention innovations and lifesaving cures.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digitalization</category>
            <category>industry/healthcare</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>industry/life-sciences</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Industry Innovation: Turning Supply Chains into Hot Spots for Meaningful Change]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/industry-innovation-supply-chains-meaningful-change</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/industry-innovation-supply-chains-meaningful-change</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The Customer Solution Support & Innovation organization at SAP works with various organizations to support and encourage industry innovation.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/banking</category>
            <category>news-tag/covid-19</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-solution-support-innovation</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>industry/life-sciences</category>
            <category>news-tag/research-development</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-advanced-track-and-trace-for-pharmaceuticals</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-information-collaboration-hub-for-life-sciences</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Turbocharging Batch Release Processes in the Life Sciences Industry to Enable Resilience and Scalability]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/turbocharging-batch-release-processes-life-sciences</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/turbocharging-batch-release-processes-life-sciences</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Batch Release Hub for Life Sciences helps address the need for transparent, flexible, integrated, and efficient batch release management.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/life-sciences</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Helping Shape the Future of the Cell and Gene Therapy Supply Chain]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/cell-and-gene-therapies-future-supply-chain</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/cell-and-gene-therapies-future-supply-chain</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Cell and gene therapies are a new frontier of patient-centric care. A new SAP solution will fill the technology gap in administering CGT.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>industry/life-sciences</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Built from a Consortium of Life Sciences Industry Experts, SAP Intelligent Clinical Supply Management Now Available]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/sap-intelligent-clinical-supply-management-available</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/sap-intelligent-clinical-supply-management-available</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Intelligent Clinical Supply Management addresses the unmet market need for a highly integrated clinical trial supplies solution.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/life-sciences</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Take: New Technology Could All But Prevent Counterfeit Drugs from Reaching Consumers]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/01/the-take-counterfeit-drugs-technology-prevention</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/01/the-take-counterfeit-drugs-technology-prevention</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New technology like blockchain and track and trace can help prevent counterfeit drugs from reaching consumers. Get SAP's take.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>content-type/perspective</category>
            <category>industry/life-sciences</category>
            <category>product/sap-information-collaboration-hub-for-life-sciences</category>
            <category>news-tag/the-take</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP and Boehringer Ingelheim Create Smart App Prototype to Track Counterfeit Pharmaceuticals]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/boehringer-ingelheim-smart-app-prototype-counterfeit-pharmaceuticals</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/boehringer-ingelheim-smart-app-prototype-counterfeit-pharmaceuticals</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A new smart app from SAP and Boehringer Ingelheim authenticates medicines in the fight against counterfeit pharmaceuticals. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16047e914d6a2f80ab2bcdd9b2b68ea5ecfdd18af.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16047e914d6a2f80ab2bcdd9b2b68ea5ecfdd18af.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_16047e914d6a2f80ab2bcdd9b2b68ea5ecfdd18af.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP and Boehringer Ingelheim Create Smart App Prototype to Track Counterfeit Pharmaceuticals" src="./media_16047e914d6a2f80ab2bcdd9b2b68ea5ecfdd18af.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-and-boehringer-ingelheim-create-smart-app-prototype-to-track-counterfeit-pharmaceuticals">SAP and Boehringer Ingelheim Create Smart App Prototype to Track Counterfeit Pharmaceuticals</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="solve-your-specific-life-sciences-needs-with-software-from-sap">Solve your specific life sciences needs with software from SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/life-sciences.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) is announcing a smart app designed to track, trace and authenticate prescription medicines in the United States. Developed in partnership with leading global pharmaceutical research company <a href="https://www.boehringer-ingelheim.us/">Boehringer Ingelheim</a>, the smart app will enable law enforcement officials to potentially detect illicit, counterfeit or unapproved Boehringer Ingelheim medicines being smuggled into the United States or sold illegally.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The smart app will allow U.S. law enforcement officials across the country to scan the 2D barcode on Boehringer Ingelheim-manufactured life-enhancing medications and authenticate them before the medicines reach patients.</p>
  <p>“The law enforcement smart app utilizes SAP’s scalable and secure blockchain solution for manufacturers to drastically improve the pharmaceutical supply chain from start to finish,” said SAP’s global GM for Consumer Industries, Matt Laukaitis. “As this app demonstrates, vertical industry expertise is a critical success factor in delivering innovations to protect patients and ensure access to authentic, life-enhancing medicines.”</p>
  <p>Passed into law in 2013, the U.S. Drug Supply Chain Security Act (DSCSA) aimed to boost the FDA’s ability to protect U.S. patients by developing a connected, digital system to trace prescription drugs throughout the country and identify counterfeit, stolen or contaminated medicine before it reached the hands of consumers.</p>
  <p>SAP’s smart app is a major step in achieving the vision of the DSCSA and is vital to protecting communities and patient safety. When counterfeit drugs are released into the supply chain, vulnerable patients and marginalized populations with limited access to safe, authentic and affordable medicines bear the brunt of the impact.</p>
  <p>“Patient safety is our top priority at our family-owned company, and unverified pharmaceuticals, especially amid a global pandemic, pose a significant threat to the safety and security of both patients and healthcare providers,” said Aaron Graham, Executive Director, Brand Safety &#x26; Security, Boehringer Ingelheim. “SAP’s blockchain-based solution allows our team to safeguard against illicit and unsafe medicines reaching the hands of those who need medicine the most.”</p>
  <p>This technology builds on SAP’s previous efforts to eliminate counterfeit products with SAP Information Collaboration Hub for Life Sciences, a blockchain-technology tool that allows users to authenticate pharmaceutical packaging as it moves between manufacturers, U.S. wholesalers and U.S. hospitals and pharmacies.</p>
  <p>To learn more, watch a <a href="https://event.on24.com/wcc/r/3355862/A2CD9C01627BDD6F71D4CAA6448EC638">webinar</a>.</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="http://news.sap.com/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP on Twitter at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Media Contact:</strong> Stacy Ries, +1 (484) 619-0411, <a href="mailto:stacy.ries@sap.com">stacy.ries@sap.com</a>, ET<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>Any statements contained in this document that are not historical facts are forward-looking statements as defined in the U.S. Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995. Words such as “anticipate,” “believe,” “estimate,” “expect,” “forecast,” “intend,” “may,” “plan,” “project,” “predict,” “should” and “will” and similar expressions as they relate to SAP are intended to identify such forward-looking statements. SAP undertakes no obligation to publicly update or revise any forward-looking statements. All forward-looking statements are subject to various risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results to differ materially from expectations. The factors that could affect SAP’s future financial results are discussed more fully in SAP’s filings with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (“SEC”), including SAP’s most recent Annual Report on Form 20-F filed with the SEC. Readers are cautioned not to place undue reliance on these forward-looking statements, which speak only as of their dates.<br>© 2021 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>industry/life-sciences</category>
            <category>product/sap-information-collaboration-hub-for-life-sciences</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Personalized Medicine Shouldn’t Be Cost Prohibitive: Life Science Business Networks Can Help]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/personalized-medicine-shouldnt-be-cost-prohibitive-life-science-business-networks</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/personalized-medicine-shouldnt-be-cost-prohibitive-life-science-business-networks</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[When professionals collaborate across the life science supply chain, personalized medicine becomes much more affordable. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/consumer-goods-cpg</category>
            <category>industry/life-sciences</category>
            <category>product/sap-information-collaboration-hub-for-life-sciences</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Solution Partners Leverage Industry Cloud to Drive Innovation in the Life Science Industry]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/life-science-partners-leverage-industry-cloud</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/life-science-partners-leverage-industry-cloud</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Aug 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP's life science partners are working to build innovative clinical trial analytics and supply chain management solutions on industry cloud.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c435fc1304cbe3bd5aa901a412cdd45bacd87070.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c435fc1304cbe3bd5aa901a412cdd45bacd87070.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1c435fc1304cbe3bd5aa901a412cdd45bacd87070.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Solution Partners Leverage Industry Cloud to Drive Innovation in the Life Science Industry" src="./media_1c435fc1304cbe3bd5aa901a412cdd45bacd87070.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="solution-partners-leverage-industry-cloud-to-drive-innovation-in-the-life-science-industry">Solution Partners Leverage Industry Cloud to Drive Innovation in the Life Science Industry</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Solution partners have been in the news of late, particularly as it relates to industry cloud and the development of new life science solutions for clinical trial analytics and supply chain management. SAP’s industry cloud gives partners access to vertical solutions that help drive tangible business outcomes and sustainable growth.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Purpose-built by SAP in conjunction with partners, these open-platform solutions are interoperable with the intelligent suite and SAP Business Network. Several partners have recently announced breakthroughs that are helping them accelerate business operations, balance cost efficiencies, and simplify the provisioning of high-value vertical solutions. Here are their stories.</p>
  <h2 id="managing-medical-device-compliance-worldwide">Managing Medical Device Compliance Worldwide</h2>
  <p>Germany’s p36 GmbH was recently recognized as a 2021 SAP Pinnacle Award finalist in the Partner Application of the Year, Industry Cloud category. The company worked closely with SAP to develop a best-in-class solution to help businesses in life sciences respond to unique device identification (UDI) requirements for medical devices.</p>
  <p>Built on SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP), p36’s new UDI solution fits into existing IT landscapes with SAP and third-party applications. It provides a holistic, managed UDI service supporting both business and IT operations with active market monitoring and process best practices for different countries – exactly what customers demand from a modern software-as-a-service (SaaS) solution. By doing so, the platform helps p36 customers achieve UDI compliance in order to become and remain competitive globally.</p>
  <p>The annual SAP Pinnacle Awards acknowledge the contributions of SAP partners that have excelled in growing their partnership with SAP and helping their customers meet their goals. “Being nominated as a finalist from more than 20,000 SAP partners worldwide is an incredible recognition of the way we have provided best-in-class cloud solutions for the life science industry. Our continued partnership with SAP has been a major factor in our success, and being a part of SAP’s industry cloud portfolio is the perfect way to support our business strategy of industry-focused SaaS solutions,<em>”</em> said Robin Wennemuth, CEO and co-founder of p36.</p>
  <h2 id="new-standard-for-life-sciences-clinical-trial-supply-operations">New Standard for Life Sciences Clinical Trial Supply Operations</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="life-sciences-industry-digitalizes-for-people-centric-clinical-drug-trials">Life Sciences Industry Digitalizes for People-Centric Clinical Drug Trials</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/08/life-sciences-symetric-people-centric-clinical-drug-trials">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>To better address the specific needs of the clinical supplies practice, SAP, Roche, and Tenthpin recently initiated an industry consortium consisting of numerous life science stakeholders, including clinical trial and interactive response technology system vendors. The consortium is focused on defining and orchestrating optimally aligned supply processes in order to harmonize clinical and commercial supply chain management systems. The next-generation SAP Intelligent Clinical Supply Management solution aims to shape the future of clinical supplies operations.</p>
  <p>To further strengthen its strategic partnership with SAP, Tenthpin opened a <a href="https://www.tenthpin.com/insights/tenthpin-announces-their-global-life-science-innovation-center-powered-by-sap-technology/">Global Life Science Innovation Center</a> that is focused on fostering innovative clinical trial solutions designed on SAP’s industry cloud.</p>
  <p>“The life science industry is at a crossroads and our clients need to reimagine their future,” said Michael Schmidt, Tenthpin partner and co-founder. “There is a strong need for innovation and the opportunity for the industry is significant. The future of the value chain for the life science industry will be data-driven and patient-centric. With the blurring of lines between pharmaceuticals and medical technology, and with the emergence of bioelectronics, the industry will provide integrated healthcare solutions and treatment that go beyond the pill. Innovation capabilities from Tenthpin in support of SAP’s industry cloud will be at the heart of this transformation.”</p>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1231514d1bf9532a4e55d6925212a90efcdad0209.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1231514d1bf9532a4e55d6925212a90efcdad0209.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1231514d1bf9532a4e55d6925212a90efcdad0209.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Intelligent Clinical Supply Management Solution" src="./media_1231514d1bf9532a4e55d6925212a90efcdad0209.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5w8MkedE3BQ&#x26;list=PLdzEJoB6CqJ9RJFQfsmtXrGGxsQ-2iRfK&#x26;index=6">SAP Intelligent Clinical Supply Management Solution</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="cloud-based-clinical-trial-analytics-solution-built-on-sap-btp">Cloud-Based Clinical Trial Analytics Solution Built on SAP BTP</h2>
  <p>In May, Achiral Systems Pvt., Ltd. launched its <a href="https://www.symetricsystems.com/trial-analytics-pr.html">SyMetric Trial Analytics</a> solution and made it available on SAP’s digital marketplace for partner offerings. The new solution provides a harmonized approach to clinical trial analytics, working to deliver increased transparency into performance, more accurate planning for future studies, greater trust in data, and ultimately higher success rates.</p>
  <p>Life science organizations conduct clinical trials worldwide through multiple contract research organizations (CRO). The success of trials depends on study planning and the performance of various sites, CROs, and the experience of researchers. Performance can vary considerably depending on the therapeutic area, the country where research is conducted, and the phase of the study. In most of these organizations, core data is scattered across departments and across multiple spreadsheets. This solution consolidates and aggregates data to bring clarity to analytics.</p>
  <p>“We are working exclusively to provide comprehensive solutions for clinical trials,” commented Uma Janapareddy, managing director of SyMetric. “Through our SAP partnership, we are able to leverage SAP Business Technology Platform to deliver flexible, cloud-based solutions to our customers. We are pleased to announce the launch of SyMetric Trial Analytics on SAP Store as part of SAP’s industry cloud.”</p>
  <p>To further the spirit of collaboration, Tenthpin and Symetic <a href="https://www.tenthpin.com/insights/tenthpin-and-symetric-announce-strategic-partnership/">announced</a> their strategic partnership to build clinical trial solutions. Bringing the industry expertise of Tenthpin with SyMetric’s clinical trial solution know-how, on top of SAP technology, is a winning match to help improve clinical trial processes.</p>
  <h2 id="vertical-solutions-drive-cost-effective-transformation-and-sustainable-growth">Vertical Solutions Drive Cost-Effective Transformation and Sustainable Growth</h2>
  <p>For life science companies, SAP’s industry cloud can provide resilience, efficiency, and flexibility while supporting strategic transformation. Its wide selection of specialized, cutting-edge solutions can be used to enhance and extend business capabilities while maintaining process integrity and compliance.</p>
  <p>Innovators can respond to changing business requirements with applications they can trust while minimizing integration and support costs. They can enable continuous innovation while protecting the security and integrity of business processes. Industry cloud solutions from SAP help increase automation and support business transformation in a safe, controlled way.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Mandar Paralkar is global head of Life Sciences at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/consumer-goods-cpg</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>industry/life-sciences</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>sap-award/sap-pinnacle-awards</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Life Sciences Industry Digitalizes for People-Centric Clinical Drug Trials]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/life-sciences-symetric-people-centric-clinical-drug-trials</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/life-sciences-symetric-people-centric-clinical-drug-trials</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SyMetric is on a mission to modernize the life sciences industry with its cloud-based analytics solution that runs on SAP BTP. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_19d2ed00090b302d73eb56a097086aa86088d546f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_19d2ed00090b302d73eb56a097086aa86088d546f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_19d2ed00090b302d73eb56a097086aa86088d546f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Life Sciences Industry Digitalizes for People-Centric Clinical Drug Trials" src="./media_19d2ed00090b302d73eb56a097086aa86088d546f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="life-sciences-industry-digitalizes-for-people-centric-clinical-drug-trials">Life Sciences Industry Digitalizes for People-Centric Clinical Drug Trials</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>After the earliest clinical trials in India for <a href="/covid-19">COVID-19</a> plasma therapy went live using <a href="https://www.symetricsystems.com/">SyMetric’s</a> cloud-based analytics solution, the startup hasn’t looked back. With 10 completed COVID-19 studies behind them, SyMetric is on a mission to modernize the <a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/life-sciences.html">life sciences industry</a>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“We are providing a holistic solution for clinical trials management, what we call ERP for clinical research,” said Uma Janapareddy, founder and managing director at SyMetric. “Having easily accessible data on one unified platform helps researchers develop more effective drugs with stronger study results so they can bring pioneering medicines faster to people.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="build-a-strong-digital-platform-with-sap-business-technology-platform">Build a strong digital platform with SAP Business Technology Platform</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="people-driven-clinical-trials">People-Driven Clinical Trials</h2>
  <p>Physicians, researchers, project managers, investigators, and biostatisticians are using SyMetric Trial Analytics to conduct studies at global pharmaceutical companies and clinical research organizations in a variety of therapeutic areas such as neurology, respiratory illness, oncology, and dermatology.</p>
  <p>Running on <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">SAP Business Technology Platform</a>, the solution captures and analyzes historical and updated clinical trial data in one system. This includes patient information indicating initial eligibility to participate in a clinical trial and progress monitoring through rigorous statistical analyses at trial completion for regulatory submission. The tool captures and analyzes electronic data from anywhere, such as a patient’s activities tracked on a mobile device or artificial intelligence (AI)-based imaging that shows medical progress.</p>
  <p>“If you’re starting a lung cancer study, you can easily find out disease prevalence rates and research histories by geography, experience of the investigators, availability of skilled coordinators or pharmacists, and other factors. Our solution brings this data together for informed planning that leads to more efficient execution,” said Janapareddy. “Once the trial is underway, our easy-to-use solutions help researchers accurately track patient recruitment, study progress, make necessary amendments to the clinical study on the fly, and conduct any other activities.”</p>
  <h2 id="time-saving-clinical-data-analytics">Time-Saving Clinical Data Analytics</h2>
  <p>According to Janapareddy, the solution gives clinicians cost-savings foresight and flexibility. Built-in algorithms automatically monitor data, for example, rejecting potential patients who don’t fit certain parameters based on gender, age, or certain health and lifestyle conditions. Real-time data saves time in data clean up at the project completion stage.</p>
  <p>Customers have reduced clinical trial setup and completion timelines by 20%. Some have saved up to 30% wastage of drug supplies during the trial manufacturing phase. One customer saved thousands of dollars using the solution to calculate the number of patient volunteers, as well as the number of drugs and testing kits required to meet randomization objectives with greater precision.</p>
  <p>“With real-time data and built-in algorithms, companies can quickly adapt protocols in response to continuous patient recruitment,” she said. “Researchers can conduct interim analyses at any time before study completion, adjusting drug dosages, delivery mechanisms, and packaging quantities. The system automatically incorporates protocol adjustments and amendments, sans any downtime and without jeopardizing overall study timelines.”</p>
  <h2 id="working-with-sap-labs-india">Working with SAP Labs India</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="the-amazing-inclusion-story-behind-indias-digital-transformation">The Amazing Inclusion Story Behind India’s Digital Transformation</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/05/code-unnati-inclusion-story-india-digital-transformation">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>While most of SyMetric’s customers are based in the United States and India, Janapareddy has set her sights on Europe, inspired by the strength of SAP’s innovation ecosystem. An alumni of SAP Startup Studio at <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/labs-india.html">SAP Labs India</a>, Janapareddy appreciated the design thinking workshops her team used to develop use cases from their collective experiences. She also valued the co-innovation relationships her startup has forged with other members of the program. These include biopharmaceutical companies, medical device manufacturers, and cosmeceutical and nutraceutical manufacturers.</p>
  <p>“We have a shared passion with SAP for the power of life sciences and integrated enterprise resource planning (ERP) data on a single platform – where every company becomes an <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/intelligent-enterprise.html">intelligent enterprise</a>,” said Janapareddy. “SAP is a global leader in life sciences including pharmaceuticals, manufacturing, and ERP, and its leaders generously share their expertise with us. We also appreciate the significant exposure to SAP customers from this partnership.”</p>
  <p>SyMetric Trial Analytics and the SyMetric Clinical Trial Platform are available on <a href="https://store.sap.com/dcp/en/industries/try-and-buy-life-sciences-apps-and-software">SAP Store</a>.</p>
  <h2 id="connected-clinical-trial-supply-chain">Connected Clinical Trial Supply Chain</h2>
  <p>Before she founded SyMetric, Janapareddy held leadership positions at an international non-profit organization that provided funding, education, and other opportunities for underprivileged women. She developed the concept for SyMetric with input from her family and friends at SAP and in the life sciences industry.</p>
  <p>“I wanted to do something big in life, contributing to the community in a way that would have lasting impact,” she said. “There was no integrated system for clinical trials anywhere in the life science industry, so I founded SyMetric to help manage the entire supply chain for people-centric research.”</p>
  <h2 id="from-data-centric-to-patient-centric-trials">From Data-Centric to Patient-Centric Trials</h2>
  <p>Janapareddy envisioned a fully interconnected data platform for everyone involved in life sciences clinical research and manufacturing.</p>
  <p>“The industry is looking ahead to patient-centricity, where people can control their data using the latest technologies to share information and act on it on secure, compliant cloud-based platforms,” she said. “It began with informed consent and now connected data brings researchers and patients even closer together.”</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Follow me @smgaler</em><br><em><a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2021/06/30/life-sciences-industry-digitalizes-for-people-centric-clinical-drug-trials/?sh=12cc7beb55bc">This blog also appeared on SAP BrandVoice on Forbes</a>.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/covid-19</category>
            <category>topic/data-analytics</category>
            <category>industry/life-sciences</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-labs-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-store</category>
            <category>news-tag/startups</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Not-So-Obvious Lessons Learned Managing a Global Vaccine Distribution Cold-Chain]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/vaccine-supply-chain-lessons-distribution-cold-chain</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/vaccine-supply-chain-lessons-distribution-cold-chain</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Vaccine supply chain lessons learned this year are setting companies up for future excellence. Discover how quick pivots have imparted wisdom.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/travel-transportation</category>
            <category>news-tag/covid-19</category>
            <category>industry/healthcare</category>
            <category>industry/life-sciences</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[CureVac Scales COVID-19 Vaccine Production and Distribution]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/curevac-covid-19-vaccine-production-distribution</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/curevac-covid-19-vaccine-production-distribution</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP está ayudando al pionero alemán de ARNm CureVac a ampliar la producción y distribución de la vacuna COVID-19. Conozca cómo.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/consumer-goods-cpg</category>
            <category>news-tag/covid-19</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>industry/life-sciences</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP and Zuellig Pharma Fight Fake Drugs]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/videos/sap-and-zuellig-pharma-fight-fake-drugs</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/videos/sap-and-zuellig-pharma-fight-fake-drugs</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Fake medicines have become a multi-billion dollar trade, with a higher profit margin then heroin trafficking. Now big healthcare corporations like Zuellig Pharma are fighting...]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/video</category>
            <category>news-tag/blockchain</category>
            <category>industry/life-sciences</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>