<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/product/sap-s4hana-cloud/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[RHI Magnesita Refines Technology Landscape with RISE with SAP]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/rhi-magnesita-refines-technology-landscape-rise-with-sap</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/rhi-magnesita-refines-technology-landscape-rise-with-sap</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn why RHI Magnesita, global leader in refractories, has chosen RISE with SAP to rebuild and streamline its technology infrastructure.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1352659f91be85216647ebf5e52a4aeba522c1850.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1352659f91be85216647ebf5e52a4aeba522c1850.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1352659f91be85216647ebf5e52a4aeba522c1850.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="RHI Magnesita Refines Technology Landscape with RISE with SAP" src="./media_1352659f91be85216647ebf5e52a4aeba522c1850.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="rhi-magnesita-refines-technology-landscape-with-rise-with-sap">RHI Magnesita Refines Technology Landscape with RISE with SAP</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>BARCELONA</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="https://www.sap.com/index.html">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) announced that RHI Magnesita (LSE: RHIM), has chosen the RISE with SAP solution to rebuild and streamline its technology infrastructure for continued growth in the refractory industry.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-sapphire-taking-business-to-the-next-level-in-the-era-of-ai">SAP Sapphire: Taking Business to the Next Level in the Era of AI</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/events/sapphire/news-guide.html">Read the news guide</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>A global leader in refractories, RHI Magnesita provides essential parts of the infrastructure that we use and need in our everyday lives. Supplying high-grade refractory products, systems and solutions, RHI Magnesita has 47 main production sites across the world, and ships its products to more than 100 countries.</p>
  <p>With its vision to sustainably manage heat to build a better world, RHI Magnesita needed a technology foundation that would allow end-to-end interaction across its customers, suppliers and business partners across all geographies, end markets and product lines. Choosing to implement a multi-tier landscape consisting of both SAP S/4HANA Cloud Private Edition and SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition, RHI Magnesita is now equipped to redefine all its technology processes and landscape.</p>
  <p>Ticiana Kobel, Executive VP Legal &#x26; Digital Transformation at RHI Magnesita, stated, “With the revamped digital landscape that we will shape together with SAP, RHI Magnesita will transform into a digitally fortified company, centered around our customers and driven by data. The transition to SAP S/4HANA Cloud marks a pivotal moment in RHI Magnesita’s journey toward unparalleled efficiency, agility, and innovation which will enable us to unlock real-time insights, streamline operations, and enhance decision-making across our global network.”</p>
  <p>With SAP S/4HANA Cloud, RHI Magnesita will have one unified view of its operations and supply chain, reducing its infrastructure footprint, and poises itself for better integration of future acquisitions while delivering cost savings.</p>
  <p>“RHI Magnesita is embarking on a true digital transformation that will see the streamlining of several landscapes that will allow it to leverage the cost savings, scalability and flexibility that comes with moving to the cloud,” said Alexander Klaeger, President of SAP MEE. “Already a leader in the industry, I’m excited to see RHI Magnesita use SAP S/4HANA Cloud to sustainably provide infrastructure the world needs.”</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="http://news.sap.com/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-news-and-coverage-from-sap-sapphire-in-2024">Get the latest news and coverage from SAP Sapphire in 2024</h3>
        <p><em><a href="/topics/sap-sapphire">Read more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><strong>Media Contacts:</strong><br>Elisabeth Wursche, +43 664 620 74 27, <a href="mailto:elisabeth.wursche@sap.com">elisabeth.wursche@sap.com</a>, CET<br>Lesa Plingen, +49 6227 76 9000, <a href="mailto:lesa.plingen@sap.com">lesa.plingen@sap.com</a>, CET<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>This document contains forward-looking statements, which are predictions, projections, or other statements about future events. These statements are based on current expectations, forecasts, and assumptions that are subject to risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results and outcomes to materially differ. Additional information regarding these risks and uncertainties may be found in our filings with the Securities and Exchange Commission, including but not limited to the risk factors section of SAP’s 2023 Annual Report on Form 20-F.<br>© 2024 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Roca Group Looks to the Future Through RISE with SAP]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/roca-group-looks-to-future-rise-with-sap</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/roca-group-looks-to-future-rise-with-sap</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn how Roca is leveraging the last SAP technology and innovations, including RISE with SAP, to boost its digital transformation.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16c0e3912183718e90a860d4272af02f88676684b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16c0e3912183718e90a860d4272af02f88676684b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_16c0e3912183718e90a860d4272af02f88676684b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Roca Group Looks to the Future Through RISE with SAP" src="./media_16c0e3912183718e90a860d4272af02f88676684b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="roca-group-looks-to-the-future-through-rise-with-sap">Roca Group Looks to the Future Through RISE with SAP</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>BARCELONA</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced that Roca Group, one of the world’s leading bathroom fixtures and design companies has selected SAP S/4HANA and the RISE with SAP solution as it embarks on its next phase of digital transformation, focused on integrating and standardizing its IT systems.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-sapphire-taking-business-to-the-next-level-in-the-era-of-ai">SAP Sapphire: Taking Business to the Next Level in the Era of AI</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/events/sapphire/news-guide.html">Read the news guide</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>A family-owned business with over 100 years of heritage, a presence in 170 markets, and more than 21,500 employees and nearly 80 factories globally, Roca Group had embraced digitalization to remain competitive and relevant in the dynamic sanitary industry. Having made several acquisitions over the years, Roca Group saw RISE with SAP as the ideal solution to consolidate various IT systems into one IT landscape. Roca’s decision in choosing SAP S/4HANA Cloud was driven by the desire to increase efficiency and the ability to make informed, real-time, data-driven business decisions.</p>
  <p>“Roca Group’s strategy is based on a long-term future vision supported by innovation, technology and sustainability,” said Albert Magrans, CEO of Roca Group. “Moving to SAP S/4HANA enables Roca to leverage the last technology and innovations of SAP software to boost our digital transformation. We are looking forward to faster execution speed, the enhancement of functionality with the Joule copilot, real-time analytics and further innovations from SAP and its ecosystem.”</p>
  <p>“Roca Group and SAP have collaborated closely for a number of years, with Roca trusting SAP with multiple SAP implementations,” said Manos Raptopoulos, VP of SAP Europe, Middle East and Africa. “Roca’s IT strategy is fully aligned with its business transformation with SAP solutions as an integral part of this strategy. Our close partnership allows our teams to have real-time insight into their business transformation, allowing for seamless integration of SAP solutions as they embark on their SAP S/4HANA Cloud journey.”</p>
  <p>In choosing SAP S/4HANA Cloud and various cloud solutions from SAP, such as SAP Customer Experience, SAP Ariba and SAP SuccessFactors solutions, Roca Group continues to be well-positioned to leverage SAP’s integrated suite of solutions that will enhance customer experience and potentially open up new business opportunities. In adopting a clean core approach, the group will have a single platform for its production centers and logistics platforms, tapping onto the SAP Integrated Business Planning for Supply Chain solution for demand and production planning, and the SAP Transportation Management application for transport management. With these solutions implemented, the operations already using them have seen a cubic capacity of their transports rise by 10%.</p>
  <p>Additionally, Roca plans to use SAP SuccessFactors to improve learning programs, manage global payroll and enhance the employee self-service portal through SAP’s suite of solutions in addition to travel expense management with SAP Concur solutions.</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="http://news.sap.com/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-news-and-coverage-from-sap-sapphire-in-2024">Get the latest news and coverage from SAP Sapphire in 2024</h3>
        <p><em><a href="/topics/sap-sapphire">Read more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><strong>Media Contacts:</strong><br>Belén Martinez, +34 914 567 220, <a href="mailto:belen.martinez@sap.com">belen.martinez@sap.com</a>, CET<br>Lesa Plingen, +49 6227 76 9000, <a href="mailto:lesa.plingen@sap.com">lesa.plingen@sap.com</a>, CET<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>This document contains forward-looking statements, which are predictions, projections, or other statements about future events. These statements are based on current expectations, forecasts, and assumptions that are subject to risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results and outcomes to materially differ. Additional information regarding these risks and uncertainties may be found in our filings with the Securities and Exchange Commission, including but not limited to the risk factors section of SAP’s 2023 Annual Report on Form 20-F.<br>© 2024 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Infuses Business AI Throughout Its Enterprise Cloud Portfolio and Partners with Cutting-Edge AI Leaders to Bring Out Customers’ Best]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-sapphire-news-business-ai-enterprise-cloud-portfolio-cutting-edge-partnerships</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-sapphire-news-business-ai-enterprise-cloud-portfolio-cutting-edge-partnerships</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New SAP Business AI innovations and collaborations with partners are igniting ingenuity. Read the news from SAP Sapphire Orlando in 2024.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18ff27978e1178b1dce994986e74f4cc1f6087f26.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18ff27978e1178b1dce994986e74f4cc1f6087f26.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_18ff27978e1178b1dce994986e74f4cc1f6087f26.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Infuses Business AI Throughout Its Enterprise Cloud Portfolio and Partners with Cutting-Edge AI Leaders to Bring Out Customers’ Best" src="./media_18ff27978e1178b1dce994986e74f4cc1f6087f26.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-infuses-business-ai-throughout-its-enterprise-cloud-portfolio-and-partners-with-cutting-edge-ai-leaders-to-bring-out-customers-best">SAP Infuses Business AI Throughout Its Enterprise Cloud Portfolio and Partners with Cutting-Edge AI Leaders to Bring Out Customers’ Best</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>SAP Business AI Innovations and Collaborations with Partners including Google Cloud, Meta, Microsoft, Mistral AI and NVIDIA Ignite Ingenuity</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <table>
          <thead>
            <tr>
              <th>Text Large</th>
            </tr>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td><strong><em>ORLANDO</em></strong> — At its annual SAP Sapphire conference, SAP unveiled generative AI innovations and partnerships that showcase how the company is taking business to the next level in the era of AI.</td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="taking-business-to-the-next-level-in-the-era-of-ai">Taking Business to the Next Level in the Era of AI</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/events/sapphire/news-guide.html">Read the news guide</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>By infusing Business AI across an enterprise cloud portfolio that powers the world’s most mission-critical processes and partnering with companies pushing the edge of what’s possible with AI, SAP is igniting a new wave of insight and ingenuity in global business.</p>
  <p>“The Business AI innovations we’re announcing at SAP Sapphire in 2024 will redefine the way businesses run,” says Christian Klein, CEO and member of the Executive Board of SAP SE. “Today’s AI announcements and partnerships build on our commitment to deliver revolutionary technology that drives real-world results, helping customers unleash the agility and ingenuity they need to succeed in today’s fast-moving business landscape.”</p>
  <h2 id="ai-that-means-business">AI That Means Business</h2>
  <p>As SAP embeds Business AI across its enterprise solutions, it puts rich insights at users’ fingertips, empowering them to deliver better outcomes and elevate the creative problem-solving humans do best. Examples include AI-generated reports in SAP SuccessFactors solutions that give people managers responsibly sourced insights for compensation-related discussions as well as forecasting capabilities in SAP Sales Cloud solutions that predict combinations of salespeople and products most likely to drive sales. Meanwhile, the SAP Business Technology Platform is adding large language models from Amazon Web Services, Meta and Mistral AI to its generative AI hub. This capability in the SAP AI Core infrastructure makes it easier to build generative AI use cases for SAP applications.</p>
  <p>SAP’s generative AI copilot Joule, which quickly sorts and contextualizes data from multiple systems to advance automation and improve decision-making, is expanding throughout the company’s solution portfolio. Joule launched in <a href="/2023/09/joule-new-generative-ai-assistant">SAP SuccessFactors solutions last fall</a> and is now embedded into SAP S/4HANA Cloud solutions and others including SAP Build and SAP Integration Suite. Further expansion by year-end will include SAP Ariba and SAP Analytics Cloud solutions. At Sapphire, SAP also announced <a href="/">plans to further broaden Joule’s scope</a> by integrating it with Microsoft Copilot to surface even richer insights. This deep, bi-directional integration gives users a unified experience built right into the flow of work, enabling seamless access to information from interactions with business applications in SAP and Microsoft 365.</p>
  <p>Reflecting Business AI’s increasing importance, SAP is redoubling its commitment to the principles of relevant, reliable, and responsible AI it pioneered. At Sapphire, SAP is adopting the 10 guiding principles of the UNESCO Recommendation on the Ethics of Artificial Intelligence, which aim to ensure that AI technologies are developed and used in ways that respect human rights, promote fairness and contribute to sustainable development.</p>
  <h2 id="partnerships-that-scale-innovation">Partnerships That Scale Innovation</h2>
  <p>SAP is partnering with best-in-class technology leaders to push the limits of what generative AI can do at an enterprise level. In addition to our expanded collaborations with <a href="/2024/05/aws-sap-generative-ai-new-innovation">AWS</a> and Microsoft, partnerships with Google Cloud, Meta, Mistral AI and NVIDIA ensure SAP can harness the power of AI-ready technology to innovate at speed and deliver richer real-world results.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Google Cloud</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP and Google Cloud are expanding their partnership, using Business AI to help enterprises better predict and mitigate supply-chain risks to minimize disruptions and maintain optimal inventory levels. The companies will integrate Joule and the SAP Integrated Business Planning for Supply Chain solution with Google Cloud’s Gemini models AI assistant and Google Cloud Cortex Framework’s data foundation.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Meta</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP will leverage Meta Llama 3 to generate scripts that render highly customized analytics applications in SAP Analytics Cloud. Meta’s next-generation AI model excels at language nuances and contextual understanding, making it an ideal candidate for translating enterprise business requirements into tangible outcomes.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Mistral AI</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP will also add <a href="/">new large language models from Mistral AI</a>, a global company headquartered in Paris specializing in generative AI, to the generative AI hub capability in SAP AI Core.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>NVIDIA</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP and NVIDIA Corporation advance a <a href="https://blogs.nvidia.com/blog/sap-sapphire-ai-omniverse/">cross-product partnership</a> to embed cutting-edge technologies into enterprise-ready business applications:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>As SAP trains Joule to serve as an AI assistant for the RISE with SAP solution implementations, NVIDIA’s state-of-the-art AI models sift through SAP consulting assets to provide relevant and precise answers to implementation-related questions;</li>
    <li>As SAP embeds Joule in the ABAP Cloud model to generate ABAP code for SAP developers, NVIDIA’s accelerated infrastructure will run, scale, and manage SAP’s generative AI model for ABAP code generation;</li>
    <li>As SAP infuses generative AI into the SAP Intelligent Product Recommendation solution, NVIDIA Omniverse Cloud APIs enable the simulation of complex manufacturing products and configurations as industrial digital twins.</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="cloud-technology-that-drives-agility-and-sustainability">Cloud Technology That Drives Agility and Sustainability</h2>
  <p>Business success in the era of AI means being in the cloud. SAP is making the move easier than ever with initiatives that help customers find partners with the expertise needed for complex SAP S/4HANA Cloud transformations. Further cloud innovations at SAP Sapphire include features that help the world’s organizations measure, manage and execute their sustainability strategies. SAP Sustainability Control Tower and SAP Sustainability Footprint Management solutions now track carbon footprints at scale and help businesses meet regulatory standards.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><a href="https://www.sap.com/events/sapphire/news-guide.html">Learn more in the 2024 SAP Sapphire News Guide</a>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Visit the <a href="/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-news-and-coverage-from-sap-sapphire-in-2024">Get the latest news and coverage from SAP Sapphire in 2024</h3>
        <p><em><a href="/topics/sap-sapphire">Read more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>About SAP</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As a global leader in enterprise applications and business AI, SAP (NYSE:SAP) stands at the nexus of business and technology. For over 50 years, organizations have trusted SAP to bring out their best by uniting business-critical operations spanning finance, procurement, HR, supply chain, and customer experience. For more information, visit <a href="http://www.sap.com">www.sap.com</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Note to editors:</strong><br>To preview and download broadcast-standard stock footage and press photos digitally, please visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/photos">www.sap.com/photos</a>. On this platform, you can find high resolution material for your media channels.</p>
  <p><strong>For customers interested in learning more about SAP products:</strong><br>Global Customer Center: +49 180 534-34-24<br>United States Only: 1 (800) 872-1SAP (1-800-872-1727)</p>
  <p><strong>For more information, press only:</strong><br>Joellen Perry, +1 (650) 445-6780, <a href="mailto:joellen.perry@sap.com">joellen.perry@sap.com</a> PT<br>Marcus Winkler, +49 6227-767497, <a href="mailto:marcus.winkler@sap.com">marcus.winkler@sap.com</a> CET<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>This document contains forward-looking statements, which are predictions, projections, or other statements about future events. These statements are based on current expectations, forecasts, and assumptions that are subject to risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results and outcomes to materially differ. Additional information regarding these risks and uncertainties may be found in our filings with the Securities and Exchange Commission, including but not limited to the risk factors section of SAP’s 2023 Annual Report on Form 20-F.<br>© 2024 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.<br>Please consider our <a href="https://www.sap.com/corporate/en/legal/privacy.html">privacy policy</a>. If you receive this press release in your e-mail and you wish to unsubscribe to our mailing list please contact <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a> and write Unsubscribe in the subject line.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/abap-cloud</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-sales-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-footprint-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[NEC Leverages RISE with SAP and AI to Build Business AI in Move to the Cloud]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/nec-move-to-cloud-rise-with-sap-business-ai</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/nec-move-to-cloud-rise-with-sap-business-ai</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[NEC is migrating to SAP S/4HANA Cloud and adopting a clean-core approach to create a sustainable society through digital transformation.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/aws</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PureTech Scientific Scores Leading Position in the Market with Move to the Cloud]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/puretech-scientific-move-to-the-cloud</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/puretech-scientific-move-to-the-cloud</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[PureTech Scientific has gone live with SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition to position itself for further growth. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c1d9fd2f027e5f5b76f97a625db59c9566ef4528.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c1d9fd2f027e5f5b76f97a625db59c9566ef4528.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1c1d9fd2f027e5f5b76f97a625db59c9566ef4528.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="PureTech Scientific Scores Leading Position in the Market with Move to the Cloud" src="./media_1c1d9fd2f027e5f5b76f97a625db59c9566ef4528.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="puretech-scientific-scores-leading-position-in-the-market-with-move-to-the-cloud">PureTech Scientific Scores Leading Position in the Market with Move to the Cloud</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>BELLE, W. Va.</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced that <a href="https://www.puretechscientific.com/">PureTech Scientific LLC</a>, a global leader in the production of glycolic acid products, with a range of uses from skin care to clean and disinfect, has gone live with SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition to position itself for further growth.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="https://ironpathcapital.com/">Iron Path Capital</a>, a private equity firm that acquired the company in 2023, has significant growth ambitions for PureTech Scientific. The first milestone for PureTech Scientific transformation was the move to the cloud to build a unified technology platform that would fully transition employees, customers and vendors with minimal disruption. Completed in 14 weeks, the implementation has already seen improved operational visibility and more timely transactional discipline.</p>
  <p>“The real-time insights and automation PureTech Scientific plans to gain from implementation of SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition will help to streamline our operations and significantly enhance our ability to serve our customers with greater speed and accuracy,” PureTech Scientific CEO James Kanicky said. “This is just the beginning, and we’re excited for the opportunities ahead as we continue to drive growth and innovation with glycolic acid in the personal care and health care markets.”</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="grow-with-sap-cloud-erp-adoption-with-speed-predictability-and-continuous-innovation">GROW with SAP: Cloud ERP adoption with speed, predictability and continuous innovation</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/grow.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>With its entire ERP now in the cloud, PureTech Scientific, the only North American glycolic acid producer, has real-time insight of its daily production and the ability to employ and automate barcoding. PureTech Scientific is now able to complete SAP goods issue and goods receipt transactions automatically with mobile devices, further reducing time needed for reporting.</p>
  <p>“SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition provides a best-in-class foundation for enterprise scalability, security and compliance,” said James Smith, executive advisor for Iron Path Capital and PureTech board member. “After an impressive 14-week implementation, PureTech Scientific is now able to have real-time business analytics and implement industry-best-practice, fit-to-standard workflows. The commencement of digital manufacturing cloud, barcoding and sales cloud capabilities will eliminate manual transactions, automate production recording and material movements, and employ mobile data collection for improved enterprise productivity and customer satisfaction.”</p>
  <p>Glycolic acid is used as the core agent in multiple industries, ranging from industrials to life science. PureTech Scientific expects the market to grow 10% CAGR over the next five years. SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition was selected specifically to support PureTech Scientific’s vision for growth. With scalability and integration as top priorities, SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition allows the company to now focus on pursuing growth opportunities in new markets and new capabilities for new and existing customers.</p>
  <p>“PureTech Scientific has undergone a significant transformation in the past year,” SAP North America President Lloyd Adams said. “It has completely revamped its ERP system and moved to the cloud. Doing so allows for quick and data-driven business decisions as it enhances its capabilities and deepens its market share in key markets.”</p>
  <p>Learn more at <a href="https://www.puretechscientific.com/">PureTech Scientific</a>.</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="http://news.sap.com/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Media Contacts:</strong><br>Bridget Carroll, +1 (267) 615-3589, <a href="mailto:bridget.carroll@sap.com">bridget.carroll@sap.com</a>, ET<br>Lesa Plingen, +49 622 776 9000, <a href="mailto:lesa.plingen@sap.com">lesa.plingen@sap.com</a>, CET<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>This document contains forward-looking statements, which are predictions, projections, or other statements about future events. These statements are based on current expectations, forecasts, and assumptions that are subject to risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results and outcomes to materially differ. Additional information regarding these risks and uncertainties may be found in our filings with the Securities and Exchange Commission, including but not limited to the risk factors section of SAP’s 2023 Annual Report on Form 20-F.<br>© 2024 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Innovative Cloud ERP at Department of Defense Agencies with SAP S/4HANA Cloud Private Edition]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/dod-agencies-sap-ns2-innovative-cloud-erp</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/dod-agencies-sap-ns2-innovative-cloud-erp</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP NS2 can now officially deploy SAP S/4HANA Cloud Private Edition within the DoD IL4 secure cloud environment. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17fe6b9f04141be0d0702008e758517683085fbcd.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17fe6b9f04141be0d0702008e758517683085fbcd.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_17fe6b9f04141be0d0702008e758517683085fbcd.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Innovative Cloud ERP at Department of Defense Agencies with SAP S/4HANA Cloud Private Edition" src="./media_17fe6b9f04141be0d0702008e758517683085fbcd.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="innovative-cloud-erp-at-department-of-defense-agencies-with-sap-s4hana-cloud-private-edition">Innovative Cloud ERP at Department of Defense Agencies with SAP S/4HANA Cloud Private Edition</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Over the past several years, defense agencies in the United States have become increasingly cloud-centric. The cloud has proven its ability to streamline operations, empower real-time decision making, and support mission success.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As <a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/sap-ns2-achieves-disa-provisional-authorization-pa-of-sap-s4hana-cloud-to-support-enterprise-cloud-operations-for-defense-agencies-302130501.html?tc=eml_cleartime">announced May 2,</a> SAP S/4HANA Cloud Private Edition has received a provisional authorization from the Defense Information and Systems Agency (DISA). This means SAP NS2, an independent subsidiary of SAP that facilitates the adoption of SAP cloud solutions for customers who require enhanced compliance, can officially deploy SAP S/4HANA Cloud Private Edition within the Department of Defense FedRAMP+Impact Level 4 (DoD IL4) secure cloud environment.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="cloud-erp-for-every-business-need-from-mission-critical-operations-to-business-model-innovation">Cloud ERP for every business need: from mission-critical operations to business model innovation</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP S/4HANA Cloud Private Edition enables a cloud experience with the same functional scope and upgrade flexibility that SAP S/4HANA Cloud offers, but with added security and compliance that allows Department of Defense customers a quick adoption of cloud solutions.</p>
  <p>With this new certification, defense customers can choose to adopt a secure cloud ERP solution that supports mission-critical operations in real time, from any location. Once limited to on-premise solutions, which exhausted budget and resources, defense agencies can now migrate operations to the cloud where data is stored on cloud servers and resources can be reallocated to support defense workforces and alternative needs.</p>
  <p>“Obtaining our FedRAMP+DoD IL4 authorization was a tremendous step in supporting our defense and federal agency customers,” said Amy Spruill, senior vice president and general manager of Regulated Industries at SAP. “SAP S/4HANA Cloud will provide the commercial cloud capabilities our customers are looking for while improving their security perimeter and mitigating attacks on critical data.”</p>
  <p>The FedRAMP+DoD IL4 secure cloud environment is dedicated to defense agencies and protected with continuous monitoring, vulnerability scanning, and intrusion detection to ensure Controlled Unclassified Information (CUI) is safeguarded. <a href="https://www.sapns2.com/security-and-trust/">SAP NS2 adheres</a> to National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST) 800-53, FedRAMP®, International Traffic and Arms (ITAR), and FedRAMP+Impact Level 2 (DoD IL2).</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Harish Luthra is CEO of SAP NS2.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/defense-security</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ns2</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[DeLaval Selects SAP S/4HANA Cloud to Cultivate Cloud Benefits]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/delaval-selects-sap-s-4hana-cloud-to-cultivate-cloud-benefits</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/delaval-selects-sap-s-4hana-cloud-to-cultivate-cloud-benefits</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Global producer of dairy and farming machinery DeLaval has chosen SAP S/4HANA Cloud to transform itself into a data-driven organization.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Navigating Tax Requirements in the Digital Era: Manage Compliance with Cloud ERP]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/tax-transformation-in-the-digital-era-course</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/tax-transformation-in-the-digital-era-course</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[To help tax professionals prepare for and become valuable members of tax transformation projects, SAP is introducing a new course.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_12d216e0addd5a9233a73cb4294d58a8906d2b314.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_12d216e0addd5a9233a73cb4294d58a8906d2b314.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_12d216e0addd5a9233a73cb4294d58a8906d2b314.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Navigating Tax Requirements in the Digital Era: Manage Compliance with Cloud ERP" src="./media_12d216e0addd5a9233a73cb4294d58a8906d2b314.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="navigating-tax-requirements-in-the-digital-era-manage-compliance-with-cloud-erp">Navigating Tax Requirements in the Digital Era: Manage Compliance with Cloud ERP</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>As businesses adapt to digitalization, they encounter various trends reshaping tax compliance. From emerging business models to governments’ digital initiatives, the tax landscape is undergoing significant transformation.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Authorities are starting to involve themselves in business transactions, disrupting well-established business processes and taking control of the invoicing flow between suppliers and buyers. As a result, they have the data needed to prevent tax evasion and start auditing taxpayers automatically or even auto-populating tax returns moving toward tax bills. Additionally, sustainability efforts and climate change regulations further impact tax regulations.</p>
  <p>Amid these shifts, SAP can provide peace of mind to navigate complexities efficiently. By understanding the evolving tax landscape, businesses can leverage SAP solutions to help streamline compliance processes and drive automation to capitalize on emerging opportunities.</p>
  <p>SAP solutions for global tax management are tailored to help address modern tax challenges. <a href="/topics/erp">SAP S/4HANA Cloud</a> can provide transparency and compliance on a global scale, enabling businesses to embed tax requirements in processes.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="pave-the-way-to-strategic-tax-management-and-automated-compliance-with-sap">Pave the way to strategic tax management and automated compliance with SAP</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/tax-management">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Through localized solutions that offer standardized but flexible business processes, a complete suite of solutions facilitates efficient tax management, from e-invoicing to statutory reporting and overall tax compliance. With SAP technology and expertise, businesses can achieve greater accuracy and agility in tax compliance, paving the way for sustainable growth and competitive advantage.</p>
  <p>To help tax professionals prepare for and become valuable members of tax transformation projects, SAP is introducing a new course: <strong><a href="https://open.sap.com/courses/s4htax-pc">Unlocking Tax Transformation with SAP</a></strong>.</p>
  <p>The course is designed to equip professionals with the knowledge needed to navigate today’s tax landscape and learn new capabilities that can be leveraged as part of SAP S/4HANA-enabled transformations to simplify tax compliance.</p>
  <p>The course offers practical strategies to learn about the different tax types, global developments and their business relevance, and the importance of technology with a focus on SAP S/4HANA and SAP solutions for global tax management. It begins on April 30 and <a href="https://open.sap.com/courses/s4htax-pc">enrollment is now open</a>. By enrolling in this course, tax professionals can gain valuable insights into industry best practices and leverage the latest SAP innovations to help optimize their tax processes.</p>
  <p>In a time of rapid change, SAP supports businesses on their journey to tax compliance and growth. Through collaboration with SAP and a commitment to continuous learning, businesses can navigate the complexities of taxation with confidence and achieve their long-term objectives.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Erika Buson is part of Product Marketing for Global Tax Management and Entity Close at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="follow-and-connect-with-sap-news-on-linkedin">Follow and connect with SAP News on LinkedIn</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news">Stay in touch</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/financial-management</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/financial-services</category>
            <category>news-tag/opensap</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[GROW with SAP: Add-On Packages Expand the Value of Cloud ERP for Growing Businesses]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/grow-with-sap-add-on-packages-expand-cloud-erp-value</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/grow-with-sap-add-on-packages-expand-cloud-erp-value</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New GROW with SAP add-on packages strengthen financial and HR management practices to become strategic pillars for growth.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/financial-management</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/grow-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[RISE with SAP: Add-On Packages Help Businesses Transform Finance and Supply Chain]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/rise-with-sap-finance-and-supply-chain-add-on-packages</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/rise-with-sap-finance-and-supply-chain-add-on-packages</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With the RISE with SAP add-on packages for finance and supply chain, customers can reap significant value from their cloud ERP investment.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/financial-management</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-supply-chain</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Churchill Downs Makes Play for Growth with Cloud Solutions from SAP]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/churchill-downs-cloud-grow-with-sap</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/churchill-downs-cloud-grow-with-sap</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Churchill Downs has selected GROW with SAP to support its financial technology transformation. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_132d042893e3fab23f4d34925b1701fd3ad6ec788.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_132d042893e3fab23f4d34925b1701fd3ad6ec788.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_132d042893e3fab23f4d34925b1701fd3ad6ec788.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Churchill Downs Makes Play for Growth with Cloud Solutions from SAP" src="./media_132d042893e3fab23f4d34925b1701fd3ad6ec788.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="churchill-downs-makes-play-for-growth-with-cloud-solutions-from-sap">Churchill Downs Makes Play for Growth with Cloud Solutions from SAP</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) announced that Churchill Downs Incorporated (NSQ: CHDN, “CDI”) has selected the GROW with SAP solution to support the company’s financial technology transformation as CDI continues to grow within the racing, online wagering and gaming entertainment industries.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>CDI has chosen cloud solutions from SAP to serve as its technology foundation for the financial systems across its portfolio of 27 properties in 14 states, including Churchill Downs Racetrack (“Churchill Downs”), the home of the Kentucky Derby. CDI’s significant technology transformation builds on the company’s partnership with SAP as a signature partner and the first official technology partner serving Churchill Downs, the Kentucky Derby and the Kentucky Oaks.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-s4hana-cloud-public-edition-ready-to-run-cloud-erp">SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition: Ready-to-run cloud ERP</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/s4hana.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>By adopting SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition, CDI can benefit from the ready-to-run cloud ERP that delivers the latest industry best practices and continuous innovation. Additionally, choosing SAP Business Technology Platform and SAP SuccessFactors solutions allows CDI to leverage the cloud to streamline its data sources while using business data to make informed strategic decisions underpinning business transformation. From creating engaging employee experiences with SAP SuccessFactors solutions to running business analytics to understand and predict data, CDI plans to be able to integrate business data from various acquisitions, allowing it to have one, unified view of its business operations.</p>
  <p>“Cloud solutions from SAP will enable us to streamline our financial processes and support the significant long-term growth of our company,” said Marcia Dall, CDI Executive Vice President and Chief Financial Officer. “We are excited to work with SAP to innovate and evolve our financial technology platform with cloud solutions from SAP.”</p>
  <p>“Churchill Downs Incorporated has a long history of entertaining and delighting people,” SAP North America President Lloyd Adams said. “By choosing SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition and several other cloud-based solutions, CDI now can integrate data across its portfolio and make data-driven decisions that help the company reach its goals. This is an incredible example of how companies invest in SAP solutions to help them grow.”</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="http://news.sap.com/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Media Contacts:</strong><br>Mallory Kuno, +1 (425) 239-9362, <a href="mailto:mallory.kuno@sap.com">mallory.kuno@sap.com</a>, ET<br>Lesa Plingen, +49 622 776 9000, <a href="mailto:lesa.plingen@sap.com">lesa.plingen@sap.com</a>, CET<br><a href="mailto:SAP%20Press%20Room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>This document contains forward-looking statements, which are predictions, projections, or other statements about future events. These statements are based on current expectations, forecasts, and assumptions that are subject to risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results and outcomes to materially differ. Additional information regarding these risks and uncertainties may be found in our filings with the Securities and Exchange Commission, including but not limited to the risk factors section of SAP’s 2023 Annual Report on Form 20-F.<br>© 2024 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>news-tag/grow-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[RISE with SAP: Extending Procurement’s Digital Transformation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/rise-with-sap-sap-business-network-procurement</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/rise-with-sap-sap-business-network-procurement</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The combination of RISE with SAP and SAP Business Network for Procurement empowers procurement teams to digitally transform. Learn how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/enterprise-resource-planning</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Convista Harmonizes Workplace Culture with SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central and SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/convista-harmonizes-workplace-culture-with-sap-successfactors</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/convista-harmonizes-workplace-culture-with-sap-successfactors</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Convista's people culture and respected brand built on trust and transparency is supported by SAP S/4HANA Cloud and SAP SuccessFactors.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11a18052b07fa380b0a184821d2508dc2d57d515a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11a18052b07fa380b0a184821d2508dc2d57d515a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_11a18052b07fa380b0a184821d2508dc2d57d515a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Convista Harmonizes Workplace Culture with SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central and SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition" src="./media_11a18052b07fa380b0a184821d2508dc2d57d515a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="convista-harmonizes-workplace-culture-with-sap-successfactors-employee-central-and-sap-s4hana-cloud-public-edition">Convista Harmonizes Workplace Culture with SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central and SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>In a merger between two well-matched organizations, cultural integration can be the key to successfully transforming into a single high-performing entity ready to take on new opportunities. Notably, more than a few high-profile mergers have failed due to cultural incompatibility. Add a third organization into the merger and the cultural complexities increase exponentially. But some multi-organization mergers do successfully navigate these challenges and reap the transformational benefits.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="https://www.convista.com/en/">Convista</a>, a consultancy and SAP partner based in Cologne, Germany, emerged stronger and better positioned to serve its clients following a <a href="https://www.convista.com/en/news/axxiome-health-and-enowa-become-part-of-the-new-convista/">recent merger</a> that brought together three former consultancies: Axxiome Health, ConVista Consulting, and enowa. With 25 years of experience delivering transformation projects to its clients, Convista used that expertise in its own rebranding to present its capabilities to clients and employees: a vibrant people culture as well as a respected and trusted brand supported by <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/s4hana.html">SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition</a> for ERP and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/employee-central-hris/features.html">SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central</a> for core HR.</p>
  <p>“Trust and transparency are common values that we share at Convista,” declares Convista CEO Martin Hinz. “Combined with a dynamic team spirit and passion, it’s what we bring to our clients every day.”</p>
  <p>With a workforce of around 1,200 employees, Convista has made a name for itself through its dedication and expertise providing end-to-end solutions to clients throughout the world with a presence in Germany, Austria, Switzerland, Poland, Spain, Brazil, Israel, and further locations across the globe. It supports client projects primarily in four sectors: insurance, industry, healthcare, and energy/utilities. In recent years, Convista has twice been awarded SAP <a href="https://www.convista.com/en/news/for-the-second-time-in-a-row-sap-partner-of-the-year-award-in-the-financial-services-sector/">Partner of the Year</a> in the Financial Services sector.</p>
  <p>“At Convista you meet everyone on the same level, independent of your skill level or where you are in your career,” says Stefanie Weber, project lead of People and Culture – HR Systems, Convista. “Also, when we’re working with customers, we try to approach them at eye level, which makes quite a good working environment. The implementation of SAP SuccessFactors came as a natural extension to our brand and our culture.”</p>
  <h2 id="the-challenges-of-data-siloed-in-three-systems">The Challenges of Data Siloed in Three Systems</h2>
  <p>Weber says one of the reasons she joined Convista in 2012 while studying business at university was the high priority its leaders place on trust and transparency, values that permeate the entire organization and empower employees in their work and career development. “Trust is one of our main values,” she underscores. “Also, the trust that people are willing to do their best to get motivated and move the company ahead.”</p>
  <p>Convista grew quickly both organically and as a result of mergers with other consultancies. In 2019, IT service provider Axxiome Health joined the ConVista Group to deepen the organization’s expertise in the health insurance sector. In 2021, enowa joined the group, infusing its knowledge of industries and insurance. With the mergers complete, the incipient organization became <a href="https://www.convista.com/en/news/axxiome-health-and-enowa-become-part-of-the-new-convista/">the new Convista</a> on January 1, 2023.</p>
  <p>Though team members were highly motivated to collaborate from the start, Convista’s vision for itself as a modern organization was held back in both its daily work for projects and internal services. Using disparate tools based on older technology and a patchwork of third-party solutions that lacked integration proved to be inefficient and unsuitable as a basis for decision-making.</p>
  <p>“Whenever we wanted to have a report, even something as simple as a headcount, we always had to go into three different systems, collect the data, and report on that,” Weber recalls. “It’s just one of the many examples of why we really urgently needed one IT platform.”</p>
  <h2 id="project-one-achieves-milestone-integration">Project ONE Achieves Milestone Integration</h2>
  <p>To build a strong foundation for future growth, Convista embarked on “Project ONE” with the goal to have one digital platform flexible and powerful enough for the entire organization. For this, it chose SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition and SAP SuccessFactors solutions with self-service capabilities for employees to log time-off.</p>
  <p>Overall, implementing SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central with SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition can result in streamlined HR processes; end-to-end integration with seamless connectivity between HR and finance functions for accurate and up-to-date employee data across the organization; greater transparency of data for analytics and reporting on workforce trends, costs, and profitability to enable better strategic planning and resource allocation; and compliance with regulatory requirements and data security.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-successfactors-solutions-can-fuel-the-success-of-every-individual-and-drive-org-agility-at-scale">SAP SuccessFactors solutions can fuel the success of every individual and drive org agility at scale</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm.html">Learn how</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Among the key advantages is the ability for employees to access their own HR-related information, such as personal details and time-off balances. This self-service capability helps empower employees, improve transparency, and enhance the overall employee experience.</p>
  <p>Convista’s project team decided for a phased approach to the implementation by first introducing the SAP solutions in Poland and later in Germany, Austria, and Switzerland – with SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition planned to launch in the German-speaking countries during the course of 2024. To optimize success, the project team used the combined best practices of Convista and SAP and hosted regular meetings that provided clear communication to steer the project. “We were always aligned on the requirements of the other teams,” says Weber, who managed the HR workstream. “We all knew the main goal of the implementation. This was helpful for everyone on the project.”</p>
  <p>In-house experts from Convista certified on SAP SuccessFactors solutions contributed valuable knowledge for the implementation. Consultants from SAP Services and Support successfully integrated the cost center replication from SAP S/4HANA Cloud to SAP SuccessFactors and the workforce replication from SAP SuccessFactors to SAP S/4HANA Cloud, and delivered a detailed administration guide on the integration setup for Convista. Additionally, they provided an overview, the architecture guidance, and the navigation through major hurdles in performing the configuration to set up identity access governence (IAG), identity provisioning service (IPS), and identity authentication services (IAS). The SAP Early Adopter Care program supported Convista for the master data integration (MDI) during the implementation and helped to solve all roadblocks efficiently.</p>
  <p>On January 1, 2023, Convista’s 80-person team in Poland was the first to go live with the new SAP solutions. “It was really a great experience for them and quite an advancement,” says Weber, citing the benefits of the new solutions that provide optimizations and intuitive workflows. The project took a pivotal turn on January 1, 2024, with the launch of SAP SuccessFactors solutions for Convista’s 800 employees in the German-speaking countries.</p>
  <p>“The biggest milestone was to have [SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition and SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central] speaking with each other,” says Weber, who emphasizes how valuable it is for the team “to have an end-to-end process within one platform.” With an integrated IT platform in place, she says that it is no longer necessary to do workflows, authorizations, or any other processes in other systems.</p>
  <p>The seamless synchronization of data by using a common data model for SAP business applications helps reduce the need for manual data entry and redundant processes. This means, for example, employee data that is maintained in SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central is available in real-time in SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition; while master data, like cost center data, flows seamlessly from SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition to SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central. Eliminating data silos enables the HR and finance teams to work with consistent, accurate data for all-important employment decisions and legal reporting obligations.</p>
  <p>Now Convista’s team is unified in its brand, values, spirit – and employee data.</p>
  <h2 id="more-transparency-and-intuitive-workflows-are-just-the-beginning">More Transparency and Intuitive Workflows Are Just the Beginning</h2>
  <p>Feedback has been overwhelmingly positive, according to Weber, with employees speaking favorably about the improved transparency and workflows. “The first thing I heard from everyone was, well, this is simple and intuitive. They were so happy about it,” she says. “They are big fans of the mobile application. They find it very transparent and easy to use.”</p>
  <p>For some colleagues, the new solution lets them view their own data for the first time. “When we went live, everyone was viewing their profile,” says Weber. “This was also quite new that you are able to see what data is maintained for your person, your address, but also job information – to view it and have this transparency. People like this very much and also the ability to have the self-services in SAP SuccessFactors.”</p>
  <p>To strengthen communication between HR and employees, Convista will bring more people processes onto the new digital platform. In fact, the team very recently implemented the SAP SuccessFactors Performance &#x26; Goals solution for annual employee appraisals, goal setting, and project feedback. “It’s just the beginning,” Weber says. “There’s still a lot of work ahead of us.”</p>
  <p>Hinz says, “We have been careful to preserve our workplace culture during the transformation. Now that we are rebranded as one organization, we are seeing the benefits of that early effort. With SAP, we now have the digital platform to build people-centered processes that advance our vision as a unified, high-performing organization serving our clients.”</p>
  <p>Find out more about <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/solutions.html?url_id=ctabutton-us-hcm-convista">SAP SuccessFactors solutions</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Jacqueline Prause is a journalist at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-sap-news-delivered-to-your-inbox-once-a-week">Get the latest SAP news delivered to your inbox once a week</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/nl/sap-news-center-newsletter/index.html">Sign up today</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-employee-central</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Deutsche Telekom Chooses RISE with SAP in Cloud Transformation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/deutsche-telekom-rise-with-sap-cloud-transformation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/deutsche-telekom-rise-with-sap-cloud-transformation</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Deutsche Telekom, a leading integrated telecommunications companies, has chosen RISE with SAP to accelerate its journey to the cloud.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1700bd00be5fff8c11a0434fa79589819e4d1ada0.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1700bd00be5fff8c11a0434fa79589819e4d1ada0.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1700bd00be5fff8c11a0434fa79589819e4d1ada0.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Deutsche Telekom Chooses RISE with SAP in Cloud Transformation" src="./media_1700bd00be5fff8c11a0434fa79589819e4d1ada0.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="deutsche-telekom-chooses-rise-with-sap-in-cloud-transformation">Deutsche Telekom Chooses RISE with SAP in Cloud Transformation</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced that Deutsche Telekom, one of the world’s leading integrated telecommunications companies, has chosen the RISE with SAP solution to accelerate its journey to the cloud.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="rise-with-sap-improve-compliance-and-build-business-resilience-in-a-managed-cloud-offering">RISE with SAP: Improve compliance and build business resilience in a managed cloud offering</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/rise.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Deutsche Telekom is the first enterprise to implement RISE with SAP through SAP’s recently expanded partnership with <a href="https://www.telekom.com/en/media/media-information/archive/tsi-announces-expanded-partnership-with-sap-1057448">T-Systems as a premium supplier of RISE with SAP</a>, marking a significant milestone in the relationship between SAP and Deutsche Telekom.</p>
  <p>As Europe’s largest telecommunications provider, with more than 252 million mobile customers, 25 million fixed-network lines and 22 million broadband lines, Deutsche Telekom operates in more than 50 countries. Aligned with the company’s vision to be the leading digital telecommunications provider in the world, Deutsche Telekom has chosen RISE with SAP to transform a major part of its ERP landscape to SAP S/4HANA Cloud. As a premium supplier of RISE with SAP, T-Systems will migrate, consolidate and manage more than 300 systems into the public and private cloud using T-Systems’ Future Cloud Infrastructure (FCI) and select hyperscalers. This is designed to enable customers to meet all German and European data protection requirements, as well as to benefit from tailored migration and orchestration of complex landscapes.</p>
  <p>Peter Leukert, chief information officer of Deutsche Telekom, said, “SAP is a trusted and important partner for Deutsche Telekom in both reliably running core business processes and accelerating innovation in the cloud. Through RISE with SAP, we can drive business transformation and take our partnership to new heights. With SAP S/4HANA Cloud, Deutsche Telekom will be able to drive efficiency across key business functions such as logistics, procurement and finance.”</p>
  <p>“Deutsche Telekom’s decision to select RISE with SAP to migrate and streamline more than 300 of their systems to the cloud marks an important milestone in their business transformation and continues a long history of our two companies innovating together for our customers,” said Scott Russell, member of the executive board of SAP SE, customer success. “This investment by Deutsche Telekom will give them new capabilities, drive greater efficiencies, and allow them to access key insights from across their enterprise so they can adjust to changing market conditions and seize new opportunities faster than they could before. We look forward to supporting Deutsche Telekom in this exciting new era of their cloud transformation.”</p>
  <p>As a premium supplier of RISE with SAP, T-Systems offers “<a href="https://www.t-systems.com/us/en/application-services/solutions/sap-solutions/rise-with-sap">Thrive with T-Systems</a>,” a collection of end-to-end transformation services that includes consulting, migration, implementation and operation of RISE with SAP and support for RISE with SAP S/4HANA Cloud Private Edition.</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>About SAP</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP’s strategy is to help every business run as an intelligent, sustainable enterprise. As a market leader in enterprise application software, we help companies of all sizes and in all industries run at their best: SAP customers generate 87% of total global commerce. Our machine learning, Internet of Things (IoT), and advanced analytics technologies help turn customers’ businesses into intelligent enterprises. SAP helps give people and organizations deep business insight and fosters collaboration that helps them stay ahead of their competition. We simplify technology for companies so they can consume our software the way they want – without disruption. Our end-to-end suite of applications and services enables business and public customers across 26 industries globally to operate profitably, adapt continuously, and make a difference. With a global network of customers, partners, employees, and thought leaders, SAP helps the world run better and improve people’s lives. For more information, visit <a href="http://www.sap.com">www.sap.com</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Note to editors:</strong><br>To preview and download broadcast-standard stock footage and press photos digitally, please visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/photos">www.sap.com/photos</a>. On this platform, you can find high resolution material for your media channels.</p>
  <p><strong>For customers interested in learning more about SAP products:</strong><br>Global Customer Center: +49 180 534-34-24<br>United States Only: 1 (800) 872-1SAP (1-800-872-1727)</p>
  <p><strong>For more information, press only:</strong><br>Lesa Plingen, +49 622 776 9000, <a href="mailto:lesa.plingen@sap.com">lesa.plingen@sap.com</a>, CET<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>This document contains forward-looking statements, which are predictions, projections, or other statements about future events. These statements are based on current expectations, forecasts, and assumptions that are subject to risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results and outcomes to materially differ. Additional information regarding these risks and uncertainties may be found in our filings with the Securities and Exchange Commission, including but not limited to the risk factors section of SAP’s 2023 Annual Report on Form 20-F.<br>© 2024 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.<br>Please consider our <a href="https://www.sap.com/corporate/en/legal/privacy.html">privacy policy</a>. If you received this press release in your e-mail and you wish to unsubscribe to our mailing list please contact <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a> and write Unsubscribe in the subject line.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/enterprise-resource-planning</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
            <category>industry/telecommunications</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[From CSRD Reporting to Sustainable Business Outcomes]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/from-csrd-reporting-to-sustainable-business-outcomes</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/from-csrd-reporting-to-sustainable-business-outcomes</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[By leveraging SAP Sustainability solutions, organizations can move beyond compliance, like CSRD reporting, and operationalize sustainability.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/compliance</category>
            <category>news-tag/esg</category>
            <category>news-tag/green-ledger</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-data-exchange</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-footprint-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-sustainability-solutions</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Offers Professionals New Digital Learning and Certification]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/sap-offers-professionals-new-digital-learning-certification</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/sap-offers-professionals-new-digital-learning-certification</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New digital learning and certification from SAP are helping to meet the dramatically growing demand for skilled IT professionals. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15c26622362450c1931dc209600aa9d2d067dc3ff.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15c26622362450c1931dc209600aa9d2d067dc3ff.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_15c26622362450c1931dc209600aa9d2d067dc3ff.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Offers Professionals New Digital Learning and Certification" src="./media_15c26622362450c1931dc209600aa9d2d067dc3ff.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-offers-professionals-new-digital-learning-and-certification">SAP Offers Professionals New Digital Learning and Certification</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced the launch of a new guided premium learning offering with SAP Learning Hub and an enhanced certification program including a new role-based certification for SAP S/4HANA Cloud implementation consultants.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The demand for skilled IT professionals is expected to grow dramatically – up 23% by 2031 in the United States alone, according to the U.S. Department of Labor. To help meet this demand, the <a href="https://learning.sap.com/certifications/sap-certified-associate-implementation-consultant-sap-s-4hana-cloud-public-edition?url_id=text-sapnewscenter-prdteng">new role-based certification for implementation consultants of SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition</a> <a href="">emphasizes</a> core skills and competencies that can be applied across various cloud solutions from SAP and related versions.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="grow-your-skills-future-proof-your-career-learn-sap-for-free-anywhere-anytime">Grow your skills. Future proof your career. Learn SAP for free, anywhere, anytime.</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://learning.sap.com/">Start now</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“The pace of change and the talent shortage call for a new approach to identifying future-focused skills and roles. Instead of focusing on traditional aspects like degrees, job histories and titles, professional competencies become more important,” says Andre Bechtold, senior vice president and head of solution and innovation experience at SAP. “By transitioning to role-based certifications that focus on core skills and competencies, the skillset of a learner becomes more valuable and gains sustainability and more relevance for longer periods of time.”</p>
  <p>Many organizations rely on SAP solutions and skilled professionals to ensure a smooth and fast transition and drive business success. The enhanced SAP Learning Hub provides access to great content and includes four certification attempts per learner per year. Subscribers can receive expert guidance in digital live sessions, on-demand hands-on practice systems, advanced analytics and learning management functionalities. This new digital premium offering marks a major step in the evolution of the SAP Learning portfolio. To meet the rapid pace of technological innovation and the need to quickly gain new and future-proof skills, SAP continues to help organizations learn and become certified faster to maximize their investment.</p>
  <p>With the need for fast, comprehensive and role-based upskilling, the new certification model will make continuous learning and assessments a priority. Starting in early second quarter, these changes will support customers, partners and individuals in gaining skills across the SAP solutions portfolio and keeping them up to date.</p>
  <p><a href="/">Partners can benefit from further advancements</a>, including a tailored partner experience with curated learning journeys, exclusive access to events and subject matter experts. A subscription to SAP Learning Hub, <a href="">partner</a> edition comes with a significantly reduced price per user per year and offers additional chances to earn certifications, as well as improved analysis and tracking features.</p>
  <p>With the move to the cloud in full swing, the enhanced SAP Learning Hub and new certification program help customers and partners meet the challenges of a tight labor market and necessary workforce transformation. Learn more about <a href="https://www.sap.com/training-certification/learning-hub.html?sort=latest_desc">SAP Learning Hub</a> and the <a href="https://learning.sap.com/staying-certified">new certification program</a>.</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="http://news.sap.com/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Media Contact:</strong><br>Martin Gwisdalla, +49 6227 7-67275, <a href="mailto:martin.gwisdalla@sap.com">martin.gwisdalla@sap.com</a>, ET<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>This document contains forward-looking statements, which are predictions, projections, or other statements about future events. These statements are based on current expectations, forecasts, and assumptions that are subject to risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results and outcomes to materially differ. Additional information regarding these risks and uncertainties may be found in our filings with the Securities and Exchange Commission, including but not limited to the risk factors section of SAP’s 2022 Annual Report on Form 20-F.<br>© 2024 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>product/sap-learning-hub</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Grow with the Latest SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition 2402 Update]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/sap-s4hana-cloud-public-edition-2402-update</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/sap-s4hana-cloud-public-edition-2402-update</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With the SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition 2402 update, we are bringing a new round of exciting innovations. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/enterprise-resource-planning</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>product/sap-intelligent-rpa</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/ux</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Accelerate Innovation with a Clean Core Strategy]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/accelerate-innovation-with-clean-core-strategy</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/accelerate-innovation-with-clean-core-strategy</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With a clean core strategy for business tech, you can stay focused on what matters most to your business. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hunkemöller Finds Perfect Fit with RISE with SAP]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/hunkemoeller-perfect-fit-rise-with-sap</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/hunkemoeller-perfect-fit-rise-with-sap</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Hunkemöller has tapped RISE with SAP to move to the cloud and offer customers personalized experiences while keeping up with strong demand.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1babc3b4bba211bb8b678216b0fff7e19a9d7ad3b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1babc3b4bba211bb8b678216b0fff7e19a9d7ad3b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1babc3b4bba211bb8b678216b0fff7e19a9d7ad3b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Hunkemöller Finds Perfect Fit with RISE with SAP" src="./media_1babc3b4bba211bb8b678216b0fff7e19a9d7ad3b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="hunkemöller-finds-perfect-fit-with-rise-with-sap">Hunkemöller Finds Perfect Fit with RISE with SAP</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced that Hunkemöller International B.V., Europe’s fastest-growing lingerie brand, has moved to the cloud, leveraging the RISE with SAP solution to offer customers personalized experiences and to keep up with strong demand.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>With more than 850 retail stores and 15 online stores across 23 countries, Hunkemöller needed a technology infrastructure that could scale and keep up with the brand’s growth. Moving from an on-premise system to the SAP S/4HANA Cloud Private Edition solution with Google Cloud marks the first milestone in Hunkemöller’s digital transformation journey to become a data-driven company.</p>
  <p>Hunkemöller has an omnichannel sales strategy, selling through its own shops and through wholesale and international franchises. Strong wholesale activities were one of the reasons the company looked to move to the cloud. Hunkemöller wanted a technology infrastructure that could offer flexibility, personalized insights into customers’ shopping behaviors and innovation to position itself for further growth.</p>
  <p>With SAP S/4HANA Cloud Private Edition, Hunkemöller is eyeing its next step in its digital transformation journey as it embarks on the implementation of the SAP S/4HANA solution for fashion and vertical business, a version of SAP S/4HANA optimized for the fashion industry. The solution will allow the company to manage its business, from design to wholesale and retail, all on one platform. This will enable Hunkemöller to deliver collections faster on its channels, optimize inventory and cost as well as increase margins.</p>
  <p>“About 75% of our customers are already a member of Hunkemöller,” said Gordon Smit, global IT director, Hunkemöller. “How great would it be if we could offer them an even more personalized experience, for example, by predicting when a customer wants to make a repeat purchase and being able to send the right offer at the right time? Thanks to our current efforts with RISE with SAP, we are ready for that next phase. This is going to be a game changer for our customer experience.”</p>
  <p>Achim Schneider, global head of industry business unit retail and wholesale distribution, SAP, said: “Having worked closely over the past few months and migrating from on-premise to cloud in 48 hours is testament to the strong collaboration that our teams have had. With RISE with SAP now implemented, Hunkemöller is ready to continue building on the strong growth momentum they’ve had, and I’m excited to see them setting new standards in the lingerie market.”</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="http://news.sap.com/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Media Contact:</strong><br>Lesa Plingen, +49 622-776-9000, <a href="mailto:lesa.plingen@sap.com">lesa.plingen@sap.com</a>, CET<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>This document contains forward-looking statements, which are predictions, projections, or other statements about future events. These statements are based on current expectations, forecasts, and assumptions that are subject to risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results and outcomes to materially differ. Additional information regarding these risks and uncertainties may be found in our filings with the Securities and Exchange Commission, including but not limited to the risk factors section of SAP’s 2022 Annual Report on Form 20-F.<br>© 2024 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>news-tag/google-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Navigating the Future: Your Guided Cloud Journey with SAP]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/navigating-the-future-guided-cloud-journey-with-sap</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/navigating-the-future-guided-cloud-journey-with-sap</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP offers several paths to migrate SAP ERP to the cloud, facilitating a smooth transition from mainstream maintenance to the cloud.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17bc841593a9fe4dfd5500e73f0477c8ca2379344.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17bc841593a9fe4dfd5500e73f0477c8ca2379344.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_17bc841593a9fe4dfd5500e73f0477c8ca2379344.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Navigating the Future: Your Guided Cloud Journey with SAP" src="./media_17bc841593a9fe4dfd5500e73f0477c8ca2379344.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="navigating-the-future-your-guided-cloud-journey-with-sap">Navigating the Future: Your Guided Cloud Journey with SAP</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Over the past decades, SAP has been continuously evolving and advancing in the <a href="/topics/erp">ERP</a> market with remarkable releases of flagship products. We are truly grateful that our valued customers and partners have been on this transformative journey with us.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="weve-come-a-long-way-together">We’ve Come a Long Way Together</h2>
  <p>As we deeply value your continuous success, it’s crucial to acknowledge that those currently operating on SAP ERP 6.0 will soon face the imminent end of mainstream maintenance provided by SAP. This is scheduled to take place in 2025, 2027, and 2030, depending on your SAP enhancement package. Without proactive measures following the end of mainstream maintenance, your ERP solution will not receive any further legal updates or support packages. Additionally, mission-critical support and service-level agreements for your ERP solution will be impacted.</p>
  <p>This is a pivotal moment, and you must start thinking about the trajectory of your ERP system. However, you do not need to worry about getting lost in the various options that lie upfront – SAP is here to empower you with adequate information and tailor-made business cases. We can help you make the decision and choose the path that suits you the best to support your future innovation and success.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="we-have-the-right-cloud-erp-for-you">We have the right cloud ERP for you</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp.html">Explore SAP solutions</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="explore-the-future-path-of-your-erp-with-sap">Explore the Future Path of Your ERP with SAP</h2>
  <p>As your trusted advisor on this evolution journey, we are pleased to present several paths for you to explore further:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>If you currently have no SAP enhancement package or SAP enhancement packages 1-5, you could extend your mainstream maintenance to 2027 by upgrading to SAP enhancement packages 6-8, which typically takes several months to complete. Please note that this path would still require a shift to SAP S/4HANA by 2027 or 2030.</li>
    <li>You might continue with your current system, venturing into customer-specific maintenance. However, this path will lead to limited support and potential costs associated with addressing new issues.</li>
    <li>You could initiate a migration to SAP S/4HANA with various transitioning paths available for you to choose, empowering you to:
      <ul>
        <li>Streamline your system by discarding unnecessary custom code, extensions, and workarounds.</li>
        <li>Boost productivity through more straightforward processes and a more intuitive user interface.</li>
        <li>Enhance user acceptance with easy-to-access help and content solutions exactly when they are needed.</li>
      </ul>
    </li>
    <li>Our top recommendation for you is to adopt <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/rise.html">RISE with SAP S/4HANA Cloud, private edition</a> to be able to enjoy multiple benefits of the latest innovation of SAP. This option can encompass all the advantages mentioned in the third option and also allows you to innovate using your data to solve business challenges with the use of generative AI.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>Embracing RISE with SAP S/4HANA Cloud, private edition can offer a multitude of benefits. Join the ranks of numerous companies across diverse sizes and industries by initiating your cloud transition today to help enhance the agility and resilience of your business.</p>
  <p>Take inspiration from B-ON’s success story, backed by SAP support. In just four months, it seamlessly migrated to its new ERP and CRM platform, resulting in an impressive 200% increase in production capacity and 100% financial visibility across subsidiary operations.</p>
  <p>As another example, after using SAP ERP Central Component 6.0 system for nearly two decades, Shanghai Clyde Bergemann Machinery encountered challenges such as operation complexity and high maintenance costs. Opting for RISE with SAP allowed SCB to improve its financial operations, with an 85% reduction in financial closing time and a 50% decrease in IT expenses.</p>
  <p>Discover the transformative power of RISE with SAP through our <a href="https://online.flippingbook.com/view/801524279/">customers’ success stories</a>, showcasing enhanced efficiency and innovation and paving the way for your own seamless transition.</p>
  <h2 id="navigate-to-the-future">Navigate to the Future</h2>
  <p><a href="/2023/10/cloud-offerings-accelerate-customer-innovation-rise-with-sap">Learn more</a> about adopting the latest cloud offering, RISE with SAP S/4HANA Cloud, private edition.</p>
  <p>The SAP Customer Evolution team is here to support you in your future transformation, helping you define and realize the next steps of your business and IT evolution so you can be well prepared for the upcoming opportunities. Enhance your digital transformation journey with the SAP Customer Evolution kit – a cost-free, quick, and efficient engagement model. Elevate your transition to the cloud through personalized, one-on-one sessions with dedicated SAP experts, leveraging powerful tools like SAP Readiness Check and Process Discovery.</p>
  <p><a href="https://webinars.sap.com/customer-evolution-kit/en/home">Register</a> today, and we look forward to unlocking the potential together with you!</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Thomas Bamberger is president of SAP Customer Evolution.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-us-on-linkedin">Connect with us on LinkedIn</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news">Follow SAP News</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Corvias Combines SAP S/4HANA Cloud and SAP BTP to Streamline Efficiency and Maximize Results]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/corvias-sap-streamline-efficiency-maximize-results</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/corvias-sap-streamline-efficiency-maximize-results</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Corvias selected SAP S/4HANA Cloud, private edition and SAP BTP to help modernize its business processes. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16b00da7ad89aecaccd983d3343285162838738c3.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16b00da7ad89aecaccd983d3343285162838738c3.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_16b00da7ad89aecaccd983d3343285162838738c3.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Corvias Combines SAP S/4HANA Cloud and SAP BTP to Streamline Efficiency and Maximize Results" src="./media_16b00da7ad89aecaccd983d3343285162838738c3.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="corvias-combines-sap-s4hana-cloud-and-sap-btp-to-streamline-efficiency-and-maximize-results">Corvias Combines SAP S/4HANA Cloud and SAP BTP to Streamline Efficiency and Maximize Results</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><a href="https://www.corvias.com/">Corvias</a> is known for its unwavering commitment to addressing critical infrastructure challenges. The company’s work isn’t merely about providing housing or energy – it’s about enhancing quality of life and promoting collaboration within communities.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>This vision is underpinned by concrete plans that will help turn it into a reality. That’s why Corvias recently began modernizing its business processes for the future. Together with <a href="https://www.avvale.com">Avvale</a>, the company embarked on a journey that led to the adoption of SAP S/4HANA Cloud, private edition and SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP).</p>
  <h2 id="a-vision-for-optimization">A Vision for Optimization</h2>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15c36d38c8030e9f6e88a0cf9cdb1cdba127470ce.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15c36d38c8030e9f6e88a0cf9cdb1cdba127470ce.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_15c36d38c8030e9f6e88a0cf9cdb1cdba127470ce.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Row of houses. Photo courtesy of Corvias" src="./media_15c36d38c8030e9f6e88a0cf9cdb1cdba127470ce.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="600" height="400">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>Photo courtesy of Corvias</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Before choosing SAP, Corvias was grappling with a complex organizational structure, one characterized by disconnected systems and processes across accounting and purchasing. The allocation process was cumbersome and required redundant updates in multiple parts of the system, causing administrative headaches.</p>
  <p>Executive leadership quickly identified the need to simplify workflows so that they could deliver information to the right stakeholders effectively and quickly and create an integrated system that could move data seamlessly between processes without human intervention.</p>
  <h2 id="choosing-sap-for-success">Choosing SAP for Success</h2>
  <p>To help overcome its challenges, Corvias selected two primary SAP solutions: <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/s4hana-private-edition.html">SAP S/4HANA Cloud, private edition</a> and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform.html">SAP BTP</a>. With them, Corvias hoped to primarily centralize its data, enabling integrated purchasing and accounting capabilities. The implementation also leveraged SAP Fiori to help develop customized applications for allocating segment costs.</p>
  <p>Today, Corvias’ processes are simplified and streamlined, thanks to real-time, actionable information accessible by key members of leadership through SAP. This allows them to be more strategic in their decision-making with greater visibility into real costs and profitability at both the individual and project levels, contributing to a more efficient financial management system for the company overall.</p>
  <h2 id="far-reaching-benefits">Far-Reaching Benefits</h2>
  <p>The adoption of SAP has empowered the company to concentrate on enhancing its working capital through ongoing improvements. This has fostered a culture of innovation and encouraged a proactive approach to operational challenges and enhancements within the organization.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-tailored-to-fit-cloud-erp-that-adapts-to-your-organizations-unique-transformation">Get tailored-to-fit cloud ERP that adapts to your organization’s unique transformation</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/s4hana-private-edition.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In accounts payable, for instance, the implementation of automated purchase order management processes has resulted in a notable decrease in touch points. The accounts payable team has seen a reduction from seven to two touch points in 75% of cases. This not only enhances efficiency but reduces the likelihood that errors will occur as often as they would with manual processes. The streamlined purchase-order management system has become a valuable asset in optimizing the company’s financial workflow.</p>
  <p>Corvias has also embraced a more unified and secure information management system. By standardizing data security roles throughout the entire organization, SAP provided a reliable and protected method for managing information. This consistency has made it easier for site teams to handle administrative tasks, freeing up their time to focus on more strategic initiatives.</p>
  <p>Best of all, these SAP solutions provided a flexible and scalable platform that allows Corvias to seamlessly incorporate acquired or new companies.</p>
  <h2 id="looking-ahead-to-the-future">Looking Ahead to the Future</h2>
  <p>Corvias’ journey with SAP and Avvale showcases the transformative power of streamlined systems and integrated solutions. By addressing the challenges of a complex organizational structure and disparate workflows, Corvias not only achieved operational efficiency but also laid the groundwork for future scalability. The collaboration with Avvale unlocked expert guidance and support throughout the process, highlighting the importance of strategic partnerships in navigating the evolving landscape of technology integration.</p>
  <p>Today, as Corvias continues to oversee diverse projects in partnership with the military, higher education institutions, and communities, the adoption of SAP stands as a testament to the company’s commitment to innovation and excellence across all its mission-critical endeavors.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Mike Kaszuk is SVP and COO for Midmarket at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/sme</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>industry/mining: industry/mill-products</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Beyond Gravity’s All-Out Mission to the Cloud]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/beyond-gravity-all-out-mission-to-cloud</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/beyond-gravity-all-out-mission-to-cloud</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Beyond Gravity wants its new ERP system to leverage all the benefits of the cloud. That’s why it chose SAP S/4HANA Cloud, public edition.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_113a605ea1984c28f221f383c1bceeb834e36b214.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_113a605ea1984c28f221f383c1bceeb834e36b214.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_113a605ea1984c28f221f383c1bceeb834e36b214.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Beyond Gravity’s All-Out Mission to the Cloud" src="./media_113a605ea1984c28f221f383c1bceeb834e36b214.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="beyond-gravitys-all-out-mission-to-the-cloud">Beyond Gravity’s All-Out Mission to the Cloud</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>As it seeks to modernize its software environment, Beyond Gravity wants to take full advantage of the cloud. That’s why this leading supplier to the space industry is on an all-out mission to move its enterprise resource planning (ERP) system to SAP S/4HANA Cloud, public edition.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>While catastrophic asteroid impacts have been rare in Earth’s history, the threat asteroids pose to life on our planet is very real. With that in mind, NASA and ESA launched a mission in 2021 to test a method of planetary defense that involved deflecting Dimorphos – one part of the Didymos double-asteroid system – from its orbit by crashing a spacecraft into it. In part two of the mission, due to begin in October 2024, an orbiter known as “Hera” will lift off and, in October 2026, begin examining the effects of the test on Dimorphos.</p>
  <h2 id="beyond-gravity-space-technology-that-protects-the-planet">Beyond Gravity: Space Technology That Protects the Planet</h2>
  <p>“Protecting Earth from asteroids that could pose a threat to us all is an exciting and important task,” says Johan Eckerstein, CIO at <a href="https://www.beyondgravity.com/en">Beyond Gravity</a>. Headquartered in Switzerland, Beyond Gravity is one of a group of suppliers of high-tech equipment for Hera and is responsible for delivering the spacecraft’s two solar wings. In addition to a variety of satellite components, the space technology specialist also builds launch vehicles, and a third, smaller division serves the growing lithography market. According to <a href="https://tracxn.com/d/companies/beyond-gravity/__QK2dffK8fa4oRH-CPhnHBwvcMXuZWSoULX-BlkhJ9pg">market intelligence platform Tracxn</a>, Beyond Gravity ranks third among 21 competitors in its field.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_108755bdc5e12d7d14543f48c7855cb4f4c61bb27.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_108755bdc5e12d7d14543f48c7855cb4f4c61bb27.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_108755bdc5e12d7d14543f48c7855cb4f4c61bb27.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_108755bdc5e12d7d14543f48c7855cb4f4c61bb27.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="742">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>Image courtesy of Beyond Gravity.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14b0ad30a9b8b56ddb5fda4631cadf07d864b5982.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14b0ad30a9b8b56ddb5fda4631cadf07d864b5982.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_14b0ad30a9b8b56ddb5fda4631cadf07d864b5982.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_14b0ad30a9b8b56ddb5fda4631cadf07d864b5982.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="681">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>Johan Eckerstein. Image courtesy of Beyond Gravity.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="ezyone-transformation-project-flight-path-to-the-future">EZYOne Transformation Project: Flight Path to the Future</h2>
  <p>“Our ambition is to be the No. 1 space technology supplier, the most innovative and most exciting company to work for,” says Eckerstein. As CIO, his job is to put the technology in place to make that vision a reality. The EZYOne program he initiated in October 2022 was a crucial first step in that process.</p>
  <p>Beyond Gravity is the legal successor to RUAG Space, the space division of Swiss technology group RUAG International. So while it only began operating as a startup under its new name in May 2022, it has decades of experience in the space industry. With the company due to be privatized soon, its EZYOne digital transformation project is as necessary as it is challenging.</p>
  <p>As the name implies, the idea is to make things easier. Beyond Gravity has historically grown from various companies and locations. Currently, there are various sites with different IT systems that are not linked to each other.</p>
  <p>With EZYOne, Beyond Gravity is preparing to become a digital-first company that will leverage artificial intelligence (AI), machine learning, augmented reality (AR), and many other emerging technologies. The first step is to build a common digital core that will enable the company to unlock tremendous value and new ways to serve customers.</p>
  <h2 id="sap-s4hana-cloud-public-edition-seven-becomes-one">SAP S/4HANA Cloud, Public Edition: Seven Becomes One</h2>
  <p>Each of Beyond Gravity’s business divisions has built up its own vast pool of expertise over the years. But when it comes to IT, the company’s colorful history means it now has a mishmash of legacy systems – comprising seven different ERP systems alone – and, thus, an array of complex, inefficient, and costly processes.</p>
  <h2 id="it-solutions-in-use-at-beyond-gravity-in-2023">IT solutions in use at Beyond Gravity in 2023</h2>
  <ul>
    <li>7 ERP systems</li>
    <li>8 product lifecycle management (PLM) systems</li>
    <li>5 business process management systems</li>
    <li>2 manufacturing execution systems (MES)</li>
  </ul>
  <p>EZYOne lifted off in October 2022. “We began by defining the architecture we wanted for our new IT landscape,” explains Eckerstein. That process led to a number of design principles aimed at ensuring the project was a success. They included:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>One solution of each type for all business units</li>
    <li>Cloud first</li>
    <li>Standard first (out of the box)</li>
    <li>No technical data in the ERP system</li>
    <li>Rapid go-live in the first quarter of 2024</li>
  </ul>
  <p>When it came to selecting an ERP solution – and based on these criteria – Beyond Gravity opted for SAP S/4HANA Cloud, public edition. “From the perspective of an agile startup and the global market leader we aspire to become, cloud is the only way to go,” says Eckerstein. “When you choose a cloud solution, you are committing more to a provider’s road map than to a static product. And, as a midsize company, we can benefit from a vendor like SAP that has the infrastructure and resources to provide the solution reliably and securely.” This, he adds, eases the pressure on IT teams and frees up time for value-adding tasks.</p>
  <h2 id="standard-covers-92-of-processes">Standard Covers 92% of Processes</h2>
  <p>Eckerstein points out, however, that if you want to enjoy the benefits of the public cloud, you have to be consistent in your approach. Essentially, when you transform business processes, that means sticking as far as possible to the standard version of the public cloud solution. Beyond Gravity defined the following rules:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>80% of processes must be covered by the standard – and adapted to it if necessary.</li>
    <li>Key processes not covered by the standard must be added to SAP’s to-do list and implemented within a specified time frame.</li>
    <li>Where non-key processes are not covered by the standard, alternatives must be explored, such as a third-party solution, manual process, or other neat solution.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>The result of this approach surprised even Eckerstein: “We managed to cover 92% of all processes with the standard solution. And in finance, we didn’t find a single gap!” There were many other practical benefits, such as:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Managers can be able to call up a status overview of all projects in real time – for any country or currency – with just a few clicks.</li>
    <li>Intracompany processes can become more efficient, thanks to the option of using fully automated ordering and confirmation and in-transit goods tracking.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>The percentage of processes not covered by the standard may be small, but it can represent a huge gap if even one of those processes is mission-critical.</p>
  <p>Beyond Gravity has also got SAP – SAP Switzerland, to be precise – on board as an implementation partner to give it the most direct line possible to the SAP developers working on the cloud ERP solution.</p>
  <h2 id="public-cloud-erp-a-calculated-risk">Public Cloud ERP: A Calculated Risk</h2>
  <p>Beyond Gravity is now halfway along the project timeline. The solution was completed in September 2023 and is currently in its initial testing phase – with the first go-live scheduled for March 2024 in Sweden. “This kind of speed is only possible in the public cloud,” says Eckerstein, “and only if you adopt the right mindset.” In other words, if you want to enjoy the benefits of the public cloud, you have to be willing to take a certain amount of risk that you would avoid with an on-premise installation and trust that the provider’s road map will take you where you want to go. But, as Eckerstein adds, “This has nothing to do with blind trust; it’s about objectively calculating the risks involved.”</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Top image courtesy of SAP employee Trupti Warad</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/aerospace-defense</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP and the Mercedes-AMG PETRONAS F1 Team Join Forces to Drive Efficiency On and Off the Racetrack]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/sap-mercedes-amg-petronas-f1-team-join-forces-drive-efficiency</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/sap-mercedes-amg-petronas-f1-team-join-forces-drive-efficiency</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is proud to partner with the Mercedes-AMG PETRONAS F1 Team to make sure its operations are as fine-tuned as its cars. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>industry/automotive</category>
            <category>news-tag/mercedes</category>
            <category>product/sap-build</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-finance</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-sponsorships</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Power of SAP S/4HANA Cloud: Revolutionizing the Midmarket Banking Industry]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/sap-s4hana-cloud-revolutionizing-midmarket-banking-industry</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/sap-s4hana-cloud-revolutionizing-midmarket-banking-industry</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP S/4HANA Cloud helps revolutionize midmarket banking with tailored simplicity, scalability, and customer-centric innovation. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17356558432084b1ac6f3aff27227d6550342794a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17356558432084b1ac6f3aff27227d6550342794a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_17356558432084b1ac6f3aff27227d6550342794a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="The Power of SAP S/4HANA Cloud: Revolutionizing the Midmarket Banking Industry" src="./media_17356558432084b1ac6f3aff27227d6550342794a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="the-power-of-sap-s4hana-cloud-revolutionizing-the-midmarket-banking-industry">The Power of SAP S/4HANA Cloud: Revolutionizing the Midmarket Banking Industry</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>In the fast-paced world of the midmarket <a href="/topics/banking">banking</a> industry, finding the perfect technology partner is like discovering a gem amidst a sea of stones. It’s about harnessing the power of innovation, scalability, and tailored solutions to meet the ever-evolving needs of both customers and businesses.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Enter <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/grow/industry/banking.html">SAP S/4HANA Cloud</a>, a game changer for the midmarket banking industry. Let’s dive into how this solution can help banks aiming to skyrocket their growth and redefine the future of banking.</p>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14692ed3dc37fd427f9eb5a242dd341d3c1119167.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14692ed3dc37fd427f9eb5a242dd341d3c1119167.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_14692ed3dc37fd427f9eb5a242dd341d3c1119167.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Industry - Banking: Introduction" src="./media_14692ed3dc37fd427f9eb5a242dd341d3c1119167.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Q93o4YvvhjA">SAP Industry – Banking: Introduction</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="tailored-for-the-midmarket">Tailored for the Midmarket</h2>
  <p>SAP S/4HANA Cloud can address the unique challenges and aspirations of midmarket banks. With a laser focus on pre-built functionality and best practices, the solution is designed to fit seamlessly into the specific requirements of midsized financial institutions, helping to ensure a match that caters to their distinct operational demands and strategic visions.</p>
  <h2 id="unleashing-the-power-of-simplicity">Unleashing the Power of Simplicity</h2>
  <p>In the complex maze of banking operations, simplicity is the ultimate sophistication. SAP S/4HANA Cloud offers a user-friendly interface and streamlined processes that can simplify complex banking tasks, helping midmarket players to navigate with ease and efficiency. It’s about fostering a culture of simplicity that can amplify productivity and enhance the overall banking experience.</p>
  <h2 id="scalability-redefined">Scalability Redefined</h2>
  <p>For midmarket banks aiming to scale their operations and expand their market presence, SAP S/4HANA Cloud can serve as the ultimate growth catalyst. With its robust scalability features, the solution can empower banks to seamlessly adapt to evolving market dynamics, embrace new opportunities, and catapult their business to new heights without the fear of outgrowing their technological backbone.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="digital-transformation-is-paving-the-way-for-innovation-in-banking">Digital transformation is paving the way for innovation in banking</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/banking.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="customer-centric-innovation">Customer-Centric Innovation</h2>
  <p>In an era where the customer experience reigns supreme, SAP S/4HANA Cloud helps place the customer at the heart of every banking endeavor. From personalized banking services to real-time insights that can drive meaningful engagements, the solution can enable midmarket banks to create unforgettable customer journeys that can foster long-term relationships and trust, helping to set them apart in a competitive landscape.</p>
  <h2 id="security-fortified">Security Fortified</h2>
  <p>In the age of digital threats and cyber vulnerabilities, the security of financial data is non-negotiable. SAP S/4HANA Cloud comes fortified with robust security features that can safeguard sensitive information, helping ensure data integrity and compliance with regulatory standards. It’s like having an impenetrable fortress protecting the valuable assets and trust of both the bank and its customers.</p>
  <h2 id="embracing-future-ready-technology">Embracing Future-Ready Technology</h2>
  <p>SAP S/4HANA Cloud is not just about meeting the current industry standards; it’s about setting the stage for future innovation and technological advancements. With a forward-thinking approach and integration of cutting-edge technologies like generative artificial intelligence (AI) and data analytics, the solution can empower midmarket banks to stay ahead of the curve and help pave the way for a future-ready banking landscape.</p>
  <p>In conclusion, SAP S/4HANA Cloud stands out as a quintessential choice for the midmarket banking industry, offering a blend of customization, simplicity, scalability, customer-centric innovation, robust security, and future-ready technology. By embracing the power of SAP S/4HANA Cloud, midmarket banks can embark on a transformative journey that can propel their growth, amplify their customer relationships, and set them on a trajectory of unprecedented success in the dynamic world of modern banking.</p>
  <p>To learn more, please visit <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/grow/industry/banking.html">GROW with SAP page for Banking</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Falk Rieker is global head of IBU Banking at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/financial-management</category>
            <category>news-topic/sme</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/banking</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Western Sugar Cooperative Achieves Cost Optimization and Efficiency with SAP S/4HANA Cloud, Public Edition]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/western-sugar-cooperative-sap-s4hana-cloud-public-edition</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/western-sugar-cooperative-sap-s4hana-cloud-public-edition</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The adoption of SAP S/4HANA Cloud marked a significant moment in the technological transformation of Western Sugar Cooperative. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/sme</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/agribusiness</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Phoenix Global Enhances Operational Excellence via GROW with SAP]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/phoenix-global-enhances-operational-excellence-with-sap</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/phoenix-global-enhances-operational-excellence-with-sap</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Phoenix Global successfully implemented GROW with SAP to accelerate its journey to a unified, digitally integrated ERP system. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/sme</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/grow-with-sap</category>
            <category>industry/mining: industry/mill-products</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[North American Customers Continue Turning to SAP in Q3 2023]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/north-american-customers-q3-2023</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/north-american-customers-q3-2023</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In the Q3 2023, our North American customers spanned all shapes, sizes, and industries, proving the momentum behind the cloud revolution.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/grow-with-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>product/sap-datasphere</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-north-america</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Customers Realize the Power of Connected Cloud HR and ERP]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/sap-customers-realize-power-of-connected-cloud-hr-erp</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/sap-customers-realize-power-of-connected-cloud-hr-erp</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP customers connect SAP SuccessFactors solutions for HR with SAP S/4HANA Cloud to improve end-to-end business processes and experiences.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_12c8a896617a0e516f610561e9bf9c127d0a779ff.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_12c8a896617a0e516f610561e9bf9c127d0a779ff.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_12c8a896617a0e516f610561e9bf9c127d0a779ff.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Customers Realize the Power of Connected Cloud HR and ERP" src="./media_12c8a896617a0e516f610561e9bf9c127d0a779ff.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-customers-realize-the-power-of-connected-cloud-hr-and-erp">SAP Customers Realize the Power of Connected Cloud HR and ERP</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>SAP customers are unlocking strategic value across the organization by using a single cloud platform to connect HR, run on <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm.html?campaigncode=CRM-YI23-HXM-2053446&#x26;source=text-glo-SAPNews">SAP SuccessFactors</a> solutions, with finance and other business operations that use <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/s4hana.html?campaigncode=crm-ya22-int-1517075&#x26;source=ppc-de-google_ads-search-71700000111912410-58700008464076060-s4hana_s4fin-x-&#x26;dfa=1&#x26;gclid=EAIaIQobChMImKnKw_7tgQMV94ZoCR1j7QLcEAAYASAAEgJPEfD_BwE&#x26;gclsrc=aw.ds?campaigncode=CRM-YI23-HXM-2053446&#x26;source=text-glo-SAPNews">SAP S/4HANA Cloud</a>. In various industries, large and midsized organizations alike are discovering the power of having a common people and skills data model that is used across the entire organization. The combined effectiveness of SAP SuccessFactors solutions and SAP S/4HANA Cloud is moving leading brands to new levels of strategic insight and organizational agility.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>With this integrated approach, real-time people data from the SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central solution is automatically consumed by SAP S/4HANA Cloud and other SAP cloud applications. This “single source of truth” helps to improve end-to-end business processes, experiences, and insights for the organization. Learn more in this SAP Community <a href="https://blogs.sap.com/2023/08/07/sap-successfactors-and-sap-s-4hana-cloud-public-edition-supercharge-your-hr-and-erp-investments-now-on-demand/?campaigncode=CRM-YI23-HXM-2053446&#x26;source=text-glo-SAPNews">blog</a>.</p>
  <p>Maryann Abbajay, chief revenue officer at SAP SuccessFactors, spoke with some of these customers at <a href="https://www.sap.com/events/successconnect/virtual.html?campaigncode=CRM-YI23-HXM-2055448&#x26;source=text-glo-SAPNews?campaigncode=CRM-YI23-HXM-2053446&#x26;source=text-glo-SAPNews">SuccessConnect</a> to find out how they are leveraging the combined power of SAP SuccessFactors solutions and SAP S/4HANA Cloud to overcome business challenges and grow their organizations with people at the center of business. “These organizations show how HR and finance come together to enable business transformation while keeping employee experience at the center,” she underscored.</p>
  <h2 id="pandora-becomes-a-future-ready-organization">Pandora Becomes a Future-Ready Organization</h2>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="catch-up-on-this-years-event-with-successconnect-virtual-on-demand">Catch up on this year’s event with SuccessConnect Virtual on-demand</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/events/successconnect/virtual.html?campaigncode=CRM-YI23-HXM-2055448&#x26;source=text-glo-SAPNews?campaigncode=CRM-YI23-HXM-2053446&#x26;source=ctabutton-glo-SAPNews">Watch now</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Connecting people in the moments that matter is at the heart of <a href="https://us.pandora.net/">Pandora</a>, the world’s largest jewelry brand. Based in Copenhagen, Denmark, Pandora employs 32,000 people worldwide. With 6,500 points of sale, including 2,500 concept stores, Pandora depends on the experience of its brick-and-mortar stores, which account for the majority of its sales.</p>
  <p>Three years ago, Pandora began its transformation from an analog retailer to a future-ready organization. It set out to strengthen and harmonize the global HR system landscape with an implementation of SAP SuccessFactors solutions to gain efficiency in how the company hires, manages, and develops employees worldwide, thus replacing a multitude of local applications.</p>
  <p>“We used the SAP SuccessFactors portfolio as a driver of transformation,” said Mihael Šutalo, vice president of People Technology, Pandora. “This is transforming the experience. The future integration of SAP S/4HANA Cloud with SAP SuccessFactors solutions will give us a tremendous opportunity to manage our workforce and manage our revenue model in a completely different way.”</p>
  <h2 id="bt-group-connects-people-for-good">BT Group Connects People for Good</h2>
  <p><a href="https://www.bt.com/about">BT Group</a>, the world’s oldest telecommunications company, recently modernized its HR information systems to provide a digital colleague experience for its 100,000 employees working in 44 countries. “In 2021, we started what we call our I-Connect program,” said Elaine Bergin, director of Colleague Experience and Delivery, BT Group. The program name highlights BT Group’s purpose: “We connect for good.”</p>
  <p>The new colleague experience, launched in 2022, now uses the SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central solution, reporting and analytics, and the full suite of talent and learning management solutions to support the organization’s big focus on skills. BT Group also uses SAP SuccessFactors and SAP Fieldglass solutions to manage a contingent workforce of 60,000 additional employees.</p>
  <p>Bergin said, “Through our SAP SuccessFactors journey, we’re in a great place with a single master source of truth on our colleague and contingent workforce data – and our organizational hierarchy.”</p>
  <h2 id="brightspeed-manages-rapid-growth-and-contingent-workforce">Brightspeed Manages Rapid Growth and Contingent Workforce</h2>
  <p><a href="https://www.brightspeedplans.com/about">Brightspeed</a> is a telecommunications company that provides affordable, quality internet in rural areas of the U.S. Since it started in 2022 with 30 permanent employees, Brightspeed has grown exponentially through acquisition. Today, it has 4,200 employees using SAP solutions and a sizable contingent workforce. To manage growth, Brightspeed implemented SAP SuccessFactors solutions, SAP Fieldglass solutions, and SAP S/4HANA Cloud.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="predict-manage-and-create-a-future-ready-workforce-with-sap-successfactors">Predict, manage, and create a future-ready workforce with SAP SuccessFactors</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm.html?campaigncode=CRM-YI23-HXM-2053446&#x26;source=text-glo-SAPNews">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Greg Williams, director of Human Resources Information Systems, Brightspeed, summarized the value of an integrated approach for the organization: “Finance is up and running on SAP S/4HANA and with SAP Fieldglass solutions. We import that data into SAP SuccessFactors Learning, so our contractors can train on compliance and technical training. The SAP S/4HANA data is integrated into <a href="https://api.sap.com/package/SuccessFactorsEmployeeCentralwithThirdPartyTimeVendorWorkForceSoftwareWFS/overview">WFS</a>, which is our time system. We capture millions of dollars of project costs. Those are sent back to SAP S/4HANA on a pay-for-period basis.”</p>
  <h2 id="versuni-gains-agility-with-hxm-and-connected-cloud-erp">Versuni Gains Agility with HXM and Connected Cloud ERP</h2>
  <p><a href="https://www.versuni.com/">Versuni</a>, formerly known as Philipps Domestic Appliances, is a consumer products company with the purpose to help people turn their houses into homes. It took the unique opportunity of reinventing itself as an independent company to transform its entire technology landscape. To succeed in a dynamic, consumer marketplace, it had to adopt best-of-suite applications that power advanced, digital-first consumer goods organizations.</p>
  <p>By connecting SAP S/4HANA Cloud to SAP SuccessFactors solutions, Versuni has achieved three key benefits: a seamless user journey based on a single source of truth across the entire landscape; increased visibility achieved from the integration with other systems, especially finance; and improved reporting, which is leading to better decision-making. Lokesh Rastogi, IT platform leader for Finance and HR at Versuni, summarized: “It’s one source of truth, one system, and one number.”</p>
  <h2 id="nestlé-creates-engaging-people-experiences-at-scale">Nestlé Creates Engaging People Experiences at Scale</h2>
  <p><a href="https://www.nestle.com/">Nestlé</a>, one of the world’s largest food and beverage companies, is using RISE with SAP to help advance its digital transformation. With 275,000 employees in 188 countries, Nestlé focused on the modernization of its HR systems. SAP SuccessFactors solutions now enable it to standardize and automate HR processes and provide a personalized employee experience from recruitment to retirement. Nestlé plans to continue its journey to migrate its entire business operations to <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/s4hana-private-edition.html">SAP S/4HANA Cloud</a> with finance and procurement already live. To learn more, watch this <a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2023/09/5c433416-8d7e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html?campaigncode=CRM-YI23-HXM-2053446&#x26;source=text-glo-SAPNews">video</a>.</p>
  <p>Giancarlo Pala, head of IT/HR, Nestlé S.A., said, “SAP SuccessFactors is our people backbone. It provides the common processes, systems, and data that let us create engaging people experiences at scale.”</p>
  <h2 id="accelerating-business-performance">Accelerating Business Performance</h2>
  <p>SAP customers are experiencing firsthand the value of having HR and finance connected on a single cloud platform to help improve speed, accuracy, and insights. This integration can extend beyond the data to connect business processes and employee experiences across all business areas. To find out more about the benefits of connected cloud HR and ERP, watch <a href="https://www.sap.com/events/successconnect/virtual.html?campaigncode=CRM-YI23-HXM-2055448&#x26;source=text-glo-SAPNews?campaigncode=CRM-YI23-HXM-2053446&#x26;source=ctabutton-glo-SAPNews">SuccessConnect Virtual</a> on demand.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="follow-sap-news-on-linkedin">Follow SAP News on LinkedIn</h3>
        <p><em><a href="">Connect with us</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fieldglass</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-employee-central</category>
            <category>sap-event/successconnect</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Accelerating Sustainability Innovation in the Cloud]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/accelerating-sustainability-innovation-in-the-cloud</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/accelerating-sustainability-innovation-in-the-cloud</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With our cloud-driven innovations, we help customers build the foundation for the evolution of their long-term sustainability strategies.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/esg</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-footprint-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tata Projects Accelerates Its Future-Ready Pace with Cloud Solutions from SAP]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/tata-projects-rise-with-sap</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/tata-projects-rise-with-sap</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Tata Projects has tapped RISE with SAP to modernize its IT landscape and reach the strategic imperative of embracing cloud. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>