<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/sap-s-4hana-success-series/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Chevron Fueling Up for Cloud Future with SAP S/4HANA Transformation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/chevron-cloud-future-sap-s4hana-transformation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/chevron-cloud-future-sap-s4hana-transformation</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With SAP S/4HANA, leading multinational oil and gas company Chevron is transforming its digital core and position itself for the cloud future.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1625660b5cc902d86b849ca67d1f7cfd58e92c63b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1625660b5cc902d86b849ca67d1f7cfd58e92c63b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1625660b5cc902d86b849ca67d1f7cfd58e92c63b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Chevron Fueling Up for Cloud Future with SAP S/4HANA Transformation" src="./media_1625660b5cc902d86b849ca67d1f7cfd58e92c63b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="chevron-fueling-up-for-cloud-future-with-sap-s4hana-transformation">Chevron Fueling Up for Cloud Future with SAP S/4HANA Transformation</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>As a leading multinational oil and gas company Chevron is dedicated to building reliable, affordable, and ever-cleaner energy in all operations, including with subsidiaries.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>However, over time, it became clear that some of its complex legacy systems were not poised to meet the requisite challenges going forward, especially with SAP’s support for SAP ECC — an impactful solution in Chevron’s enterprise resource planning (ERP) portfolio — coming to an end in 2027. That’s why Chevron is now teaming up with SAP as a customer and co-innovation partner to transform its digital core and position itself for the cloud future.</p>
  <p>“Our motivation was clear: We are embracing a more reliable digital foundation that can enhance production efficiency and enable faster, more informed decisions,” said Michelle LaPoint, general manager of Enterprise Digital Delivery at Chevron. “We wanted up-to-the-minute, forward-looking, embedded analytics and the ability to simplify enterprise processes, automate where possible, and innovate around the digital core going into the future.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="test-drive-sap-s4hana-today">Test drive SAP S/4HANA today</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/s4hana-erp.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="designing-a-clean-digital-core">Designing a Clean Digital Core</h2>
  <p>Currently, Chevron operates on more than a dozen distinct ERP systems across its business segments. Given that complex landscape, and taking into account the varying processes across business units, standardizing business processes, data, and technology were top of mind for business and IT leadership.</p>
  <p>“For a large company like Chevron, transformation is a global, phased, multi-year journey,” said LaPoint. “We want one common platform with standard data and processes and now we’re well on the path toward that goal.”</p>
  <p>Historically, Chevron modified and customized its legacy systems to meet complex and varying global requirements. By transforming its digital core, the company is now working to position itself for whatever comes next, taking advantage of SAP’s standard cloud product to adopt new functionality as it becomes available in <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/s4hana-erp.html">SAP S/4HANA</a>. It is expected that this will enable Chevron to:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Increase overall speed and agility</li>
    <li>Decrease total cost of ownership of business solutions</li>
    <li>Drive greater digital innovation</li>
  </ul>
  <p>More so, through its co-innovation partnership with SAP, Chevron is working to position itself as a key player in what the “standard” product will look like in the months and years to come.</p>
  <h2 id="co-innovating-collaborating-communicating">Co-Innovating, Collaborating, Communicating</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="drive-game-changing-outcomes-and-become-an-experience-leader-via-unique-innovation">Drive game-changing outcomes and become an experience leader via unique innovation</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/services/innovation.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>For large customers, the standard functionality of SAP software may not perfectly line up with their sophisticated system needs and requirements. That’s where SAP’s co-innovation program comes into play. Partners like Chevron regularly connect with the SAP Services team to discuss their business needs and make their voices heard regarding the overall product road map going forward.</p>
  <p>“This is just an extension of working closely with SAP as a co-innovation partner,” said Rajesh Sahajwani, services partner at SAP. “We are the design authority. We create the way ‘standard’ runs. It’s important that we are in communication with our largest customers, so we can find gaps, feed information to our product teams, and strengthen our future product road map. Ultimately, it’s all about building a better product.”</p>
  <p>Chevron’s close collaboration with SAP in asset management is already delivering a reduction in future technical costs. This is made possible by Chevron’s strong governance efforts and positions the company as a unique SAP partner and customer going forward.</p>
  <p>In other words, this partnership is expected to keep each company from remaining stagnant on the path to the cloud, so that tomorrow’s Chevron — and tomorrow’s SAP — will be even better than today’s.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>The <a href="/topics/sap-s-4hana-success-series">SAP S/4HANA Success series</a> features content by leaders from SAP North America focused on highlighting customer success with SAP S/4HANA. Learn how customers in this region manage successful implementations with the partner ecosystem and SAP Services as well as leverage the platform to transform their industries.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Michael Mahoney is head of Services for SAP North America.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/enterprise-resource-planning</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s-4hana-success-series</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ecobat Engages RISE with SAP to Power the Circular Economy Forward]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/ecobat-rise-with-sap-circular-economy</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/ecobat-rise-with-sap-circular-economy</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[For Ecobat, the circular economy is inseparable from business. Moving to SAP S/4HANA Cloud will support its sustainability-focused mission.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_19fba871c92e6aa6391a86b7473a10ec3f84e5f3f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_19fba871c92e6aa6391a86b7473a10ec3f84e5f3f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_19fba871c92e6aa6391a86b7473a10ec3f84e5f3f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Ecobat Engages RISE with SAP to Power the Circular Economy Forward" src="./media_19fba871c92e6aa6391a86b7473a10ec3f84e5f3f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="ecobat-engages-rise-with-sap-to-power-the-circular-economy-forward">Ecobat Engages RISE with SAP to Power the Circular Economy Forward</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>If you’ve ever started your car only to find it sputtering, “it’s time for a new battery” is likely one of the first thoughts that crossed your mind. While you focus your attention on replacing the battery at a mechanic or an auto parts store, it’s easy to overlook an important detail that dominates conversations on sustainability today: what happens to the dead battery?</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>This question, which can be applied to a wide range of products, including plastics and metals, that are used to power and connect society, is at the heart of the <a href="/topics/circular-economy">circular economy</a>, a term to describe the concept of making growth and the recycling of finite resources interlocked.</p>
  <p>For <strong>Ecobat</strong>, the world’s leader in battery recycling and lead production, the circular economy is inseparable from its business, which focuses on the recovery and repurposing of more than 99% of the metal in many of the batteries companies and consumers use on a daily basis. Given the gravity of this initiative and the complex coordination required by the circular economy, Ecobat’s leaders know technology must be a part of this equation and have doubled down on investments in this area to achieve its mission of leading in the responsible collection, recycling, production, and distribution of resources essential to modern life.</p>
  <p>Ecobat CIO Jamie Lee has spearheaded these efforts. A recent example is that Ecobat signed a deal with SAP to engage the new <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/rise.html">RISE with SAP</a> offering to facilitate its move to SAP S/4HANA Cloud.</p>
  <p>We sat down virtually with Lee to learn how the world’s leading battery recycler is helping drive the circular economy and where cloud adoption will help the company move its sustainability-focused mission forward.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="rise-with-sap-transform-your-business-in-the-way-that-works-best-for-you">RISE with SAP: Transform your business in the way that works best for you</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/rise.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="a-driving-force-in-sustainability">A Driving Force in Sustainability</h2>
  <p>According to Lee, Ecobat takes a full-circle approach to recycling and repurposing materials that people use in their daily lives — from lead and other alloys to lithium and the plastics from which batteries are crafted. The company prides itself on meaningful manufacturing partnerships to get this done because it has a much bigger global purpose: transforming resources to power a more connected, sustainable world.</p>
  <p>It’s the company’s approach to innovation that has positioned Ecobat as a leader in circular economy conversations.</p>
  <p>“We either recycle, manufacture, or refurbish products and core materials that come from those batteries. Keeping them out of landfills is key because there are so many batteries in the world today,” Lee said. Using an example of battery manufacturers wanting to use lead, lithium, and plastics, Lee shared how that’s when consumers see the fruit of these efforts: from our devices, phones, and data centers to electric vehicles, stored, and mobile energy backup systems.</p>
  <p>“We believe we serve as a very important part of sustainability in this world,” Lee said. The numbers bear this out as well. Ecobat and other companies have noticed the immense importance and economic weight consumers are putting on sustainability in products.</p>
  <h2 id="sap-s4hana-is-helping-ecobat-grow">SAP S/4HANA Is Helping Ecobat Grow</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="test-drive-sap-s4hana-today">Test drive SAP S/4HANA today</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/s4hana-erp.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>With the company priding itself on its circular economy leadership, Lee shared that SAP S/4HANA Cloud will be an essential tool for its unique business to scale globally. As a manufacturing industry veteran, Lee has seen the negative outcomes that have occurred when peers did not proactively invest talent and resources into a technology strategy. In a world full of constant change, Lee points to these learnings and his extensive experience with the SAP ecosystem as the crucial factors behind Ecobat’s strategic investment in technology.</p>
  <p>With the help of SAP, Ecobat plans to connect its supply chain and customers so that the nature of what they recycle as a product aligns with a digital flow of data and information. “For us, SAP is less of ERP and more of an enterprise business platform. Leveraging SAP is where we will succeed,” he said.</p>
  <h2 id="rise-with-sap-comes-at-the-perfect-time">RISE with SAP Comes at the Perfect Time</h2>
  <p>As someone who has worked with SAP for decades, Lee was ecstatic when RISE with SAP was announced, calling it the very definition of customer empathy, especially for organizations — like those in manufacturing — that may not have been able to make years-long investments in technology. “It says: ‘Look, we understand you may not be able to take a generalized approach to the cloud, so we are going to invest in the right, customized approach adapted to your company to help get you there,’” Lee said.</p>
  <p>That help comes in the form of a support team, not just one salesperson leading the charge. “I’ve got a team,” Lee said. “I know the team members behind [the scenes]. They’re all active.” Indeed while the team structure is helping Ecobat put its plans into action, Lee was especially appreciative of having a single point of contact on the licensing side. “My hat is off to Christian Klein and SAP for the new licensing structure and the customer-centric branding behind RISE with SAP.”</p>
  <p>Looking forward, Lee is eager to incorporate SAP Analytics Cloud to help the company forecast and predict important supply chain trends and continue adapting the business to an ever-changing global economy. In the meantime, <a href="/topics/rise-with-sap">RISE with SAP</a> will enable Ecobat to develop innovative and sustainable products that meet the ever-growing need for more efficient, reliable energy storage solutions.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>The <a href="/topics/sap-s-4hana-success-series">SAP S/4HANA Success series</a> features content by leaders from SAP North America focused on highlighting customer success with SAP S/4HANA. Learn how customers in this region manage successful implementations with the partner ecosystem and SAP Services as well as leverage the platform to transform their industries.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>John Tully is senior vice president and managing director of the South Region for SAP North America.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/circular-economy</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s-4hana-success-series</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[RISE with SAP to Power Delek’s SAP S/4HANA Transformation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/delek-rise-with-sap-sap-s4hana-transformation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/delek-rise-with-sap-sap-s4hana-transformation</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[At Delek, technology — including RISE with SAP and SAP S/4HANA — will help position the company for future growth. Learn how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15d0dcd3a1d15d04bed4848a596bb2a6f0ac3f331.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15d0dcd3a1d15d04bed4848a596bb2a6f0ac3f331.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_15d0dcd3a1d15d04bed4848a596bb2a6f0ac3f331.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="RISE with SAP to Power Delek’s SAP S/4HANA Transformation" src="./media_15d0dcd3a1d15d04bed4848a596bb2a6f0ac3f331.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="rise-with-sap-to-power-deleks-sap-s4hana-transformation">RISE with SAP to Power Delek’s SAP S/4HANA Transformation</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>The energy industry is undergoing a massive transformation, one sparked by the <a href="/covid-19">COVID-19</a> pandemic and the shifting consumer behaviors and fluctuating world markets that have taken shape in its wake. Midsize North American energy operator Delek is tackling these changes head on — by placing technology at the heart of its corporate strategy.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In fact, the company has now reached a critical moment in its history of unprecedented growth, with over 300 stores and four refineries on the continent, in addition to the separate companies currently leading its logistics and innovation development.</p>
  <p>This made it a perfect time to sit down with Delek’s vice president of Enterprise Information Management, Nir Yatziv, to better understand how technology — and SAP S/4HANA — will help position the company for future growth.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="rise-with-sap-transform-your-business-in-the-way-that-works-best-for-you">RISE with SAP: Transform your business in the way that works best for you</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/rise.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="channeling-acquired-assets-into-a-single-source-of-truth">Channeling Acquired Assets Into a Single Source of Truth</h2>
  <p>Delek has been an SAP customer for more than 11 years, and made a series of strategic acquisitions in that time. While each addition has positioned the company to accelerate its growth, each acquired asset also came with a unique set of SAP systems and customizations. “Years of acquisitions had created a system with different standards and more than 6,000 objects to consolidate,” Yatziv explained.</p>
  <p>As a result, Delek’s strategy focuses on maximizing utilization and standardization to achieve new efficiencies across the organization. SAP S/4HANA quickly emerged as the solution of choice, as the refinery team felt it was the best solution presented and could handle such a large integration of systems.</p>
  <p>“All of the members of our team carry more than 30 years of SAP experience, and they very happy with what they were seeing with SAP S/4HANA,” Yatziv said. “When we compared SAP to the competition, it quickly became clear why SAP has succeeded in the energy sector: the industry speaks the language of SAP without even knowing it sometimes, something the competition couldn’t contend with.”</p>
  <p>SAP CEO Christian Klein’s <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/rise.html">RISE with SAP</a> announcement could not have come at a better time.</p>
  <h2 id="the-case-for-rise-with-sap-and-sap-s4hana-at-delek">The Case for RISE with SAP and SAP S/4HANA at Delek</h2>
  <p>As an SAP veteran, Yatziv evaluated the new RISE with SAP offering and immediately saw benefits, from simplifying the order processing process to better navigating complex implementation scenarios. However, making such a transformational change is not a trivial decision. So, why should an SAP customer make the move now?</p>
  <p>“Most companies that use SAP are large data companies, and SAP S/4HANA has an in-memory database that provides quick calculation capabilities,” Yatziv said. “SAP S/4HANA brings unparalleled ease of use, flexibility, and user experience.”</p>
  <h2 id="going-forward-the-importance-of-standardization">Going Forward: The Importance of Standardization</h2>
  <p>Today, Yatziv and his team are preparing for first phase of their SAP S/4HANA greenfield implementation, which is set to begin in July and continue through the end of 2021. The Delek team is itching to get started.</p>
  <p>“SAP best practices work,” Yatziv said. “Challenge yourself to be humble with your approach. We committed to achieving the standard, even though it meant changing our working processes. If your SAP system doesn’t match the way you work, check your processes. Because SAP best practices have been well-established – and have been proven to be highly successful.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>The <a href="/topics/sap-s-4hana-success-series">SAP S/4HANA Success series</a> features content by leaders from SAP North America focused on highlighting customer success with SAP S/4HANA. Learn how customers in this region manage successful implementations with the partner ecosystem and SAP Services as well as leverage the platform to transform their industries.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>John Tully is senior vice president and managing director of the South Region for SAP North America.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="test-drive-sap-s4hana-today">Test drive SAP S/4HANA today</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/s4hana-erp.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>industry/oil-gas-energy</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s-4hana-success-series</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[FMC Grows Its Strong Aspirations with SAP S/4HANA]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/fmc-aspirations-sap-s4hana</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/fmc-aspirations-sap-s4hana</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[For FMC, upgrading to SAP S/4HANA helped modernize a global landscape of IT systems and disparate business processes.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/accenture</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/enterprise-resource-planning</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s-4hana-success-series</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hasbro's Game-Winning Strategy with SAP S/4HANA]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/03/hasbro-sap-s4hana-game-winning-strategy</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/03/hasbro-sap-s4hana-game-winning-strategy</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Long-time SAP customer Hasbro moved to SAP S/4HANA to support its business and strategic growth plan. Learn more about the journey.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/enterprise-resource-planning</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s-4hana-success-series</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Merit Energy’s Culture Powers Seamless Integration]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/03/merit-energy-culture-powers-seamless-integration</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/03/merit-energy-culture-powers-seamless-integration</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[To seamlessly implement SAP S/4HANA, longtime customer Merit Energy leveraged SAP resources and a self-starter culture. Learn its story.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10428630c59ad3e501043cf783e8d7ce092640094.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10428630c59ad3e501043cf783e8d7ce092640094.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_10428630c59ad3e501043cf783e8d7ce092640094.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Merit Energy’s Culture Powers Seamless Integration" src="./media_10428630c59ad3e501043cf783e8d7ce092640094.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="merit-energys-culture-powers-seamless-integration">Merit Energy’s Culture Powers Seamless Integration</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Merit Energy is a leading energy company headquartered in Dallas, Texas, and much like the energy sector overall, is no stranger to the world of mergers and acquisitions (M&#x26;A).</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Frequently cited as a top workplace in local publications like the <a href="https://www.dallasnews.com/business/top-100/2020/11/12/meet-the-13-companies-that-have-made-the-top-100-places-to-work-list-nine-times-or-more/">Dallas Morning News</a>, Merit Energy has led more than 130 acquisitions since its founding in the 1990s – all aimed at helping it grow and guard against the short-term volatility that characterizes the industry as a whole.</p>
  <p>In a <a href="https://www.asug.com/insights/sap-north-america-president-dj-paoni-talks-rise-with-sap">recent discussion with ASUG News</a> about RISE with SAP, SAP North America President DJ Paoni characterized the Intelligent Enterprise as “an insurance policy against future disruption.” This is exactly the mindset Merit Energy, as a leading user of SAP S/4HANA, has adopted as a company.</p>
  <p>Russ Hulme, Financial Systems Manager at Merit Energy, recently joined <a href="https://event.on24.com/eventRegistration/EventLobbyServlet?target=reg20.jsp&#x26;partnerref=aefwd&#x26;eventid=2925378&#x26;sessionid=1&#x26;key=E5A7B8673DDDCB3D06AC3FB2932B3A9C&#x26;regTag=1915857&#x26;V2=false&#x26;sourcepage=register">SAP’s virtual roadshow series on RISE with SAP and SAP S/4HANA</a> to discuss why the energy leader has gone down the path of becoming an intelligent enterprise.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="test-drive-sap-s4hana-today">Test drive SAP S/4HANA today</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/s4hana-erp.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="sap-s4hana-movement-uncovers-business-case">SAP S/4HANA Movement Uncovers Business Case</h2>
  <p>Merit Energy has leveraged SAP solutions for more than 15 years, testing and implementing new enhancement packages as they were made available and being an early adopter for new releases. In 2019, Hulme and his team had to tackle a challenging strategic question: invest in five more years of on-premise hardware or start the move to SAP S/4HANA? To answer this question, they needed to be able to present a legitimate business case for choosing the latter option. This is where <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/s4hana-movement.html">SAP’s S/4HANA Movement program</a> entered the picture.</p>
  <p>“Within IT, we didn’t want to be the ones making the business case; we wanted to partner with our business to do so,” Hulme said. “This is where SAP S/4HANA Movement program proved pivotal. The SAP team engaged our business in a fact-finding mission that helped us have intentional conversations that got members of the Merit Energy business excited for the possibilities that SAP technology has to offer.”</p>
  <p>One of the business drivers that surfaced early in the process was the ability to collate, manage, and analyze the wealth of data that was being generated across Merit’s many IT systems resulting from years of acquisitions. “We had more than 130 different applications serving our organization,” Hulme said. “We quickly realized that SAP was the sun at the center of our universe that we could use to establish standardization.”</p>
  <h2 id="unique-self-starter-approach-to-implementation">Unique, Self-Starter Approach to Implementation</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-s4hana-success-nextier-is-energized-for-the-future">SAP S/4HANA Success: NexTier Is Energized for the Future</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/02/nextier-energized-future-sap-s4hana-success">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Most of Merit Energy’s corporate operations are in Dallas, which means that most, if not all, of its user base is together in one location. When you add that to the company’s “get stuff done” culture that prizes scrappiness, it became clear that the Merit Energy IT team had the resources and know-how to be able to manage the implementation of SAP S/4HANA 1909 in-house.</p>
  <p>While many customers see the flexibility and scalability of the enterprise resource planning (ERP) system as an opportunity to fully refresh IT strategies, the Merit team elected to instead make the platform complement its existing systems and felt a full IT reboot wasn’t needed. To support the move, Hulme’s team landed on a four-step, multi-phased approach to product implementation, starting with the initial system upgrade to SAP S/4HANA 1909, the latest version at the time, to “see what hypercare is needed.” Expanded user testing, third-party add-ons, and full-team user acceptance testing followed, resulting in a seamless implementation process in as little as 10 months.</p>
  <p>While the Merit Energy team prides itself on self-sufficiency, Hulme was quick to praise one resource offered by SAP in particular. “We saw immense value in engaging <a href="https://www.sap.com/services/implementation/implementation-pkg.html">SAP Value Assurance</a>,” he confirmed. “We considered them our ‘bat phone’ resource to help us get the job done right.”</p>
  <h2 id="lesson-learned-rethink-your-work-with-strategic-partners">Lesson Learned: Rethink Your Work with Strategic Partners</h2>
  <p>When asked what his top learnings from the project were, Hulme had two conclusions. First, in retrospect, Merit Energy would have started the SAP S/4HANA journey earlier given the immense value the team has seen from the ERP system to-date. Second — and his biggest advice for peers at other companies — is to get outside of thinking of SAP as an accounting program.</p>
  <p>“There are so many other efficiencies and innovations that are generated by the SAP ecosystem that it’s a mistake to only think in terms of ERP or finance,” Hulme said. “The quicker you adopt this mindset, the more results you will drive.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>The <a href="/topics/sap-s-4hana-success-series">SAP S/4HANA Success series</a> features content by leaders from SAP North America focused on highlighting customer success with SAP S/4HANA . Learn how customers in this region manage successful implementations with the partner ecosystem and SAP Services as well as leverage the platform to transform their industries.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>John Tully is senior vice president and managing director of the South Region for SAP North America.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s-4hana-success-series</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[NexTier Is Energized for the Future with SAP S/4HANA]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/nextier-energized-future-sap-s4hana-success</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/nextier-energized-future-sap-s4hana-success</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[As energy leader NexTier grows its busines, SAP S/4HANA Cloud has played a role in the process. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14da4737b611f1e50a10d612f5943f33beada5680.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14da4737b611f1e50a10d612f5943f33beada5680.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_14da4737b611f1e50a10d612f5943f33beada5680.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="NexTier Is Energized for the Future with SAP S/4HANA" src="./media_14da4737b611f1e50a10d612f5943f33beada5680.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="nextier-is-energized-for-the-future-with-sap-s4hana">NexTier Is Energized for the Future with SAP S/4HANA</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>As any company that is heavily involved in the world of mergers and acquisitions (M&#x26;A) knows, the integration of services, systems, and processes can be make or break. This was exactly the challenge—and opportunity—Umar Farooq, vice president of Information Technology at NexTier and one of the leading minds modernizing IT standards across the energy sector, faced as he took over the lead IT role upon the company’s 2019 formation.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>We recently sat down virtually with Farooq to discuss the strategy he’s been executing to grow the energy leader’s business since the merger as well as the role SAP S/4HANA Cloud has played in this process.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="test-drive-sap-s4hana-today">Test drive SAP S/4HANA today</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/s4hana-erp.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="merger-gives-rise-to-new-industry-leader">Merger Gives Rise to New Industry Leader</h2>
  <p>Houston-based well completion and production services company NexTier Oilfield Solutions has quickly become one of the leading providers of such services in the United States. However, in the grand scheme of things, it is still a relatively new company that emerged onto the global energy scene following a <a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/cj-energy-services-and-keane-complete-merger-of-equals-establishing-nextier-oilfield-solutions-a-leader-in-well-completion-and-production-services-300949064.html">2019 merger of long-time leaders Keane Group and C&#x26;J Services</a>. It was important for Farooq and his team to get some early momentum to ensure a strong footing for the company’s future. This is where NexTier’s digital transformation strategy would play a pivotal role, revolving around boosting operational efficiency wherever possible.</p>
  <p>Two examples include the company’s Equipment Health Monitoring and NexHub tools, which help them track activities on the rig site, granting teams a real-time view of operations that enables them to provide centralized monitoring, real-time reporting, and workflow automation—all advancements that are critical in the world of energy production.</p>
  <p>Specific to the merger, one of the biggest value drivers within NexTier’s digital transformation strategy—and one of Farooq’s top priorities—is to manage the technological integration of disparate systems resulting from the merger of two different companies so the team could take advantage of the massive scale, technical expertise, and resources the move opened for the company. Enter SAP S/4HANA.</p>
  <h2 id="sap-s4hana-emerges-as-an-ma-lever">SAP S/4HANA Emerges as an M&#x26;A Lever</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="rise-with-sap-explore-saps-newest-offering">RISE with SAP: Explore SAP's newest offering</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/rise.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>One beneficial feature of the merger was that SAP ERP was already in use at both companies, so SAP S/4HANA was a natural stepping-stone to help Farooq and his team redesign and simplify business processes. Add this to the oil and gas industry standards SAP has established with the help of leaders like NexTier, and SAP S/4HANA Cloud quickly helped the company unlock millions in merger synergies through reduced costs across IT.</p>
  <p>“SAP S/4HANA allowed us to build an ecosystem of tools that were fit for purpose and aligned with the business. In addition, it helped us reduce our run rate costs for the maintenance of an ERP application,” Farooq said.</p>
  <p>Since implementing the solution, NexTier’s team has seen significant improvements, including a smooth integration with a third-party solution for integrated field ticketing and customer invoicing, more efficient exchange of supply chain partner information, and greater operational and financial visibility thanks to improved data aided by spread-level profitability reporting and increased process discipline. In an industry where margins are everything, SAP S/4HANA has proved to be a valuable tool in Farooq’s overarching and industry-leading digital transformation strategy. But functionality wasn’t the only ingredient for success.</p>
  <h2 id="cios-secret-ingredient-familiarity-with-sap">CIO’s Secret Ingredient: Familiarity with SAP</h2>
  <p>Farooq has gathered many best practices throughout his extensive career, but one element of his background played a particularly important role in ensuring NexTier’s success with SAP S/4HANA Cloud. His first job out of college was with Nissan Motors, where he led the implementation of their SAP-powered vehicle management system.</p>
  <p>“This is where my current role as the leader of technology strategy at NexTier came full circle with the positive career experiences with SAP,” Farooq said. “SAP S/4HANA Cloud became a foundation for NexTier’s ERP system consolidation efforts, and it was thanks to early experiences with the world of SAP that the process has gone smoothly.”</p>
  <p>A certified video game tester and avid reader in his spare time, Farooq has seen tremendous success in his career of helping organizations solve large-scale challenges with technology. When asked what advice he’d give to other aspiring IT leaders, he responded, “The biggest mistake you can make is to shy away from taking calculated risks in your career. You never know when a role you maybe thought wouldn’t be the right fit or a project that you believed might be too challenging uncovers fruitful growth opportunities.”</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>The <strong><a href="/topics/sap-s-4hana-success-series">SAP S/4HANA Success series</a></strong> features content by leaders from SAP North America focused on highlighting customer success with SAP S/4HANA. Learn how customers in this region manage successful implementations with the partner ecosystem and SAP Services as well as leverage the software to transform their industries.</p>
        <p><em>John Tully is senior vice president and managing director of the South Region of SAP North America.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/enterprise-resource-planning</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s-4hana-success-series</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>