<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/premium-engagement/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Offers Maximum Attention for Customers’ High Standards]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/sap-offers-maximum-attention-for-customers-high-standards</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/sap-offers-maximum-attention-for-customers-high-standards</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Every customer has its own cloud strategies. That's why SAP MaxAttention prioritizes individualization within the customer's success plan.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/premium-engagement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-activeattention</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-erp</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-integrated-delivery-framework</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-maxattention</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-maxattention-summit</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How to Set the Course of Business Innovation with Intelligent ERP]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/set-course-of-business-innovation-with-intelligent-erp</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/set-course-of-business-innovation-with-intelligent-erp</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A cloud-based ERP helps organizations prioritize business innovation to keep up with market dynamics and workplace and customer expectations.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
            <category>news-tag/premium-engagement</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hyperscaling the Cloud: The Future of Digitalization Emerges from Premium Engagements]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/hyperscaling-the-cloud-premium-engagements</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/hyperscaling-the-cloud-premium-engagements</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Premium engagements help companies navigate the infrastructure, scale, security, and functionality of hyperscalers when moving to the cloud.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1dd2c32b428934735b8ac109b65f46aab0501d990.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1dd2c32b428934735b8ac109b65f46aab0501d990.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1dd2c32b428934735b8ac109b65f46aab0501d990.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Hyperscaling the Cloud: The Future of Digitalization Emerges from Premium Engagements" src="./media_1dd2c32b428934735b8ac109b65f46aab0501d990.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="hyperscaling-the-cloud-the-future-of-digitalization-emerges-from-premium-engagements">Hyperscaling the Cloud: The Future of Digitalization Emerges from Premium Engagements</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>As migration to the cloud becomes a critical part of business continuity, companies seek the infrastructure, scale, security, and functionality of hyperscalers to accelerate their move. But it’s a task that needs a plan extensive and forward-looking enough to reap the full value of the cloud.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Hyperscalers – such as Amazon Web Services, Google Cloud Platform, and Microsoft Azure – have become an answer to some of the most complex concerns over <a href="https://insights.sap.com/what-is-digital-transformation/">digital transformation</a>. Some organizations view it as an opportunity to keep up with the constant need to adopt new technologies and adapt to changing requirements. IT teams may feel relieved to have the right infrastructure and the capacity to enable every change. And, better yet, existing and new data, applications, and connections in between can remain secure and protected.</p>
  <p>Despite the advantages, decoupling the business from an on-premise approach to IT requires a line of thinking that includes considering:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>What are the company’s unique needs?</li>
    <li>How much support is needed from the hyperscaler platform?</li>
    <li>How can the business avoid being locked into one hyperscaler?</li>
    <li>Does the chosen hyperscaler reflect the true end-to-end nature of the existing IT landscape?</li>
    <li>How could revenue growth impact future architectural decisions and software investments?</li>
  </ul>
  <p>Reflecting on these questions requires a long-term view of the overall relationship with hyperscalers – even when running an SAP solution landscape in the cloud. Otherwise, companies risk introducing many points of failure that may limit the ability to scale the cloud architecture optimally. Or worse, they could miss opportunities to further leverage new database architecture and application capabilities in the cloud.</p>
  <h2 id="mitigating-risks-to-drive-cloud-scalability-and-elasticity">Mitigating Risks to Drive Cloud Scalability and Elasticity</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="test-drive-sap-s4hana-cloud">Test drive SAP S/4HANA Cloud</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/s4hana-erp/trial.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>For many of our customers, the portfolio of premium engagements from SAP helps crystallize their cloud strategy without getting sidetracked by perceived IT barriers and short-term thinking. Whether moving a legacy enterprise resource planning (ERP) system to SAP S/4HANA Cloud or a database to SAP HANA, our premium engagements can offer insights into unlocking the full potential of existing technology in the cloud.</p>
  <p>Recently, a customer wanted to move its 20-year-old instance of SAP ERP Central Component (SAP ECC) to SAP S/4HANA Cloud running on a hyperscaler platform. The CIO initially thought that our involvement was needed only to plan the physical aspects of a fast-paced cloud migration.</p>
  <p>Over time, he began to understand how everyday IT operations – including <a href="https://insights.sap.com/what-is-data-management/">data and database management</a> – could be optimized with an architectural strategy that supports future growth. Instead of viewing data management as a pure archiving activity, the CIO discovered data and database management in the cloud can reduce monthly capital and operational expenditures because the hyperscaler removed the need to support expensive hardware.</p>
  <p>In this case, the customer quickly realized that its cloud migration was more than the short-term move of data and applications. Premium engagements helped define the larger vision of the company’s digital transformation, weighing risks and exploring best practices for smooth integration of multiple SAP and third-party software-as-a-service (SaaS) and platform-as-a-service (PaaS) solutions.</p>
  <p>In return, a hyperscaler-supported cloud environment was set up to help provide simpler and more cost-efficient IT operations, increased capacity for innovation, and harmonized processes to boost the flexibility to adapt to changing business requirements.</p>
  <h2 id="creating-a-road-map-for-future-innovation-with-expert-insight">Creating a Road Map for Future Innovation with Expert Insight</h2>
  <p>Digital trends – for example, fast-paced application innovation and the explosion of enterprise data – present a wider need for the scalability and flexibility of cloud platforms. And SAP makes that option available to every customer by working with a variety of hyperscalers.</p>
  <p>But such a transition is not a simple switch from an on-premise landscape to the cloud. A strategic move to a hyperscaler environment requires the expertise and guidance of a software vendor that understands the current and future demands of a business’s technology.</p>
  <p>That’s the beauty of the portfolio of premium engagements from SAP. By tapping a unique knowledge base on how SAP applications can best run on a scalable and elastic cloud infrastructure-as-a-service (IaaS) platform, our customers can map their entire transformation journey while safeguarding the data and applications that drive their operations.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="receive-the-highest-level-of-collaboration-and-expertise-with-premium-engagements">Receive the highest level of collaboration and expertise with premium engagements</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/services/premium-engagement.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="learn-more-about-how-premium-engagements-from-sap-can-help-secure-your-business-success-with-the-highest-level-of-collaboration-and-expertise-on-cloud-technology">Learn more about how <a href="https://www.sap.com/services/premium-engagement.html">premium engagements from SAP</a> can help secure your business’ success with the highest level of collaboration and expertise on cloud technology.</h3>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Nicholas Del Grande is head of Premium Engagement Sales for North America at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/premium-engagement</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Expanded SAP Integrated Delivery Framework Makes the Journey to the Cloud Smoother Than Ever]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/expanded-integrated-delivery-framework-cloud-journey</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/expanded-integrated-delivery-framework-cloud-journey</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Integrated Delivery Framework is expanding to cover any implementation scenario: on-premise, RISE with SAP, cloud, or line-of-business.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16a1d2391be96b459bfa16d2f260245c9df839dc9.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16a1d2391be96b459bfa16d2f260245c9df839dc9.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_16a1d2391be96b459bfa16d2f260245c9df839dc9.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Expanded SAP Integrated Delivery Framework Makes the Journey to the Cloud Smoother Than Ever" src="./media_16a1d2391be96b459bfa16d2f260245c9df839dc9.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="expanded-sap-integrated-delivery-framework-makes-the-journey-to-the-cloud-smoother-than-ever">Expanded SAP Integrated Delivery Framework Makes the Journey to the Cloud Smoother Than Ever</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="faster-smoother-and-less-risky-go-lives-with-sap-integrated-delivery-framework">Faster, smoother, and less risky go-lives with SAP Integrated Delivery Framework</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2018/11/08f1c6fc-297d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>It’s a common problem in today’s complicated, high-speed work environments: everyone on a team is working on the same project, but not everyone is working <em>together</em>. This can result in delays, duplicated efforts, and missed deadlines.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>That’s why, in 2019, SAP introduced <a href="/2019/09/sap-integrated-delivery-framework-sap-s4hana-customers">SAP Integrated Delivery Framework</a>. This framework lays out roles and responsibilities for the customer, partner, and SAP in projects led by a partner. It’s not a product or a package of services; rather it’s an engagement model for joint partner projects. By creating a structure for SAP and partners to position their strengths to support implementations, the framework can accelerate joint engagements from sales through delivery.</p>
  <p>Since 2019, adoption of SAP Integrated Delivery Framework has grown tremendously. With over 70% growth and hundreds of projects in the first year since its launch, soon close to half of our premium engagement services will be delivered within the framework, which then will be central to our partner collaboration mode.</p>
  <p>Along the way, we’ve refined the framework to make it a complement to delivering success for our customers, by blending the skills of SAP Services with those of our delivery partners.</p>
  <p>SAP Integrated Delivery Framework works to fully address customer needs by integrating the partner’s and SAP’s solutions and services, building trust to help ensure the relationship between SAP Services and Support and the partner remains positive. It also helps to make sure SAP and partner expertise is leveraged at key points, from initial engagement to go-live. It is an umbrella framework for a variety of SAP services that remains flexible and scalable, continually evolving to meet customer and partner needs rather than enforcing a one-size-fits-all approach on customers. It can make it easier than ever for customers to move to the cloud or gain the benefits of business transformation as a service through RISE with SAP.</p>
  <p>Since 2019, SAP, partners, and customers have had some incredible outcomes thanks to the framework. But the world has changed a lot in just the last two years. In speaking with customers, SAP learned that an expansion of SAP Integrated Delivery Framework to cover cloud solutions would help customers achieve their business goals. Now, SAP is doing just that: expanding the framework to cover any SAP implementation scenario, including on-premise, RISE with SAP, cloud, or line-of-business solutions.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="rise-with-sap-simplify-the-transformation-of-your-business-for-the-digital-age">RISE with SAP: Simplify the transformation of your business for the digital age</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/rise.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>When the framework was first introduced two years ago, SAP included the RACI matrix, one of the essential pieces of the framework. As part of the expansion, an “S” is now being added to accommodate “who is supporting.” The new RASCI matrix provides a means of determining who is <strong>R</strong> esponsible, <strong>A</strong> ccountable, <strong>S</strong> upporting, <strong>C</strong> onsulted, and <strong>I</strong> nformed to help keep cloud implementations on schedule and moving smoothly between SAP, partners, and customers.</p>
  <p>SAP Integrated Delivery Framework can benefit all parties involved, but, most importantly, it can benefit customers. The clearly defined roles and responsibilities outlined in the framework and implemented with support from the RASCI matrix can reduce risk through clear accountability and governance. It provides an orientation for SAP, the partner, and the customer to agree on, helping to drive results and time-to-value. It can accelerate value realization through early engagement of a partner and SAP as well as helps enhance innovation by utilizing the best of each company’s solutions and services.</p>
  <p>Here’s one example: with the help of IBM, SAP worked with the ANTA Group to upgrade from its legacy applications to SAP S/4HANA. By implementing SAP S/4HANA, ANTA was able to reap the benefits of a smooth, secure move to a new intelligent enterprise resource planning (ERP) solution that could improve business processes and enable growth. In addition, ANTA enhanced some critical functionalities in the <a href="https://insights.sap.com/what-is-MRP/">material requirements planning (MRP)</a> calculation mechanism to fully meet new business requirements. “SAP Integrated Delivery Framework as part of SAP Value Assurance provided clearly defined roles and responsibilities that allowed our company, IBM, and SAP to efficiently collaborate and ensure a successful go-live of SAP S/4HANA,” says Donghai Chen, senior director, IT, ANTA Group.</p>
  <p>The expanded SAP Integrated Delivery Framework and RASCI matrix make it easier than ever for customers to solve their business challenges and reach their full potential by moving to the cloud with SAP and a trusted partner. Through the good governance and collaborative systems created through the framework, every customer, no matter where they are on their technology journey, can take advantage of SAP’s innovation by moving to the cloud, on time and with minimal risk.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Harald Martin is head of Services Partner Business Development for SAP Services at SAP SE.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/premium-engagement</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-integrated-delivery-framework</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>