<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/well-being-at-work/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Organizations Are Using SAP SuccessFactors Solutions to Prepare for What’s Next]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/organizations-using-sap-successfactors-2023-hr-meta-trends</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/organizations-using-sap-successfactors-2023-hr-meta-trends</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Organizations are using SAP SuccessFactors solutions to get ahead – and stay ahead – of the curve. Read about our 2023 HR meta-trends.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/mental-health-well-being</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-work-zone</category>
            <category>news-tag/well-being-at-work</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Drive Key Business Outcomes through People Sustainability]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/drive-key-business-outcomes-people-sustainability</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/drive-key-business-outcomes-people-sustainability</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[HR has both the opportunity and responsibility to ensure that people are at the center of work. Learn more about people sustainability.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/mental-health-well-being</category>
            <category>news-tag/people-sustainability</category>
            <category>news-tag/well-being-at-work</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Surprising Truth about Workers Who Can Be Productive Anywhere]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/surprising-truth-workers-productive-anywhere</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/surprising-truth-workers-productive-anywhere</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A study by Accenture identified valuable resources that enable employees in a hybrid workforce to be productive anywhere. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/accenture</category>
            <category>news-tag/covid-19</category>
            <category>news-tag/future-of-work</category>
            <category>news-tag/well-being-at-work</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Improve Employee Well-Being through Smarter Healthcare Spend]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/06/improve-employee-well-being-through-smarter-healthcare-spend</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/06/improve-employee-well-being-through-smarter-healthcare-spend</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Make the most of your benefits budget by proactively managing your healthcare spend with advanced analytics and modeling tools. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/healthcare</category>
            <category>news-tag/well-being-at-work</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Sanlam Developed a Diverse, Engaged, and Future-Ready Workforce]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/sanlam-diverse-engaged-future-ready-workforce</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/sanlam-diverse-engaged-future-ready-workforce</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Sanlam launched a HR shared services model using SAP solutions to embrace a total workforce management strategy. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/contingent-workforce-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>sap-award/sap-innovation-awards</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
            <category>news-tag/total-workforce-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/well-being-at-work</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Deloitte Is Beating Burnout at Scale]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/how-deloitte-is-beating-burnout-at-scale</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/how-deloitte-is-beating-burnout-at-scale</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In trying to address overwork issues before they impact mental health, professional services company Deloitte is a pioneer. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/deloitte</category>
            <category>news-tag/mental-health-well-being</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-original-series-forward</category>
            <category>news-tag/well-being-at-work</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Kaspersky Empowers Its People by Fostering a Listening Culture]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/kaspersky-empowers-its-people-by-fostering-listening-culture</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/kaspersky-empowers-its-people-by-fostering-listening-culture</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Understanding its employees is critical to everything Kaspersky does. The SAP Qualtrics Employee Experience solution helps do just that.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18117bf5d567c0ed4efe2af0e5c56aa850f825c0e.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18117bf5d567c0ed4efe2af0e5c56aa850f825c0e.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_18117bf5d567c0ed4efe2af0e5c56aa850f825c0e.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Kaspersky Empowers Its People by Fostering a Listening Culture" src="./media_18117bf5d567c0ed4efe2af0e5c56aa850f825c0e.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="kaspersky-empowers-its-people-by-fostering-a-listening-culture">Kaspersky Empowers Its People by Fostering a Listening Culture</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="kaspersky-building-a-better-workplace-centered-on-the-employee-experience">Kaspersky: Building a Better Workplace Centered on the Employee Experience</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2021/12/728bfa83-0a7e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Kaspersky is one of the world’s leading cybersecurity companies, and its innovative technologies protect businesses, industrial and critical infrastructure, and governments, as well as individual users across the globe. The company serves a single goal: to defend the digital world and make it safer for everyone.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The driving force of Kaspersky is its employees – the world-class professionals who research cyber-threats and create leading security technologies. The company relies on the knowledge and expertise of its employees, and therefore strives to provide an exceptional workplace experience for its people to attract and retain the best talent.</p>
  <p>“We have long known that, to make Kaspersky a great place to work, we need to listen to the wants, needs, and desires of our employees,” says Marina Alekseeva, the company’s chief human resources officer. “Previously, we didn’t have a unified resource to conduct employee surveys, and we wanted to launch a platform that we could integrate with our core HR system to listen to employees’ feedback more regularly, to understand how they feel and learn about their concerns.”</p>
  <p>To support the shift to a continuous listening strategy, Kaspersky selected <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/employee-engagement.html">SAP Qualtrics Employee Engagement</a> to help gather employee experience data at regular touchpoints and gain insights based on employee feedback.</p>
  <p>Kaspersky deployed the SAP Qualtrics Employee Engagement solution in just four weeks, building dynamic surveys and response surveys all while working remotely due to the <a href="/covid-19">COVID-19</a> pandemic. Integration between the SAP Qualtrics Employee Engagement solution and SAP SuccessFactors Human Experience Management (HXM) Suite enables the company to combine employee experience data with operational HR data to get a better understanding of its workforce.</p>
  <p>Kaspersky conducted 10 global surveys and more than 30 local pulse surveys in 2020, providing new insights into the employee experience and helping the company to identify areas for improvement.</p>
  <p>The results were very encouraging: 80% of Kaspersky’s 4,000 employees participated in the 2020 global engagement survey (a 14% increase on the previous year), and shorter pulse survey participation rates were also high. Moreover, 50% of employees took the time to enrich their responses with free-text comments, providing deeper insights into their thoughts and feelings.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="gain-real-time-insights-with-employee-engagement-surveys-and-feedback">Gain real-time insights with employee engagement surveys and feedback</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/employee-engagement.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Business leaders also benefit from instant access to survey analytics. For example, in the past, they could wait up to two months to see the outcome of a global engagement survey; today, they can track results and participation rates in real time via interactive dashboards.</p>
  <p>But what’s the point of conducting employee surveys and gathering data if you don’t act on it? With unique insight into the employee experience, Kaspersky can take targeted action to support its people, fast. For example, just two days after receiving feedback on remote working conditions, Kaspersky made a new company policy to deliver a desk chair to any employee who needs one, so that they could work more comfortably – and therefore productively – from home. Although it may seem trivial, having a comfy chair can make a huge difference to your employees’ health, well-being, and happiness. Kaspersky wants to ensure that its people have everything they need to work at their best.</p>
  <p>Regular pulse surveys also gave managers a convenient way to check in with their team while they were working remotely during the COVID-19 lockdowns, helping them to monitor employee well-being and workload, and to provide support to prevent burnout and maintain pre-pandemic performance levels.</p>
  <p>“Understanding our employees is critical to everything we do,” says Alekseeva. “With the SAP Qualtrics Employee Engagement solution, we get regular feedback that helps us to build a more attractive and engaging workplace.”</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Edith Krieg is part of SAP Reference Management and Content.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/covid-19</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/qualtrics</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
            <category>news-tag/well-being-at-work</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Five Dimensions to Create a Robust Employee Well-Being Strategy]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/five-dimensions-to-create-robust-employee-well-being-strategy-telus</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/five-dimensions-to-create-robust-employee-well-being-strategy-telus</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[TELUS has developed a strategy that includes five interlocking dimensions that align with emerging industry best practices. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e9ef10a46e14836a5b028351769a9327d59a02b0.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e9ef10a46e14836a5b028351769a9327d59a02b0.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1e9ef10a46e14836a5b028351769a9327d59a02b0.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Five Dimensions to Create a Robust Employee Well-Being Strategy" src="./media_1e9ef10a46e14836a5b028351769a9327d59a02b0.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="five-dimensions-to-create-a-robust-employee-well-being-strategy">Five Dimensions to Create a Robust Employee Well-Being Strategy</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>What does it mean to have a robust employee well-being strategy?</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Just ask TELUS, a leading communications and information technology company with $16 billion in annual revenue and 15.2 million customer connections spanning wireless, data, IP, voice, television, entertainment, video and security, healthcare, and agriculture. TELUS connects people to what matters most to improve lives and build a better future – and it starts with supporting and enabling its employees.</p>
  <p>TELUS’ employees have long depended on the company’s technology, devices, and services to work from home – well before remote work became all the rage. Since 2006, TELUS’ employees have enjoyed flexible work arrangements, with approximately 75% of its Canadian workforce spending a portion of time working remotely.</p>
  <p>In response to the global health <a href="/covid-19">pandemic</a>, 95% of TELUS employees work from home, including 99% of domestic call center employees. As a result, the company has achieved higher levels of workplace satisfaction and productivity, as employees are empowered to find new ways to fit work into their evolving lives.</p>
  <p>Just as TELUS was ahead of its time with its flexible work styles, the company is proving to be a pioneer in supporting employee well-being.</p>
  <p>According to Sandy McIntosh, TELUS’ executive vice president, People and Culture, and chief human resources officer, “without a robust people strategy, you won’t have a business that will thrive or succeed.”</p>
  <p>Under McIntosh’s leadership, well-being has become an ongoing cultural commitment and business imperative. TELUS has developed a strategy that recognizes the whole person and includes five interlocking dimensions that align with emerging industry best practices from the National Standard for Psychological Health and Safety in the Workplace, the Mental Health Commission of Canada, and the World Health Organization:</p>
  <ol>
    <li><strong>Physical</strong>: The company offers physical fitness and well-being centers, as well as virtual fitness classes and apps, virtual care solutions, nutritional counseling, health coaching, and more. TELUS also hosts biannual well-being challenges for employees and household family members to promote healthy habits.</li>
    <li><strong>Psychological</strong>: TELUS understands its employees are all somewhere on the well-being continuum and that each person’s situation is dynamic. The company offers industry-leading benefits coverage for mental health support and 24/7 support to mental health counselors and therapists through its Employee and Family Assistance Program and virtual care. In 2020, TELUS launched custom mental health training for leaders and over 90% have completed it. In May 2021, the company extended the reach by introducing similar training to all employees.</li>
    <li><strong>Social</strong>: TELUS creates opportunities to connect employees at work, home, and in the community through initiatives like TELUS Days of Giving, as well as supportive resources, collaboration tools, and employee resource groups that offer mentoring, networking, peer support, volunteering, and coaching.</li>
    <li><strong>Environmental</strong>: TELUS helps employees maintain healthy workspaces at home and in offices. In fact, TELUS is reimagining its offices for the future of work with work styles and well-being top of mind, offering a mix of private and collaborative spaces to support whitespace and brainstorming.</li>
    <li><strong>Financial</strong>: TELUS supports all aspects of its employees’ financial well-being, offering competitive salaries and benefits and financial literacy resources, including a financial well-being hub where employees can find tools to help them reach their financial and life goals.</li>
  </ol>
  <p>“Our job as leaders is to come at well-being from all five dimensions because well-being is not just mental and it’s not just physical,” said McIntosh. “Leaders have a responsibility to make sure that employees understand their financial situation, that the environment is appropriate, and their social connections are healthy. If you understand all of that and keep pressing the gas on all levers, you create a magical place where people want to be,” McIntosh explained.</p>
  <p>For TELUS, it’s deeper than providing technology and tools. The company is working to create a common language, build leadership competencies and practices, and use data insights to shift mindsets and behaviors.</p>
  <p><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm/hxm-suite.html">SAP SuccessFactors Human Experience Management (HXM) Suite</a> provides TELUS with the technology to create a company culture dedicated to flexible work that in turn supports employee well-being. With cloud-based tools, employees can tap into engaging, individualized experiences. The company knows that a better employee experience will empower the workforce to provide better experiences to customers.</p>
  <p>Very rarely does a superior or business leader say an employee must give up the things they love. But McIntosh says that employees often feel this way, especially after they have been promoted or move into a new role. Employees who quit a beloved hobby or stop exercising because they feel they don’t have the time may soon see the rest of their lives – including their performance at work – begin to free-fall.</p>
  <p>“Nobody explicitly says to you, ‘Stop doing these things,’” said McIntosh. “But also, unfortunately, nobody explicitly says to you, ‘Keep doing these things.’ We have to, as leaders, overtly come out and say, ‘Is your self-care in check?’”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="watch-forward-a-new-series-about-a-better-human-experience-at-work">Watch Forward, a new series about a better human experience at work</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="http://www.sap.com/HXMForward">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="making-good-on-a-commitment-to-employee-well-being">Making Good on a Commitment to Employee Well-Being</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="put-employees-at-the-heart-of-everything-you-do-with-sap-successfactors">Put employees at the heart of everything you do with SAP SuccessFactors</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm/hxm-suite.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>At TELUS, team member well-being initiatives aren’t designed to simply make the company look good. Rather, they exist to make employees feel good and perform at their best.</p>
  <p>“We’re really focused on helping leaders understand we don’t mean fluffy stuff,” said McIntosh. “We don’t mean every Friday we’re having a pizza party. We mean that you understand that you’re leading other human beings.”</p>
  <p>Take, for example, one TELUS benefit that provides employees, including their dependents, with up to CAD5,000 per year to spend on psychologists, psychotherapists, and social workers – a benefit unmatched by its peers. TELUS also enables its team members to connect with registered mental health clinicians through a range of virtual care solutions and provides a free, unlimited subscription to the leading mental fitness app Calm.</p>
  <p>“Human beings are complex, and we need to look at all five dimensions and put all of these ingredients together,” said McIntosh.</p>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div>To learn more, <a href="https://www.sap.com/HXMForwardAdamGrant">watch Sandy McIntosh’s interview</a> in an episode of Forward with Adam Grant.</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>Carolyn Judge Phillip is VP of Corporate Marketing for SAP SuccessFactors. <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2021/10/14/5-dimensions-to-create-a-robust-employee-well-being-strategy/?sh=3d0c882a5e18">This also appeared on SAP BrandVoice on Forbes.</a></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/mental-health-well-being</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-original-series-forward</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
            <category>news-tag/well-being-at-work</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Chobani Creates Positive Change for Its Dynamic and Diverse Workforce]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/chobani-creates-positive-change-for-dynamic-and-diverse-workforce</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/chobani-creates-positive-change-for-dynamic-and-diverse-workforce</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Empowered by an integrated suite of SAP solutions, Chobani is even better equipped to continue to lead in making the world a healthier place.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b683315f4787218c78d03bb6eaa883935b3f2b30.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b683315f4787218c78d03bb6eaa883935b3f2b30.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1b683315f4787218c78d03bb6eaa883935b3f2b30.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Chobani Creates Positive Change for Its Dynamic and Diverse Workforce" src="./media_1b683315f4787218c78d03bb6eaa883935b3f2b30.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="chobani-creates-positive-change-for-its-dynamic-and-diverse-workforce">Chobani Creates Positive Change for Its Dynamic and Diverse Workforce</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Founded in 2005 when Hamdi Ulukaya brought together a small group of passionate individuals to make the real, wholesome yogurt he remembered from his childhood, Chobani now produces the top-selling Greek yogurt brand in the United States. The company’s yogurt, oat milk, dairy and plant-based creamers, ready-to-drink coffee, and plant-based probiotic drinks are made with natural ingredients and without artificial preservatives, keeping with its mission to make “good food for all.”</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Chobani prides itself on being a values-driven, people-first food and wellness company. Employees describe it as “One Chobani – we work in different places and do different things, but we are one.” Its energetic work environment comprises diverse backgrounds and cultures, with tight-knit teams that feed off innovation and creativity.</p>
  <p>This unity is reflected in Chobani’s efforts to reduce inequities in the workplace by offering programs that benefit the entire workforce, regardless of job title.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1320c990b64986b59a05e760b3d1133d364f1b49a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1320c990b64986b59a05e760b3d1133d364f1b49a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1320c990b64986b59a05e760b3d1133d364f1b49a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Chobani employee in PPE giving thumbs-up" src="./media_1320c990b64986b59a05e760b3d1133d364f1b49a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="300" height="259">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p><em>Photo courtesy of Chobani</em></p>
  <p>“Chobani is fundamentally about access to delicious, nutritious, natural, and affordable food,” said Grace Zuncic, chief people officer, Chobani. “But it also stands for access to a living wage, good benefits, and a workplace that lifts you up, makes you feel appreciated and welcome for who you are, and where you can really be yourself. Our values are simple: people, integrity, leadership, giving back, innovation, and craftsmanship.”</p>
  <p>But merely expressing these values is not enough: Zuncic says it’s important how these words are enacted across the entire organization and how they make employees feel. The company strives to transform employees’ lives through the experience employees have from their first day.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="watch-forward-a-new-series-about-a-better-human-experience-at-work">Watch Forward, a new series about a better human experience at work</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="http://www.sap.com/HXMForward">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="putting-its-values-into-practice">Putting Its Values Into Practice</h2>
  <p>According to Zuncic, <a href="/covid-19">COVID-19</a> gave Chobani an opportunity to show its workforce how much it cares. While Chobani’s executive leadership team always led in service of essential workers – who comprise the majority of its workforce – during the pandemic, the company offered financial incentives for employees to get tested and vaccinated.</p>
  <p>It was one of the first companies in the United States to offer paid leave for vaccination. It also opened up discussions about mental health among frontline employees and implemented new policies to help ensure employees at all levels have access to the right mental health support and resources.</p>
  <p>In addition, Chobani introduced a US$100 daily subsidy to help cover the cost of childcare. This financial support helped the company keep production moving in the face of extremely high demand while supporting employees during a difficult and uncertain time.</p>
  <h2 id="delivering-an-exceptional-people-experience">Delivering an Exceptional People Experience</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="deliver-engaging-individualized-experiences-that-enable-employees-to-be-their-best-with-sap-successfactors">Deliver engaging, individualized experiences that enable employees to be their best with SAP SuccessFactors</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm/hxm-suite.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In order to help power its people and workforce strategies, Chobani relies on <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm/hxm-suite.html">SAP SuccessFactors Human Experience Management (HXM) Suite</a> to provide a robust experience across the entire employee life cycle, help upskill and reskill its people, and deliver the data and insights to further the company’s mission.</p>
  <p>“SAP SuccessFactors HXM Suite has helped us deepen engagement for both managers and employees and strengthen their understanding of our people strategy as well as the tools and resources we offer,” said Zuncic. “Eliminating barriers between management and employees enables meaningful conversations around goals, performance, learning, career development, and succession.”</p>
  <p>Empowered by an integrated suite of SAP solutions, Chobani is even better equipped to continue to lead in making work better for all, elevate communities, and make the world a healthier place.</p>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div><strong>To learn more, <a href="https://www.sap.com/HXMForward">watch “Forward with Baratunde Thurston” and Grace Zuncic</a>.</strong></div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>Deb Lyons is senior director of Global Marketing for SAP SuccessFactors. <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2021/10/07/learn-how-chobani-creates-positive-change-for-its-dynamic-and-diverse-workforce/?sh=7f82450214ed">This also appeared on SAP BrandVoice on Forbes.</a> Top image courtesy of Chobani.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/covid-19</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-original-series-forward</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
            <category>news-tag/well-being-at-work</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prioritize These HR Trends Now to Enhance Employee Well-Being]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/hr-trends-enhance-employee-well-being</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/hr-trends-enhance-employee-well-being</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The more organizations address employee well-being, the more likely engaged, motivated people will stay and give their best. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/data-privacy</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
            <category>news-tag/well-being-at-work</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Make 2021 Count: Your Guide to Creating the Best Employee Experience]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/create-best-employee-experience</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/create-best-employee-experience</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Companies that do more for employee well-being see real business impact. Read to learn how you can improve your employee experience.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/mental-health-well-being</category>
            <category>news-tag/well-being-at-work</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>