<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/product/sap-datasphere/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bonprix Catwalks Onto Business Intelligence with SAP]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/bonprix-business-intelligence-sap</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/bonprix-business-intelligence-sap</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Leading international fashion company Bonprix has successfully completed implementation of SAP BW/4HANA and SAP Datasphere. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
            <category>product/sap-datasphere</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Partnerships Help Customers Successfully Navigate a Data-Driven World]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/partnerships-help-customers-navigate-data-driven-world</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/partnerships-help-customers-navigate-data-driven-world</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP partners can deploy SAP Datasphere and SAP Analytics Cloud to provide data access, effective planning, and trusted AI across operations.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16fa40a8c4f0c1be7eb9eaf1afe27075d1230ec25.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16fa40a8c4f0c1be7eb9eaf1afe27075d1230ec25.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_16fa40a8c4f0c1be7eb9eaf1afe27075d1230ec25.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Partnerships Help Customers Successfully Navigate a Data-Driven World" src="./media_16fa40a8c4f0c1be7eb9eaf1afe27075d1230ec25.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="partnerships-help-customers-successfully-navigate-a-data-driven-world">Partnerships Help Customers Successfully Navigate a Data-Driven World</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>In the modern business environment, the critical need to effectively harness data is undeniable. Companies that fail to become data-driven risk falling behind in a world where agility and informed decision-making are paramount. In the recent <a href="https://www.sap.com/events/data-unleashed.html">SAP Data Unleashed</a> event we explored strategies to help organizations access data from any source, transform planning and analysis with a business data fabric, and foster trusted artificial intelligence (AI) across their businesses. Central to this transformation are <a href="/topics/ecosystem">SAP partners</a>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>For decades, our partners have leveraged their industry expertise and technological know-how to bring immense value to companies of all sizes. They possess a rare fusion of deep industry insights and technological expertise, which they leverage to guide businesses through the delicate process of modernization while ensuring that the essence of their identity remains intact.</p>
  <p>We recently <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/partners.html#trending">asked several of our strategic SAP partners</a> how they’re helping customers take better advantage of their organization’s data. Our partners have observed a significant shift in the way data is perceived and utilized. It’s no longer just a byproduct of business operations but a core asset that, when effectively distributed and made accessible, can revolutionize customer experiences and enable a more strategic, company-wide approach to decision-making.</p>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11f5934a69f41fbb435d136fc80e11b26ab8eb2f5.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11f5934a69f41fbb435d136fc80e11b26ab8eb2f5.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_11f5934a69f41fbb435d136fc80e11b26ab8eb2f5.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Partners Bring Out Your Best as a Data-Driven Organization" src="./media_11f5934a69f41fbb435d136fc80e11b26ab8eb2f5.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://youtu.be/Cj3BF9-9I30">SAP Partners Bring Out Your Best as a Data-Driven Organization</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>However, the mere availability of data is not a panacea. The crux of the matter is transforming data into actionable insights. This is where our partners excel, mapping out advanced use cases and facilitating the transition to cutting-edge platforms like SAP Datasphere and SAP Analytics Cloud. These solutions can empower organizations to evolve into entities where data is not just present but central to every action and decision.</p>
  <p>The practical implications of data are vast and deeply rooted in the operational successes of our clients. AI, for instance, is a frontier rich with potential, but its success is inextricably linked to the quality and accessibility of data. Recognizing this, SAP partners are investing in building AI capabilities that can not only propel new business functions but also deliver substantial value.</p>
  <p>Another key area of focus for our partners is the concept of a business data fabric, which is critical in developing a flexible enterprise architecture. Such an architecture allows for co-innovation and customization of solutions, ensuring that data is not just an afterthought but a driving force in business operations.</p>
  <p>The journey toward a data- and AI-centric business model is an ongoing one, marked by evolving needs, emerging challenges, and a relentless pursuit of innovation. The ultimate aim is to convert potential into lasting business success.</p>
  <p>The essence of our relationship with our partners is rooted in a shared vision. We are united in our pursuit of discovery, innovation, and improvement as we navigate the future together. Be sure to <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/partners.html#trending">watch the videos</a> with our seven strategic partners and discover how the <a href="https://www.sap.com/partners.html">SAP partner ecosystem</a> can help your company become a data-driven organization.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Karl Fahrbach is chief partner officer at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-partners-are-helping-their-clients-solve-critical-business-challenges">SAP partners are helping their clients solve critical business challenges</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/partners.html#trending">Discover how</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>topic/data-analytics</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-datasphere</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP and NVIDIA to Accelerate Generative AI Adoption Across Enterprise Applications Powering Global Industries]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/sap-and-nvidia-to-accelerate-generative-ai-adoption</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/sap-and-nvidia-to-accelerate-generative-ai-adoption</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Together, SAP and NVIDIA will bring custom generative AI to thousands of enterprises around the world. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b3fcf19084a91c9721f2b9169c59bd16f3f8e1b6.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b3fcf19084a91c9721f2b9169c59bd16f3f8e1b6.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1b3fcf19084a91c9721f2b9169c59bd16f3f8e1b6.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP and NVIDIA to Accelerate Generative AI Adoption Across Enterprise Applications Powering Global Industries" src="./media_1b3fcf19084a91c9721f2b9169c59bd16f3f8e1b6.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-and-nvidia-to-accelerate-generative-ai-adoption-across-enterprise-applications-powering-global-industries">SAP and NVIDIA to Accelerate Generative AI Adoption Across Enterprise Applications Powering Global Industries</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Customers Can Harness Their Business Data in Cloud Solutions from SAP Using Customized LLMs Deployed with NVIDIA AI Foundry Services and New NVIDIA NIM Microservices</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <table>
          <thead>
            <tr>
              <th>Text Large</th>
            </tr>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td>
                <p><strong><em>WALLDORF and SANTA CLARA, Calif.</em></strong></p>
                <hr>
                <p><a href="http://www.nvidia.com">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) and <a href="http://www.nvidia.com">NVIDIA</a> (NASDAQ: NVDA) today announced a partnership expansion focused on accelerating enterprise customers’ ability to harness the transformative power of data and generative AI across SAP’s portfolio of cloud solutions and applications.</p>
              </td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
        <p>The companies are collaborating to build and deliver SAP Business AI, including scalable, business-specific generative AI capabilities inside the Joule copilot from SAP and across SAP’s portfolio of cloud solutions and applications – all of which are underpinned by the SAP generative AI hub. The generative AI hub facilitates relevant, reliable and responsible business AI and provides instant access to a broad range of large language models (LLMs).</p>
        <p>As part of SAP’s ongoing initiative to build generative AI directly into the applications that power the world’s businesses, the partnership aims to help customers adopt generative AI capabilities at scale across their organizations. SAP will use <a href="https://www.nvidia.com/en-us/ai-data-science/generative-ai/">NVIDIA’s generative AI foundry service</a> to fine-tune LLMs for domain-specific scenarios and deploy applications with new <a href="https://nvidianews.nvidia.com/news/generative-ai-microservices-for-developers">NVIDIA NIM</a>™ microservices. SAP and NVIDIA plan to make the new integrated capabilities available by the end of 2024.</p>
        <p>“Enterprise customers want to leverage state-of-the-art technology that delivers real business value,” said Christian Klein, CEO and Member of the Executive Board of SAP SE. “Strategic technology partnerships, like the one between SAP and NVIDIA, are at the core of our strategy to invest in technology that maximizes the potential and opportunity of AI for business. NVIDIA’s expertise in delivering AI capabilities at scale will help SAP accelerate the pace of transformation and better serve our customers in the cloud.”</p>
        <p>“SAP is sitting on a gold mine of enterprise data that can be transformed into custom generative AI agents to help customers automate their businesses,” said Jensen Huang, founder and CEO of NVIDIA. “Together, NVIDIA and SAP will bring custom generative AI to the thousands of enterprises around the world that rely on SAP to power their operations.”</p>
        <h2 id="harnessing-business-data-and-generative-ai-to-advance-customer-insights">Harnessing Business Data and Generative AI to Advance Customer Insights</h2>
        <p>SAP and NVIDIA plan to collaborate to integrate generative AI into cloud solutions from SAP, which include the latest release of the SAP Datasphere solution, SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP) and RISE with SAP.</p>
        <p>SAP plans to build additional generative AI capabilities within SAP BTP using NVIDIA’s generative AI foundry service, featuring <a href="https://www.nvidia.com/en-us/data-center/dgx-cloud/">NVIDIA DGX™ Cloud</a> AI supercomputing, <a href="https://www.nvidia.com/en-us/data-center/products/ai-enterprise/">NVIDIA AI Enterprise</a> software and NVIDIA AI Foundation models. These new capabilities are designed to be the basis of SAP’s development and deployment of generative AI for customers and is expected to be accessible in the generative AI hub in SAP AI Core and SAP Datasphere.</p>
        <p>Additional generative AI initiatives include:</p>
        <ul>
          <li><strong>New capabilities for the Joule copilot</strong>: Joule can leverage <a href="https://blogs.nvidia.com/blog/2023/11/15/what-is-retrieval-augmented-generation/">retrieval-augmented generation</a> (RAG) capabilities built by NVIDIA and SAP, which can be deployed on leading hyperscalers or SAP’s own cloud environments. As a natural-language, generative AI copilot, Joule helps customers unlock the potential in their business by automating time-consuming tasks and quickly analyzing business-critical data to deliver more intelligent, personalized experiences.</li>
          <li><strong>Innovative use cases leveraging SAP S/4HANA Cloud, SAP SuccessFactors and SAP Signavio</strong>: SAP and NVIDIA are exploring more than 20 generative AI use cases where the companies can combine assets to simplify and enhance digital transformation. Among these are generative AI features that can automate enterprise resource planning with intelligent invoice matching in SAP S/4HANA Cloud; improve human resources use cases leveraging SAP SuccessFactors; and accelerate new generative AI insights from SAP Signavio to better process business recommendations and optimize SAP’s customer support processes.</li>
          <li><strong>Unifying AI data sources with SAP Datasphere</strong>: Built on SAP BTP, SAP Datasphere enables integration and a unified view of semantically rich SAP data with third-party data across the enterprise landscape to help customers adapt faster to market changes and make more efficient and better informed decisions. With SAP Datasphere, customers can confidently access a high-quality data fabric using AI and machine learning (ML) models. To accelerate SAP’s federated machine learning (FedML) capabilities for SAP Datasphere, NVIDIA and SAP are facilitating easier access to data for data scientists and enhancing ML workload performance with the support of NVIDIA accelerated computing platforms and NVIDIA AI Enterprise data science software such as <a href="https://developer.nvidia.com/rapids">NVIDIA RAPIDS</a>™.</li>
          <li><strong>Using LLMs for the ABAP programming language</strong>: To aid developers in creating domain-specific language code, SAP plans to use NVIDIA AI foundry services to assist in fine-tuning LLMs. This will build on SAP’s use of generative AI models to assist developers who use ABAP through the company’s ABAP Cloud model and SAP Cloud Application Programming model.</li>
        </ul>
        <h2 id="nvidia-ai-enterprise-powers-production-grade-generative-ai-across-cloud-solutions-from-sap">NVIDIA AI Enterprise Powers Production-Grade Generative AI Across Cloud Solutions from SAP</h2>
        <p>Once models are ready for deployment in cloud solutions from SAP, SAP plans to use NVIDIA AI Enterprise software, including NVIDIA NIM inference microservices and NVIDIA NeMo Retriever™ microservices. NVIDIA NIM can be used to accelerate and maximize inference performance across the accelerated infrastructure from SAP. Using NVIDIA NeMo Retriever microservices, SAP plans to add RAG capabilities that enable generative AI applications to more securely access data running on SAP software to improve accuracy and insights. Customers can plan to use RAG on both SAP and third-party data.</p>
        <p>To learn more about the SAP and NVIDIA partnership, <a href="https://www.nvidia.com/gtc/keynote/">watch the replay of Huang’s GTC keynote address</a>.</p>
        <p>Visit the <a href="/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
        <h2 id="about-nvidia">About NVIDIA</h2>
        <p>Since its founding in 1993, <a href="https://www.nvidia.com/">NVIDIA</a> (NASDAQ: NVDA) has been a pioneer in accelerated computing. The company’s invention of the GPU in 1999 sparked the growth of the PC gaming market, redefined computer graphics, ignited the era of modern AI and is fueling industrial digitalization across markets. NVIDIA is now a full-stack computing infrastructure company with data-center-scale offerings that are reshaping industry. More information at <a href="https://nvidianews.nvidia.com/">https://nvidianews.nvidia.com/</a>.</p>
        <table>
          <thead>
            <tr>
              <th>Text Large</th>
            </tr>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td><strong>About SAP</strong></td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
        <p>SAP’s strategy is to help every business run as an intelligent, sustainable enterprise. As a market leader in enterprise application software, we help companies of all sizes and in all industries run at their best: SAP customers generate 87% of total global commerce. Our machine learning, Internet of Things (IoT), and advanced analytics technologies help turn customers’ businesses into intelligent enterprises. SAP helps give people and organizations deep business insight and fosters collaboration that helps them stay ahead of their competition. We simplify technology for companies so they can consume our software the way they want – without disruption. Our end-to-end suite of applications and services enables business and public customers across 26 industries globally to operate profitably, adapt continuously, and make a difference. With a global network of customers, partners, employees, and thought leaders, SAP helps the world run better and improve people’s lives. For more information, visit <a href="http://www.sap.com">www.sap.com</a>.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="revolutionize-how-you-interact-with-sap-business-system-while-simplifying-your-day-to-day-with-faster-work-smarter-insights-and-better-outcomes">Revolutionize how you interact with SAP business system while simplifying your day-to-day with faster work, smarter insights and better outcomes</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/ai-assistant.html">Meet Joule</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><strong>Note to editors:</strong><br>To preview and download broadcast-standard stock footage and press photos digitally, please visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/photos">www.sap.com/photos</a>. On this platform, you can find high-resolution material for your media channels.</p>
  <p><strong>For customers interested in learning more about SAP products:</strong> Global Customer Center: +49 180 534-34-24<br>United States Only: 1 (800) 872-1SAP (1-800-872-1727)</p>
  <p><strong>For further information, contact:</strong><br>SAP: Scott Malinowski, +1 (617) 538-6297, <a href="mailto:scott.malinowski@sap.com">scott.malinowski@sap.com</a><br><a href="mailto:SAP%20Press%20Room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a><br>NVIDIA: Shannon McPhee, +1 (310) 920-9642, <a href="mailto:smcphee@nvidia.com">smcphee@nvidia.com</a></p>
  <p>Certain statements in this press release including, but not limited to, statements as to: the benefits, impact, performance, features, and availability of NVIDIA’s products and technologies, including NVIDIA’s generative AI foundry service, NVIDIA NIM microservices, NVIDIA DGX Cloud AI supercomputing, NVIDIA AI Enterprise software, and NVIDIA AI Foundation models, NVIDIA accelerated computing platforms, NVIDIA AI Enterprise data science software such as NVIDIA RAPIDS, RAPIDS cuDF and cuML, NVIDIA NeMo Retriever microservices; NVIDIA’s partnership with SAP, the benefits and impact of such partnership, and the features and availability of its services and offerings; SAP sitting on a gold mine of enterprise data that can be transformed into custom generative AI agents to help customers automate their businesses; and NVIDIA and SAP bringing custom generative AI to the thousands of enterprises around the world that rely on SAP to power their operations are forward-looking statements that are subject to risks and uncertainties that could cause results to be materially different than expectations. Important factors that could cause actual results to differ materially include: global economic conditions; our reliance on third parties to manufacture, assemble, package and test our products; the impact of technological development and competition; development of new products and technologies or enhancements to our existing product and technologies; market acceptance of our products or our partners’ products; design, manufacturing or software defects; changes in consumer preferences or demands; changes in industry standards and interfaces; unexpected loss of performance of our products or technologies when integrated into systems; as well as other factors detailed from time to time in the most recent reports NVIDIA files with the Securities and Exchange Commission, or SEC, including, but not limited to, its annual report on Form 10-K and quarterly reports on Form 10-Q. Copies of reports filed with the SEC are posted on the company’s website and are available from NVIDIA without charge. These forward-looking statements are not guarantees of future performance and speak only as of the date hereof, and, except as required by law, NVIDIA disclaims any obligation to update these forward-looking statements to reflect future events or circumstances.</p>
  <p>This document contains forward-looking statements, which are predictions, projections, or other statements about future events. These statements are based on current expectations, forecasts, and assumptions that are subject to risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results and outcomes to materially differ. Additional information regarding these risks and uncertainties may be found in our filings with the Securities and Exchange Commission, including but not limited to the risk factors section of SAP’s 2023 Annual Report on Form 20-F.</p>
  <p>© 2024 SAP SE and NVIDIA Corporation. All rights reserved.</p>
  <p>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p>NVIDIA, the NVIDIA logo, DGX, NVIDIA NeMo Retriever, NVIDIA NIM, and RAPIDS are trademarks and/or registered trademarks of NVIDIA Corporation in the U.S. and/or other countries. Other company and product names may be trademarks of the respective companies with which they are associated. Features, pricing, availability, and specifications are subject to change without notice.</p>
  <p>Please consider our <a href="https://www.sap.com/corporate/en/legal/privacy.html">privacy policy</a>. If you received this press release in your e-mail and you wish to unsubscribe to our mailing list please contact <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a> and write Unsubscribe in the subject line.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
            <category>product/sap-datasphere</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Biggest Opportunity for Businesses Today: Using the Right Business Data]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2024/03/business-opportunity-use-the-right-business-data</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2024/03/business-opportunity-use-the-right-business-data</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Having a central hub for data is more critical than ever. Updates to SAP Datasphere empower businesses with more innovations.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10cb3ea6ef420b80f58847074323ded1ddf40b734.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10cb3ea6ef420b80f58847074323ded1ddf40b734.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_10cb3ea6ef420b80f58847074323ded1ddf40b734.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="The Biggest Opportunity for Businesses Today: Using the Right Business Data" src="./media_10cb3ea6ef420b80f58847074323ded1ddf40b734.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="the-biggest-opportunity-for-businesses-today-using-the-right-business-data">The Biggest Opportunity for Businesses Today: Using the Right Business Data</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>There is no doubt that generative AI for business will transform every aspect of how business is done. But the reality is that generative AI is only as good as the data that it’s trained on.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>While data may be the fuel powering the engine of AI, it’s good data that’s the real game changer. With good data, a company can automate processes — freeing up their people to do the most impactful work — and analyze the most important variables facing their business to create intelligent insights.</p>
  <p>That’s where a datasphere comes in. It makes data more complete and logical by understanding the different relationships within a company’s data. And that’s what can truly bring out the best in any business today.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="deliver-seamless-and-scalable-access-to-mission-critical-business-data">Deliver seamless and scalable access to mission-critical business data</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/datasphere.html">Explore SAP Datasphere</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Having a central hub for data is more critical than ever. It allows our customers to better model their business across all SAP business applications. That’s exactly why we introduced <strong>SAP Datasphere</strong> last year to empower businesses with insights they need – based on the right data – in the context of their business. Since then, generative AI has disrupted and simplified even more business processes, and data capture is no different. This week <a href="/2024/03/future-of-data-driven-business-new-sap-datasphere-capabilities">we announced new generative-AI features in SAP Datasphere that will transform enterprise planning</a> through simplified data landscapes and more-intuitive data interaction.</p>
  <p>Why is this important? Because having a unified data view that simplifies the data landscapes while retaining context and logic is what enables businesses to adapt faster to market changes and make better decisions. It’s also a more efficient way of working. Because while you’re busy pulling data together, competitors are circling your customers.</p>
  <p>I am constantly speaking with our customers about the value of SAP Datasphere. It’s a data architecture that harmonizes mission-critical data across an organization. I hear amazing outcomes they’re able to achieve: from PwC breaking down silos in the different countries where it stores sensitive data so its workforce can access it more efficiently and securely for customers, to the Lufthansa Group taking data from different parts of its operations like aircraft, HR, and procurement, to see how decisions from one could impact the other.<br><br>With our additional news this week, such as making our generative AI copilot Joule available in SAP Analytics Cloud and expanding our partnership with Collibra to help our customers meet compliance, privacy, and regulatory requirements related to AI as they evolve, we’re making it easier to find the right data and use it to drive deeper insights, more efficiencies, faster growth, and more trust in their business.</p>
  <p>While PwC and Lufthansa show what’s possible today with a simplified data fabric, imagine what is about to become possible when you infuse it with the power of generative AI that understands your business – and then learns from that data. This has the potential to deliver exponential value from your data.</p>
  <p>Or think of it this way: years ago, the biggest differentiators for businesses were price, location, products, and services. Today, and especially in the years ahead, it could very well be how effectively a business is training their AI models. That’s why building the right data fabric is one of the most important investments any business can make today.</p>
  <p>It’s been said that the best way to predict the future is to invent it. And in an era where data is being created exponentially, I believe that those businesses that can separate the signal from the noise when it comes to their data will be the ones that invent the future in an AI-first world.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Scott Russell is a member of the Executive Board of SAP SE.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="take-a-guided-tour-and-experience-firsthand-the-power-of-business-data-with-sap-datasphere">Take a guided tour and experience firsthand the power of business data with SAP Datasphere</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/datasphere/guided-experience.html">Start now</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/blog/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/blog/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/blog/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/blog/article-read-more</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/executive-blog</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-datasphere</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unleashing the Latest SAP Data and Analytics Innovations]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/latest-sap-data-and-analytics-innovations-sap-data-unleashed</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/latest-sap-data-and-analytics-innovations-sap-data-unleashed</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP has shared the latest innovations in data and analytics. Read on to learn more about the company's transformative announcements.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1025728cedc072568e25830043a6185f08eca8f64.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1025728cedc072568e25830043a6185f08eca8f64.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1025728cedc072568e25830043a6185f08eca8f64.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Unleashing the Latest SAP Data and Analytics Innovations" src="./media_1025728cedc072568e25830043a6185f08eca8f64.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="unleashing-the-latest-sap-data-and-analytics-innovations">Unleashing the Latest SAP Data and Analytics Innovations</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Today at <a href="/">SAP Data Unleashed</a>, SAP proudly announced the latest innovations in data and analytics.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Read on to learn more about these transformative announcements, which will enable businesses to unlock new potential in the areas of data management, AI-driven planning, and analytics.</p>
  <h2 id="access-insights-wherever-your-data-resides">Access Insights Wherever Your Data Resides</h2>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>SAP Datasphere Knowledge Graph</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP Datasphere knowledge graph will enable organizations to better represent their real-world use of data, leading to more effectively leveraging it for generative AI and better reasoning.</p>
  <p>As data is onboarded, transformed, and integrated in SAP Datasphere, SAP Datasphere knowledge graph automatically creates an ontology representing the relationships in the data, including the inherent business context from SAP application sources like SAP S/4HANA. This is then available to be extended and augmented via an ontology editor to reflect specific attributes within an organization. Finally, the data in SAP Datasphere is automatically applied to this ontology to create a knowledge graph that allows the data to be processed as a semantic web of relationships, drawing new insights from connections that are otherwise difficult to follow.</p>
  <p>These knowledge graphs are better suited for answering complex, often open-ended questions. For example, a marketing manager might ask a question like: “What type of campaign for mountain bikes works best for my highest performing cities with a population over 1 million?”</p>
  <p>Knowledge graphs can provide better context to large language models (LLMs) and prevent AI-generated “hallucinations.” SAP Datasphere knowledge graph will enable organizations to unleash the power of AI for even the most complex queries.</p>
  <p>The effort and cost of manually creating knowledge graphs is typically very high. SAP Datasphere knowledge graph overcomes this by pre-populating the knowledge graphs using all the valuable content already available in SAP Datasphere. The knowledge graph can then be used with Joule, SAP’s generative AI co-pilot, allowing business users to ask both open-ended and specific questions and get instant and well-documented answers. Sign up for a preview of SAP Datasphere knowledge graph via the link below.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15c1af20ba8e68937af5d24f99fac41cebc44dce7.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15c1af20ba8e68937af5d24f99fac41cebc44dce7.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_15c1af20ba8e68937af5d24f99fac41cebc44dce7.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_15c1af20ba8e68937af5d24f99fac41cebc44dce7.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="576">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>Auto-generated knowledge graphs enable AI to answer complex, open-ended questions</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>SAP HANA Cloud Vector Engine</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>With the next release of SAP HANA Cloud, a vector capability will be added to existing multi-model capabilities, allowing customers to gain value from all relevant types of business data using a single database. The inclusion of a vector engine further enables customers to build <a href="https://pages.community.sap.com/topics/hana/intelligent-data-applications">intelligent data applications</a> that combine the natural intuition of human interaction with powerful machine learning and multi-model processing capabilities.</p>
  <p>The vector engine in SAP HANA Cloud provides the ability to store and compare vectors using SQL. Determining similarity between vectors enables use cases such as retrieval-augmented generation (RAG), recommendations, classifications, clustering, and more. Key benefits of SAP HANA Cloud vector engine include:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Simplify data architecture and security with a single multi-model database with SQL interaction</li>
    <li>Gain new insights by combining spatial, graph, JSON, and relational data with vector queries</li>
    <li>Easily incorporate vector use cases in solutions based on the HANA Cloud ecosystem (clients, Python libraries, CAP, etc.)</li>
    <li>Integrate with open-source community tools such as LangChain via plug-ins</li>
  </ul>
  <p>SAP HANA Cloud vector engine is currently in public preview and is planned for general availability in late Q1 2024.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Simplified Consumption of Data Products in SAP Datasphere</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Data products facilitate self-service access to data as a product and enable data sharing across application boundaries. Data consumers need an easy way to explore, understand, and activate the data needed to perform their tasks — and data providers need an easy way to publish their assets and make them available to data consumers.</p>
  <p>SAP is innovating in this space with an improved user experience that drives data sharing at scale. This starts with published data products, whether produced by SAP line-of-business applications, industry solutions, or third parties, and follows with simple consumption in SAP Datasphere.</p>
  <p>In SAP Datasphere, customers will find ready access to SAP and non-SAP data products and easily install them into their SAP Datasphere instance. The procedure establishes relevant connections and creates the necessary artifacts in SAP Datasphere without the user having to enter those details. Key to this is making data provisioning easier via metadata, which are described via the Open Resource Directory (ORD) protocol. The experience will be harmonized within SAP Datasphere by bringing catalog and the data product installation closely together. Visit <a href="https://roadmaps.sap.com/board?range=FIRST-LAST&#x26;PRODUCT=73555000100800002141&#x26;q=data%20products#Q1%202024">SAP Road Map Explorer</a> for the latest updates.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15b1605af3a6110198283ea2725e4e982d88adc28.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15b1605af3a6110198283ea2725e4e982d88adc28.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_15b1605af3a6110198283ea2725e4e982d88adc28.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_15b1605af3a6110198283ea2725e4e982d88adc28.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="576">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>Data products available in catalog enhances the experience and productivity of data users</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>SAP Datasphere Semantic Onboarding Enhancements</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Semantic onboarding provides a seamless import of semantically rich objects from SAP S/4HANA and SAP BW/4HANA into SAP Datasphere. Now, we are taking the next step by adding support for SAP HANA Cloud and SAP data products through the same unified onboarding experience.</p>
  <p>Customers will be able to combine their SAP HANA Cloud modeling approach with SAP Datasphere by importing calculation views into the data layer of SAP Datasphere. This preserves the semantic information such as measures, attributes, hierarchies, aggregations, and currencies/units, while keeping SAP HANA Cloud and SAP Datasphere objects in sync — allowing customers to leverage their prior investments in SAP HANA modeling.</p>
  <p>Likewise, semantic onboarding of SAP data products will enable inheritance of business context from SAP line-of-business applications and industry solutions. By providing the semantics of the source systems and transferring that into the business data fabric as a foundation, SAP Datasphere drastically improves the analytic workflow and accelerates and simplifies data-driven insights.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Collibra AI Governance Integration with SAP Solutions</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The SAP and Collibra partnership enables end-to-end data governance and delivers trusted data to all users across the business data fabric. As more tasks and decisions are automated by AI within critical business processes, the need to extend governance to AI has also become apparent.</p>
  <p>The partnership with Collibra is being expanded to address the data and AI governance needs of joint customers via Collibra AI Governance. We will build tailored integrations between Collibra AI Governance and SAP solutions to connect the data used for AI with the models themselves in a single platform, allowing enterprises to track and manage their AI development efforts.</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Customers will better understand data lineage and metadata of SAP data that is utilized in AI modeling. With that, users can see what data their AI models were trained on to ensure that the data is accurate and from a trusted source.</li>
    <li>Customers will benefit from a single view to understand what AI models exist in their organization, and what data is being used to power them. AI/machine learning models created with SAP technology will be registered with the Collibra AI Governance platform.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>This extension of the SAP partnership with Collibra will increase transparency and accountability for organizations, and help ensure that regulatory, compliance, and privacy policies are being met. More importantly, it will build user trust by preventing biased decision-making, inaccurate recommendations, and other risks arising from AI.</p>
  <p>Together, SAP and Collibra will help joint customers address the data and AI governance needs across their organizations. Collibra AI Governance was <a href="https://www.collibra.com/us/en/company/newsroom/press-releases/collibra-introduces-collibra-ai-governance">launched last week</a> and is available to interested customers.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>SAP Datasphere Confluent Integration</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Core to the SAP data strategy is providing customers with the ability to interoperate with the world’s leading data and AI vendors through an open data ecosystem. To this end, the newly enhanced Confluent integration enables real-time streaming of data to and from SAP Datasphere.</p>
  <p>First, the outbound capabilities were extended by taking advantage of Confluent’s proprietary schema registry capabilities. Second, the Confluent schema registry will be used to enable seamless consumption of Confluent data within SAP Datasphere.</p>
  <p>The integration is specifically tailored to Confluent and provides a superior user experience for joint customers. It allows connections on the application level without additional custom application development. The integration is a pre-established replication flow in SAP Datasphere, which already includes delta and real-time processing natively. This makes the process very efficient as it does not force customers to load all the data at every step, but only when data has changed.</p>
  <p>The first integration for data ingestion into Kafka and Confluent is generally available. Additional capabilities for Confluent specific outbound and inbound integration will be generally available at the end of Q1 and Q3, respectively.</p>
  <h2 id="transform-planning-with-a-business-data-fabric">Transform Planning with a Business Data Fabric</h2>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>SAP Analytics Cloud for Planning Deep Integration to SAP Datasphere</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP Datasphere and SAP Analytics Cloud for planning will be more closely integrated to expand the business data fabric to planning use cases. SAP Analytics Cloud planning models can be deployed into SAP Datasphere, bringing plan and actuals data together for real-time steering.</p>
  <p>Through a reduction in both data footprint and modeling efforts, SAP Analytics Cloud extends planning functionality via SAP Datasphere and its native capabilities for transformation and integration. This reduces the complexity and risk inherent in storing multiple copies of data which is prevalent today.</p>
  <p>SAP Analytics Cloud for planning will have live access to actual and plan data for extended planning and analysis scenarios, including the live usage of master data. With this, SAP Datasphere will become the platform on which planning processes and tools can integrate.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14d5d8f4cd6ea2a14b3cb7d88fc159719e39722c7.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14d5d8f4cd6ea2a14b3cb7d88fc159719e39722c7.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_14d5d8f4cd6ea2a14b3cb7d88fc159719e39722c7.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_14d5d8f4cd6ea2a14b3cb7d88fc159719e39722c7.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="558">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>In this example, third-party inflation data from the World Bank (blue box) is provisioned through Datasphere to help planners do scenario planning with SAP Analytics Cloud compass</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP is the only vendor to offer a business data fabric that seamlessly integrates planning and therefore covers the entire technology stack required to transform data into insights and future actions. Visit <a href="https://roadmaps.sap.com/board?PRODUCT=67838200100800006884&#x26;q=seamless&#x26;range=CURRENT-LAST#;INNO=1FA75F34ABA51EDEADDAB4FD3ACC8288">SAP Road Map Explorer</a> for the latest updates.</p>
  <h2 id="foster-trusted-ai-across-your-business">Foster Trusted AI Across Your Business</h2>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>SAP Analytics Cloud Generative AI Co-Pilot</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP customers will embrace the power of generative AI to create and simulate business plans in SAP Analytics Cloud. With the power of Joule, planning and analytics professionals can leverage generative AI capabilities in a wide range of business processes. Activities such as data discovery, dashboard creation, planning model maintenance, and more are benefitting from a boost in core capabilities and an unmatched user experience.</p>
  <p>With the power of natural language processing, end users can easily run analytical queries, simulate driver impacts, plan resource allocations, and auto-generate dashboards and calculations. For example, a business user seeking to understand why gross margins declined in the latest version of a plan could query Joule, which could automatically look through previous plan iterations and attached comments, and uncover the fact that planners were estimating higher commodity costs.</p>
  <p>SAP’s investment in AI and its understanding of the context of business data provides truly limitless potential in unleashing the world of planning and analytics.</p>
  <p>A preview of Joule co-pilot functionality in SAP Analytics Cloud is planned to be available in Q2 2024. Sign up for the preview via the link below.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_135bdf52547a43026234fdf26c84defd9f04f1334.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_135bdf52547a43026234fdf26c84defd9f04f1334.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_135bdf52547a43026234fdf26c84defd9f04f1334.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_135bdf52547a43026234fdf26c84defd9f04f1334.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="574">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>With Joule co-pilot, planning and analytics professionals can prompt Joule to analyze all aspects of extended planning and create new analytical views on the fly, provisioned specially for individual user types</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>SAP Analytics Cloud Compass</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In an increasingly volatile business climate, it is essential to create operational and financial plans and provision BI insights with risk mitigation in mind. This requires the ability to simulate uncertainties and the probability of their impact. Knowing how uncertainties in commodity prices, labor costs, or production volumes will hit your operational expenses or revenue means that companies can quickly prepare and plan counter measures for any scenario.</p>
  <p>SAP Analytics Cloud compass provides Monte Carlo simulation capabilities with a business user-friendly interface. This enables non-technical users to perform real-time multi-variate analysis without prior IT setup or advanced statistical skills.</p>
  <p>Users can perform business simulations directly in SAP Analytics Cloud at a fraction of the time and effort required to perform similar analysis manually. Scenario modeling capabilities will allow comparisons between assumptions, and the reporting of impact variances provides real-time insight, concept validation, and reveals the sensitivity of the drivers chosen. Now customers can identify their major drivers and combinations over time, enabling a better understanding of the dynamics between the data, and how to continuously simulate better and faster. With compass, customers can face the future with confidence.</p>
  <p>A preview of SAP Analytics Cloud compass is planned to be available at the end of Q3 2024. Sign up for the preview via the link below.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b407deea790db28d0775959ab3574632b1f5e085.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b407deea790db28d0775959ab3574632b1f5e085.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1b407deea790db28d0775959ab3574632b1f5e085.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_1b407deea790db28d0775959ab3574632b1f5e085.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>SAP Analytics Cloud compass showing distribution of impact probability on the operating income based on a simulation of uncertainty in inputs such as inflation or other relevant drivers.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="get-started-today">Get Started Today</h3>
  <p>Begin your path toward unlocking the full potential of your business data with SAP Datasphere. Embrace the opportunity to seamlessly integrate and activate your data landscape, propelling your business into a new era of insights and efficiency. Start now and transform how your organization leverages data with SAP Datasphere.</p>
  <p>Start your journey today to bring out your best with SAP data and AI:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><a href="https://www.sap.com/registration/trial.4d48ec23-eadf-4399-8595-ac3f9c66c64f.html">Take a complete tour and try the latest features of SAP Datasphere</a> with the 30-day guided experience.</li>
    <li><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/datasphere/migration.html">Begin your SAP Business Warehouse cloud modernization journey</a> with a free assessment and special offers.</li>
    <li><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/oth/business-data-fabric/index.html?campaigncode=CRM-YJ24-BTP-2560577&#x26;source=blog-glo">Save on costs and learn how to implement a business data fabric architecture</a> with the Total Cost of Ownership study and getting started package</li>
    <li><a href="https://events.sap.com/dataunleashed-previews/en/home">Sign up today for an early preview</a> of the upcoming SAP Datasphere and SAP Analytics Cloud features</li>
  </ul>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Irfan Khan is chief product officer and president for SAP HANA Database &#x26; Analytics.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="deliver-seamless-and-scalable-access-to-mission-critical-business-data">Deliver seamless and scalable access to mission-critical business data</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/datasphere.html">Explore SAP Datasphere</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-data-unleashed</category>
            <category>product/sap-datasphere</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Data Unleashed: The Future Belongs to Data-Driven Organizations]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/future-belongs-to-data-driven-organizations-sap-data-unleashed</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/future-belongs-to-data-driven-organizations-sap-data-unleashed</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With the latest updates to SAP Datasphere, SAP is empowering data-driven organizations to bring out their best. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-data-unleashed</category>
            <category>product/sap-datasphere</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Shapes the Future of Data-Driven Business Transformation with Innovations that Equip Customers to Succeed in the Era of AI]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/future-of-data-driven-business-new-sap-datasphere-capabilities</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/future-of-data-driven-business-new-sap-datasphere-capabilities</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New SAP Datasphere capabilities will drive deeper insights, faster growth and more efficiency in the era of AI. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ca92906e5e003a06f25ac5a8b837a5576894477a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ca92906e5e003a06f25ac5a8b837a5576894477a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1ca92906e5e003a06f25ac5a8b837a5576894477a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Shapes the Future of Data-Driven Business Transformation with Innovations that Equip Customers to Succeed in the Era of AI" src="./media_1ca92906e5e003a06f25ac5a8b837a5576894477a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-shapes-the-future-of-data-driven-business-transformation-with-innovations-that-equip-customers-to-succeed-in-the-era-of-ai">SAP Shapes the Future of Data-Driven Business Transformation with Innovations that Equip Customers to Succeed in the Era of AI</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced transformative data innovations that will help customers harness the full power of their data to drive deeper insights, faster growth and more efficiency in the era of AI. New capabilities in the SAP Datasphere solution, including new generative-AI features, transform enterprise planning through simplified data landscapes and more-intuitive data interaction.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“Capturing data to make better decisions is an enterprise technology imperative that’s become increasingly critical as AI – which relies on quality data – revolutionizes every aspect of business,” said Juergen Mueller, SAP Chief Technology Officer and member of the Executive Board. “Our newest SAP Datasphere innovations, as well as an expanded partnership with Collibra, represent a quantum leap in our ability to help customers drive intelligent business transformations through data.”</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="deliver-seamless-and-scalable-access-to-mission-critical-business-data">Deliver seamless and scalable access to mission-critical business data</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/datasphere.html">Explore SAP Datasphere</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>At the heart of these announcements is the business data fabric, an architecture that helps ensure data is not just an asset but also the core underpinning of strategic initiatives. The innovations and partnership announced today equip organizations to deliver meaningful data to data consumers – with business context and logic intact.</p>
  <p>“We have decided to leverage SAP Datasphere for a modern business data fabric architecture in conjunction with our SAP S/4HANA landscape. It allows us to effectively establish a modern data analytics platform that enables a business self service capability on the basis of trusted data and data models,” said Achim Welter, Senior Director ERP, Digital &#x26; IT Strategy, Hershey’s.</p>
  <p>Today’s SAP Datasphere innovations help customers achieve a unified data view that simplifies their data landscapes while retaining context and logic – enabling them to adapt faster to market changes and make more-efficient decisions. From new copilot and vector database capabilities that help ensure business context remains constant in generative AI outputs to a new knowledge graph that helps uncover insights and patterns in complex data, SAP’s data innovations help ensure customers have the full power of their data at their fingertips.</p>
  <p>Today’s key innovations include:</p>
  <h2 id="generative-ai-copilot-and-ai-governance">Generative-AI Copilot and AI Governance</h2>
  <p>SAP’s generative-AI assistant, the <a href="https://www.sap.com/joule">Joule</a> copilot, is now coming to the SAP Analytics Cloud solution to automate the creation and development of reports, dashboards, plans and more. This automation is enabled by the <strong>SAP HANA Cloud vector engine capabilities,</strong> which combine the power of large language models with the relevant data of your organization – helping ensure business context is a constant for generative-AI outputs.</p>
  <p>Incorporating generative AI across the business isn’t possible without trusted and governed data. To provide organizations with a solution to govern the policies, processes and practices of AI, SAP is announcing an <strong>expansion of our partnership with Collibra</strong> to integrate Collibra’s AI Governance with SAP data assets. This can help provide transparency and accountability for organizations and help ensure regulatory, compliance and privacy policies are met.</p>
  <h2 id="discover-hidden-insights-and-patterns-with-knowledge-graph">Discover Hidden Insights and Patterns with Knowledge Graph</h2>
  <p>With the new <strong>SAP Datasphere knowledge graph,</strong> organizations can discover hidden insights and patterns across their applications and systems. This enables both technical and business users to deeply understand the relationships between data, metadata and business processes, as well as boost the effectiveness of machine learning and large language models.</p>
  <h2 id="unified-and-advanced-planning-and-analytics">Unified and Advanced Planning and Analytics</h2>
  <p>The new SAP Datasphere integration with SAP Analytics Cloud offers a single data management system and advanced analytics to power cross-organizational planning. Planners can leverage a single flexible model to break down silos between planning using one tool for data preparation, modeling and planning.</p>
  <p>Additionally, business users can use the <strong>new compass</strong> capability in SAP Analytics Cloud to realize better outcomes in planning and analytics through data-driven simulation. It enables organizations to run complex simulations using a chat interface to evaluate predictive outcomes and continually adjust controllable variables to find the optimal plan.</p>
  <p>This supports customers to transform their planning by unifying financial, operational, supply chain and workforce planning with native connection to SAP applications and third-party data.</p>
  <p>To learn more, please read: <strong><a href="/">Unleashing the Latest SAP Data and Analytics Innovations</a></strong>.</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="take-a-guided-tour-and-experience-firsthand-the-power-of-business-data-with-sap-datasphere">Take a guided tour and experience firsthand the power of business data with SAP Datasphere</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/datasphere/guided-experience.html">Start now</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>About SAP</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP’s strategy is to help every business run as an intelligent, sustainable enterprise. As a market leader in enterprise application software, we help companies of all sizes and in all industries run at their best: SAP customers generate 87% of total global commerce. Our machine learning, Internet of Things (IoT), and advanced analytics technologies help turn customers’ businesses into intelligent enterprises. SAP helps give people and organizations deep business insight and fosters collaboration that helps them stay ahead of their competition. We simplify technology for companies so they can consume our software the way they want – without disruption. Our end-to-end suite of applications and services enables business and public customers across 26 industries globally to operate profitably, adapt continuously, and make a difference. With a global network of customers, partners, employees, and thought leaders, SAP helps the world run better and improve people’s lives. For more information, visit <a href="http://www.sap.com">www.sap.com</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Note to editors:</strong><br>To preview and download broadcast-standard stock footage and press photos digitally, please visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/photos">www.sap.com/photos</a>. On this platform, you can find high resolution material for your media channels.</p>
  <p><strong>For customers interested in learning more about SAP products:</strong><br>Global Customer Center: +49 180 534-34-24<br>United States Only: 1 (800) 872-1SAP (1-800-872-1727)</p>
  <p><strong>For more information, press only:</strong><br>Julia Fargel, +1 (650) 276-8964, <a href="mailto:julia.fargel@sap.com">julia.fargel@sap.com</a>, PT<br>Martin Gwisdalla, +49 (6227) 767 275, <a href="mailto:martin.gwisdalla@sap.com">martin.gwisdalla@sap.com</a>, CET<br><a href="mailto:SAP%20Press%20Room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>This document contains forward-looking statements, which are predictions, projections, or other statements about future events. These statements are based on current expectations, forecasts, and assumptions that are subject to risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results and outcomes to materially differ. Additional information regarding these risks and uncertainties may be found in our filings with the Securities and Exchange Commission, including but not limited to the risk factors section of SAP’s 2023 Annual Report on Form 20-F.<br>© 2024 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.<br>Please consider our <a href="https://www.sap.com/corporate/en/legal/privacy.html">privacy policy</a>. If you received this press release in your e-mail and you wish to unsubscribe to our mailing list please contact <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a> and write Unsubscribe in the subject line.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-data-unleashed</category>
            <category>product/sap-datasphere</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Modernize SAP Business Warehouse with SAP Datasphere and Its Open Data Ecosystem]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/modernize-sap-bw-with-sap-datasphere-open-data-ecosystem</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/modernize-sap-bw-with-sap-datasphere-open-data-ecosystem</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is now offering a limited-time, complimentary SAP BW system assessment to help you optimize your transition to SAP Datasphere.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16bae8ef497f5c9c6bdf1b5fdaf69f1f911aad108.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16bae8ef497f5c9c6bdf1b5fdaf69f1f911aad108.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_16bae8ef497f5c9c6bdf1b5fdaf69f1f911aad108.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Modernize SAP Business Warehouse with SAP Datasphere and Its Open Data Ecosystem" src="./media_16bae8ef497f5c9c6bdf1b5fdaf69f1f911aad108.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="modernize-sap-business-warehouse-with-sap-datasphere-and-its-open-data-ecosystem">Modernize SAP Business Warehouse with SAP Datasphere and Its Open Data Ecosystem</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Many SAP Business Warehouse (SAP BW) customers are seeking to leverage cloud-based solutions but want to ensure that their previous investments are safeguarded. While the benefits of modernizing to the cloud are clear, customers need a flexible path that builds upon their existing technology and talent.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP Datasphere can offer that path. Its native connectivity to SAP BW means customers can reuse up to 80% of existing SAP BW content, retaining value while adding cloud speed, scale, and interoperability and avoiding costly and unnecessary rework.</p>
  <p>Delivering meaningful data to every data professional requires a comprehensive cloud data service. With SAP Datasphere, organizations can:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Access authoritative data, accelerating time-to-value by automatically reusing the semantical definitions and associations from SAP applications.</li>
    <li>Enrich all data projects, harmonizing heterogeneous data into a business semantic model of their diverse data landscapes.</li>
    <li>Simplify the data landscape, accessing all their data across hybrid and cloud environments no matter where it resides.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>SAP has also partnered with an open data ecosystem of leading technology vendors to provide tailored integration between SAP Datasphere and their solutions. The first set of industry-leading data and AI vendors includes Collibra, Confluent, Databricks, DataRobot, and Google Cloud. By closely integrating their data and AI platforms with SAP Datasphere, organizations can access their mission-critical business data across any cloud infrastructure.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="transition-to-a-modern-business-data-fabric-at-your-pace-with-sap-datasphere">Transition to a modern business data fabric at your pace with SAP Datasphere</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/datasphere/migration.html#migration">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="flexible-paths-to-the-cloud">Flexible Paths to the Cloud</h2>
  <p>Many SAP BW users have always-on projects that depend on SAP BW data and objects, which requires flexibility in modernizing to the cloud.</p>
  <p>SAP offers flexible paths. Whether you’re moving directly or integrating SAP Datasphere as part of your data landscape to enhance your SAP BW deployment, there’s a strategy:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Gradually transition functionality over time using <a href="https://community.sap.com/topics/datasphere/bw-bridge">SAP Datasphere, SAP BW bridge</a> to reuse and integrate SAP BW objects.</li>
    <li>Leverage SAP BW data ingestion and staging to accelerate the move or, for SAP Business Suite customers without SAP BW, move directly to SAP Datasphere.</li>
    <li>In some cases, migrate SAP BW systems to SAP Datasphere for a complete transition.</li>
    <li>Modernize with a combination of SAP Datasphere and SAP HANA Cloud to benefit from the capabilities of both solutions. SAP Datasphere can provide the foundation for a business data fabric, while SAP HANA Cloud enables the development of intelligent data applications.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>The goal is to provide options to fit each customer’s unique environment and timeline. With the right approach, the move to SAP Datasphere can be straightforward while optimizing previous investments.</p>
  <p>Our experienced SAP partners understand the importance of flexible paths. They work with our customers to outline customized modernization paths that can safeguard their technology and fit their goals.</p>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div>We are excited to help SAP BW customers experience the power of SAP Datasphere. We’ve already seen multiple customers take this modernization approach and it’s the ideal modernization path to protect the customer’s existing SAP BW investments.</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>Deepu Sasidharan, Vice President, Analytics, Applexus</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>No matter which path a customer takes, they can always progress to SAP Datasphere. Technically, this can be achieved with the support of SAP Datasphere, SAP BW bridge and modernization tools. That’s why customers like <a href="https://www.sap.com/asset/dynamic/2022/7/cd349586-5fc8-4a25-8486-4204460ca03d.html">Nipro</a> chose SAP Datasphere.</p>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div>SAP Datasphere, SAP BW bridge is a complete game changer. The cloud architecture allows us to simplify our landscape. We are also seeing significant improvements in our performance.</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>Iaroslav Korzh, SAP Technology Manager, Nipro Europe Group Companies</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="new-professional-readiness-assessment">New Professional Readiness Assessment</h2>
  <p>Whether you’re starting fresh or modernizing an existing system, having a solid plan is key for a successful move to the cloud.</p>
  <p>SAP is now offering a limited-time, complimentary SAP BW system assessment to help you optimize your transition to SAP Datasphere. Through this assessment, you can gain insight into your SAP BW environment and learn which objects are active and frequently used and whether they can be migrated.</p>
  <p>This assessment helps deliver a reliable basis for an actionable modernization plan. With the right information, you can modernize on your terms. Get started today by applying for your complimentary <a href="https://www.sap.com/registration/free-assessment-offer-for-bw-customers.html">assessment</a>.</p>
  <h2 id="get-started">Get Started</h2>
  <p>Visit our <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/datasphere/migration.html#migration">Web site</a> for the latest modernization tools, including our <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2023/10/96cfbee0-8f7e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">getting started guide</a>, <a href="https://community.sap.com/t5/technology-blogs-by-sap/watch-the-sap-bw-modernization-webinar-series/ba-p/13699559">technical deep dive webinar series</a>, and <a href="https://www.sap.com/registration/free-assessment-offer-for-bw-customers.html">professional readiness assessment</a>.</p>
  <p>SAP BW customers moving to SAP Datasphere may also qualify for exclusive incentives. Contact your SAP representative before this limited-time opportunity expires.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Daniel Yu is senior vice president of Solution Management and Product Marketing for SAP Data and Analytics.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-sap-news-delivered-to-your-inbox-once-a-week">Get the latest SAP news delivered to your inbox once a week</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/nl/sap-news-center-newsletter/index.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/data-fabric</category>
            <category>news-tag/database-and-data-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-warehouse</category>
            <category>product/sap-datasphere</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Recognized as a Leader in 2023 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Data Integration Tools]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/sap-a-leader-gartner-magic-quadrant-data-integration-tools</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/sap-a-leader-gartner-magic-quadrant-data-integration-tools</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[For the 16th consecutive time, Gartner has recognized SAP as a Leader in its Magic Quadrant for Data Integration Tools.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18676e13249083c87480612ffdb6501c1181d00cd.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18676e13249083c87480612ffdb6501c1181d00cd.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_18676e13249083c87480612ffdb6501c1181d00cd.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Recognized as a Leader in 2023 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Data Integration Tools" src="./media_18676e13249083c87480612ffdb6501c1181d00cd.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-recognized-as-a-leader-in-2023-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-data-integration-tools">SAP Recognized as a Leader in 2023 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Data Integration Tools</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>We are proud to announce that Gartner has recognized SAP as a Leader in its 2023 <a href="https://www.gartner.com/reprints/?id=1-2FTDYPZU&#x26;ct=231204&#x26;st=sb">Magic Quadrant for Data Integration Tools</a> for the 16th consecutive time.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-an-engaging-hands-on-experience-with-sap-datasphere">Get an engaging, hands-on experience with SAP Datasphere</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/datasphere/guided-experience.html">Start now</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>To achieve true digital transformation, organizations must have seamless access to their mission-critical business data no matter where it resides. Yet with data landscapes distributed among different applications and systems both in the cloud and on premises, organizations spend countless resources extracting, rebuilding, and integrating their data.</p>
  <p>By leveraging the right data integration tools and strategies, organizations can easily discover, connect, integrate, govern, and orchestrate their data assets. Data integration offerings from SAP deliver trusted, relevant, and timely information to enable customers to simplify their data landscape and unleash the power of business data. Our primary solutions include <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/datasphere.html">SAP Datasphere</a>, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/cloud-platform/capabilities/integration.html">SAP Data Intelligence</a> Cloud, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/data-services.html">SAP Data Services</a>, and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/cloud-platform/capabilities/integration.html">SAP Integration Suite</a>. These offerings are part of <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">SAP Business Technology Platform</a> (SAP BTP).</p>
  <p>Gartner evaluated 21 vendors and named SAP a Leader based on our “ability to execute” and “completeness of vision.” We believe this recognition serves as acknowledgment of SAP’s continued commitment to providing our customers with world-class data integration tools.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b4a7dd1fbccb32babb1428357e9df797fb738917.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b4a7dd1fbccb32babb1428357e9df797fb738917.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1b4a7dd1fbccb32babb1428357e9df797fb738917.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_1b4a7dd1fbccb32babb1428357e9df797fb738917.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="926" height="1024">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>This graphic was published by Gartner, Inc. as part of a larger research document and should be evaluated in the context of the entire document. The Gartner document is available upon request from SAP here.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="unleash-the-power-of-business-data">Unleash the Power of Business Data</h2>
  <p>Data integration is necessary for customers to gain intelligent, relevant, and contextual insights for better decision-making. However, without the right data management approach and technology, companies can face an uphill battle in integrating, processing, curating, governing, and augmenting their data.</p>
  <p>SAP takes a business data fabric approach, which goes beyond a traditional data fabric. A business data fabric is a data management architecture that delivers an integrated, semantically rich data layer over underlying data landscapes to provide users with scalable access to their data without duplication.</p>
  <p>It eliminates the need to recreate the business context that was lost from extracting and replicating data. This gives users the ability to accelerate their decision-making with trust and confidence, knowing they always have the complete picture of their data regardless of where it is stored or how it was designed.</p>
  <p>SAP Datasphere — and its open data ecosystem — is the foundation for a business data fabric. It equips any organization to deliver meaningful data to every data consumer — with business context and logic intact. SAP Datasphere helps customers:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Access authoritative data:</strong> Accelerate time-to-value by automatically reusing the semantical definitions and associations from SAP applications</li>
    <li><strong>Enrich all data projects:</strong> Harmonize heterogeneous data into a business semantic model of diverse data landscape</li>
    <li><strong>Simplify the data landscape:</strong> Access all data across hybrid and cloud environments no matter where it resides</li>
  </ul>
  <p>With a unified experience for data integration, data cataloging, semantic modeling, data warehousing, data federation, and data virtualization, SAP Datasphere enables data professionals to easily distribute authoritative business data — with business context and logic preserved — across the data landscape.</p>
  <p>Since the launch of SAP Datasphere, we have seen tremendous growth of customers innovating with this technology. For example, Messer CIO David Johnston describes his experience with the solution this way:“The business data fabric architecture enables us to bring SAP and non-SAP data together in the seamless and self-service way we’ve been envisioning. SAP Datasphere provided us with a solution to build a harmonized layer, or business data fabric, across SAP and non-SAP, cloud or on-premise data sources, making the best use of our existing investments in SAP, Microsoft Azure, Salesforce, and Oracle.”</p>
  <h2 id="next-steps">Next Steps</h2>
  <p>For over 16 years, data integration tools from SAP have enabled our customers to turn disjoined data assets into actionable business insights at scale. Take the next step and begin your business data fabric journey today:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Visit the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/datasphere.html">SAP Datasphere page</a></li>
    <li>Try the free <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/datasphere/guided-experience.html">SAP Datasphere guided experience</a></li>
    <li>Read the <a href="https://www.gartner.com/reprints/?id=1-2FTDYPZU&#x26;ct=231204&#x26;st=sb">2023 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Data Integration Tools report</a></li>
  </ul>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Kaiser Larsen is vice president of Data and Analytics at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Gartner, Magic Quadrant for Data Integration Tools, Ehtisham Zaidi, Robert Thanaraj, Sharat Menon, Thornton Craig, Roxane Edjlali, Michele Launi, 4 December 2023<br>Gartner does not endorse any vendor, product or service depicted in its research publications and does not advise technology users to select only those vendors with the highest ratings or other designation. Gartner research publications consist of the opinions of Gartner’s Research &#x26; Advisory organization and should not be construed as statements of fact. Gartner disclaims all warranties, expressed or implied, with respect to this research, including any warranties of merchantability or fitness for a particular purpose.<br>GARTNER is a registered trademark and service mark of Gartner, Inc. and/or its affiliates in the U.S. and internationally, Magic Quadrant is a registered trademark of Gartner, Inc. and/or its affiliates and is used herein with permission. All rights reserved.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/data-fabric</category>
            <category>news-tag/data-integration</category>
            <category>news-tag/database-and-data-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/magic-quadrant</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-datasphere</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[North American Customers Continue Turning to SAP in Q3 2023]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/north-american-customers-q3-2023</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/north-american-customers-q3-2023</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In the Q3 2023, our North American customers spanned all shapes, sizes, and industries, proving the momentum behind the cloud revolution.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/grow-with-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>product/sap-datasphere</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-north-america</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How HCLTech Uses SAP BTP Innovations to Combat Water Scarcity]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/hcltech-uses-sap-btp-combat-water-scarcity</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/hcltech-uses-sap-btp-combat-water-scarcity</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP partner and global tech company HCLTech is tackling the problem of water scarcity with its AquaSphere solution. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/blockchain</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-datasphere</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Kemira Leaps Forward with SAP and cbs Corporate Business Solutions]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/kemira-leaps-forward-with-sap-and-cbs</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/kemira-leaps-forward-with-sap-and-cbs</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Industrial enterprise Kemira launched its digital business process platform based on SAP with help from cbs Corporate Business Solutions.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/chemicals</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-datasphere</category>
            <category>product/sap-integration-suite</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP and Google Cloud Enhance Open Data Cloud With New Generative AI Solutions for Enterprises]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/sap-google-cloud-partnership-open-data-cloud-new-generative-ai-solutions-for-enterprises</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/sap-google-cloud-partnership-open-data-cloud-new-generative-ai-solutions-for-enterprises</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The expanded SAP and Google Cloud partnership will launch new generative AI-powered industry solutions supporting improved sustainability.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>industry/automotive</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/google-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
            <category>product/sap-datasphere</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Data and Analytics Solutions Earn Multiple 2023 Best Of Awards from TrustRadius]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/06/sap-data-and-analytics-solutions-trustradius-awards</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/06/sap-data-and-analytics-solutions-trustradius-awards</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP data and analytics solutions have won multiple Best Of awards from TrustRadius, recognizing our excellence in the industry. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/data-analytics</category>
            <category>news-tag/database-and-data-management</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-datasphere</category>
            <category>product/sap-hana-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/trustradius</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Innovating with SAP Business Technology Platform]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/innovating-with-sap-btp</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/innovating-with-sap-btp</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[At SAP Sapphire, we introduced new SAP BTP capabilities in application development, automation, integration, data and analytics, and AI.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-build</category>
            <category>product/sap-datasphere</category>
            <category>product/sap-integration-suite</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-signavio</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Defining the Future Through Innovation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/sap-sapphire-orlando-keynote-defining-future-through-innovation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/sap-sapphire-orlando-keynote-defining-future-through-innovation</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In a keynote at SAP Sapphire, Thomas Saueressig and Juergen Mueller highlighted the innovations the company is delivering to its customers.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/green-ledger</category>
            <category>news-tag/grow-with-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>product/sap-datasphere</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP and Google Cloud Expand Partnership to Build the Future of Open Data and AI for Enterprises]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/sap-google-cloud-expanded-partnership-open-data-ai-enterprises</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/sap-google-cloud-expanded-partnership-open-data-ai-enterprises</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP and Google Cloud are introducing an open data offering designed to simplify data landscapes and unleash the power of business data.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/google-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/machine-learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-datasphere</category>
            <category>product/sap-hana-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Three Key Highlights from the Gartner Data & Analytics Summit 2023]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/three-key-highlights-gartner-data-analytics-summit</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/three-key-highlights-gartner-data-analytics-summit</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[At the Gartner Data & Analytics Summit attendees explored recent data and analytics trends, technologies, and strategies, like SAP Datasphere.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/data-analytics</category>
            <category>news-tag/data-fabric</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-datasphere</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unleashing the Power of Business Data with SAP Datasphere]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/sap-datasphere-power-of-business-data</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/sap-datasphere-power-of-business-data</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Datasphere and its open data ecosystem comprise the technology foundation that enables a business data fabric. Learn more now.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-data-unleashed</category>
            <category>product/sap-datasphere</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Partner Quotes: SAP Introduces SAP Datasphere]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/sap-introduces-sap-datasphere-partner-quotes</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/sap-introduces-sap-datasphere-partner-quotes</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP has introduced SAP Datasphere to give customers access to mission-critical data. Read the SAP partner comments on the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/statement</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-data-unleashed</category>
            <category>product/sap-datasphere</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Introduces SAP Datasphere to Simplify Customers’ Data Landscape – Partners with Collibra, Confluent, Databricks and DataRobot]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/sap-datasphere-simplify-data-landscape-partnerships-collibra-confluent-databricks-datarobot</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/sap-datasphere-simplify-data-landscape-partnerships-collibra-confluent-databricks-datarobot</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With SAP Datasphere, SAP announces key innovations and partnerships that enable faster time to insights and better business decision-making.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-data-unleashed</category>
            <category>product/sap-datasphere</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Deeper Look Into How SAP Datasphere Enables a Business Data Fabric]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2023/03/sap-datasphere-business-data-fabric</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2023/03/sap-datasphere-business-data-fabric</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Datasphere leads to seamless and scalable access to mission-critical business data. Take a deep dive into its capabilities.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/executive-blog</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-data-unleashed</category>
            <category>product/sap-datasphere</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>