<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/product/sap-sales-cloud/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Infuses Business AI Throughout Its Enterprise Cloud Portfolio and Partners with Cutting-Edge AI Leaders to Bring Out Customers’ Best]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-sapphire-news-business-ai-enterprise-cloud-portfolio-cutting-edge-partnerships</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-sapphire-news-business-ai-enterprise-cloud-portfolio-cutting-edge-partnerships</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New SAP Business AI innovations and collaborations with partners are igniting ingenuity. Read the news from SAP Sapphire Orlando in 2024.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18ff27978e1178b1dce994986e74f4cc1f6087f26.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18ff27978e1178b1dce994986e74f4cc1f6087f26.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_18ff27978e1178b1dce994986e74f4cc1f6087f26.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Infuses Business AI Throughout Its Enterprise Cloud Portfolio and Partners with Cutting-Edge AI Leaders to Bring Out Customers’ Best" src="./media_18ff27978e1178b1dce994986e74f4cc1f6087f26.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-infuses-business-ai-throughout-its-enterprise-cloud-portfolio-and-partners-with-cutting-edge-ai-leaders-to-bring-out-customers-best">SAP Infuses Business AI Throughout Its Enterprise Cloud Portfolio and Partners with Cutting-Edge AI Leaders to Bring Out Customers’ Best</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>SAP Business AI Innovations and Collaborations with Partners including Google Cloud, Meta, Microsoft, Mistral AI and NVIDIA Ignite Ingenuity</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <table>
          <thead>
            <tr>
              <th>Text Large</th>
            </tr>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td><strong><em>ORLANDO</em></strong> — At its annual SAP Sapphire conference, SAP unveiled generative AI innovations and partnerships that showcase how the company is taking business to the next level in the era of AI.</td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="taking-business-to-the-next-level-in-the-era-of-ai">Taking Business to the Next Level in the Era of AI</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/events/sapphire/news-guide.html">Read the news guide</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>By infusing Business AI across an enterprise cloud portfolio that powers the world’s most mission-critical processes and partnering with companies pushing the edge of what’s possible with AI, SAP is igniting a new wave of insight and ingenuity in global business.</p>
  <p>“The Business AI innovations we’re announcing at SAP Sapphire in 2024 will redefine the way businesses run,” says Christian Klein, CEO and member of the Executive Board of SAP SE. “Today’s AI announcements and partnerships build on our commitment to deliver revolutionary technology that drives real-world results, helping customers unleash the agility and ingenuity they need to succeed in today’s fast-moving business landscape.”</p>
  <h2 id="ai-that-means-business">AI That Means Business</h2>
  <p>As SAP embeds Business AI across its enterprise solutions, it puts rich insights at users’ fingertips, empowering them to deliver better outcomes and elevate the creative problem-solving humans do best. Examples include AI-generated reports in SAP SuccessFactors solutions that give people managers responsibly sourced insights for compensation-related discussions as well as forecasting capabilities in SAP Sales Cloud solutions that predict combinations of salespeople and products most likely to drive sales. Meanwhile, the SAP Business Technology Platform is adding large language models from Amazon Web Services, Meta and Mistral AI to its generative AI hub. This capability in the SAP AI Core infrastructure makes it easier to build generative AI use cases for SAP applications.</p>
  <p>SAP’s generative AI copilot Joule, which quickly sorts and contextualizes data from multiple systems to advance automation and improve decision-making, is expanding throughout the company’s solution portfolio. Joule launched in <a href="/2023/09/joule-new-generative-ai-assistant">SAP SuccessFactors solutions last fall</a> and is now embedded into SAP S/4HANA Cloud solutions and others including SAP Build and SAP Integration Suite. Further expansion by year-end will include SAP Ariba and SAP Analytics Cloud solutions. At Sapphire, SAP also announced <a href="/">plans to further broaden Joule’s scope</a> by integrating it with Microsoft Copilot to surface even richer insights. This deep, bi-directional integration gives users a unified experience built right into the flow of work, enabling seamless access to information from interactions with business applications in SAP and Microsoft 365.</p>
  <p>Reflecting Business AI’s increasing importance, SAP is redoubling its commitment to the principles of relevant, reliable, and responsible AI it pioneered. At Sapphire, SAP is adopting the 10 guiding principles of the UNESCO Recommendation on the Ethics of Artificial Intelligence, which aim to ensure that AI technologies are developed and used in ways that respect human rights, promote fairness and contribute to sustainable development.</p>
  <h2 id="partnerships-that-scale-innovation">Partnerships That Scale Innovation</h2>
  <p>SAP is partnering with best-in-class technology leaders to push the limits of what generative AI can do at an enterprise level. In addition to our expanded collaborations with <a href="/2024/05/aws-sap-generative-ai-new-innovation">AWS</a> and Microsoft, partnerships with Google Cloud, Meta, Mistral AI and NVIDIA ensure SAP can harness the power of AI-ready technology to innovate at speed and deliver richer real-world results.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Google Cloud</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP and Google Cloud are expanding their partnership, using Business AI to help enterprises better predict and mitigate supply-chain risks to minimize disruptions and maintain optimal inventory levels. The companies will integrate Joule and the SAP Integrated Business Planning for Supply Chain solution with Google Cloud’s Gemini models AI assistant and Google Cloud Cortex Framework’s data foundation.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Meta</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP will leverage Meta Llama 3 to generate scripts that render highly customized analytics applications in SAP Analytics Cloud. Meta’s next-generation AI model excels at language nuances and contextual understanding, making it an ideal candidate for translating enterprise business requirements into tangible outcomes.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Mistral AI</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP will also add <a href="/">new large language models from Mistral AI</a>, a global company headquartered in Paris specializing in generative AI, to the generative AI hub capability in SAP AI Core.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>NVIDIA</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP and NVIDIA Corporation advance a <a href="https://blogs.nvidia.com/blog/sap-sapphire-ai-omniverse/">cross-product partnership</a> to embed cutting-edge technologies into enterprise-ready business applications:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>As SAP trains Joule to serve as an AI assistant for the RISE with SAP solution implementations, NVIDIA’s state-of-the-art AI models sift through SAP consulting assets to provide relevant and precise answers to implementation-related questions;</li>
    <li>As SAP embeds Joule in the ABAP Cloud model to generate ABAP code for SAP developers, NVIDIA’s accelerated infrastructure will run, scale, and manage SAP’s generative AI model for ABAP code generation;</li>
    <li>As SAP infuses generative AI into the SAP Intelligent Product Recommendation solution, NVIDIA Omniverse Cloud APIs enable the simulation of complex manufacturing products and configurations as industrial digital twins.</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="cloud-technology-that-drives-agility-and-sustainability">Cloud Technology That Drives Agility and Sustainability</h2>
  <p>Business success in the era of AI means being in the cloud. SAP is making the move easier than ever with initiatives that help customers find partners with the expertise needed for complex SAP S/4HANA Cloud transformations. Further cloud innovations at SAP Sapphire include features that help the world’s organizations measure, manage and execute their sustainability strategies. SAP Sustainability Control Tower and SAP Sustainability Footprint Management solutions now track carbon footprints at scale and help businesses meet regulatory standards.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><a href="https://www.sap.com/events/sapphire/news-guide.html">Learn more in the 2024 SAP Sapphire News Guide</a>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Visit the <a href="/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-news-and-coverage-from-sap-sapphire-in-2024">Get the latest news and coverage from SAP Sapphire in 2024</h3>
        <p><em><a href="/topics/sap-sapphire">Read more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>About SAP</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As a global leader in enterprise applications and business AI, SAP (NYSE:SAP) stands at the nexus of business and technology. For over 50 years, organizations have trusted SAP to bring out their best by uniting business-critical operations spanning finance, procurement, HR, supply chain, and customer experience. For more information, visit <a href="http://www.sap.com">www.sap.com</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Note to editors:</strong><br>To preview and download broadcast-standard stock footage and press photos digitally, please visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/photos">www.sap.com/photos</a>. On this platform, you can find high resolution material for your media channels.</p>
  <p><strong>For customers interested in learning more about SAP products:</strong><br>Global Customer Center: +49 180 534-34-24<br>United States Only: 1 (800) 872-1SAP (1-800-872-1727)</p>
  <p><strong>For more information, press only:</strong><br>Joellen Perry, +1 (650) 445-6780, <a href="mailto:joellen.perry@sap.com">joellen.perry@sap.com</a> PT<br>Marcus Winkler, +49 6227-767497, <a href="mailto:marcus.winkler@sap.com">marcus.winkler@sap.com</a> CET<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>This document contains forward-looking statements, which are predictions, projections, or other statements about future events. These statements are based on current expectations, forecasts, and assumptions that are subject to risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results and outcomes to materially differ. Additional information regarding these risks and uncertainties may be found in our filings with the Securities and Exchange Commission, including but not limited to the risk factors section of SAP’s 2023 Annual Report on Form 20-F.<br>© 2024 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.<br>Please consider our <a href="https://www.sap.com/corporate/en/legal/privacy.html">privacy policy</a>. If you receive this press release in your e-mail and you wish to unsubscribe to our mailing list please contact <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a> and write Unsubscribe in the subject line.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/abap-cloud</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-sales-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-footprint-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Expanded Partnership Turns Transactions into Lasting Connections]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/expanded-sap-preferred-success-sales-services-lasting-connections</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/expanded-sap-preferred-success-sales-services-lasting-connections</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Preferred Success for SAP Sales Cloud and SAP Service Cloud, expanded edition, helps businesses create personalized customer experiences.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-preferred-success</category>
            <category>product/sap-sales-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-service-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Debuts New CX Generative AI Capabilities to Enhance Customer Experiences and Boost Business Operations]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/new-cx-generative-ai-capabilities</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/new-cx-generative-ai-capabilities</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[From SAP Customer Experience LIVE, SAP has announced new generative AI capabilities for the CX solution portfolio. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>product/sap-customer-data-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-customer-experience</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-customer-experience-live</category>
            <category>product/sap-emarsys-customer-engagement</category>
            <category>product/sap-sales-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-service-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How PILLER Increased Customer Service with SAP Customer Experience Solutions]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/piller-increased-customer-service-sap-cx</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/piller-increased-customer-service-sap-cx</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With the help of SAP, PILLER was able to share information and optimize business processes across sales, service, and marketing.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_183ba6c7acd6d09f1a49eb03d61c336ed1830707f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_183ba6c7acd6d09f1a49eb03d61c336ed1830707f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_183ba6c7acd6d09f1a49eb03d61c336ed1830707f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="How PILLER Increased Customer Service with SAP Customer Experience Solutions" src="./media_183ba6c7acd6d09f1a49eb03d61c336ed1830707f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="how-piller-increased-customer-service-with-sap-customer-experience-solutions">How PILLER Increased Customer Service with SAP Customer Experience Solutions</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><a href="https://www.piller.de/">PILLER Blowers &#x26; Compressors</a> produces high-performance blowers and compressors and customized solutions to meet specific requirements of various industries. Its global network of wholly owned subsidiaries and joint ventures enables it to serve an international customer base.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>To increase customer service quality, the company wanted to share information and optimize business processes across its sales, service, and marketing activities.</p>
  <h2 id="moving-from-manual-processes-to-integrated-activities">Moving from Manual Processes to Integrated Activities</h2>
  <p>At PILLER, different departments were using their own IT solutions.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-customer-experience-solutions-help-connect-customer-data-improve-loyalty-and-grow-your-business">SAP Customer Experience solutions help connect customer data, improve loyalty, and grow your business</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The service department had manual processes, such as Microsoft Excel spreadsheets, to dispatch service technicians. The technicians were logging into a central server to retrieve data and recording customer support by e-mails and conversations. The sales department had a basic access environment due to custom-made products with individual serial numbers. There was no master data; tailored sales quotes were done on paper, posing challenges for data updating and quality. The marketing department was conducting its business, like capturing trade-fair leads or planning and executing campaigns, by hand and with spreadsheets. All these manual activities were time intensive and prone to human error.</p>
  <p>To enable the marketing, sales, and service teams to perform to the best of their abilities, PILLER wanted solutions that allowed it to share important information. It wished to harmonize all customer-related processes, from initial contact and order management to delivery of spare parts and follow-up.</p>
  <p>“For new products or customers, it’s important that real-time master data in our core software is mirrored in our sales, service, and marketing systems. We can do this by integrating SAP Customer Experience solutions and SAP Field Service Management with SAP S/4HANA,” said Frank Münzner, in-house SAP consultant for Lead to Cash at PILLER Blowers &#x26; Compressors GmbH.</p>
  <h2 id="adopting-cloud-solutions-to-achieve-innovative-customer-service">Adopting Cloud Solutions to Achieve Innovative Customer Service</h2>
  <p>PILLER employed the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm/sales-cloud.html">SAP Sales Cloud</a> solution to help address the needs of its sales team and integrate functionalities, such as managing quotes and orders, in one place. The solution offers a search capability and a modern, intuitive user interface.</p>
  <p>The company is using the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/field-service-management.html">SAP Field Service Management mobile app</a> to help create service tickets, which are the single point of customer contact, with product serial numbers and metadata. Integrating this mobile app with the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm/service-cloud.html">SAP Service Cloud</a> solution can enable technicians to receive service ticket information on an Apple iPad, so they can have everything they need to carry out their work. This can also translate to good customer support.</p>
  <p>By deploying the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm/marketing.html">SAP Marketing Cloud</a> solution and integrating it with SAP Sales Cloud, PILLER now proactively shares data, such as service tickets, lead opportunities, and customer contacts, between the sales and marketing teams. This lets the company contact a customer with a warranty option or service cost reduction, for example.</p>
  <p>PILLER has now integrated the three SAP Customer Experience solutions for sales, service, and marketing and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/field-service-management.html">SAP Field Service Management</a> with <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/s4hana.html">SAP S/4HANA</a>, the company’s enterprise resource planning (ERP) software.</p>
  <p>PILLER partnered with <a href="https://www.fis-gmbh.de/en/">FIS Global</a> to gain advice about new functionalities and implementation support, while <a href="https://www.ibsolution.com/en/">IBsolution</a> provided guidance around leveraging the potential in terms of business transformation and digitization.</p>
  <h2 id="gaining-comprehensive-customer-visibility-with-integrated-solutions">Gaining Comprehensive Customer Visibility with Integrated Solutions</h2>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="resolve-customer-issues-faster-with-proactive-ai-enabled-field-service-management-software-from-sap">Resolve customer issues faster with proactive, AI-enabled field service management software from SAP</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/field-service-management.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The major advantage in connecting the SAP Customer Experience portfolio, SAP Field Service Management, and SAP S/4HANA is that real-time data can be available across all these solutions. While master data, such as for a new product, customer, or material, is entered and kept in SAP S/4HANA as the core software, it’s automatically pushed into the other integrated solutions.</p>
  <p>This is helping PILLER deliver highly efficient and innovative customer service and business models. The company gains a comprehensive view of worldwide customers in real time while interacting with them at each stage of their journey in a targeted manner.</p>
  <p>There are now customer-related processes across departments, sites, and systems as well as consistent communication throughout the company, thanks to standardized forms and templates. The business is achieving agile sales with faster response times and better allocation of target groups. It’s also making decisions for customer management based on facts and analyses.</p>
  <p>Other benefits the company achieved were:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>360-degree view of customers worldwide in real time</li>
    <li>90% less paper with digital processes</li>
    <li>30% reduction in effort by using digital processes</li>
  </ul>
  <p>“We’ve always combined tradition with innovation when manufacturing our blowers. With SAP Customer Experience solutions, our customer management operations are superior to those of our competitors. We’re able to keep a close eye on processes and respond quickly and accordingly,” said Thomas Henzler, CIO at PILLER Blowers &#x26; Compressors GmbH.</p>
  <h2 id="rolling-out-customer-centric-solutions">Rolling Out Customer-Centric Solutions</h2>
  <p>Combining <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm.html">SAP Customer Experience solutions</a> and the SAP Field Service Management mobile app with SAP S/4HANA is helping deliver real-time data for integrated processes.</p>
  <p>The integration of the SAP Field Service Management mobile app with SAP Service Cloud is being piloted with three service technicians and garnering positive feedback so far.</p>
  <p>Watch an <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm/sales-cloud.html?video=189daad3-437e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b">overview video</a> of SAP Sales Cloud to help build lasting customer relationships and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm/service-cloud.html?pdf-asset=983be5bb-b27d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff&#x26;page=1">learn more about SAP Service Cloud</a> to maximize customer lifetime value with connected service. Read about the benefits companies achieved with <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/customer-stories/topcon.html">SAP Customer Experience solutions</a>. View a <a href="https://www.sap.com/sea/products/scm/field-service-management/features.html?video=66ec8033-617e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b">solution demo</a> and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/field-service-management/features.html?video=f83398c5-247e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b">overview video</a> to learn how to maximize productivity and asset uptime with SAP Field Service Management. <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/field-service-management.html?video=14f5efa9-427e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b">Learn what benefits other enterprises achieved</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Karin Fent is senior director of Global Customer Success Digital Supply Chain at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-sap-news-delivered-to-your-inbox-once-a-week">Get the latest SAP news delivered to your inbox once a week</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/nl/sap-news-center-newsletter/index.html">Sign Up</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/field-service-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-customer-experience</category>
            <category>product/sap-marketing-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>product/sap-sales-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-service-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Delivers the Future of Intelligent Customer Experience for Utilities]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/future-intelligent-cx-for-utilities</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/future-intelligent-cx-for-utilities</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[An industry-first approach to CX for utilities allows for involving end customers in the energy transition journey. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>product/sap-commerce-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-customer-experience</category>
            <category>product/sap-emarsys-customer-engagement</category>
            <category>product/sap-sales-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-service-cloud</category>
            <category>industry/utilities</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Revolution in Product Discovery with Zoovu Apps on SAP Store]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/revolution-in-product-discovery-zoovu-sap-store</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/revolution-in-product-discovery-zoovu-sap-store</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Zoovu humanizes product discovery, making products easier to find, evaluate, and buy by bringing context to your search. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-commerce</category>
            <category>news-tag/e-commerce</category>
            <category>product/sap-commerce-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-cpq</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-digital-commerce</category>
            <category>product/sap-sales-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-store</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Customer Experience Helps Marketing and Sales Teams Win Together]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/sap-customer-experience-account-engagement-marketing-and-sales-teams-win</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/sap-customer-experience-account-engagement-marketing-and-sales-teams-win</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The new account engagement option for SAP Customer Experience helps marketing and sales teams accelerate performance and grow revenue.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-engagement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-customer-experience</category>
            <category>product/sap-emarsys-customer-engagement</category>
            <category>product/sap-sales-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Why Is CX Critical for Future-Proofing B2B Sales?]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/future-proof-b2b-sales-cx-critical</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/future-proof-b2b-sales-cx-critical</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[To future-proof your B2B sales, SAP Sales Cloud can connects experiences to outcomes that matter for your customer. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-customer-experience</category>
            <category>product/sap-sales-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Digital Strategy Behind Moen’s Customer Experience Magic]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/09/moen-customer-experience-digital-strategy</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/09/moen-customer-experience-digital-strategy</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Moen, North America's leading faucet maker, is digitalizing on a cloud-based platform to get closer to customers and innovate business models.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-customer-experience</category>
            <category>product/sap-sales-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-service-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bots Meet Humans for Top-Notch Customer Service with CommBox Platform]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/bots-meet-humans-top-notch-customer-service-commbox</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/bots-meet-humans-top-notch-customer-service-commbox</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The CommBox platform, available on SAP Store, succeeds in bridging the gap between automated processes and human contact. Learn more!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>product/sap-sales-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-store</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Sales Cloud and Microsoft Teams Help Businesses Grow by Removing Barriers to Remote Selling]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/sap-sales-cloud-and-microsoft-teams-remote-selling</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/sap-sales-cloud-and-microsoft-teams-remote-selling</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The integration of SAP Sales Cloud and Microsoft Teams is now available to all customers. Read the announcement.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17b8952c43a637b0afef6fb6de63bf78b580e5e7d.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17b8952c43a637b0afef6fb6de63bf78b580e5e7d.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_17b8952c43a637b0afef6fb6de63bf78b580e5e7d.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Sales Cloud and Microsoft Teams Help Businesses Grow by Removing Barriers to Remote Selling" src="./media_17b8952c43a637b0afef6fb6de63bf78b580e5e7d.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-sales-cloud-and-microsoft-teams-help-businesses-grow-by-removing-barriers-to-remote-selling">SAP Sales Cloud and Microsoft Teams Help Businesses Grow by Removing Barriers to Remote Selling</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-whats-happening-at-sap-customer-experience-live-unplugged">Learn more about what's happening at SAP Customer Experience LIVE: Unplugged</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://events.sap.com/sap-cx-live-2021/en/home">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced that the integration of the SAP Sales Cloud solution with Microsoft Teams is now available to all customers. SAP made this announcement at the <a href="https://events.sap.com/sap-cx-live-2021/en/home">SAP Customer Experience LIVE: Unplugged</a> event being held October 26–27, 2021.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In today’s world, “remote selling” is no longer an exception, it has become the norm. Sales professionals across the globe use Microsoft Teams to meet with customers and engage in sales activities. The integration of SAP Sales Cloud and Microsoft teams enables users to access customer and sales information instantly from Microsoft Teams. While in customer meetings, they can update records in real time without ever leaving the Microsoft Teams environment.</p>
  <p>“Traditional sales automation solutions are record-keeping tools that focus on performing administrative tasks,” said Sameer Patel, chief marketing and solutions officer of Customer Experience at SAP. “They can distract sales professionals from high-value activities. SAP Sales Cloud is different because it removes complexities, adapts to changing needs of sales professionals and strives to make it easier for them to focus on customers and closing deals. The integration with Microsoft Teams is another great example of how SAP makes it easier for sales professionals to engage with customers and grow revenues.”</p>
  <p>“Microsoft Teams is the new way people and sales professionals connect, collaborate and stay in the flow of work in today’s hybrid world,” said Nicole Herskowitz, Microsoft Teams general manager. “We are excited that partners like SAP are building Teams Apps and native integration to enable collaborative solutions that help our mutual customers improve team productivity and better serve customers.”</p>
  <p>“It is more important than ever to eliminate friction in the sales process, remove administrative tasks and provide our sales professionals with the right sales solutions that help them focus on our customers and engage with them anywhere and anytime,” said Gamze Senkal, manager of Information Technology at <a href="https://www.eczacibasi.com.tr/en/brands/companies-building-products">Eczacıbaşı Building Products</a>, part of one of the leading industrial holding companies in Turkey. “With the integration of SAP Sales Cloud and Microsoft Teams, our sales professionals can access the latest customer information with one click from Microsoft Teams and are able to update sales records in real time without ever leaving Microsoft Teams. By eliminating duplicate data entry and record keeping, SAP Sales Cloud helps ensure that our sales professionals are focusing on our customers and value-added activities.”</p>
  <p>To attend <a href="https://events.sap.com/sap-cx-live-2021/en/home">SAP Customer Experience LIVE: Unplugged</a>, please check out the <a href="https://events.sap.com/sap-cx-live-2021/en/home#agenda">agenda</a> and <a href="https://vshow.on24.com/clients/SAP/3309743/">register</a>.</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP on Twitter at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-sales-cloud-connect-with-every-customer">SAP Sales Cloud: Connect with every customer</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm/sales.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><strong>About SAP</strong></p>
  <p>SAP’s strategy is to help every business run as a sustainable intelligent enterprise. As a market leader in enterprise application software, we help companies of all sizes and in all industries run at their best: SAP customers generate 87% of total global commerce. Our machine learning, Internet of Things (IoT), and advanced analytics technologies help turn customers’ businesses into sustainable intelligent enterprises. SAP helps give people and organizations deep business insight and fosters collaboration that helps them stay ahead of their competition. We simplify technology for companies so they can consume our software the way they want — without disruption. Our end-to-end suite of applications and services enables business and public customers across 25 industries globally to operate profitably, adapt continuously, and make a difference. With a global network of customers, partners, employees, and thought leaders, SAP helps the world run better and improve people’s lives. For more information, visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/">www.sap.com</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Note to editors:</strong><br>To preview and download broadcast-standard stock footage and press photos digitally, please visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/photos">www.sap.com/photos</a>. On this platform, you can find high resolution material for your media channels. To view video stories on diverse topics, visit <a href="http://www.sap-tv.com">www.sap-tv.com</a>. From this site, you can embed videos into your own Web pages, share video via email links, and subscribe to RSS feeds from SAP TV.</p>
  <p><strong>For customers interested in learning more about SAP products:</strong><br>Global Customer Center: +49 180 534-34-24<br>United States Only: 1 (800) 872-1SAP (1-800-872-1727)</p>
  <p><strong>For more information, press only:</strong><br>Samantha Finnegan, +1 (415) 377-0475, <a href="mailto:samantha.finnegan@sap.com">samantha.finnegan@sap.com</a>, ET<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>Any statements contained in this document that are not historical facts are forward-looking statements as defined in the U.S. Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995. Words such as “anticipate,” “believe,” “estimate,” “expect,” “forecast,” “intend,” “may,” “plan,” “project,” “predict,” “should” and “will” and similar expressions as they relate to SAP are intended to identify such forward-looking statements. SAP undertakes no obligation to publicly update or revise any forward-looking statements. All forward-looking statements are subject to various risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results to differ materially from expectations. The factors that could affect SAP’s future financial results are discussed more fully in SAP’s filings with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (“SEC”), including SAP’s most recent Annual Report on Form 20-F filed with the SEC. Readers are cautioned not to place undue reliance on these forward-looking statements, which speak only as of their dates.<br>© 2021 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.<br>Please consider our <a href="https://www.sap.com/corporate/en/legal/privacy.html">privacy policy</a>. If you received this press release in your e-mail and you wish to unsubscribe to our mailing list please contact <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a> and write Unsubscribe in the subject line.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/microsoft</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-customer-experience-live</category>
            <category>product/sap-sales-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How CPG Brands Keep Up with Retail’s Fastest-Moving Consumer Demands]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/cpg-brands-keep-up-with-consumer-demands</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/cpg-brands-keep-up-with-consumer-demands</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[CPG sales teams use AI solutions, like startup Teamcore's, to help meet fast-changing supply chain disruptions and consumer demands.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_19d9e6cfca5a5c2d3608a3e8197461ba7d52ebc70.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_19d9e6cfca5a5c2d3608a3e8197461ba7d52ebc70.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_19d9e6cfca5a5c2d3608a3e8197461ba7d52ebc70.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="How CPG Brands Keep Up with Retail’s Fastest-Moving Consumer Demands" src="./media_19d9e6cfca5a5c2d3608a3e8197461ba7d52ebc70.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="how-cpg-brands-keep-up-with-retails-fastest-moving-consumer-demands">How CPG Brands Keep Up with Retail’s Fastest-Moving Consumer Demands</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Nobody understands the frustration of consumers who can’t find the products they’re looking for more than the experts at <a href="https://www.teamcore.net/en/">Teamcore</a>, an artificial intelligence (AI)-based startup with operations in Latin America and the United States. Teamcore’s cloud-based software platform uses machine learning to power intelligent workflow automation that tells consumer packaged goods (CPG) companies and retailers why products aren’t selling and what they can do about it fast.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“We help CPG companies and retailers make sure products are available when their customers are ready to buy,” said Sergio Della Maggiora, founder and CEO of Teamcore. “Whether someone is shopping online or in a physical store, our retail execution platform based on intelligent workflows helps connect data across the supply chain – from warehouse to shelf, virtually or in-store – so companies don’t miss out on sales opportunities.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="reinvent-how-businesses-run-with-sapio">Reinvent how businesses run with SAP.iO</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://sap.io/foundries/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="intelligent-automated-workflows-boost-cpg-sales">Intelligent Automated Workflows Boost CPG Sales</h2>
  <p>Based on sales data analytics, Della Maggiora said that Teamcore’s machine learning algorithm detects when products aren’t selling as planned and, in over 94% of cases, finds the root cause of the problem before assigning a task. Unlike garden variety alerts, Teamcore’s intelligent workflow notifications keep going until they reach the people who solve the problem. If someone in replenishment can’t find the product in the warehouse to restock virtual or in-store shelves, the workflow automatically routes that task to the appropriate store sales representatives, all the way up to regional store and supply chain managers.</p>
  <p>“Teamcore connects the whole CPG and retail team for opportunity detection sales and doesn’t stop until someone actually fixes the problem,” said Della Maggiora. “Over time, the collected data trains the model, improving its accuracy and ability to make predictions about potential issues.”</p>
  <h2 id="automated-retail-execution-leaves-no-opportunity-unturned">Automated Retail Execution Leaves No Opportunity Unturned</h2>
  <p>Teamcore tackles some of the biggest challenges retailers face. Consider the problem of phantom inventory, which happens when company systems show products at a location, but they aren’t actually there. Another issue is underperforming promotions. CPG companies can have the best intentions in giving discounts to retailers, but if the right-priced products aren’t available to customers for whatever reason, the items won’t sell. Addressing these problems is not as simple as it sounds.</p>
  <p>“Retailers deal with thousands of product-related issues happening every day in virtual and brick and mortar stores,” said Della Maggiora. “Data from our automatic workflows lets retailers see where the problems are and act faster to correct them. If the algorithm detects that a product is underperforming compared to the same promotions in other locations, sales teams can take appropriate steps, like prioritizing in-store visits, replacing missing signage, or other activities, to help the retailer take full advantage of the promotion.”</p>
  <p>Teamcore’s customers include well-known global brands in food and beverage, personal care, and other CPG sectors across Latin America and the United States. On average, these companies have increased product sales from 3% to 5% by improving on-shelf product availability from 4% to 9% and online product availability from 5% to 15%.</p>
  <p>“One major CPG company reallocated its field sales team to activities where they could impact greater sales,” said Della Maggiora. “Once our data revealed how much time reps wasted on low value store visits, the company shifted the same team to dynamic, higher-value activities that had bottom line business results.”</p>
  <h2 id="data-science-meets-fast-changing-consumer-demands">Data Science Meets Fast-Changing Consumer Demands</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="affordable-products-a-eureka-moment-for-sustainability">Affordable Products: A Eureka Moment for Sustainability</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/09/affordable-products-eureka-moment-for-sustainability-simreka">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Born in Chile, Della Maggiora initially studied business, then began exploring technology during his undergraduate work. He and his cofounders took advantage of a government grant program in Chile to start a software company that developed mobile solutions. Eventually, he applied his eight years of retail operations experience at Walmart to cofound Teamcore. After seeing huge process inefficiencies firsthand, he and his team conceptualized a mobile and desktop app based on data science. Then the <a href="/covid-19">pandemic</a> hit.</p>
  <p>“We knew that designing a simple user experience on top of a solid data science platform would help retail operations become more efficient, selling what consumers want to purchase,” he said. “When COVID-19 disrupted supply chains, many CPG organizations shifted to e-commerce and faced customer demands in unexpected ways – everything from rising home cooking trends to spikes in uptake of particular products. Our solution helps brands better understand and adapt to these fluctuating sales cycles.”</p>
  <h2 id="sapio-hones-targeted-cpg-product-design-and-messaging">SAP.iO Hones Targeted CPG Product Design and Messaging</h2>
  <p>Della Maggiora and his team began working with experts across SAP while participating in the <a href="https://sap.io/foundry-berlin/">SAP.iO Foundry Berlin</a> data and analytics cohort. He saw alignment with SAP’s intelligent enterprise vision and expected Teamcore to deliver greater value by integrating with SAP solutions in <a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/consumer-goods-cpg.html">consumer products</a> and <a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/retail.html">retail</a>. Teamcore is already integrated with <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm/sales.html">SAP Sales Cloud</a>.</p>
  <p>“We’ve learned so much from SAP’s consumer products and retail experts about how customers can generate value from our data when it’s integrated with their enterprise resource planning (ERP), financial, and supply chain systems,” said Della Maggiora. “These insights have helped us in product design and crafting our messages for stronger market resonance on a global scale.”</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Follow me @smgaler.</em><br><em><a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2021/08/26/how-cpg-brands-are-keeping-up-with-retails-fastest-moving-consumer-demands/?sh=e42349048a4d">This blog also appeared on SAP BrandVoice on Forbes.</a></em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/consumer-goods-cpg</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
            <category>product/sap-sales-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-io</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Fastest Route to Sales Planning with maiTour for SAP Sales Cloud on SAP Store]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/fastest-route-to-sales-planning-maitour</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/fastest-route-to-sales-planning-maitour</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[maiTour for SAP Sales Cloud from Nagarro ES uses advanced technology to help sales professionals plan their schedules down to the minute.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_19adcd5b01c2ba9b22b326919c75a9e6664a7df8f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_19adcd5b01c2ba9b22b326919c75a9e6664a7df8f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_19adcd5b01c2ba9b22b326919c75a9e6664a7df8f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="The Fastest Route to Sales Planning with maiTour for SAP Sales Cloud on SAP Store" src="./media_19adcd5b01c2ba9b22b326919c75a9e6664a7df8f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="the-fastest-route-to-sales-planning-with-maitour-for-sap-sales-cloud-on-sap-store">The Fastest Route to Sales Planning with maiTour for SAP Sales Cloud on SAP Store</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Anyone in professional sales knows how important it is to use time efficiently. As a former account executive, I remember the demands of meeting my revenue goals while making sure I had enough time to spend with my customers.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>That’s why I am so enthusiastic about <a href="https://www.store.sap.com/apps/3967?source=blog-NagarroES">maiTour for SAP Sales Cloud</a> from Nagarro ES, which uses advanced technology to help sales professionals plan their schedules down to the minute. Now available on <a href="https://store.sap.com/en/">SAP Store</a>, maiTour integrates with SAP Sales Cloud to pair customer insights with intelligent tour planning and real-time geo-optimization.</p>
  <h2 id="driving-efficiency-in-tour-and-call-planning">Driving Efficiency in Tour and Call Planning</h2>
  <p>Oliver Mosick, senior sales manager for Nagarro ES, explained that the heart of maiTour is high-value customer relationships. “In sales, you need to spend more of your time with high-value contacts than the ones who might have the best coffee,” he commented.</p>
  <p>He went on to explain that maiTour uses key metrics stored in SAP Sales Cloud – classification and visit frequency, their commitments, planned activities, contact details, visit duration, and so on – to determine the importance of each customer. The solution incorporates appointments from a calendar in SAP Sales Cloud and automatically selects which customers to visit and in what order. It geo-optimizes sales routes with both real-time and historical traffic information and adjusts planning periods and overnight stays automatically.</p>
  <p>“And to top it all off,” Mosick noted, “maiTour transfers all your visits and necessary details to your calendar with one click. The life of every field sales executive is instantly more manageable and productive. No more cut and paste from your CRM to Google Maps and fiddling around with your calendar to figure out the right time to leave from one customer to arrive at the next.” He added that, by driving smarter, maiTour users have cut mileage by up to 15%.</p>
  <h2 id="mapping-product-design-for-future-customer-requirements">Mapping Product Design for Future Customer Requirements</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="discover-more-solutions-from-nagarro-es-on-sap-store">Discover more solutions from Nagarro ES on SAP Store</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://store.sap.com/dcp/en/search/nagarro">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Like me, Mosick speaks from experience, having spent his career in sales. Now working directly with customers interested in improving sales processes with maiTour, “we speak the same language,” he observed. And customer input is inherent in the design. Dominik Girstenbrei, product manager for maiTour and a developer himself, works directly with customers to understand their requirements. He approaches product design from the customer’s perspective and thinks ahead to build in features they will need in the future. “We are continuously improving with every new release, looking at new capabilities and working with the SAP team on the product road map.”</p>
  <p>Clearly, integration with SAP Sales Cloud is paramount. As a full-service IT provider for enterprise applications, Nagarro ES is a long-time SAP partner. CX Services, a Nagarro ES business unit, specializes in developing innovative, best-of-breed software extensions and embedded solutions to complement SAP IT landscapes, focusing primarily on add-ons for SAP Sales Cloud and SAP S/4HANA. In fact, Nagarro ES currently has six apps on SAP Store.</p>
  <p>That includes a new product, <a href="https://www.store.sap.com/apps/59943?source=blog-NagarroES">Invoice Scanner for SAP S/4HANA</a>, that enhances the digital invoice-receipt workflow. That level of diversification, Mosick said, was instrumental in helping the company weather the <a href="/covid-19">pandemic</a>, when sales opportunities for maiTour were interrupted with the sudden suspension of business travel.</p>
  <h2 id="steering-business-through-sap-store">Steering Business Through SAP Store</h2>
  <p>“I see that more and more customers are coming to SAP Store. The team is always helpful and has supported us in numerous customer activities,” Mosick remarked. That goes both ways. “We recently collaborated on a request for proposal from a major German beer brand, and actually, maiTour was the decision point.”</p>
  <p>Mosick’s advice for others considering publishing on SAP Store? “Get in touch with the SAP Store team! Or talk to us if you have an idea for enhancing end-to-end processes for the SAP ecosystem. We are pushing innovation whenever we can. We are available to support startups and solution providers to develop and implement new and current solutions for the SAP world.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="plan-the-most-efficient-route-to-your-customers-doors-with-maitour-for-sap-sales-cloud">Plan the most efficient route to your customers' doors with maiTour for SAP Sales Cloud</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.store.sap.com/apps/3967?source=blog-NagarroES">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="test-drive-maitour-for-sap-sales-cloud-or-watch-a-demo-right-on-sap-store">Test drive <a href="https://www.store.sap.com/apps/3967?source=blog-NagarroES">maiTour for SAP Sales Cloud</a> or watch a demo right on SAP Store.</h3>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Bill Rojas is senior director of Business Development and Partner Alliances for SAP Digital Commerce.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>product/sap-sales-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-store</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Recognized as a Leader in 2021 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Sales Force Automation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/sap-leader-2021-gartner-magic-quadrant-sales-force-automation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/sap-leader-2021-gartner-magic-quadrant-sales-force-automation</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Aug 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[For the third consecutive year, SAP has been recognized as a Leader in the Gartner Magic Quadrant for Sales Force Automation. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_192b9acfd6c0206875099c76186dff8d21cec0319.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_192b9acfd6c0206875099c76186dff8d21cec0319.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_192b9acfd6c0206875099c76186dff8d21cec0319.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Recognized as a Leader in 2021 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Sales Force Automation" src="./media_192b9acfd6c0206875099c76186dff8d21cec0319.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-recognized-as-a-leader-in-2021-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-sales-force-automation">SAP Recognized as a Leader in 2021 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Sales Force Automation</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="deliver-exceptional-sales-experiences-with-sap-sales-cloud">Deliver exceptional sales experiences with SAP Sales Cloud</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/sales-cloud.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced it is again recognized as a Leader in the 2021 Gartner Magic Quadrant™ for Sales Force Automation.* This is the third consecutive year that SAP has been recognized as a Leader based on its “ability to execute” and “completeness of vision.” In its latest report, Gartner assessed SAP for the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/sales-cloud.html">SAP Sales Cloud</a> solution.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“Businesses that understand their customers can ultimately improve how they engage with them and build relationships that last,” said Sameer Patel, chief marketing and solution officer for SAP Customer Experience. “SAP Sales Cloud empowers organizations to deliver customer-centric processes that maximize sales by addressing customers’ needs at each stage of their purchase journey. With the integrated SAP Customer Experience portfolio of cloud solutions, businesses can manage the complete customer experience to improve outcomes based on empathy and trust.”</p>
  <p>The SAP Sales Cloud solution is part of the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm.html">SAP Customer Experience</a> portfolio, which goes beyond traditional CRM solutions by bringing together customer data, experiential and operational data, and machine learning. SAP Customer Experience offers organizations a complete platform to address all customer interactions using a common data model and functionality from commerce, marketing, sales and service to address their business needs.</p>
  <p>To learn more, download a <a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/cx/salesforce-automation-gartner-report/index.html?campaigncode=CRM-HY21-SIP-AGMQSFA&#x26;source=onlinedisplay-glo--sales-evolution">complimentary copy</a> of the report, including Gartner’s in-depth analysis of the sales force automation landscape.</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="http://news.sap.com/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP on Twitter at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><strong>Media Contact:</strong> Susan Miller, +1 (610) 661-9225, <a href="mailto:susan.miller@sap.com">susan.miller@sap.com</a>, ET<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>*Gartner, Magic Quadrant for Sales Force Automation, Adnan Zijadic, Ilona Hansen, Melissa Hilbert, Steve Rietberg, 4 August 2021.<br>Gartner does not endorse any vendor, product or service depicted in its research publications, and does not advise technology users to select only those vendors with the highest ratings or other designation. Gartner research publications consist of the opinions of Gartner’s research organization and should not be construed as statements of fact. Gartner disclaims all warranties, expressed or implied, with respect to this research, including any warranties of merchantability or fitness for a particular purpose. Gartner and Magic Quadrant are registered trademarks of Gartner, Inc. and/or its affiliates in the U.S. and internationally and is used herein with permission. All rights reserved.</p>
  <p>Any statements contained in this document that are not historical facts are forward-looking statements as defined in the U.S. Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995. Words such as “anticipate,” “believe,” “estimate,” “expect,” “forecast,” “intend,” “may,” “plan,” “project,” “predict,” “should” and “will” and similar expressions as they relate to SAP are intended to identify such forward-looking statements. SAP undertakes no obligation to publicly update or revise any forward-looking statements. All forward-looking statements are subject to various risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results to differ materially from expectations. The factors that could affect SAP’s future financial results are discussed more fully in SAP’s filings with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (“SEC”), including SAP’s most recent Annual Report on Form 20-F filed with the SEC. Readers are cautioned not to place undue reliance on these forward-looking statements, which speak only as of their dates.<br>© 2021 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-customer-experience</category>
            <category>product/sap-sales-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP CPQ Transforms the Sales Process]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/03/sap-cpq-transform-sales-process</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/03/sap-cpq-transform-sales-process</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Constellation Research finds that SAP CPQ prompts both behavior change and better customer interactions in the complex world of sales.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>product/sap-cpq</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-customer-experience</category>
            <category>product/sap-sales-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP and Microsoft: How We Simplify Business Collaboration]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2021/02/microsoft-teams-sap-solutions-simplify-business-collaboration</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2021/02/microsoft-teams-sap-solutions-simplify-business-collaboration</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[By integrating SAP solutions with Microsoft Teams, the companies are lifting collaboration to the next level. Learn more about what's planned.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/executive-blog</category>
            <category>news-tag/microsoft</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>product/sap-sales-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Microsoft and SAP: Expanding Our Partnership]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2021/01/expanding-microsoft-sap-partnership</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2021/01/expanding-microsoft-sap-partnership</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP and Microsoft will expand integration scenarios with Microsoft Teams and SAP solutions and improve SAP S/4HANA on Microsoft Azure. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1876d61f48b27527d21736c822aacc4a0e62dbb6c.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1876d61f48b27527d21736c822aacc4a0e62dbb6c.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1876d61f48b27527d21736c822aacc4a0e62dbb6c.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Microsoft and SAP: Expanding Our Partnership" src="./media_1876d61f48b27527d21736c822aacc4a0e62dbb6c.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="microsoft-and-sap-expanding-our-partnership">Microsoft and SAP: Expanding Our Partnership</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Our world is becoming more digital every day, with an increasing number of people working remotely. The <a href="/covid-19">COVID-19</a> pandemic has only accelerated these trends.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Efficient virtual collaboration has never been more important, and we want to provide our customers with solutions that help them cope with business disruptions. When done right, these can be powerful tools to increase workplace productivity, raise flexibility, and foster agility within and across organizations.</p>
  <p>One key aspect to this is the integration of business software applications with business collaboration tools. <a href="/">Together with Microsoft</a>, we want to better support end users in their daily work and bridge the gap between enterprise software and collaboration tools more effectively and efficiently. Our two companies combine the market-leading business software applications from SAP with the market-leading business collaboration tools from Microsoft.</p>
  <p>Together with Microsoft, we will drive joint innovation to integrate Microsoft Teams and SAP’s business software applications. By doing so, we aim to simplify processes, enable collaboration without switching applications, and guide users of the solutions intuitively. Ultimately, the integration scenarios can help to achieve enhanced workplace productivity by offering our customers significant value to work better together with their employees, customers, and partners—anywhere and anytime.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="press-release-sap-and-microsoft-expand-partnership">Press Release: SAP and Microsoft Expand Partnership</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/01/sap-and-microsoft-expand-partnership-integrate-teams">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="bringing-together-microsoft-teams-and-sap-solutions">Bringing Together Microsoft Teams and SAP Solutions</h2>
  <p>We are looking to expand the integration scenarios with Microsoft Teams and SAP solutions in the following areas to:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Effectively collaborate with business partners:</strong> Especially in the case of disruptions in business, fast communication with clients and partners is imperative. One of our first integration scenarios relates to <strong>SAP S/4HANA and Microsoft Teams</strong>. With the solution alignment, customers will be able to identify their business partners easily and initiate contact directly from SAP S/4HANA—with no need to switch between applications or devices. This will help customers swiftly react to business situations based on real-time data and constant communication with relevant stakeholders.</li>
    <li><strong>Simplify and modernize the remote sales experience:</strong> Today, remote selling has become an imperative for companies across the globe. Integrating <strong>SAP Sales Cloud</strong> with <strong>Microsoft Teams</strong> simplifies the remote selling process and removes barriers to customer engagement through an embedded in-app integration of the two solutions. For example, without switching applications, customer calls can be initiated directly from the customer experience application—helping ensure transparency and consistency within customer relationship management (CRM) and saving time through user-friendly workflows.</li>
    <li><strong>Foster collaboration and build learning communities:</strong> Organizations have realized the necessity of providing simple, intuitive, and engaging ways for employees to learn new skills, share knowledge, and stay informed—all in a virtual environment. Bringing together <strong>SAP SuccessFactors solutions</strong> and <strong>Microsoft Teams</strong> will support learning experiences that enable collaboration, social learning, and remote conferencing.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>This news makes one characteristic of the two companies’ enduring alliance very clear: the ability and commitment to continually evolve to make our customers even more successful. Every time an end user works with SAP solutions, there is an opportunity for real-time collaboration such as chats, conference calls, alerts, and so much more. It is exciting to see the opportunities for collaboration culture and frictionless enterprises that our partnership with Microsoft creates for our customers.</p>
  <h2 id="accelerating-migration-and-increasing-operational-efficiencies">Accelerating Migration and Increasing Operational Efficiencies</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-the-sap-and-microsoft-partnership">Learn more about the SAP and Microsoft partnership</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://discover.sap.com/microsoft/en-us/index.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In addition, SAP and Microsoft are further simplifying and improving the experience for customers running SAP S/4HANA on Microsoft Azure. Together, we will continue to make our customers’ migration from SAP ERP to SAP S/4HANA in the cloud simpler, while at the same time ensuring choice for customers that prefer multi-cloud environments in their enterprise IT landscapes.</p>
  <p>This means that our customers will see more guidance from SAP and Microsoft on the initial setup and architecture design of SAP S/4HANA on Microsoft Azure.</p>
  <p>We also plan to collaborate with Microsoft to enhance SAP Cloud Appliance Library, a tool that makes it easier for users to quickly provision SAP applications for immediate use in the cloud, and offer automated SAP system installations for SAP S/4HANA. Customers can also subscribe to SAP Landscape Management Cloud, improving scalability and operation efforts, and benefit from an SAP system-centered view of their Microsoft Azure landscape. Additionally, we are working on a more guided approach for customers to quickly deploy SAP S/4HANA directly into Microsoft Azure. For better transparency within the transformation process, we will provide guidance on data migration tool usage for the transition of SAP workloads from on premise to SAP S/4HANA on Microsoft Azure.</p>
  <h2 id="bringing-platform-services-closer-together">Bringing Platform Services Closer Together</h2>
  <p>We will also continue to expand the global availability of SAP solutions on Microsoft Azure during 2021. Together, we will drive co-innovation between <a href="https://www.sap.com/germany/products/business-technology-platform.html?campaigncode=CRM-DE20-PPC-DDE_PLTTA0&#x26;source=ppc-mee-ao-dg_PT_x_DE_x_x-GOO-x-x&#x26;DFA=1&#x26;gclid=EAIaIQobChMIy-qk-YOR7AIVRM3tCh2oqQtUEAAYASAAEgIwa_D_BwE&#x26;gclsrc=aw.ds&#x26;pdf-asset=fa09d6fc-4b7d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff&#x26;page=7&#x26;btp=18743a19-5b7f-4397-aa1d-2a1ccc3c4142">SAP Business Technology Platform</a> (SAP BTP) and Microsoft Azure services to deliver business outcomes to our customers. The range of capabilities includes event integration based on open standards, single sign-on and provisioning of users between Microsoft and SAP, secure network connectivity, and improved application development experience on SAP BTP. My SAP Executive Board colleague and our Chief Technology Officer Juergen Mueller will give more insight on the role of SAP BTP in the upcoming days.</p>
  <p>With our partnership, we bring together Microsoft Teams with SAP solutions, accelerate migration and improve operational efficiencies, and bring platform services closer together. We are working on making these enhancements and integrations of SAP solutions with Microsoft a reality for our customers soon. You can find the latest status of our joint work in <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/01/ca0f4c25-c87d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff.html">this e-book</a>, which we will update regularly. I look forward to more joint innovation to come.</p>
  <p>The next generation of enterprise software is intelligent and integrated, networked, sustainable, and collaborative.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Thomas Saueressig is a member of the Executive Board of SAP SE, Product Engineering.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sign-up-for-the-weekly-sap-news-center-newsletter">Sign up for the weekly SAP News Center newsletter</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/nl/sap-innovation-and-transformation-newsletter/index.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/blog/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/blog/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/blog/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/blog/article-read-more</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/executive-blog</category>
            <category>news-tag/microsoft</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>product/sap-sales-cloud</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>