<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/sap-s4hana-2/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[In the Era of AI, Trust Is the Essence of Business]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/era-of-ai-trust-essence-business</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/era-of-ai-trust-essence-business</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Implementing new technology like generative AI requires trust; SAP’s commitment to relevant, reliable, and responsible AI is crucial.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Transform with Confidence Using RISE with SAP Methodology]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/transform-confidence-rise-with-sap-methodology</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/transform-confidence-rise-with-sap-methodology</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[We're introducing a new customer onboarding experience and quality check enhancements in RISE with SAP Methodology. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1885c69bbf9dcd29bb29f03d58f391fc97b8d7c88.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1885c69bbf9dcd29bb29f03d58f391fc97b8d7c88.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1885c69bbf9dcd29bb29f03d58f391fc97b8d7c88.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Transform with Confidence Using RISE with SAP Methodology" src="./media_1885c69bbf9dcd29bb29f03d58f391fc97b8d7c88.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="transform-with-confidence-using-rise-with-sap-methodology">Transform with Confidence Using RISE with SAP Methodology</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Today we’re introducing a new customer onboarding experience and quality check enhancements in RISE with SAP Methodology. After April 1, 2024, all customers subscribing to RISE with SAP for the first time will go through this improved experience at no additional cost.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/topics/rise-with-sap">RISE with SAP</a> is a managed cloud offering that can enable customers to unlock continued innovation and transformation by modernizing their business-critical systems and processes in a highly collaborative and measurable way. This offering includes the newly announced <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/rise.html#migration">RISE with SAP Migration and Modernization program</a> that helps bring renewed focus on the cloud transformation journey by enabling smooth, secure migration of on-premise SAP ERP Central Component (SAP ECC) and SAP S/4HANA customers to the cloud. The key pillars of the program are the RISE with SAP Methodology, transformation incentives, and the innovation road map. The program features offerings tailored to each customer’s unique starting point. Its components are differentiated for SAP ECC and SAP S/4HANA customers and can run with a clean core approach, taking advantage of the latest innovations in RISE with SAP.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="cloud-solutions-infrastructure-and-services-combined-to-deliver-a-clear-cloud-migration-path">Cloud solutions, infrastructure, and services combined to deliver a clear cloud migration path</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/rise.html#migration">Explore RISE with SAP</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The cornerstone of the program is the RISE with SAP Methodology. The methodology captures the best practices of successful implementations from thousands of RISE with SAP customers over three years and is designed to provide a consistent approach – from planning to go-live to ongoing operations and evolution – that can meet customers’ business transformation goals. Whether through SAP or partner-led engagements, customers can get a clear path with specific implementation stages and success KPIs to be able to take advantage of speed, agility, and all the benefits of the cloud.</p>
  <p>Today we’re adding enhancements to the RISE with SAP Methodology, including a new onboarding experience and quality checks throughout the project implementation phases. All new RISE with SAP customers will go through this onboarding experience at no additional cost. The new experience provides guided enablement by SAP-assigned onboarding advisors and related tools and services to help customers implement their cloud ERP solutions with clarity and confidence. The onboarding advisors can guide customers through the overall process aligned with the RISE with SAP Methodology and prepare them to get started with their implementation. The new experience also helps simplify best practice implementation of the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/rise/clean-core.html">clean core</a>, helping to make it a more central, actionable, and measurable standard of all implementations. This helps ensure all RISE with SAP customers can benefit from business agility, faster innovation cycles, and improved value realization.</p>
  <p>The new improvements to the RISE with SAP Methodology include:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Expert onboarding guidance through embedded launch activities:</strong> A dedicated SAP advisor can deliver 1:1 enablement sessions to help educate customers on the RISE with SAP Methodology, clean core strategy, and related tools for implementation. Also, there are role-based, recorded enablement sessions covering business process best practices, solution architectures, and other strategic topics leading up to the go-live milestone. Check out this <a href="https://community.sap.com/t5/enterprise-resource-planning-blogs-by-sap/jumpstart-your-cloud-erp-journey-with-guided-enablement-in-rise-with-sap/ba-p/13679776">blog</a> on embedded launch activities to get a full view on what enablement resources are delivered through this new onboarding experience with RISE with SAP.</li>
    <li><strong>Clean core-focused success plan, runbook, and quality checks:</strong> We’ve developed a clean core success plan with clear milestones and KPIs. The clean core success plan is now added to the SAP Activate road map viewer, where customers – with the support of SAP advisors and partners – can review the recommended actions in uniquely created road maps, aligning their needs with best practices to help continually unlock business value faster. We’re also adding new quality gate checks to validate that the actual implementation is in line with recommended clean core best practices before customers proceed to the next project phase. The outcome of the quality gate is the SAP clean core report with feedback and recommendations on how to implement the clean core strategy. These recommendations are recorded and tracked via the updated runbook in the SAP Cloud ALM solution. To learn more, read a <a href="https://community.sap.com/t5/enterprise-resource-planning-blogs-by-sap/new-quality-check-enhancements-with-a-focus-on-clean-core-implementation/ba-p/13679681">blog post</a> on this topic.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>We’ll continue to deliver more tools, templates, training, and oversight to help make it easier for customers to execute an optimal migration or transition to the cloud and achieve their business objectives. Coming later this year is the RISE with SAP system transition workbench. This tool will help the technical implementation of migrating to cloud ERP by providing digital access to SAP-approved best practices and guidance for migrations, automation of tasks, health, and system checks. Stay tuned as we get ready to share more on this in the coming weeks.</p>
  <p>To learn more, join us for our upcoming webinar on May 23, where we will go deeper into this new onboarding experience in the RISE with SAP Methodology. Register <a href="https://event.on24.com/wcc/r/4573875/470481A80AAF443E29CBBDD9B1C29F4B/5433671?partnerref=PressRelease">here</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>Panda Priyadarsana is SVP and GM of Customer Services &#x26; Delivery and head of Cloud ERP at SAP.</p>
        <p>Photo courtesy of SAP employee Juelma Guerreiro.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="receive-weekly-news-highlights-from-the-sap-news-center">Receive weekly news highlights from the SAP News Center</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/nl/sap-news-center-newsletter/index.html">Sign up now</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Solutions from SAP and Icertis Empower Enterprises with Contract Intelligence Innovation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-icertis-contract-intelligence-innovation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-icertis-contract-intelligence-innovation</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP and Icertis are working to improve contract intelligence for enterprises, reducing revenue leakage and increasing efficiency. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/icertis</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[What the Automotive Industry Can Learn from the Next Wave of Digital Transformations]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2024/02/next-wave-digital-transformation-automotive-industry</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2024/02/next-wave-digital-transformation-automotive-industry</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In the automotive industry, disruption is a massive opportunity. Learn more about the next wave of digital transformation in the industry.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/executive-blog</category>
            <category>industry/automotive</category>
            <category>news-tag/bmw</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Accelerates Seagate Technology's Digital Evolution with SAP S/4HANA]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/seagate-technology-digital-evolution-sap-s4hana</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/seagate-technology-digital-evolution-sap-s4hana</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Seagate Technology Holdings plc has had a successful launch of SAP S/4HANA and the SAP BW/4HANA solution. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>news-tag/enterprise-resource-planning</category>
            <category>product/sap-bw4hana</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Grow with the Latest SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition 2402 Update]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/sap-s4hana-cloud-public-edition-2402-update</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/sap-s4hana-cloud-public-edition-2402-update</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With the SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition 2402 update, we are bringing a new round of exciting innovations. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/enterprise-resource-planning</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>product/sap-intelligent-rpa</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/ux</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Top Retailers Using Tech to Build Lifelong Customer Relationships]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/retail-sap-customers-using-tech-to-build-lifelong-relationships</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/retail-sap-customers-using-tech-to-build-lifelong-relationships</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP customers in retail leverage tech to drive meaningful customer experiences, adopt sustainability, and position for success. Read more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/nrf</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-analytics</category>
            <category>product/sap-commerce-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Zamora Company Is Helping Create a Better World by Reducing Packaging with SAP Responsible Design and Production]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/zamora-company-reducing-packaging-sap-responsible-design-and-production</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/zamora-company-reducing-packaging-sap-responsible-design-and-production</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Responsible Design and Production helped Zamora Company adhere to new packaging taxes in Spain. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18070844b43147c00d535b4fc2b7e284b2b6e0bcf.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18070844b43147c00d535b4fc2b7e284b2b6e0bcf.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_18070844b43147c00d535b4fc2b7e284b2b6e0bcf.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Zamora Company Is Helping Create a Better World by Reducing Packaging with SAP Responsible Design and Production" src="./media_18070844b43147c00d535b4fc2b7e284b2b6e0bcf.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="zamora-company-is-helping-create-a-better-world-by-reducing-packaging-with-sap-responsible-design-and-production">Zamora Company Is Helping Create a Better World by Reducing Packaging with SAP Responsible Design and Production</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>As a consumer you may not have heard of <a href="https://zamoracompany.com/conscious-company/">Zamora Company</a>, but it will surely ring a bell when you hear the names of some of its most popular premium spirit and wine brands, such as Licor 43, Martin Miller’s Gin, Yellow Rose, Ramón Bilbao, Champagne Pommery, and many others.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The international enterprise with headquarters in Spain and operations in more than 80 countries has been including environmental protection and economic growth into its DNA and is constantly working on achieving a sustainable business model that will be its future legacy to society and to the planet. Its commitment to the planet is based on four pillars: climate action, biodiversity protection, circularity, and conscious suppliers.</p>
  <p>The mission of Zamora Company toward its suppliers is to encourage them to be more sustainable by collaborating closely to substitute product and packaging materials with more sustainable alternatives and to use more recyclable packaging materials to support circular economy principles. It’s no wonder that, for Zamora, <a href="/topics/sustainability">sustainability</a> goes hand in hand with innovation without compromising the highest quality standards. <a href="https://zamoracompany.com/conscious-company/">Zamora Company’s strategy</a> as a conscious company is also focused and aligned with the achievement of the <a href="https://www.un.org/sustainabledevelopment/">Sustainable Development Goals (SDGs)</a> set by the United Nations 2030 agenda.</p>
  <h2 id="accelerating-innovation-through-new-packaging-legislation">Accelerating Innovation Through New Packaging Legislation</h2>
  <p>Since the introduction of a <a href="https://sede.agenciatributaria.gob.es/Sede/en_gb/impuestos-especiales-medioambientales/impuesto-especial-sobre-envases-plastico-reutilizables.html">new packaging tax</a> in Spain on January 1, 2023 on non-reusable plastic packaging, companies are required to meet comprehensive reporting requirements.</p>
  <p>The tax is an indirect excise tax with an environmental purpose. It aims to internalize the environmental costs related to the manufacturing and consumption of plastic packaging in the price of final products.</p>
  <p>The taxable event is the manufacturing, import, or intra-community acquisition of non-reusable plastic packaging for its use within the Spanish market. The plastic packaging tax captures a broad concept of “non-reusable plastic packaging” in its scope, which includes:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Non-reusable plastic containers – the law provides definitions of “non-reusable,” “plastic,” and “container” for the purpose of this tax</li>
    <li>Semi-finished plastic products, such as preforms and thermoplastic sheets, intended for production of non-reusable plastic containers</li>
    <li>Plastic products aimed to facilitate the closing, trading, or presentation of non-reusable containers</li>
  </ul>
  <p>“The new legislation required us to respond to governmental requisitions and was an additional driver to accelerate our sustainability efforts,” Enrique Gonzalo Mecández, SAP manager in Operations at Zamora Company, explained. “With a cross-departmental team, we were looking to find the most appropriate and scalable software solution to meet the country’s regulatory requirements and help us with data management, a tax monitor, and reporting and insights.”</p>
  <h2 id="keeping-all-data-in-one-central-place">Keeping All Data in One Central Place</h2>
  <p>As a result, Zamora Company found that <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/responsible-design-and-production.html">SAP Responsible Design and Production</a>, an industry cloud-based solution, would best meet its needs. SAP Responsible Design and Production can support manufacturers and retailers in calculating extended producer responsibility (EPR) obligations and fees, plastic taxes, and corporate commitments to optimize material choices. In addition, it helps improve design decisions based on costs and planetary impact.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="start-acting-on-a-circular-economy-and-eliminate-waste-with-sap">Start acting on a circular economy and eliminate waste with SAP</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/responsible-design-and-production.html">Learn how</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“From a process standpoint, SAP Responsible Design and Production facilitates the incorporation of everything related to sustainability data linked to the material, so that all relevant information is unified in the material master,” Gonzalo Mecández said. “As all information is kept in one place, purchasing work and master data maintenance required to ensure regulatory compliance is centralized, without the need to manually replicate information in different systems.”</p>
  <p>“Moreover, leveraging a single and integrated platform with <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/s4hana.html">SAP S/4HANA</a> provides the security of working with up-to-date and correct data. Additionally, the data quality application allows our users to detect any lack of information and correct it,” he added. “With deep knowledge and solution experience, our trusted partner <a href="https://www.indracompany.com/en/minsait">Minsait</a>, an <a href="https://www.indracompany.com/en/">Indra</a> company, closely supported us during the implementation of SAP Responsible Design and Production, as well as the integration with our SAP S/4HANA platform.”</p>
  <p>The benefits Zamora Company achieved include:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Ability to rely on 100% correct data, fully aligned with material registration processes</li>
    <li>Cost savings thanks to less administrative work, eased reporting, and a central data repository</li>
    <li>Reduced risk of non-compliance with extended producer responsibility regulations in Spain</li>
    <li>A simple, user-friendly tool to support legal reporting requirements in a timely manner</li>
    <li>Ability to expand solution usage to meet upcoming EPR legislation in other countries, like Italy</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="positive-impact-on-customers-economy-society-and-environment">Positive Impact on Customers, Economy, Society, and Environment</h2>
  <p>“The project helped us learn more about our products and incorporate their packaging details, so that our company knows exactly how much plastic and non-recycled plastic is being used. In a more strategic phase, this will allow us to evaluate alternative materials and compositions, which can create cost savings for the company and positively contribute to the environment by being able to transition to more sustainable elements,” Gonzalo Mecández concluded.</p>
  <p>Watch a solution <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/responsible-design-and-production.html?video=d287b342-047e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b">overview video</a> to learn how to start acting on a circular economy, design products sustainably, and eliminate waste with SAP Responsible Design and Production. <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/responsible-design-and-production.html?pdf-asset=6e06c630-667e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b&#x26;page=1">Read</a> about what benefits other enterprises achieved.</p>
  <p>To explore how the comprehensive, cloud-based sustainability solution portfolio from SAP can support carbon footprint management, reducing material waste, and becoming a socially responsible business, visit <a href="https://www.sap.com/sustainability.html">here</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Karin Fent is senior director of Global Customer Success, Digital Supply Chain, at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="stay-in-touch-by-following-sap-news-on-linkedin">Stay in touch by following SAP News on LinkedIn</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news">Connect with us</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/circular-economy</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>product/sap-responsible-design-and-production</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Jowat Doubles Productivity with Smarter Maintenance and Strategic Insight into Asset Management]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/jowat-smarter-maintenance-strategic-insight-asset-management</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/jowat-smarter-maintenance-strategic-insight-asset-management</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With SAP solutions, Jowat empowered its technicians to prioritize work more effectively and make smarter decisions about asset investments.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/asset-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-enterprise-support</category>
            <category>product/sap-integrated-business-planning-for-supply-chain</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Digital Transformation Helps Companies Keep Promises]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/digital-transformation-helps-keep-promises-blue-diamond</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/digital-transformation-helps-keep-promises-blue-diamond</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Innovation Award winner Blue Diamond Growers transformed for brand success, enhanced customer relationships, and supply chain visibility.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/consumer-goods-cpg</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>sap-award/sap-innovation-awards</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Turns Every Developer Into a Generative AI Developer at SAP TechEd in 2023]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/sap-teched-2023-generative-ai-developers</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/sap-teched-2023-generative-ai-developers</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[From SAP TechEd, SAP has unveiled new innovations in generative AI, vector database capabilities, and new learning opportunities.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1372d56f0d8353651580c6665a37ae494d4534f9d.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1372d56f0d8353651580c6665a37ae494d4534f9d.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1372d56f0d8353651580c6665a37ae494d4534f9d.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Turns Every Developer Into a Generative AI Developer at SAP TechEd in 2023" src="./media_1372d56f0d8353651580c6665a37ae494d4534f9d.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-turns-every-developer-into-a-generative-ai-developer-at-sap-teched-in-2023">SAP Turns Every Developer Into a Generative AI Developer at SAP TechEd in 2023</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>BANGALORE</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p>At the SAP TechEd event in 2023, <a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) announced a comprehensive series of generative AI capabilities and advancements aimed at empowering developers of all skill levels to supercharge their businesses in the age of AI.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h2 id="sap-unveils-innovations-in-generative-ai-application-development-and-vector-database-capabilities-as-well-as-new-learning-opportunities-for-developers-in-the-era-of-ai">SAP Unveils Innovations in Generative AI Application Development and Vector Database Capabilities as Well as New Learning Opportunities for Developers in the Era of AI</h2>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="enterprise-innovation-in-the-age-of-ai">Enterprise Innovation in the Age of AI</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/events/teched/news-guide.html">Read the news guide</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“Today’s dynamic technology and business landscape means every developer needs to be an AI developer,” said Juergen Mueller, Chief Technology Officer and member of the Executive Board of SAP SE. “The innovations we’re launching at SAP TechEd, from AI-infused pro-code tools to a one-stop shop to create generative AI extensions and applications on SAP Business Technology Platform, support the developers at the heart of the AI revolution and provide them with resources they need to transform the way businesses run.”</p>
  <p>As organizations aim to derive business value from generative AI, effective collaboration between professional and citizen developers is essential. SAP is launching the SAP Build Code solutions, which streamline cooperation with business experts who use the low-code <a href="/2022/11/sap-teched-sap-build-business-expertise-coursera-partnership">SAP Build</a> solutions launched at SAP TechEd in 2022. Uniquely built for SAP applications and the SAP ecosystem, SAP Build Code solutions offer AI-powered productivity tools for developers and are optimized for Java and JavaScript development. SAP Build Code also draws on the power of SAP’s new generative AI copilot Joule – the copilot that truly understands business – to further boost productivity, embedding code generation capabilities for data model, application logic and test script creation.</p>
  <p>Good data is the foundation of good AI, and SAP HANA Cloud continues to pioneer innovation in the data space by adding new vector database features to its multimodel offerings at no additional cost. Vector data stores manage unstructured data – such as text, images or audio – to provide long-term memory and better context to AI models. This makes it easy to find and retrieve similar objects quickly. For example, users can search for suppliers based on the language in their contracts to examine payment history and trace individual orders. These powerful new vector database features enhance interactions between large language models and an organization’s mission-critical data. The innovation helps put SAP developers at the forefront of delivering radically new levels of data insight within a secure, private framework that uses industry-specific customer data to reduce hallucinations.</p>
  <p>AI Foundation on SAP BTP, a new one-stop shop for developers to create AI- and generative AI-powered extensions and applications on SAP BTP, will further help increase developers’ impact and efficiency. AI Foundation includes everything developers need to start creating business-ready AI tools on SAP BTP – from ready-to-use AI services and access to the top large language models to vector database capabilities and AI runtime and lifecycle management.</p>
  <p>The rapid pace of technological innovation has driven up global demand for skilled developers – and SAP is increasing its learning opportunities in tandem. As part of a commitment to upskill two million professionals by 2025 and complement free AI learning content already available, SAP today launched <a href="https://learning.sap.com/certification/sap-certified-associate-back-end-developer-abap-cloud?url_id=text-sapnewscenter-prdteng-LSC-TechEd">new role-based certification</a> and free learning resources for back-end developers using the ABAP Cloud development model. The two new learning resources covering ABAP development tools on SAP BTP and SAP S/4HANA are available on the <a href="https://learning.sap.com/?url_id=text-sapnewscenter-prdteng-LSC-TechEd">SAP Learning site</a>. They are designed for agile and cloud-compliant business transformation, providing developers with skills to build cloud-ready extensions that are aligned with SAP’s clean core strategy. SAP <a href="/">has also joined</a> the Stanford HAI (Institute for Human-Centered AI) <a href="https://hai.stanford.edu/corporate-affiliate-program">Corporate Affiliate Program</a>. Researchers and engineers at SAP will work with the Stanford academic community, including research faculty and students, on the intersection of generative AI and business.</p>
  <p>For details on all the announcements made at SAP TechEd in 2023, please <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/events/teched/news-guide.html">visit our news guide here</a>.</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-teched-in-2023-join-us-live-in-bangalore-or-attend-virtually">SAP TechEd in 2023: Join us live in Bangalore or attend virtually</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/events/teched/bangalore.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>About SAP</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP’s strategy is to help every business run as an intelligent, sustainable enterprise. As a market leader in enterprise application software, we help companies of all sizes and in all industries run at their best: SAP customers generate 87% of total global commerce. Our machine learning, Internet of Things (IoT), and advanced analytics technologies help turn customers’ businesses into intelligent enterprises. SAP helps give people and organizations deep business insight and fosters collaboration that helps them stay ahead of their competition. We simplify technology for companies so they can consume our software the way they want – without disruption. Our end-to-end suite of applications and services enables business and public customers across 26 industries globally to operate profitably, adapt continuously, and make a difference. With a global network of customers, partners, employees, and thought leaders, SAP helps the world run better and improve people’s lives. For more information, visit <a href="http://www.sap.com">www.sap.com</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Note to editors:</strong><br>To preview and download broadcast-standard stock footage and press photos digitally, please visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/photos">www.sap.com/photos</a>. On this platform, you can find high resolution material for your media channels.</p>
  <p><strong>For customers interested in learning more about SAP products:</strong><br>Global Customer Center: +49 180 534-34-24<br>United States Only: 1 (800) 872-1SAP (1-800-872-1727)</p>
  <p><strong>For more information, press only:</strong><br>Joellen Perry, +1 (626) 265-0370, <a href="mailto:joellen.perry@sap.com">joellen.perry@sap.com</a>, PT<br>Stacy Ries, +1 (484) 619-0411, <a href="mailto:stacy.ries@sap.com">stacy.ries@sap.com</a>, ET<br>Marcus Winkler, +49 6227-767497, <a href="mailto:marcus.winkler@sap.com">marcus.winkler@sap.com</a>, CEST<br><a href="mailto:SAP%20Press%20Room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>This document contains forward-looking statements, which are predictions, projections, or other statements about future events. These statements are based on current expectations, forecasts, and assumptions that are subject to risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results and outcomes to materially differ. Additional information regarding these risks and uncertainties may be found in our filings with the Securities and Exchange Commission, including but not limited to the risk factors section of SAP’s 2022 Annual Report on Form 20-F.<br>© 2023 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.<br>Please consider our <a href="https://www.sap.com/corporate/en/legal/privacy.html">privacy policy</a>. If you received this press release in your e-mail and you wish to unsubscribe to our mailing list please contact <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a> and write Unsubscribe in the subject line.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-teched</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/abap-cloud</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-build</category>
            <category>product/sap-build-code</category>
            <category>product/sap-hana-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/stanford-hai</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Are You Working Harder Than Your Working Capital?]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/working-capital-cash-flow-cloud-erp</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/working-capital-cash-flow-cloud-erp</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Managing cash flow is vital to keep plans on track, steer through challenges, and keep a lid on risk. Cloud ERP can help. Learn how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/financial-management</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-treasury-and-risk-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Kemira Leaps Forward with SAP and cbs Corporate Business Solutions]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/kemira-leaps-forward-with-sap-and-cbs</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/kemira-leaps-forward-with-sap-and-cbs</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Industrial enterprise Kemira launched its digital business process platform based on SAP with help from cbs Corporate Business Solutions.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/chemicals</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-datasphere</category>
            <category>product/sap-integration-suite</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[BMW Group Revs Up iFACTORY Plants with SAP S/4HANA and Supply Chain Logistics]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/bmw-ifactory-sap-s-4hana-supply-chain-logistics</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/bmw-ifactory-sap-s-4hana-supply-chain-logistics</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The BMW iFACTORY in Oxford, UK, has successfully gone live with SAP S/4HANA, a milestone for BMW’s iFACTORY. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>industry/automotive</category>
            <category>news-tag/bmw</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Shinhwa Auto Drives North American Expansion with Public Cloud ERP]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/shinhwa-auto-drives-expansion-public-cloud-erp</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/shinhwa-auto-drives-expansion-public-cloud-erp</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Shinhwa Auto chose GROW with SAP so the company can operate in a more streamlined manner on a global, standardized scale. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/automotive</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/grow-with-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>product/sap-digital-manufacturing</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How PILLER Increased Customer Service with SAP Customer Experience Solutions]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/piller-increased-customer-service-sap-cx</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/piller-increased-customer-service-sap-cx</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With the help of SAP, PILLER was able to share information and optimize business processes across sales, service, and marketing.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_183ba6c7acd6d09f1a49eb03d61c336ed1830707f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_183ba6c7acd6d09f1a49eb03d61c336ed1830707f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_183ba6c7acd6d09f1a49eb03d61c336ed1830707f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="How PILLER Increased Customer Service with SAP Customer Experience Solutions" src="./media_183ba6c7acd6d09f1a49eb03d61c336ed1830707f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="how-piller-increased-customer-service-with-sap-customer-experience-solutions">How PILLER Increased Customer Service with SAP Customer Experience Solutions</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><a href="https://www.piller.de/">PILLER Blowers &#x26; Compressors</a> produces high-performance blowers and compressors and customized solutions to meet specific requirements of various industries. Its global network of wholly owned subsidiaries and joint ventures enables it to serve an international customer base.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>To increase customer service quality, the company wanted to share information and optimize business processes across its sales, service, and marketing activities.</p>
  <h2 id="moving-from-manual-processes-to-integrated-activities">Moving from Manual Processes to Integrated Activities</h2>
  <p>At PILLER, different departments were using their own IT solutions.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-customer-experience-solutions-help-connect-customer-data-improve-loyalty-and-grow-your-business">SAP Customer Experience solutions help connect customer data, improve loyalty, and grow your business</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The service department had manual processes, such as Microsoft Excel spreadsheets, to dispatch service technicians. The technicians were logging into a central server to retrieve data and recording customer support by e-mails and conversations. The sales department had a basic access environment due to custom-made products with individual serial numbers. There was no master data; tailored sales quotes were done on paper, posing challenges for data updating and quality. The marketing department was conducting its business, like capturing trade-fair leads or planning and executing campaigns, by hand and with spreadsheets. All these manual activities were time intensive and prone to human error.</p>
  <p>To enable the marketing, sales, and service teams to perform to the best of their abilities, PILLER wanted solutions that allowed it to share important information. It wished to harmonize all customer-related processes, from initial contact and order management to delivery of spare parts and follow-up.</p>
  <p>“For new products or customers, it’s important that real-time master data in our core software is mirrored in our sales, service, and marketing systems. We can do this by integrating SAP Customer Experience solutions and SAP Field Service Management with SAP S/4HANA,” said Frank Münzner, in-house SAP consultant for Lead to Cash at PILLER Blowers &#x26; Compressors GmbH.</p>
  <h2 id="adopting-cloud-solutions-to-achieve-innovative-customer-service">Adopting Cloud Solutions to Achieve Innovative Customer Service</h2>
  <p>PILLER employed the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm/sales-cloud.html">SAP Sales Cloud</a> solution to help address the needs of its sales team and integrate functionalities, such as managing quotes and orders, in one place. The solution offers a search capability and a modern, intuitive user interface.</p>
  <p>The company is using the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/field-service-management.html">SAP Field Service Management mobile app</a> to help create service tickets, which are the single point of customer contact, with product serial numbers and metadata. Integrating this mobile app with the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm/service-cloud.html">SAP Service Cloud</a> solution can enable technicians to receive service ticket information on an Apple iPad, so they can have everything they need to carry out their work. This can also translate to good customer support.</p>
  <p>By deploying the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm/marketing.html">SAP Marketing Cloud</a> solution and integrating it with SAP Sales Cloud, PILLER now proactively shares data, such as service tickets, lead opportunities, and customer contacts, between the sales and marketing teams. This lets the company contact a customer with a warranty option or service cost reduction, for example.</p>
  <p>PILLER has now integrated the three SAP Customer Experience solutions for sales, service, and marketing and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/field-service-management.html">SAP Field Service Management</a> with <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/s4hana.html">SAP S/4HANA</a>, the company’s enterprise resource planning (ERP) software.</p>
  <p>PILLER partnered with <a href="https://www.fis-gmbh.de/en/">FIS Global</a> to gain advice about new functionalities and implementation support, while <a href="https://www.ibsolution.com/en/">IBsolution</a> provided guidance around leveraging the potential in terms of business transformation and digitization.</p>
  <h2 id="gaining-comprehensive-customer-visibility-with-integrated-solutions">Gaining Comprehensive Customer Visibility with Integrated Solutions</h2>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="resolve-customer-issues-faster-with-proactive-ai-enabled-field-service-management-software-from-sap">Resolve customer issues faster with proactive, AI-enabled field service management software from SAP</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/field-service-management.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The major advantage in connecting the SAP Customer Experience portfolio, SAP Field Service Management, and SAP S/4HANA is that real-time data can be available across all these solutions. While master data, such as for a new product, customer, or material, is entered and kept in SAP S/4HANA as the core software, it’s automatically pushed into the other integrated solutions.</p>
  <p>This is helping PILLER deliver highly efficient and innovative customer service and business models. The company gains a comprehensive view of worldwide customers in real time while interacting with them at each stage of their journey in a targeted manner.</p>
  <p>There are now customer-related processes across departments, sites, and systems as well as consistent communication throughout the company, thanks to standardized forms and templates. The business is achieving agile sales with faster response times and better allocation of target groups. It’s also making decisions for customer management based on facts and analyses.</p>
  <p>Other benefits the company achieved were:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>360-degree view of customers worldwide in real time</li>
    <li>90% less paper with digital processes</li>
    <li>30% reduction in effort by using digital processes</li>
  </ul>
  <p>“We’ve always combined tradition with innovation when manufacturing our blowers. With SAP Customer Experience solutions, our customer management operations are superior to those of our competitors. We’re able to keep a close eye on processes and respond quickly and accordingly,” said Thomas Henzler, CIO at PILLER Blowers &#x26; Compressors GmbH.</p>
  <h2 id="rolling-out-customer-centric-solutions">Rolling Out Customer-Centric Solutions</h2>
  <p>Combining <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm.html">SAP Customer Experience solutions</a> and the SAP Field Service Management mobile app with SAP S/4HANA is helping deliver real-time data for integrated processes.</p>
  <p>The integration of the SAP Field Service Management mobile app with SAP Service Cloud is being piloted with three service technicians and garnering positive feedback so far.</p>
  <p>Watch an <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm/sales-cloud.html?video=189daad3-437e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b">overview video</a> of SAP Sales Cloud to help build lasting customer relationships and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm/service-cloud.html?pdf-asset=983be5bb-b27d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff&#x26;page=1">learn more about SAP Service Cloud</a> to maximize customer lifetime value with connected service. Read about the benefits companies achieved with <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/customer-stories/topcon.html">SAP Customer Experience solutions</a>. View a <a href="https://www.sap.com/sea/products/scm/field-service-management/features.html?video=66ec8033-617e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b">solution demo</a> and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/field-service-management/features.html?video=f83398c5-247e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b">overview video</a> to learn how to maximize productivity and asset uptime with SAP Field Service Management. <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/field-service-management.html?video=14f5efa9-427e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b">Learn what benefits other enterprises achieved</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Karin Fent is senior director of Global Customer Success Digital Supply Chain at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-sap-news-delivered-to-your-inbox-once-a-week">Get the latest SAP news delivered to your inbox once a week</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/nl/sap-news-center-newsletter/index.html">Sign Up</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/field-service-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-customer-experience</category>
            <category>product/sap-marketing-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>product/sap-sales-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-service-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[RISE with SAP Accelerates Biotech Innovation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/rise-with-sap-accelerates-innovation-stemcell</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/rise-with-sap-accelerates-innovation-stemcell</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[STEMCELL Technologies is digitally transforming to speed up advanced healthcare discoveries, bringing hope to patients and their families.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/digitalization</category>
            <category>industry/healthcare</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>industry/life-sciences</category>
            <category>news-tag/research-development</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How High Tech Helps S.Oleum Deliver ESG Metrics You Can Trust]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/high-tech-helps-s-oleum-deliver-esg-metrics</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/high-tech-helps-s-oleum-deliver-esg-metrics</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[S.Oleum’s data-driven sustainability efforts will generate revenue and sequester carbon. Read how SAP helps lay the foundation for success.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_130d6fab1e2941e378a85881bd255a5fab73223e2.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_130d6fab1e2941e378a85881bd255a5fab73223e2.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_130d6fab1e2941e378a85881bd255a5fab73223e2.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="How High Tech Helps S.Oleum Deliver ESG Metrics You Can Trust" src="./media_130d6fab1e2941e378a85881bd255a5fab73223e2.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="how-high-tech-helps-soleum-deliver-esg-metrics-you-can-trust">How High Tech Helps S.Oleum Deliver ESG Metrics You Can Trust</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>How can a three-year-old agroforestry company produce trustworthy, <a href="/topics/sustainability">sustainable</a> feedstock – raw materials for finished goods, energy, and more – while reducing the amount of carbon in the atmosphere?</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“We do that by using the biodiversity of this region, the Cerrado in Brazil,” Francisco de Blanco, S.Oleum co-founder and CEO, told SAP at the company’s headquarters, an innovative farm just outside João Pinheiro.</p>
  <p>Why the Brazilian outback? This tropical savanna is home to the macaúba, a highly adaptable oil-producing tree with a penchant for scrubbing harmful CO2 from the air. Macaúba fruit yields advanced vegetable oils (AVOs) and high-protein food – and it can be 15 times more productive than soybeans.</p>
  <p>“We are restoring the landscape that was deforested…Macaúba was native here many, many years ago,” Felipe Morbi, S.Oleum co-founder and Agroforestry VP, said. “Now we are bringing back these trees, and also all the other species, to restore this biodiversity.”</p>
  <p>S.Oleum seeks to accomplish this scientifically, using macaúba and other crops in an integrated crop-livestock-forest approach, according to Morbi. The goal is to create working farms that rejuvenate degraded, low-yielding soil – and that sequester into the soil more carbon than they generate.</p>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ba7dafe5dd92eabd85315450bbf0bdc404c57879.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ba7dafe5dd92eabd85315450bbf0bdc404c57879.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1ba7dafe5dd92eabd85315450bbf0bdc404c57879.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="How S.Oleum Will Use High Tech to Get Back to Brazil’s Roots" src="./media_1ba7dafe5dd92eabd85315450bbf0bdc404c57879.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://youtu.be/czukYJD_15c">How S.Oleum Will Use High Tech to Get Back to Brazil’s Roots</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="science-based-approach-to-reforesting-the-cerrado">Science-Based Approach to Reforesting the Cerrado</h2>
  <p>“We are looking for the balance of the system,” Morbi said in a new <a href="https://youtu.be/czukYJD_15c">SAP video</a>. “We will measure the amount of carbon in the soil, the moisture, the biodiversity in terms of the plants we have, and also native animals coming back to the area.”</p>
  <p>Toward that end, S.Oleum is starting small, but aiming big. Most of the current crop grows on a 700-hectare, or more than 1,700-acre, pilot farm. But S.Oleum intends to plant more than 65 million additional macaúba trees by 2029, which would reforest 180,00 hectares – about 444,800 acres – in Brazil’s southeastern state of Minas Gerais.</p>
  <p>Over time, macaúba trees also help improve the nutrient and moisture capacity of the soil, making it easier to grow other crops, according to de Blanco. And S.Oleum increases farm productivity by growing carefully chosen crops in between rows of macaúba trees, such as sunflowers, peanuts, and yucas.</p>
  <p>“If you do it right, agriculture as a system is positive for the environment,” de Blanco said. “Plants that were deforested a few decades ago, they are currently in a poor state because they were depleted by poor management…We believe there are better ways, and that’s what we are pursuing here.”</p>
  <p>An innovative case in point: macaúba trees increase a biome’s carbon sequestration levels. Removing this greenhouse gas helps more than the planet; S.Oleum also generates revenue by selling carbon credits and building trust via its data.</p>
  <h2 id="any-little-bit-of-data">Any Little Bit of Data</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="earth-overshoot-day-2023-reversing-the-clock-for-a-sustainable-future">Earth Overshoot Day 2023: Reversing the Clock for a Sustainable Future</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2023/08/earth-overshoot-day-2023-sustainable-future">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“Any little thing, any generation of data that R&#x26;D is currently developing, is extremely important,” Mirelle Santos, S.Oleum Agroforestry R&#x26;D manager, said. “We want to deploy technologies as dictated by those urgent needs.”</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_117cccc01d32d21d19b8033c668004e09a27b9c1b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_117cccc01d32d21d19b8033c668004e09a27b9c1b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_117cccc01d32d21d19b8033c668004e09a27b9c1b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Macaúba thorns" src="./media_117cccc01d32d21d19b8033c668004e09a27b9c1b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="300" height="225">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p><em>Photo by Derek Klobucher</em></p>
  <p>This could include remote sensing via drones that run fruit-recognition software, according to Santos. This would help S.Oleum gather and compile data quickly, without human error – and without sending workers, who must dress in personal protective equipment (PPE) to defend against snakes, mosquitos, the brutal Cerrado sun (even in winter), and dangerous macaúba thorns, which grow even on seedlings.</p>
  <p>S.Oleum’s intricate business model combines agriculture, forestry, biodiversity, and carbon offsetting – and that leads to a lot of complexity. SAP technology will be an important differentiator for this small enterprise, as well as a foundation for its future growth.</p>
  <p>“We have a big project to run; so, a lot of people, a lot of machines, a lot of suppliers,” Morbi said. “And we need everything in the right moment, in the right way.”</p>
  <h2 id="how-to-best-manage-esg-metrics">How to Best Manage ESG Metrics</h2>
  <p>“SAP is different because it is recognized as one of the most reliable ERP systems on the market, not only based on the technology,” de Blanco said. “Also, because it has well-established and well-defined processes.”</p>
  <p>Standardizing processes was “extremely important” for S.Oleum both internally and to inspire customer, stakeholder, and regulatory confidence, according to de Blanco. SAP will also enable S.Oleum to run its circular enterprise as well as record, report, and act on its sustainability data.</p>
  <p>“We have a very integrated system, and a very circular way to produce things,” de Blanco said. “Finding out where waste is generated – and where it’s being used – is very important to ensure the carbon intensity and the circularity of our systems at our entire site…This is where SAP helps us.”</p>
  <p>SAP S/4HANA, SAP Ariba solutions, SAP Concur solutions, and SAP SuccessFactors solutions will help standardize all of S.Oleum’s processes, which will improve transparency and compliance, according to S.Oleum IT Director Marcio Propp. To help better manage and understand its myriad environmental, social, and governance (ESG) metrics, the company has also begun implementation of <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/sustainability-control-tower.html">SAP Sustainability Control Tower</a> and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/sustainability-footprint-management.html">SAP Sustainability Footprint Management</a>.</p>
  <p>“It is super important that we have a very robust core system in place because it will serve as the basis for all our other processes…and practically all niche applications focused on digital agriculture connect with this core with SAP,” Propp said. “SAP is an agribusiness market standard, and it makes perfect sense for S.Oleum to be part of this ecosystem.”</p>
  <p>That’s a big deal because compliant, transparent ESG metrics are crucial to S.Oleum’s success, according to de Blanco.</p>
  <h2 id="a-matter-of-trust">A Matter of Trust</h2>
  <p>“Somewhere around one-third of our revenues come from carbon credits,” de Blanco said. “This is our, let’s say, core business…to convert sustainability into revenues and financial results.”</p>
  <p>That will require trust. SAP core technologies, such as SAP S/4HANA Cloud and <a href="https://www.sap.com/sustainability.html">SAP Sustainability solutions</a>, will help S.Oleum keep that trust, thanks to a reliable foundation of sustainability data and robust, auditable ESG metrics for reporting.</p>
  <p>“My advice for companies that are starting their sustainability endeavor: do it as quick as you can,” de Blanco said. “And do it attached to science.”</p>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div>For more information on how SAP helps companies record, report, and act on their sustainability goals, visit <a href="https://www.sap.com/sustainability.html">www.sap.com/sustainability</a>.</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>Top photo credit S.Oleum</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/agribusiness</category>
            <category>news-tag/circular-economy</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/esg</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-concur</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-footprint-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-sustainability-solutions</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Roche Connects Asset Data to Contextualize and Improve Every Decision]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/roche-asset-data-contextualize-improve-decisions</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/roche-asset-data-contextualize-improve-decisions</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Pharmaceutical company Roche has been improving its asset management and maintenance processes with the help of SAP solutions.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f4368188f69034eaee3b53188d1e3cd047f4908b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f4368188f69034eaee3b53188d1e3cd047f4908b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1f4368188f69034eaee3b53188d1e3cd047f4908b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Roche Connects Asset Data to Contextualize and Improve Every Decision" src="./media_1f4368188f69034eaee3b53188d1e3cd047f4908b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="roche-connects-asset-data-to-contextualize-and-improve-every-decision">Roche Connects Asset Data to Contextualize and Improve Every Decision</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>In a recent webinar, Iago Accioli, project manager of Assets at Roche, discussed how the pharmaceutical company has been improving its asset management and maintenance processes from a broader supply chain perspective.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="https://www.roche.com/about/">Roche</a> is one of the world’s largest biotech companies, a leading provider of in-vitro diagnostics and a global supplier of transformative, innovative solutions across major disease areas.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="find-a-balance-between-performance-cost-and-risk-with-sap-asset-performance-management">Find a balance between performance, cost, and risk with SAP Asset Performance Management</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/apm.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="cost-as-a-main-driver-for-asset-intensive-organizations">Cost as a Main Driver for Asset-Intensive Organizations</h2>
  <p>“As a pharmaceutical company, Roche was founded more than 100 years ago in Basel, Switzerland, with both pharma and diagnostics divisions. We are in the middle of an <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/s4hana.html">SAP S/4HANA</a> journey with the goal to harmonize business processes on all sites and divisions around the world,” said Accioli.</p>
  <p>To <a href="/topics/asset-management">manage assets</a> under volatile conditions effectively, just like other asset-intensive organizations, Roche focuses on <strong>reducing maintenance cost</strong> and <strong>increasing asset reliability</strong>, which are key to its customers and patients.</p>
  <p>The challenge is “the handover from original manufacturer to engineering to maintenance and how to interact with each other,” explained Accioli. “We resolve this with these business process harmonization initiatives.”</p>
  <h2 id="risk-resilience-as-an-investment-for-the-future">Risk Resilience as an Investment for the Future</h2>
  <p>SAP suggests three strategies to help companies manage their business holistically, including cost, speed, profit, customer service, and risk:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Connecting supply chains</strong> to the entire business so that information insight flows go quickly from operations to manufacturing, design, and into the business to respond to disruptions</li>
    <li><strong>Contextualizing information</strong> during the work process to equip users with technology to get real-time insights and make decisions during the business process to increase impact</li>
    <li><strong>Collaborating externally</strong> with suppliers, asset operators, OEMs, and logistics providers to ensure that information is flowing beyond the internal network to set up a risk-resilient business while mitigating risk</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="closing-the-loop-between-strategy-and-execution">Closing the Loop Between Strategy and Execution</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="watch-a-video-to-learn-more-about-enterprise-asset-management">Watch a video to learn more about enterprise asset management</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2020/10/9870e39a-b97d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Managing costs and increasing equipment reliability is a major factor and closing the loop between asset strategy and maintenance execution, such as to make assets more reliable and connected to maintenance execution considering different asset type, is a big opportunity.</p>
  <p>“Five to 10 years ago, reliability engineering became a shining topic at Roche, and we discussed where to start, how much we spend on maintenance, what our most important assets were, and where we should spend more energy and money. We standardized processes to classify our equipment into different asset criticalities – high, medium, and low – and, based on each category, we established a maintenance strategy,” explained Accioli.</p>
  <p>“Afterwards, we looked for a tool that would best suit Roche given the amount of data. Now we have an asset and maintenance strategy in place that is reflected in our system. In 2019, we started harmonizing our processes and were pleased that SAP solutions could support us,” he continued.</p>
  <p>In particular, Roche looked to:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/asset-strategy-performance.html">SAP Asset Strategy and Performance Management</a>, which helps with performing criticality evaluations directly in the SAP system instead of spreadsheets. With criticality results reflected in the system, the maintenance strategy can result in preventive maintenance plans. “Roche is in the middle of the journey. No sites are live yet,” said Accioli. Roche is also enabling access to its service providers to get design insights and improve collaboration.</li>
    <li><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/asset-manager.html">SAP Service and Asset Manager</a>, which enables maintenance plans and work orders to be accessible to maintenance technicians so that they can make instant material reservations and get access to maintenance manuals on mobile devices.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>“I expect a significant <strong>decrease of maintenance execution</strong> as we can plan our work better thanks to a mobile-supported solution,” said Accioli. “The experience with the solution is quite good.”</p>
  <p>Roche was already using SAP at different sites with its own work order types and data model, but it was not automated and connected.</p>
  <p>“We also intend to migrate to <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/apm.html">SAP Asset Performance Management</a>, a successor cloud-based application, where Roche’s enhancement ideas have been incorporated,” explained the manager.</p>
  <h2 id="connected-asset-data-helps-contextualize-business-decisions">Connected Asset Data Helps Contextualize Business Decisions</h2>
  <p>For contextualizing every business process through the eyes of maintenance, it is necessary to converge enterprise IT data with equipment and sensor data to run analyses based on algorithms and machine learning technology. Accioli explained: “Being able to schedule maintenance activities is a substantial improvement for maintenance organizations. To monitor both targets and results, we are using <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/cloud-analytics/features.html">SAP Analytics Cloud</a>, which has many good capabilities. We are developing maintenance KPIs with the insights we get from artificial intelligence (AI) and rolling these back into the asset strategy and reliability process. These are particularly good tools.”</p>
  <h2 id="effective-collaboration-across-the-ecosystem-to-build-a-collaborative-supply-chain">Effective Collaboration Across the Ecosystem to Build a Collaborative Supply Chain</h2>
  <p>“For Roche, sharing information and effective collaboration with asset providers and across our ecosystem is particularly important. Vendors and different equipment suppliers must exchange and collaborate on asset data. Operators and service providers should be able to use the network but also manage the work order process,” said Accioli.</p>
  <p>To summarize, the key benefits of SAP Asset Strategy and Performance Management and SAP Service and Asset Manager Accioli sees are:</p>
  <p><strong>SAP Asset Strategy and Performance Management:</strong></p>
  <ul>
    <li>Defining which maintenance strategy applies to which classification of equipment</li>
    <li>Maintaining assessments in the system</li>
    <li>Generating criticality based on assessments</li>
    <li>Reflecting reliability-centered maintenance in the system, including decision trees and supportive templates</li>
  </ul>
  <p><strong>SAP Service and Asset Manager:</strong></p>
  <ul>
    <li>Being a digitized, automated, paperless solution</li>
    <li>Being able to work offline</li>
    <li>Having all maintenance data at hand in one place</li>
  </ul>
  <p>Listen to the webinar recording <a href="https://event.on24.com/eventRegistration/console/apollox/mainEvent?&#x26;eventid=4174635&#x26;sessionid=1&#x26;username=&#x26;partnerref=&#x26;format=fhvideo1&#x26;mobile=&#x26;flashsupportedmobiledevice=&#x26;helpcenter=&#x26;key=56D188F6DDC0731803732D04D9287E5F&#x26;newConsole=true&#x26;nxChe=true&#x26;newTabCon=true&#x26;consoleEarEventConsole=false&#x26;text_language_id=en&#x26;playerwidth=748&#x26;playerheight=526&#x26;eventuserid=616413864&#x26;contenttype=A&#x26;mediametricsessionid=533671932&#x26;mediametricid=5886174&#x26;usercd=616413864&#x26;mode=launch">here</a>. In addition, watch this <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/asset-management-eam.html?video=9870e39a-b97d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff">overview video</a> to learn how to maximize asset health and performance with SAP Intelligent Asset Management solutions and read what <a href="https://www.sap.com/asset/dynamic/2022/09/77fdedf5-7bbb-4ed6-bc18-1d3febe209ca.html">benefits other enterprises achieved</a>. To know more about the role of service and asset management in your industry, <a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/dg/idc-info-brief-on-service-excellence/index.html">download this complimentary paper from IDC</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Karin Fent is senior director of Global Customer Success Digital Supply Chain at SAP.</em><br><em>Top photo credit: Roche</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/asset-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/enterprise-asset-management</category>
            <category>industry/life-sciences</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Lundin Mining Modernizes for Sustainable Growth in the New Energy Economy]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/lundin-mining-sustainable-growth-new-energy-economy</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/lundin-mining-sustainable-growth-new-energy-economy</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[As the world shifts to a lower carbon future, Lundin Mining pursues an ambitious expansion strategy for leadership in the new energy economy.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/mining: industry/mill-products</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Three Market Leaders on What It Takes to Become a Service-Based Business]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/three-market-leaders-service-based-xaas-business</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/three-market-leaders-service-based-xaas-business</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[At SAP Sapphire, industry leaders shared XaaS experiences, including business drivers and results, lessons learned, and future strategies.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/grow-with-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/quote-to-cash</category>
            <category>news-tag/recurring-revenue-models</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-billing-and-revenue-innovation-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/xaas</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Global Manufacturer Jabil Transforms and Innovates with SAP S/4HANA Cloud]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/06/jabil-transforms-innovates-sap-s-4hana-cloud</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/06/jabil-transforms-innovates-sap-s-4hana-cloud</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP customer Jabil shares how organizations can prepare today for their SAP S/4HANA Cloud journey so they’ll be future-ready for tomorrow.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>industry/mining: industry/mill-products</category>
            <category>product/sap-hana-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Future of Buying: Personalization, Predictive Recommendations, and Sustainability Awareness]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/buying-360-capability-personalization-predictive-sustainable-recommendations</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/buying-360-capability-personalization-predictive-sustainable-recommendations</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The buying 360 capability adds new services that help make purchasing more predictive, personalized, and sustainable. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>product/sap-ariba-buying</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[AI Built for Business]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/sap-sapphire-business-ai</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/sap-sapphire-business-ai</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Turning AI technology advancement into business impact remains a challenge for many companies, SAP's unique approach to AI can help.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/financial-management</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/microsoft</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-digital-assistant</category>
            <category>product/sap-extended-warehouse-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>product/sap-signavio-process-manager</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-transportation-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP and Icertis Enable Critical Outcomes around Revenue, Savings, and Risk by Integrating Contract Data to SAP S/4HANA for Procurement]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/sap-sapphire-icertis</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/sap-sapphire-icertis</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Contracts play a critical role in core business processes. To best address this, SAP continues to co-innovate with Icertis at a rapid pace.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/icertis</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP and Google Cloud Expand Partnership to Build the Future of Open Data and AI for Enterprises]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/sap-google-cloud-expanded-partnership-open-data-ai-enterprises</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/sap-google-cloud-expanded-partnership-open-data-ai-enterprises</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP and Google Cloud are introducing an open data offering designed to simplify data landscapes and unleash the power of business data.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/google-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/machine-learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-datasphere</category>
            <category>product/sap-hana-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How ERP Is Breaking Down Silos and Driving Sustainable Change]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/sustainability-and-erp-breaking-down-silos-driving-change</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/sustainability-and-erp-breaking-down-silos-driving-change</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Sustainability and ERP go hand in hand, and IBM and SAP bring together technologies, services, and platforms to help break down silos.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/ibm</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Giant Leap: Henkel Moves to the Cloud with SAP]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/sap-and-henkel-cloud-transformation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/sap-and-henkel-cloud-transformation</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP and Henkel are leveling up their strategic partnership so the consumer goods group can accelerate its digital transformation. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[AMD and SAP's 25-Year Partnership Reaches New Heights with Successful Migration to SAP S/4HANA]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/amd-and-sap-migration-s4hana-sap-25-year-partnership</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/amd-and-sap-migration-s4hana-sap-25-year-partnership</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The AMD and SAP partnership has been strengthened by AMD's successfully migration to SAP S/4HANA Cloud, private edition.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Three Steps to Profitable and Sustainable Energy Management]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/three-steps-profitable-sustainable-energy-management</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/three-steps-profitable-sustainable-energy-management</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Energy-intensive industries are exploring new trends for profitable, sustainable business and energy management. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-emissions</category>
            <category>news-tag/decarbonization</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-twin</category>
            <category>news-tag/greenhouse-gas-emissions</category>
            <category>industry/oil-gas-energy</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-io</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>