<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/digital-education/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Why It’s Better to Accept Generative AI Sooner, Not Later]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/videos/why-its-better-to-accept-generative-ai-sooner-not-later</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/videos/why-its-better-to-accept-generative-ai-sooner-not-later</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP's Julia White joins experts from Deloitte, BCG, and StartSteps Digital Education to discuss society’s scramble to get the right people into new jobs.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/video</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-education</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>non-sap-event/wef-davos</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Houston SAP Program Graduate Comes Full Circle to Attain Dream Job with HISD Mentors]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/houston-hisd-sap-program</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/houston-hisd-sap-program</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[An SAP University Alliances program in the Houston Independent School District (HISD) aims to empower youth with SAP technology skills.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-education</category>
            <category>news-tag/education</category>
            <category>industry/higher-education-research</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-university-alliances</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Code Unnati: Inspiring Bright Futures through Digital Inclusion]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/code-unnati-digital-inclusion</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/code-unnati-digital-inclusion</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Code Unnati aims to impart digital literacy among adolescents, citizens, and children as well as employable IT skills among youth. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-education</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/redefining-youth</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[German Chancellor Olaf Scholz Says Innovation Creates Hope for Society]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/german-chancellor-olaf-scholz-innovation-creates-hope</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/german-chancellor-olaf-scholz-innovation-creates-hope</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[German Chancellor Olaf Scholz attended an event celebrating SAP's 50th anniversary, where he spoke on the potential of the digital economy.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-education</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Australian Entrepreneur Turns Award-Winning Cloud Platform into Digital Career]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/06/australian-entrepreneur-digital-career</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/06/australian-entrepreneur-digital-career</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[After Blake Garrett won the Young ICT Explorers (YICTE) competition, he went on to found a cloud-based startup for educators. Learn more!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_104e832fe8b9d057bbf7af532ab0c9e841cf33686.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_104e832fe8b9d057bbf7af532ab0c9e841cf33686.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_104e832fe8b9d057bbf7af532ab0c9e841cf33686.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Australian Entrepreneur Turns Award-Winning Cloud Platform into Digital Career" src="./media_104e832fe8b9d057bbf7af532ab0c9e841cf33686.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="australian-entrepreneur-turns-award-winning-cloud-platform-into-digital-career">Australian Entrepreneur Turns Award-Winning Cloud Platform into Digital Career</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Blake Garrett, CEO of <a href="https://www.schoolbytes.education/">School Bytes</a>, never envisioned that winning a high school tech competition would lead to him founding a cloud-based company that streamlines daily administrative tasks for 440 educational institutions in Australia.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Fascinated by technology throughout his school years, Garrett had already been working on a solution to automate paper-based front office processes that he saw firsthand at Chatsworth High School. With his teacher’s encouragement, Garrett entered his project in the 2015 <a href="https://www.youngictexplorers.net.au/">Young ICT Explorers (YICTE)</a> competition, going on to win at the national level. He credited the valuable feedback from both judges and other entrants with helping him iterate and scale what has now become Sydney-based School Bytes.</p>
  <p>“I was always interested in programming and computers, and my experience with YICTE provided the chance to refine my presentation skills, meet tech industry experts, and learn from like-minded contestants,” said Garrett. “Seeing what others were working on and getting that exposure helped validate my ideas. I realized I could turn this into a viable business, and it ended up jump-starting my career.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-the-young-ict-explorers-competition">Learn more about the Young ICT Explorers competition</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.youngictexplorers.net.au/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="early-innovation-fun-leads-to-tech-careers">Early Innovation Fun Leads to Tech Careers</h2>
  <p>SAP ANZ launched YICTE 12 years ago to help stoke the region’s next generation of technology leaders. Since then, almost 8,000 students from 850 schools across Australia and New Zealand have participated in YICTE competitions. YICTE is supported by <a href="https://www.csiro.au/en/">CSIRO</a>, with help from universities, other corporate sponsors, and a long-running partnership with The Smith Family, Australia’s largest independent children’s education charity.</p>
  <p>“We want to get children in primary and high school interested in and excited about STEM careers,” said Pete Andrew, chief operating officer at <a href="https://www.sap.com/australia/index.html">SAP ANZ</a>. “The competition shows them how they can use technology to solve actual problems in the world while having fun and unleashing their creativity.”</p>
  <p>Andrew said that contest participants have pursued STEM studies, with some going on to university and internships at SAP ANZ. Similar to Garrett, others have founded <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2021/02/02/predictive-trendspotting-2021-how-to-genetically-sequence-the-lifecycle-of-a-trend/?sh=68d2fb266b0b">startups</a> of their own. Competition entries have evolved with community priorities, including sustainability, which was added as a prize category this year.</p>
  <p>“The increase in sustainability-related projects in the competition has been phenomenal. You can see the energy and passion these youths have for important topics like environmental change,” said Andrew. “Imagine being a nine-year-old interacting with your friends and presenting to a panel of judges your creative ideas to create a more sustainable future for our planet. From SAP’s perspective, this aligns with our <a href="/2021/03/sap-carbon-neutrality-goal-2023">carbon-neutral commitment</a> and <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/purpose-and-sustainability.html">corporate vision</a>.”</p>
  <h2 id="students-do-well-through-doing-good">Students Do Well Through Doing Good</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="find-out-more-about-saps-corporate-social-responsibility-partnerships">Find out more about SAP’s Corporate Social Responsibility partnerships</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/csr.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>YICTE Accelerator is among The Smith Family programs designed to help young people break the cycle of poverty through education. As part of the program, the charity provides teachers with resource support and professional development, so they can encourage students from disadvantaged backgrounds to explore career paths in tech. Students who participate in the competition are energized by developing digital tech projects that solve social issues while finding innovative solutions to real-world issues personally, locally, or nationally.</p>
  <p>“Being able to creatively solve problems in their own communities is incredibly motivating for students,” said Judy Barraclough, acting CEO at The Smith Family. “For children who might not have Internet access or computers, the YICTE Accelerator program is a wonderful chance for them to develop digital skills, showcasing their initiative and innovation. I’ve talked with many children who’ve participated, and they are committed to their own achievement so they can give back and change the experience of others in their communities.”</p>
  <p>According to <a href="https://www.educationandemployers.org/wp-content/uploads/2014/06/its_who_you_meet_final_26_06_12.pdf">research out of the UK</a>, children who have at least four exposures to career-based activities or insights during their schooling are much likelier to participate in employment beyond school. Barraclough had high praise for the partnerships that make this possible for the charity.</p>
  <p>“We depend on the support of partners like SAP to bring students incredible access to resources and professionals in the tech industry,” she said.</p>
  <h2 id="digital-transformation-through-education">Digital Transformation Through Education</h2>
  <p>Garrett’s passion for technology has come full circle. Following his YICTE competition win during the last year of high school, two schools interested in his solution immediately reached out to Garrett. School Bytes is a sponsor in this year’s virtual YICTE competition, providing judging and financial support for other aspiring youths. His advice to anyone thinking about a career in tech was simple.</p>
  <p>“Just go for it and keep iterating. One of the most exciting aspects of being in high tech is the constant change,” said Garrett. “Bringing administrative tasks into a modular, cloud subscription-based model provides schools with incredible time-saving efficiencies when it comes to managing events, sports, logistics and payments, and professional learning for teacher accreditation. To this day, we continue evolving with innovations like bringing machine learning and artificial intelligence (AI) into our solutions.”</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Follow me: @smgaler</em><br><em>This blog also appeared on <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2021/05/24/australian-entrepreneur-turns-award-winning-cloud-platform-into-digital-career/?sh=43a286993918">SAP BrandVoice on Forbes</a>.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-education</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-anz</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Amazing Inclusion Story Behind India's Digital Transformation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/05/code-unnati-inclusion-story-india-digital-transformation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/05/code-unnati-inclusion-story-india-digital-transformation</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Since SAP Labs India launched Code Unnati four years ago, the program has trained more than 1 million students in digital literacy.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15ab812331322b95cc220a54a291b18fd8d726639.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15ab812331322b95cc220a54a291b18fd8d726639.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_15ab812331322b95cc220a54a291b18fd8d726639.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="The Amazing Inclusion Story Behind India’s Digital Transformation" src="./media_15ab812331322b95cc220a54a291b18fd8d726639.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="the-amazing-inclusion-story-behind-indias-digital-transformation">The Amazing Inclusion Story Behind India’s Digital Transformation</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>As a young woman living in a rural area of Karnataka, a state located in the south western region of India, Manjula Naganur knew that education was critical to achieving her dream of a career in government administration. After completing training and education courses at <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tBRu7qwrtNk">Code Unnati</a>, she joined a fintech company and now is pursuing her post-graduate studies.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“I gained a greater understanding of what organizations expect from job candidates,” said Naganur. “The courses in software development, marketing, communications, English, banking, and problem-solving have provided me with valuable knowledge to stand out in a competitive market, giving me greater career opportunities.”</p>
  <p>Naganur is among the over 1 million students educated at Code Unnati since <a href="https://www.sap.com/india/about/labs-india.html">SAP Labs India</a> launched the program four years ago. So far, it has trained over 1 million students ages 10 to 16 years in digital literacy; 65% of these children and adolescents were girls.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="explore-how-sap-is-working-to-make-sustainability-profitable-and-profitability-sustainable">Explore how SAP is working to make sustainability profitable and profitability sustainable</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/purpose-and-sustainability.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="partnerships-scale-equitable-digital-training">Partnerships Scale Equitable Digital Training</h2>
  <p>Code Unnati is among SAP’s global <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/sustainability-csr.html">corporate social responsibility (CSR)</a> programs, in this case, supporting India’s digital readiness commitment. SAP Labs India works with partners in government as well as the non-profit and private sectors, including customers and education, to bridge the immense digital divide between people in the country’s urban and rural communities. In addition to a digital-rich learning curriculum, the program offers students the opportunity for internships and employment at SAP.</p>
  <p>“We have the incredible opportunity to help transform India from a developing to a developed economy,” said Sindhu Gangadharan, senior vice president and managing director of SAP Labs India. “We’re driving significant engagements to support the digital-first mindset that’s reflected across numerous government initiatives. Code Unnati builds digital literacy among youth and equips them with employable skills for workforce readiness, particularly beyond large, metropolitan areas.”</p>
  <p>A total of over 6,000 youth have participated in the vocational curriculum, which includes learning future IT skills, such as data science and analytics, and next-gen technologies like <a href="https://insights.sap.com/what-is-artificial-intelligence/">artificial intelligence (AI)</a> and <a href="https://insights.sap.com/what-is-machine-learning/">machine learning</a>. Most importantly, an average of over 40% of program graduates obtain jobs after program completion.</p>
  <h2 id="responsible-inclusive-use-of-technology">Responsible, Inclusive Use of Technology</h2>
  <p>Code Unnati reflects just about every one of the Indian government’s “digital readiness for the next billion” commitment, notably talent development, amped up investments in research and development, innovations for both India and the world, and inclusiveness. <a href="https://nasscom.in/">The National Association of Software and Service Companies (NASSCOM)</a> is among the groups leading this initiative, working with the government and companies like SAP.</p>
  <p>“We want to leverage technology as best as possible to solve some of India’s biggest challenges,” said Debjani Ghosh, president of NASSCOM. “As we bring technology into pretty much everything we do, it can become an equalizer, as long as we start at the design stage to make sure that it’s truly inclusive across sectors, regardless of rural or urban, gender, culture, or religion.”</p>
  <h2 id="digital-literacy-for-indias-specific-needs">Digital Literacy for India’s Specific Needs</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="at-goodwill-wine-procurement-with-a-purpose">At Goodwill Wine, Procurement with a Purpose</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/05/goodwill-wine-procurement-with-purpose">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Although India is digitally transforming like the rest of the world, the magnitude of its revolution is much bigger in scale and scope compared to many other regions. Ghosh said that talent development is among the government’s highest priorities, helping to build the population’s digital skills through public-private sector partnerships that provide training and education, mentoring, and internships.</p>
  <p>“Whether you call it a challenge or an opportunity, India has an amazing diversity of socioeconomic levels, cultures, religions, and languages,” she said. “We’re committed to partnering with the government and companies like SAP to build and foster ecosystems that use accelerators, mentorships, hackathons, and other opportunities to drive the IT charter for India.”</p>
  <h2 id="community-wide-purpose-plus-business-profit">Community-Wide Purpose Plus Business Profit</h2>
  <p>More than anything, Code Unnati reflects a commitment to purposeful business that positively impacts people’s lives.</p>
  <p>“It’s not just about bringing technology into pretty much everything we do to make things easier and personalized, but also that we build and use the technology responsibly,” said Ghosh.</p>
  <p>Democratizing technology education is also central to SAP’s purpose-driven mission, helping organizations become intelligent enterprises using <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/intelligent-technologies.html">SAP Business Technology Platform</a>. Spearheading Code Unnati with funds and resources from customers, partners, and its own employees, SAP is also at the forefront of India’s mission to provide disadvantaged students with digital skills for their future, as well as India’s.</p>
  <p>“We’ve been able to quickly scale and achieve meaningful business outcomes with partners focusing on purpose plus profit,” said Gangadharan. “We’re helping everyone lift up society for the sustainable change that’s much needed in India.”</p>
  <p>In this context, Naganur’s singular educational experience is a shining example of the tremendous opportunities in store for India’s next billion people with digital empowerment.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Follow me: @smgaler</em><br><em><a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2021/05/04/the-amazing-inclusion-story-behind-indias-digital-transformation/?sh=49137a2c47b5">This story originally appeared on SAP BrandVoice on Forbes</a></em>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-education</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-labs-network</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>