<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/chasing-zero/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Earth Overshoot Day 2022: Can We Live in Balance with the Earth?]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/earth-overshoot-day-2022-live-balance</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/earth-overshoot-day-2022-live-balance</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[On Earth Overshoot Dat 2022, we focus on what can and has to be done to turn the human economy around to be more sustainable.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/chasing-zero</category>
            <category>non-sap-event/earth-overshoot-day</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Chasing Zero with SAP Industry Network for Automotive]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/sap-industry-network-for-automotive-greentoken-product-carbon-footprint</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/sap-industry-network-for-automotive-greentoken-product-carbon-footprint</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Solutions like SAP Industry Network for Automotive and GreenToken help enterprises gain insights into their product carbon footprint data.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/automotive</category>
            <category>news-tag/catena-x</category>
            <category>news-tag/chasing-zero</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-industry-network-for-automotive</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Earth Day 2022: Teaming Up to Invest in Our Planet]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/04/earth-day-2022-invest-in-our-planet</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/04/earth-day-2022-invest-in-our-planet</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[On Earth Day 2022, it is up to all of us to reflect on what our contribution to “investing in our planet” is and what more we can do.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/chasing-zero</category>
            <category>non-sap-event/earth-day</category>
            <category>news-tag/economics</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reimagining the Fashion Industry by Designing Out Waste]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2021/10/reimagining-fashion-industry-sustainability-queen-of-raw</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2021/10/reimagining-fashion-industry-sustainability-queen-of-raw</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Scott Russell and Stephanie Benedetto of Queen of Raw discuss how the fashion industry can help ensure a more sustainable future.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14763198f62b34a409f6b5785d1019aef5368bd9a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14763198f62b34a409f6b5785d1019aef5368bd9a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_14763198f62b34a409f6b5785d1019aef5368bd9a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Reimagining the Fashion Industry by Designing Out Waste" src="./media_14763198f62b34a409f6b5785d1019aef5368bd9a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="reimagining-the-fashion-industry-by-designing-out-waste">Reimagining the Fashion Industry by Designing Out Waste</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>As climate disasters continue to devastate communities around the world, businesses, governments, and citizens increasingly seek to understand the major contributors to climate change to reverse any reparable effects and ensure a more sustainable future for all.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The fashion industry is one of the most significant contributors to the climate crisis today. Between excess water, dangerous chemicals, carbon emissions, and huge amounts of waste, the fashion industry faces a critical juncture. Will the industry seize the opportunity to change its course and positively impact the planet? Despite the huge task at hand, creative and innovative entrepreneurs provide hope for a more sustainable future for fashion.</p>
  <p>I had the privilege to sit down and speak with one such entrepreneur, <strong>Stephanie Benedetto</strong>, to learn more about how she is changing the textile industry and the world while encouraging others to have courage in their convictions and act on their beliefs. <strong><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fZY0ivl0K6g">Listen to our conversation</a></strong> and read more about her story below.</p>
  <h2 id="from-rags-to-circular-riches">From Rags to Circular Riches</h2>
  <p>In 1896, an Austrian man arrived on a boat on Ellis Island. As an immigrant chasing the “American dream” in the Lower East Side of New York, he started a business, one that generated profit while doing good for the planet. He repurposed old fabrics and furs brought over by other immigrants and transformed them into beautiful fashion garments.</p>
  <p>One hundred years later, this profitable clothing business with humble beginnings would inspire the Austrian immigrant’s great granddaughter, Benedetto, to leave her job as a corporate attorney and become a fashion tech and sustainability entrepreneur. Benedetto returned to her roots and sparked disruption with the goal of building a business to change the world, scaling her grandfather’s efforts for even greater impact.</p>
  <h2 id="meet-the-queen-of-raw">Meet the Queen of Raw</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-more-stories-about-the-chasing-zero-initiative">Read more stories about the Chasing Zero initiative</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/topics/chasing-zero">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Stephanie Benedetto, CEO and founder of <a href="https://www.queenofraw.com/">Queen of Raw</a>, is a visionary entrepreneur, creating opportunity out of the seemingly insurmountable challenges facing the fashion industry. Today, <a href="https://www.queenofraw.com/about-us">$120 billion worth of excess fabric</a> sits in warehouses and <a href="https://www.queenofraw.com/about-us">87% of fiber input</a> used for clothing ends up burned or in landfills.</p>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f7c8e5f66f4072a73f6b703b404ad9f13bcfb08d.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f7c8e5f66f4072a73f6b703b404ad9f13bcfb08d.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1f7c8e5f66f4072a73f6b703b404ad9f13bcfb08d.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Chasing Zero Podcast with Scott Russell, SAP and Stephanie Benedetto, Queen of Raw" src="./media_1f7c8e5f66f4072a73f6b703b404ad9f13bcfb08d.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://youtu.be/fZY0ivl0K6g">Chasing Zero Podcast with Scott Russell, SAP and Stephanie Benedetto, Queen of Raw</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Benedetto wanted to eliminate the excess water, waste, and emissions that had become an inherent part of the value chain for clothing production. She sought to turn pollution into profit through the creation of a global marketplace that allowed users to list, sell, and buy deadstock fabric. This led to Queen of Raw, which offers new life to sustainable materials, including organic cotton, peace silk, faux leather and fur, and quality luxury deadstock fabrics.</p>
  <h2 id="technology-to-scale-for-impact">Technology to Scale for Impact</h2>
  <p>Using supply chain software, powered by artificial intelligence (AI), Queen of Raw alters the linear economic model typical of the fashion industry and transforms it into a circular economic model, protecting the environment while driving value financially. At its core, Queen of Raw uses technology to drive sustainability at scale, repurposing textile waste so it can be turned into something beautiful.</p>
  <p>But Queen of Raw seeks to go beyond creating a marketplace for deadstock fabric.</p>
  <p>“A marketplace to sell waste is great,” said Benedetto. “It’s powerful, but it’s kind of just slapping a band aid on the problem.”</p>
  <p>So how do you get to the root of the problem to figure out how to minimize waste <em>?</em></p>
  <p>“That’s where we leverage our incredible partnership with SAP, helping businesses capture data through machine learning, AI, and blockchain so they can act on the waste — and water — challenge at hand,” said Benedetto.</p>
  <p>Data insights and transparency provide a key piece of the puzzle when it comes to enabling more sustainable business practices globally. Technology, collaboration, and innovation make widespread change possible, and Queen of Raw provides an encouraging, real-life example of how business leaders can bring these elements together to marry people, planet, and profit at scale.</p>
  <h2 id="reimagining-fashion-textiles-and-supply-chains">Reimagining Fashion, Textiles and Supply Chains</h2>
  <p>Benedetto demonstrates firsthand the incredible potential of technology to reimagine fashion, textiles, and value chains. Her optimism and creativity in the face of a water crisis and a waste problem provides hope for a better future. And she has strong reason to believe that her business and the commitment of other purpose-driven entrepreneurs can make a difference.</p>
  <p>Since it began in 2018, Queen of Raw has already saved 1 billion gallons of water. By democratizing access to the resale technologies, Benedetto is empowering groups across industries to participate in the circular economy.</p>
  <p>Together, through creative solutions like Queen of Raw, we can help foster a more sustainable world, one we can be proud of leaving behind for the next generation – with fresh water to drink and clean air to breathe.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Scott Russell is a member of the Executive Board of SAP SE.</em><br><em><a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2021/10/20/reimagining-the-fashion-industry-by-designing-out-waste/?sh=61a521529e08">This story originally appeared on SAP BrandVoice on Forbes</a>.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/blog/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/blog/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/blog/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/blog/article-read-more</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/executive-blog</category>
            <category>news-tag/chasing-zero</category>
            <category>news-tag/economics</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[New openSAP Course on the Circular Economy]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/new-circular-economy-course-opensap</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/new-circular-economy-course-opensap</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A new circular economy course on openSAP is free and open to anyone who wants to make a difference to the future of the planet. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_113f2308f10670c1d9eb45f0e2ab7e83fb6637d2f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_113f2308f10670c1d9eb45f0e2ab7e83fb6637d2f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_113f2308f10670c1d9eb45f0e2ab7e83fb6637d2f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="New openSAP Course on the Circular Economy" src="./media_113f2308f10670c1d9eb45f0e2ab7e83fb6637d2f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="new-opensap-course-on-the-circular-economy">New openSAP Course on the Circular Economy</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="register-for-the-new-opensap-course-now">Register for the new openSAP course now</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://open.sap.com/courses/ce1">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>The world is on track to increase waste generation by <a href="https://openknowledge.worldbank.org/bitstream/handle/10986/30317/211329ov.pdf?sequence=11&#x26;isAllowed=y">70%</a> over the next 30 years. Much of this garbage is plastic, and it’s no surprise why: plastic production increased from <a href="https://www.nationalgeographic.com/environment/article/plastic-pollution">2.3 million tons in 1950 to 448 million tons in 2015</a> and is expected to double to 896 million by 2050. Now, about 8 million tons of plastic waste winds up in the ocean each year.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>George Leonard, <a href="https://www.nationalgeographic.com/science/article/plastic-pollution-huge-problem-not-too-late-to-fix-it">chief scientist at the Ocean Conservancy</a>, says, “If we don’t get the plastic pollution problem in the ocean under control, we threaten contaminating the entire marine food web, from phytoplankton to whales. And by the time the science catches up to this, perhaps definitively concluding that this is problematic, it will be too late. We will not be able to go back. That massive amount of plastic will be embedded in the ocean’s wildlife essentially forever.”</p>
  <p>Clearly, the time for action is now. “We must rethink, innovate, and implement at an unprecedented pace and scale to enable a thriving future for environment, economy, and society,” says Thomas Saueressig, member of Executive Board of SAP SE, Product Engineering.</p>
  <p>It can be easy to feel overwhelmed by the enormity of the waste crisis facing the planet. Through education, the leaders of today can be empowered to change how we consume, how we operate, and how we do business.</p>
  <p>That thriving future will not be built on the current disposable culture but instead by embracing the <a href="https://ellenmacarthurfoundation.org/topics/circular-economy-introduction/overview">circular economy</a> model, one in which waste is eliminated, resources are recirculated, and nature is regenerated.</p>
  <p>As a leader in business software — including product design and manufacturing, supply chain and logistics, and product lifecycle management — SAP has both the technology and the responsibility to help global enterprises to develop circular systems. Indeed, the company has already started this vital work by providing the tools to companies that are interested in the circular economy through <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/purpose-and-sustainability/economy.html">sustainability solutions</a>.</p>
  <p>With these business models already in place, a new openSAP course, <a href="https://open.sap.com/courses/ce1">Helping Business Thrive in a Circular Economy</a>, offers anyone — SAP customer or not — a better understanding of how to apply these principles to their own business.</p>
  <p>Specifically, three key principles are defined by the Ellen MacArthur Foundation, an NGO dedicated to accelerating the adoption of this sustainable model:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Keep products and materials in use as long as possible</li>
    <li>Design out waste and pollution</li>
    <li>Regenerate natural systems</li>
  </ul>
  <p>With these three directives as a guide, the free on-demand course features pioneering experts in the circular economy, such as <a href="https://ellenmacarthurfoundation.org/our-story/the-team/ceo-trustees/andrew-morlet">Andrew Morlet</a>, CEO of the Ellen MacArthur Foundation, and <a href="http://business-school.exeter.ac.uk/about/people/profile/index.php?web_id=Peter_Hopkinson">Peter Hopkinson</a>, professor of Circular Economy and co-director of the Exeter Center for the Circular Economy. It also features environmental activists and sustainable product luminaries, including <a href="https://www.emilypenn.com/">Emily Penn</a>, an ocean advocate and co-founder of eXXpedition, a trip that took 300 remarkable women on a circumnavigation of the globe to study the problem of plastics in the ocean. <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/stephaniebenedetto/">Stephanie Benedetto</a>, CEO and co-founder of Queen of Raw, a marketplace for sustainable textiles, is a featured lecturer.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="chasing-zero-the-future-can-be-greener-cleaner-and-more-equal">Chasing Zero: The future can be greener, cleaner, and more equal</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/purpose-and-sustainability.html#chasing-zero">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="https://open.sap.com/courses/ce1">Helping Business Thrive in a Circular Economy</a> is more than just a course. It tackles some of the most important issues of the day and is intended to change the global trajectory on waste by bringing businesses into the process. According to Saueressig, “Now more than ever, to achieve circularity, we must connect linear fragmented supply chains into unified, collaborative, and intelligent business networks that enable the reuse of materials.”</p>
  <p>At SAP, we believe that technology is an important enabler to driving a circular and regenerative economy. It’s not the whole answer, but a key part of the solution. We need organizations to come together to tackle this, so SAP has launched the course to help spread the word and evangelize on why we must move to a world of zero waste — and move now.</p>
  <p>The course begins October 4, 2021, and is free and open to anyone who wants to make a difference to the future of the planet.Content is available on demand. <a href="https://open.sap.com/courses/ce1">Sign up here</a>, and share it with your networks.</p>
  <p>Participating in just a few hours of coursework each week provides a cutting-edge education in how to bring the principles of a circular economy to businesses operating today. In five weeks, participants can gain a new understanding of this pivotal concept for their edification and to share with friends and colleagues, and see how to apply this to their own organizations.</p>
  <p>In addition, it’s a valuable opportunity for team building. There are many options for collaboration within the course, including a discussion forum as well as optional peer-graded teamwork activities to gain extra credits. Those who complete all coursework will be eligible for a Record of Achievement certificate.</p>
  <p>Importantly, participants will also be engaging with a vital concept that is already helping to build a sustainable future through partnerships between SAP and their clients. This course could be the first step on the journey to a better future for all.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Darren West is business development director for Circular Economy at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/chasing-zero</category>
            <category>news-tag/circular-economy</category>
            <category>news-tag/economics</category>
            <category>news-tag/opensap</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Building Solutions for a Future That Has Already Arrived]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2021/09/building-solutions-future-arrived</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2021/09/building-solutions-future-arrived</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[When we embed emissions data into underlying business processes, leaders can drive real change. Learn how SAP software makes it possible.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ce4079fb9ff43bc587f3a1cfa56f34bc9756b8f9.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ce4079fb9ff43bc587f3a1cfa56f34bc9756b8f9.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1ce4079fb9ff43bc587f3a1cfa56f34bc9756b8f9.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Building Solutions for a Future That Has Already Arrived" src="./media_1ce4079fb9ff43bc587f3a1cfa56f34bc9756b8f9.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="building-solutions-for-a-future-that-has-already-arrived">Building Solutions for a Future That Has Already Arrived</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="register-now-for-the-upcoming-sap-sustainability-day-to-experience-what-sap-innovations-have-to-offer">Register now for the upcoming SAP Sustainability Day to experience what SAP innovations have to offer</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://events.sap.com/sap-sustainability-summit/en/home">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>The time for climate action is now. Many are talking about it. We are acting. This is humanity’s chance to recalibrate and respond to the dire threats we ourselves created. We are continuing to deeply embed sustainability into the enterprise software this world needs now more than ever. With the help of our solution portfolio, SAP – together with our unparalleled customer and partner base – is best positioned to systematically reduce carbon emissions and help business tackle today’s most complex challenges.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“The world is on fire,” according to <a href="https://www.nasa.gov/image-feature/goddard/2018/a-world-on-fire">satellite images captured by NASA</a> and a recent <a href="https://www.businessinsider.com/nasa-astronauts-saddened-to-see-climate-crisis-wildfires-from-space-2021-8">Business Insider interview</a> with astronauts from the International Space Station. While many parts of the world deal with extreme heat, others struggle with extreme flooding. The <a href="https://www.ipcc.ch/report/ar6/wg1/">recent United Nation (UN) Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change (IPCC) climate report</a> says nations are “nowhere close” to the level of action needed to fight global warming and the effects of extreme weather caused by climate change. The need for climate action is undeniable and opportunities for green house gas (GHG) reductions are within our grasp. Action to date has been slow, but it’s accelerating.</p>
  <p>I see a surge in companies seeking to reduce GHG emissions coming. November’s upcoming <a href="https://ukcop26.org/">COP26</a>, the 26th UN Climate Change Conference of the Parties, is set to ensure that action around science-based target setting will accelerate. And I’m hearing from industry and government leaders that we will see unprecedented corporate climate action, driven by regulation and good business, that aligns with the <a href="https://www.mckinsey.com/business-functions/sustainability/our-insights/climate-math-what-a-1-point-5-degree-pathway-would-take">1.5 degree of global warming limit set by the Paris Agreement</a>.</p>
  <p>Pressure from governments and consumers is mounting as climate change is unfolding before our eyes — faster even than scientists predicted. I’m watching the upcoming COP26 where the International Financial Reporting Standards (IFRS) Foundation’s International Sustainability Standard Board (ISSB) will be launched in November. This robust, <a href="https://assets.ey.com/content/dam/ey-sites/ey-com/en_gl/topics/sustainability/ey-the-future-of-sustainability-reporting-standards-june-2021.pdf">globally consistent sustainability reporting standard</a> will adopt a climate-first approach and have a big impact on our customers.</p>
  <p>Our customers are asking us to help them make the necessary change at scale. And we are ready to help them meet the requirements. But many businesses have moved forward without reassessing their business models or focusing on the underlying process, data, and governance changes that they must make to accurately measure, manage, and reduce their carbon emissions. Why? Because it’s complex!</p>
  <p>Calculating environmental and social impacts across a company’s products and services and across the entirety of their life cycles is simply complicated. Yet supply chain emissions are on average <a href="https://www.cdp.net/en/research/global-reports/transparency-to-transformation">11.4 times higher than operational emissions</a>. So merely focusing on individual operational emissions is no longer enough. Actually, it was always just a first step.</p>
  <p>Understanding complex business challenges and optimizing existing business processes has always been SAP’s strength. The breadth and depth of our industry expertise, spanning 50 years, enables us to help businesses today to not just optimize, but reinvent their business processes, like no other company can. That’s what today’s challenges call for.</p>
  <p>As we near our 50-year company anniversary, we build on that legacy today by enabling business to meet new challenges. We know that dashboarding is not enough. When we embed emissions data into underlying business processes, leaders can drive real change by making conscious decisions across the entire value chain. That’s what scales the transition to low carbon pathways, and SAP is uniquely positioned to drive this change across collaborative, intelligent, and sustainable business networks.</p>
  <p>These activities are interconnected and must be done together to achieve maximum impact. Our business software applications bring together materials, energy, and financial flows to steer businesses in a holistic way. These are not add-ons. We have found significant value from the interconnectedness of these factors over our decade of integrated reporting and steering, and are working closely with our customers through organizations such as the <a href="https://www.value-balancing.com/">Value Balancing Alliance</a> to accelerate this approach for all sectors.</p>
  <p>We not only enable individual intelligent enterprises, we connect them to each other. We support the move from intelligent sustainable enterprises to a network of intelligent sustainable enterprises. This is the key to achieving real change for the planet. Just as GHG emissions go beyond the four walls of a company, efforts to reduce those emissions must also extend beyond individual companies, into the network of companies.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-carbon-footprint-solution-helps-companies-redesign-for-sustainability">SAP Carbon Footprint Solution Helps Companies Redesign for Sustainability</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>While every company can start by focusing on their own individual supply chains, those further down the path to sustainability can use the <a href="/2021/08/value-networks-sustainable-business">network as a pathway to scale</a>. <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/08/0605ebb8-f07d-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">According to IDC</a>*, “Consolidating data into a unified network means better access, streamlined analysis and the opportunity to more effectively turn insights into action.” Systemic industry change needs the network effect, and it needs a spark.</p>
  <p>The customer base that we currently serve covers 94% of the world’s 500 largest companies which represents an immense capacity for real change at scale. Partnerships also help accelerate our product innovation. SAP is <a href="https://www.wbcsd.org/Overview/News-Insights/General/News/SAP-Joins-the-World-Business-Council-for-Sustainable-Development-to-innovate-in-global-decarbonization-effort">innovation partner in WBCSD’s Value Chain Carbon Transparency Pathfinder</a>, dedicated to enhancing transparency in corporate carbon emissions with the objective to ultimately decarbonize supply chains.</p>
  <p>We emphasize the role of technology for the green transition and EU taxonomy as a founding member of <a href="https://digital-strategy.ec.europa.eu/en/policies/european-green-digital-coalition">European Green Digital Coalition</a>. In addition to working with these established partners and others, SAP is supporting sustainability innovation from startups around the world. For example, through our <a href="https://sap.io/sustainability/">SAP.iO Foundries</a> program, startups play a pivotal role in catalyzing innovations on sustainability across the globe.</p>
  <p>We facilitated systemic industry change 50 years ago with our enterprise software based on our founders’ vision. Now we are doing it again in order to tackle the climate crisis. The business model innovation we drive helps improve energy efficiency across both conventional and renewable energy value chains, it supports decarbonizing through electricity generation and transmission such as green hydrogen, and it helps our customers to decarbonize their products and services, for example, by adopting circularity.</p>
  <p>We have not slowed down on our promise to innovate in this product space throughout the <a href="/covid-19">pandemic</a>. Just recently, we made our <a href="/">SAP Product Footprint Management solution generally available to our customers</a> to support them in monitoring, analyzing, and reducing emissions to deliver on their climate commitments.</p>
  <p>We are building for the future. And I believe that future is coming faster than anyone even thought.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>Read more about our exciting sustainability product developments from <a href="/">Jan Gilg</a> and review the product deep dives by <a href="https://blogs.sap.com/2021/08/31/sap-enables-turning-environmental-footprint-calculations-at-scale-into-a-regular-habit/">Gunther Rothermel</a> and <a href="https://blogs.sap.com/2021/09/02/product-deep-dive-welcome-to-product-footprint-management-from-sap/">Nico Wottke</a>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><em>Thomas Saueressig is a member of the Executive Board of SAP SE.</em></p>
        <p><em>*IDC InfoBrief, Sponsored by SAP, Global B2B Collaboration Networks: Critical Enablers of Business Resiliency, IDC Doc. #US47857121, August 2021.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="changing-the-future-with-sap-s4hana-at-the-core-of-a-sustainable-intelligent-enterprise">Changing the Future with SAP S/4HANA at the Core of a Sustainable, Intelligent Enterprise</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/blog/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/blog/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/blog/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/blog/article-read-more</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/executive-blog</category>
            <category>news-tag/chasing-zero</category>
            <category>news-tag/economics</category>
            <category>product/sap-product-footprint-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Carbon Footprint Solution Helps Companies Redesign for Sustainability]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/sap-product-footprint-management-redesign-sustainability</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/sap-product-footprint-management-redesign-sustainability</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Product Footprint Management, which lets companies calculate carbon footprints for products and across the value chain, is now available.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_19d36522df6973ef89439b8c7028f4f5c82fbe843.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_19d36522df6973ef89439b8c7028f4f5c82fbe843.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_19d36522df6973ef89439b8c7028f4f5c82fbe843.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Carbon Footprint Solution Helps Companies Redesign for Sustainability" src="./media_19d36522df6973ef89439b8c7028f4f5c82fbe843.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-carbon-footprint-solution-helps-companies-redesign-for-sustainability">SAP Carbon Footprint Solution Helps Companies Redesign for Sustainability</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced the availability of SAP Product Footprint Management, a solution that lets companies calculate carbon footprints for their products and across the value chain. It considers the entire product lifecycle, helping companies disclose their products’ environmental footprints to regulators and enabling them to make their products more sustainable.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP Product Footprint Management is part of a new portfolio of sustainability-specific business applications that deliver transparency and measurement capability across the supply chain, allowing companies to move toward lower carbon emissions and more sustainable operations.</p>
  <p>“Customers want it, the world needs it. There is no time to waste for businesses to act more responsibly and sustainably. Sustainability goals are increasingly as important to business success as financial goals,” said <a href="/">Thomas Saueressig</a>, member of the Executive Board of SAP SE and responsible for SAP Product Engineering. “When companies embed emissions data into underlying business processes, leaders can drive real change by making conscious decisions across the entire value chain. That is what scales the transition to low emission pathways, and SAP is uniquely positioned to drive this change throughout collaborative, intelligent and sustainable business networks.”</p>
  <p>By integrating data across all solutions that govern production processes with master data from business applications such as SAP S/4HANA, SAP Product Footprint Management can calculate the environmental impact of various production scenarios. For example, <a href="https://blogs.sap.com/2021/09/02/product-deep-dive-welcome-to-product-footprint-management-from-sap/">a cookie company</a> can choose its source for chocolate based both on the cost of the raw material as well as on its carbon footprint.</p>
  <p>SAP’s data-driven approach lets businesses embed sustainability comprehensively and gain actionable insights across the entire value chain to enable companies to transition to low-carbon business processes. Taking a differentiating approach, SAP enables businesses to proactively identify the carbon impact at the beginning of the product lifecycle instead of reactively after a product has been produced. Moreover, SAP Product Footprint Management not only equips companies with the insight to reduce carbon emissions across their value chains but can enable data exchange with customers, suppliers and business partners — driving transparency across a company’s scope 1, scope 2 and scope 3 emissions.</p>
  <p>SAP Product Footprint Management, a cloud-native solution built on <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">SAP Business Technology Platform</a>, is designed to measure and report greenhouse gas emissions. Proposed governmental regulations designed to combat the harmful effects of climate change could cost businesses <a href="https://www.cdp.net/en/articles/supply-chain/environmental-supply-chain-risks-to-cost-companies-120-billion-by-2026">up to $120 billion</a>. A recent IDC survey showed linking financial and environmental indications in financial reporting, as well as reducing carbon emissions, are top topics for IT decision-makers.*</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="building-solutions-for-a-future-that-has-already-arrived">Building Solutions for a Future that Has Already Arrived</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="saps-commitment-to-sustainability">SAP’s Commitment to Sustainability</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="changing-the-future-with-sap-s4hana-at-the-core-of-a-sustainable-intelligent-enterprise">Changing the Future with SAP S/4HANA at the Core of a Sustainable, Intelligent Enterprise</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP has been leading by example in sustainable business practices for more than a decade. In addition to being named the software industry leader in the <a href="/2020/11/dow-jones-sustainability-indices-sap-again-leads">Dow Jones Sustainability Indices</a> (DJSI) for 14 consecutive years, SAP’s membership in the <a href="/2019/08/value-balancing-alliance-sap-founding-member">Value Balancing Alliance</a> and the <a href="https://nam12.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.sap.com%2Fintegrated-reports%2F2020%2Fen.html&#x26;data=04%7C01%7CCameron.Baker%40edelman.com%7C6fe81550b14a4592eea308d95dd601d6%7Cb824bfb3918e43c2bb1cdcc1ba40a82b%7C0%7C0%7C637643996927963163%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJWIjoiMC4wLjAwMDAiLCJQIjoiV2luMzIiLCJBTiI6Ik1haWwiLCJXVCI6Mn0%3D%7C1000&#x26;sdata=Fi22Vatgtc0gQD8YUjmw3BUZqTabx4hqwenHYSnJdgk%3D&#x26;reserved=0">SAP Integrated Report</a> illustrates our commitment to integrating economic, environmental and social performance to drive business decisions.</p>
  <p>“SAP has long had a strong, dedicated focus on its own sustainability operations. The launch of the SAP Product Footprint Management solution, combined with the <a href="https://www.wbcsd.org/Programs/Climate-and-Energy/Climate/SOS-1.5/Resources/Value-Chain-Carbon-Transparency-Pathfinder-Enabling-decarbonization-through-Scope-3-emissions-transparency">WBCSD’s Pathfinder Project</a>, represents a unique opportunity to bring together companies to jointly drive decarbonization across value chains and industries,” said Marta Muñoz, senior research director and Lead Technology &#x26; Sustainability Practice, IDC EME.</p>
  <p>To learn more visit the <a href="/">SAP News Center</a> and follow SAP on Twitter at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>About SAP</strong></p>
  <p>SAP’s strategy is to help every business run as an intelligent enterprise. As a market leader in enterprise application software, we help companies of all sizes and in all industries run at their best: 77% of the world’s transaction revenue touches an SAP system. Our machine learning, Internet of Things (IoT), and advanced analytics technologies help turn customers’ businesses into intelligent enterprises. SAP helps give people and organizations deep business insight and fosters collaboration that helps them stay ahead of their competition. We simplify technology for companies so they can consume our software the way they want — without disruption. Our end-to-end suite of applications and services enables business and public customers across 25 industries globally to operate profitably, adapt continuously, and make a difference. With a global network of customers, partners, employees, and thought leaders, SAP helps the world run better and improve people’s lives. For more information, visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/">www.sap.com</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Note to editors:</strong><br>To preview and download broadcast-standard stock footage and press photos digitally, please visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/photos">www.sap.com/photos</a>. On this platform, you can find high resolution material for your media channels. To view video stories on diverse topics, visit <a href="http://www.sap-tv.com">www.sap-tv.com</a>. From this site, you can embed videos into your own Web pages, share video via email links, and subscribe to RSS feeds from SAP TV.</p>
  <p><strong>For customers interested in learning more about SAP products:</strong><br>Global Customer Center: +49 180 534-34-24<br>United States Only: 1 (800) 872-1SAP (1-800-872-1727)</p>
  <p><strong>For more information, press only:</strong><br>Stacy Ries, +1 (484) 619-0411, <a href="mailto:stacy.ries@sap.com">stacy.ries@sap.com</a>, ET<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p><em>*IDC, The Increasing Importance of ESG Principles for Enterprises, Doc # EUR147475621, February 2021.</em></p>
  <p>Any statements contained in this document that are not historical facts are forward-looking statements as defined in the U.S. Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995. Words such as “anticipate,” “believe,” “estimate,” “expect,” “forecast,” “intend,” “may,” “plan,” “project,” “predict,” “should” and “will” and similar expressions as they relate to SAP are intended to identify such forward-looking statements. SAP undertakes no obligation to publicly update or revise any forward-looking statements. All forward-looking statements are subject to various risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results to differ materially from expectations. The factors that could affect SAP’s future financial results are discussed more fully in SAP’s filings with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (“SEC”), including SAP’s most recent Annual Report on Form 20-F filed with the SEC. Readers are cautioned not to place undue reliance on these forward-looking statements, which speak only as of their dates.<br>© 2021 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.<br>Please consider our <a href="https://www.sap.com/corporate/en/legal/privacy.html">privacy policy</a>. If you received this press release in your e-mail and you wish to unsubscribe to our mailing list please contact <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a> and write Unsubscribe in the subject line.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/chasing-zero</category>
            <category>news-tag/economics</category>
            <category>product/sap-product-footprint-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Changing the Future with SAP S/4HANA at the Core of a Sustainable, Intelligent Enterprise]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/sap-s4hana-core-sustainable-intelligent-enterprise</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/sap-s4hana-core-sustainable-intelligent-enterprise</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With SAP S/4HANA at the core, SAP supports the sustainable intelligent enterprise for a lasting positive impact on the world.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18d6b52af6ef4f063989b96299cec7c07c8064b6b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18d6b52af6ef4f063989b96299cec7c07c8064b6b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_18d6b52af6ef4f063989b96299cec7c07c8064b6b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Changing the Future with SAP S/4HANA at the Core of a Sustainable, Intelligent Enterprise" src="./media_18d6b52af6ef4f063989b96299cec7c07c8064b6b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="changing-the-future-with-sap-s4hana-at-the-core-of-a-sustainable-intelligent-enterprise">Changing the Future with SAP S/4HANA at the Core of a Sustainable, Intelligent Enterprise</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>With the recent launch of the SAP Product Footprint Management solution, SAP S/4HANA is uniquely positioned to create and mold a lasting positive impact for our future generations.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>I grew up in Germany and can still remember when we started to separate our trash for recycling back in the 80s or 90s – our rivers and forests were suffering, and the environment was becoming a big topic. Even though we have seen progress on this front here in Germany, if you look at the global situation today, it’s clear we need to do more. It goes far beyond separating our trash. I sometimes wonder if I am part of the last generation that had the privilege to grow up in a world where natural disasters were an exception rather than the rule. Thinking about my own children, this is certainly a gut-wrenching thought.</p>
  <p>I do not know if there is a guide through a slow-motion emergency, but the fact that climate change is already at our front door is inescapable. With the current state of the planet setting the context for us, talking about sustainability is talking about survival. It is about redefining growth, rethinking progress, and limiting financial risk. How we view our business or our industry will be a key driver in how well we proceed in creating a sustainability vision for our organization, both from within and without.</p>
  <p>And <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/sustainability.html">sustainability is core to our vision at SAP</a>. By placing sustainability at the front and center of our purpose, SAP’s strategy underlines the importance of technology, and specifically technological innovation, in enabling and accelerating climate action, hand in hand with our customers and partners.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-carbon-footprint-solution-helps-companies-redesign-for-sustainability">SAP Carbon Footprint Solution Helps Companies Redesign for Sustainability</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="placing-sustainability-at-the-front-and-center">Placing Sustainability at the Front and Center</h2>
  <p>With <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/s4hana-erp.html">SAP S/4HANA Cloud</a>, we are uniquely positioned to create a lasting, positive impact for our future generations. Leveraging SAP’s exemplary track record of managing enterprise resources for close to five decades, we want to collaborate and work closely with our customers to transition to sustainable business models. Our vision to enable customers to transform into intelligent, sustainable enterprises is based on our shared values in “<a href="/topics/chasing-zero">chasing zero</a>“: zero emissions (GHG), zero waste, and zero inequality.</p>
  <p>By integrating sustainability data into end-to-end business processes across industries and value chains, we can have a significant impact and accelerate the pace of change needed. In close collaboration with our partners, customers, market makers, and standard bodies, we intend to jointly shape the future sustainability landscape that enables and drives new, redefined business process models.</p>
  <p>The success of the <a href="https://events.sap.com/sap-sustainability-summit/en/home">SAP Sustainability Summit</a> in April this year clearly shows that our ecosystem is ready to join forces with us, making it clear that business leaders — in addition to their top and bottom lines — also want to focus on managing their “green line” for sustainable business success. This has become the guiding principle for the way we want to evaluate and steer businesses in the future.</p>
  <h2 id="embedding-sustainability-across-the-entire-value-chain">Embedding Sustainability Across the Entire Value Chain</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="building-solutions-for-a-future-that-has-already-arrived">Building Solutions for a Future that Has Already Arrived</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP S/4HANA Cloud’s sustainability portfolio addresses four dimensions, including climate action, circular economy, holistic steering and reporting, and social responsibility.</p>
  <p>Through a highly differentiated set of products, we will enable organizations to assess and reduce their carbon footprint, increase resource productivity through circular processes, and run safer, sustainable business processes while providing industry-specific insights that combine operational and financial data across value chains, embedded in core business processes.</p>
  <p><a href="/">SAP Product Footprint Management has now been released</a>. In the next few months, we will release SAP Responsible Design and Production, already available as beta, and SAP Sustainability Control Tower, and we will deliver innovations via modular embedded SAP S/4HANA Cloud services, based on an open, flexible architecture built on top of SAP Business Technology Platform. We will continue to expand across the breadth of our SAP portfolio, bringing additional capabilities with SAP Business Network and different lines of businesses, addressing most critical use cases in different industries to enable our customers to manage their environmental, societal, and planetary impact.</p>
  <p>SAP Product Footprint Management is an embedded SAP S/4HANA cloud-native application that enables our customers to optimize their business decisions by integrating footprint scores, preconfigured and flexible, in end-to-end business processes, periodically and at scale, considering the entire product life cycle. Our customers can gain insights by combining financial, logistic, and environmental data in analytics and can evaluate and derive footprints at scale by leveraging SAP S/4HANA Cloud data and capabilities as much as possible.</p>
  <p>SAP Product Footprint Management is preconfigured, prescriptive, and focuses on business users (persona-based). It is based on SAP’s business data and application logic and is consistent in the calculated product footprints being integrated into the end-to-end operational processes covering all relevant business users in every department.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_12971a6dff11b744b4ad8c35f22fb33aff96bf8ae.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_12971a6dff11b744b4ad8c35f22fb33aff96bf8ae.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_12971a6dff11b744b4ad8c35f22fb33aff96bf8ae.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Product Footprint Management – Business Architecture" src="./media_12971a6dff11b744b4ad8c35f22fb33aff96bf8ae.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="1080">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p><em>SAP Product Footprint Management – Business Architecture (click to enlarge).</em></p>
  <p><a href="/">SAP Product Footprint Management is an answer to various challenges</a> that our customers have encountered, whether it is the availability of emissions data to calculate product footprint across the product life cycle or the availability of calculation adhering to standards aligned to GHG Protocol ISO 14040. These indicate that high efforts are required for calculating the footprints and understanding how to use the results or the data gained from it to better optimize the way businesses are run.</p>
  <p>Businesses agree that they need to calculate the footprint on a product level in the future, but they are unsure about how to go about it. They are still exploring different data and calculation methods. Our customers want to calculate the product footprints and then they want to analyze it — with their own tools.</p>
  <p>To evaluate the environmental impact of the collected business data and goods movements and to be able to calculate footprints at scale, this data needs to be combined with emission factors. <a href="https://www.ecoinvent.org/">Ecoinvent</a>, a not-for-profit organization, is our first partner to offer product-related emission factor datasets from its database. Building on more than 20 years of experience in lifecycle assessment methodology and around 18,000 datasets covering global supply chains, the ecoinvent emission factor datasets can be, with a license, easily imported into SAP Product Footprint Management.</p>
  <p>In the future, we plan to enable other content providers as well so that our customers can use every provider whose data is standardized as per our applications.</p>
  <p>It is important to establish a clear governance, ownership, and process for managing and reporting on carbon emissions. Clarity on governance will in turn drive the clarity on underlying data needs, as well as system requirements. Our partnership with the United Nations (UN) Global Compact and Accenture on <a href="https://www.unglobalcompact.org/take-action/sdg-ambition">SDG Ambition</a> is an important component of our sustainability efforts. SDG Ambition aims to engage leaders across more than 1,000 companies in over 40 countries over the next two years and draw greater focus on making sustainability core to business strategy.</p>
  <p>With our technologies, we will enable our customers to accelerate their journeys to achieving ambitious targets, helping them advance the integration of the UN Sustainable Development Goals (SDGs) into their core business systems, thereby systematically working toward their <a href="https://www.unglobalcompact.org/take-action/events/climate-action-summit-2019/business-ambition">Business Ambition for 1.5°C</a>.</p>
  <h2 id="completing-the-picture-by-achieving-sustainability-multi-dimensionally">Completing the Picture by Achieving Sustainability Multi-Dimensionally</h2>
  <p>With <a href="https://www.sap.com/hk/products/ehs-management-health-safety.html">SAP Environment, Health, and Safety Management</a>, we enable our customers to manage their corporate environmental footprint — air, water, waste, carbon — as well as their GHG emissions at a corporate level. SAP Product Footprint Management captures product lifecycle emissions required by Product Standards, as outlined in <a href="https://ghgprotocol.org/sites/default/files/standards/ghg-protocol-revised.pdf">GHG Protocol</a>.</p>
  <p>To approach the challenge of climate change in a holistic manner and to expand it along further aspects, including water, energy, and land use as well as social dimensions, we need to begin at the core: SAP S/4HANA Cloud.</p>
  <p>Having recognized and taken this major step, we plan to build on it and will expand to include and embed exchange emissions data into our line-of-business applications, including procurement, travel, and expense, to help bring a complete emissions transparency for our customers through SAP Sustainability Control Tower.</p>
  <p>As an example, companies can gain visibility into carbon footprint data throughout a product’s supply chain, bringing the ability to take sustainable supply chain decisions based on actionable insights. Product-related carbon footprint data, such as for production, material sourcing, or transport, from SAP Product Footprint Management can be utilized in <a href="https://roadmaps.sap.com/board?PRODUCT=67838200100800006742&#x26;range=2021Q4-2021Q4#Q4%202021;INNO=000D3A47875C1EEB96E01207898774B6">SAP Integrated Business Planning for Supply Chain</a>.</p>
  <p>The issue of sustainability can sometimes be overwhelming and it is easy to feel hopeless. But because it is a global, complex issue, it has risen to the forefront, not only in policy conversations about how to make a change, but also in the business consciousness. There is a real shift happening now in terms of how we view climate change and how we believe we can turn concern into action.</p>
  <p>Businesses are well positioned to lead on innovations and technology that will help slow down their impact on the environment and recognize that business can only succeed if society thrives.</p>
  <p>While there is no ready-made, off-the-shelf answer to the questions our next generation asks us, we simply must make sure that what we do today gets us closer to where we want to be tomorrow — because what we save also saves us.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Jan Gilg is president of SAP S/4HANA.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/chasing-zero</category>
            <category>news-tag/economics</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
            <category>product/sap-product-footprint-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Converging on Stakeholder Capitalism]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/converging-stakeholder-capitalism</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/converging-stakeholder-capitalism</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Stakeholder capitalism is resurgent in the business world today. SAP Chief Sustainability Officer Daniel Schmid explains.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1dc67c3d72d90f816f7df7e989ec2e210fdb850b9.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1dc67c3d72d90f816f7df7e989ec2e210fdb850b9.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1dc67c3d72d90f816f7df7e989ec2e210fdb850b9.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Converging on Stakeholder Capitalism" src="./media_1dc67c3d72d90f816f7df7e989ec2e210fdb850b9.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="converging-on-stakeholder-capitalism">Converging on Stakeholder Capitalism</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="build-sustainability-directly-into-your-core-business-processes-with-sap">Build sustainability directly into your core business processes with SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/sustainability.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>There is no shortage of crises in the headlines today. Stories on the ongoing <a href="/covid-19">pandemic</a>, floods, wildfires, droughts, wildlife extinctions, racial and gender injustices, and corporate corruption fill our screens. The role of businesses around the world to pull together and collectively contribute to solving these problems is more urgent than ever.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>But across global boardrooms there remains a philosophical divide about the purpose of business. It is becoming more apparent that the concept of “shareholder capitalism” — putting corporate earnings above all else — is a diminishing notion. Resurgent is “<a href="https://www.weforum.org/agenda/2021/01/what-is-the-difference-between-stakeholder-capitalism-shareholder-capitalism-and-state-capitalism-davos-agenda-2021/">stakeholder capitalism</a>,” where business considers the broader interests of investors, employees, society, and the planet.</p>
  <p>Top executives are prioritizing environmental, social, and governance (ESG) activities that support the interests of the broader group of stakeholders. Time is of the essence because the impacts of <a href="https://www.ipcc.ch/ar6-syr/">climate change</a> and <a href="https://livingplanet.panda.org/en-us/">biodiversity</a> loss are plainly obvious. ESG topics are affected by more stringent regulations as well as employee, customer, and investor scrutiny. It’s also increasingly clear that strong performance in these traditionally non-financial issues is a competitive advantage and <a href="https://www.mckinsey.com/business-functions/sustainability/our-insights/the-esg-premium-new-perspectives-on-value-and-performance">supports long-term value creation</a>. With companies making <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/dishashetty/2021/03/24/a-fifth-of-worlds-largest-companies-committed-to-net-zero-target/?sh=62cc3a83662f">a slew of ambitious public commitments</a>, from diversity to net-zero, it is clear that measuring performance will be essential to effective management, performance assessments, and collective achievement.</p>
  <p>For years, companies have reported their ESG or non-financial performance. This kind of reporting is increasingly mandatory for listed companies, while private and smaller companies are increasingly reporting voluntarily.</p>
  <p>The challenge for all of them, however, is the broad range of reporting frameworks and standards. More than 100 ESG reporting guidelines are in use, oftentimes conflicting and redundant, making it virtually impossible for executives, investors, and other stakeholders to determine credible progress or compare impacts across different companies and industries. Ninety percent of corporates <a href="https://www.weforum.org/whitepapers/toward-common-metrics-and-consistent-reporting-of-sustainable-value-creation">said that a set of universal ESG metrics</a> and disclosures would be useful for financial markets and the economy. Consolidation around a universal, comparable set of reporting standards is urgently needed.</p>
  <p>The World Economic Forum’s (WEF) International Business Council (IBC) asked a number of global accounting firms to agree on a set of ESG metrics that all companies can use as a “foundation” in their ESG reporting. Drawing from the range of existing widely used frameworks and standards, the <a href="https://www.weforum.org/reports/measuring-stakeholder-capitalism-towards-common-metrics-and-consistent-reporting-of-sustainable-value-creation">World Economic Forum Stakeholder Capitalism metrics</a> were released last year. The initiative aims to accelerate the convergence of reporting standards. The framework uses a set of measures to value and report the business performance across four “Ps”: Principles of Governance, Planet, People, and Prosperity.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b2453c578036bf4aaf9f54be9709554be25a4965.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b2453c578036bf4aaf9f54be9709554be25a4965.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1b2453c578036bf4aaf9f54be9709554be25a4965.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="WEF: Four Ps" src="./media_1b2453c578036bf4aaf9f54be9709554be25a4965.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="575" height="309">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p><em>Image via WEF</em></p>
  <p>Today, <a href="https://www.weforum.org/stakeholdercapitalism/our-community">more than 100 companies</a> have committed to the concept of stakeholder capitalism and support using the WEF metrics. Around 30 companies have already begun implementing them in their corporate reporting. In the few years ahead, rapid adoption and use of the WEF metrics by thousands of companies, as well as cooperation among other standards organizations and regulators, will be crucial to the widespread support needed to accelerate convergence.</p>
  <p>SAP has committed to the WEF Stakeholder Capitalism metrics and encourages further global standardization and convergence in the ESG reporting landscape. We offer support to the initiative by including the standards in our own global reporting and also offering the framework in our core sustainability software solutions. Our hundreds of thousands of international customers, including 80% of the Fortune 500, are encouraged to implement the Stakeholder Capitalism metrics. Companies that already have established reporting systems can add the WEF framework, and companies just beginning to report can use the framework as their starting point.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div><em>The metrics will be recommended in our</em><br><em>sustainability software solutions to help fast-track a</em><br><em>vital “core and common” reporting language.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The areas covered in the four Ps have been translated into a set of 21 core metrics, which are seen as critically important across industries. A number of additional measures are available to provide more detail and industry-specific information. The metrics are supported in our sustainability software solutions to help fast-track a vital “core and common” reporting language.</p>
  <p>Converging the overly complex world of ESG reporting and understanding the stakeholder perspective of how companies positively and negatively impact society is the first step. A vital evolution will be the widespread adoption of a value-to-business perspective and applying financial values to these traditional non-financial ESG actions. It is an important distinction between reporting the performance of an ESG metric and putting a monetary value on an ESG performance.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="the-balance-sheet-blind-spot-how-sustainability-affects-competitiveness-and-profits">The Balance Sheet Blind Spot: How Sustainability Affects Competitiveness and Profits</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://insights.sap.com/environmental-sustainability-affects-competitiveness/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>For comparability and holistic corporate management and decision-making, it is essential to monetize impacts in financial terms and include them in disclosures. This financial-driven view clarifies how these ESG impacts affect the company’s financial performance. Both perspectives are intrinsically related and are often referred to as “double materiality.”</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1267dac3abd8826d381492c891e433cb7d7dac9fd.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1267dac3abd8826d381492c891e433cb7d7dac9fd.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1267dac3abd8826d381492c891e433cb7d7dac9fd.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_1267dac3abd8826d381492c891e433cb7d7dac9fd.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1378" height="668">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p><em>Image via VBA</em></p>
  <p>Both perspectives are fundamental for understanding a company’s long-term value creation. SAP is a founding member of the <a href="https://www.value-balancing.com/">Value Balancing Alliance</a>, which aims to standardize measurement and valuation methodologies to <a href="https://www.weforum.org/whitepapers/the-future-of-the-corporation-moving-from-balance-sheet-to-value-sheet">put ESG impacts on the P&#x26;L statement</a>, act as practitioner’s lab and pilot the methodologies to create a unified voice for the industry.</p>
  <p>The VBA and the Stakeholder Capitalism metrics are similar and share a common goal. In April of this year, the VBA and the WEF issued a joint announcement supporting a shared view on accounting standards.</p>
  <p>Way back in 2013, a prescient Peter Bakker, CEO of the World Business Council for Sustainable Development (WBCSD), said that <a href="https://hbr.org/2013/03/accountants-will-save-the-worl">accountants would save the world</a> and that we needed to change accounting rules. Those changes are coming. We believe <a href="https://insights.sap.com/redefine-success-sustainability-reporting/">standardized approaches to valuating ESG impacts</a> should be established globally. A “balance sheet” set of impact measures is not enough; we also need an impact profit-and-loss sheet.</p>
  <p>With financial values assigned to these traditionally non-financial ESG measures, a new accounting standard is required. Organizations like the International Financial Reporting Standards (IFRS) Foundation are now considering broadening their mandates to include sustainability issues. All major reporting standards groups and the WEF are part of a core working committee of the IFRS on a new accounting standard. Their approach is scheduled to be announced at the upcoming COP26 in Glasgow in November.</p>
  <p>As industries and markets mature, they tend to converge and establish clearer standards, processes, and players. In the rapidly expanding area of corporate ESG measurement and reporting, we encourage the use of technology solutions to more efficiently capture, manage, analyze, and use sustainability data for better sustainability stewardship.</p>
  <p>Companies across industries, supply chains, and geographies will have to focus their disparate systems to better support data collection and management, supplier connectivity, employee and customer engagement. This is essential for competitive decision-making and making investments in activities that support stakeholder capitalism.</p>
  <p>When global business has more connected, validated, and accurate sustainability performance information, combined with a shared vision and common reporting and valuating language, we will have the power to achieve our most ambitious goals together.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Daniel Schmid is chief sustainability officer of SAP SE.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/chasing-zero</category>
            <category>news-tag/economics</category>
            <category>news-tag/world-economic-forum</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Interconnected Nature of Profitability and Sustainability]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/sustainability-journey-profitability-interconnected-nature</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/sustainability-journey-profitability-interconnected-nature</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Companies that commit to a sustainability journey today will be the ones that remain competitive and relevant tomorrow. Learn why.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_128b56351e31d3f600b1103bd3d2cb09d32e35259.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_128b56351e31d3f600b1103bd3d2cb09d32e35259.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_128b56351e31d3f600b1103bd3d2cb09d32e35259.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="The Interconnected Nature of Profitability and Sustainability" src="./media_128b56351e31d3f600b1103bd3d2cb09d32e35259.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="the-interconnected-nature-of-profitability-and-sustainability">The Interconnected Nature of Profitability and Sustainability</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>At SAP, we often discuss the link between profitability and sustainability, asking, “Are companies that are more sustainable also more profitable?” But upon further reflection, the better question is “Can a company that is not sustainable be successful long term?”</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>I believe that companies that commit to their sustainability journeys today will be the ones that remain competitive and relevant tomorrow. To explore the link between profitability and sustainability in more depth, we need to consider the <strong>time frame</strong>, the way we define <strong>success</strong>, and how we <strong>measure</strong> a company’s value.</p>
  <p>These factors accelerate the paradigm shift from profit maximization to value optimization.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="chasing-zero-aspire-to-a-world-with-zero-emissions-zero-waste-and-zero-inequality">Chasing Zero: Aspire to a world with zero emissions, zero waste, and zero inequality</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/purpose-and-sustainability.html#chasing-zero">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="time-frame">Time Frame</h2>
  <p>As companies recover from <a href="/covid-19">COVID-19</a>, business leaders must consider short-term financial profitability and maximizing shareholder value alongside environmental and social factors that could affect the business’ success in the future. It comes back to the question: “Can a company that is not sustainable be successful long term?”</p>
  <p>Fortunately, even in the short term, a clear link exists between sustainability and profitability. For example, the replacement of business travel with remote collaboration enhances sustainability and cuts down on travel costs. At SAP, a focus on climate action has contributed to a cumulative cost avoidance of €354.3 million in the past three years. However, we achieved 92% of this cost avoidance in 2020, when we were forced to rethink business as usual, illustrating the immense possibility for large-scale impact.</p>
  <p>Nevertheless, sustainability can sometimes require investing today in the long-run profitability of a company and incurring costs that will pay off later. Companies already make many investments with the hopes of “returns” at a future date, such as marketing campaigns or <a href="/2021/03/mental-health-day-sap-employees">giving employees an extra day off</a> to boost their motivation, improve well-being, and increase productivity. Employee training offers another example of an initial investment with payoff down the line.</p>
  <p>In 2019, SAP joined the <a href="/2019/08/value-balancing-alliance-sap-founding-member">Value Balancing Alliance</a> (VBA) to better understand the entire value contribution of our business, which will be further explored below. According to the VBA, our global employee training programs were valued at €1.3 billion, but much of this payoff will be seen years from now through employee output, retention, and satisfaction.</p>
  <p>Broadening the time frame through which you view business success can enable more strategic decision making that sets the company up to thrive not just today, but tomorrow and for years to come.</p>
  <h2 id="redefining-success">Redefining Success</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-more-stories-about-the-chasing-zero-initiative">Read more stories about the Chasing Zero initiative</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/topics/chasing-zero">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Long-term profitability and sustainability present the opportunity to question historical definitions of business success. Profit maximization and increasing shareholder value alone will no longer suffice. The concept of <a href="https://www.sharedvalue.org/about/what-is-shared-value/">shared value</a> presents an alternative way to define success, one that uses core business processes to drive societal change.</p>
  <p>In Harvard Business School’s <em>Sustainable Business Strategy</em> concept, the “wheel of change” illustrates how large-scale transformation occurs across entire industries, starting with shared value. When businesses “do well and do good” through legitimate, innovative practices, it can inspire industry-wide cooperation that alters consumer, investor, and state behavior. This encourages companies to adopt more sustainable practices, ultimately redefining success in a way that considers the entire value creation of an entity.</p>
  <p>Consumer, investor, and state behaviors play a critical role in holding the private sector accountable for prioritizing shared value. Consumers and employees want to support and work for purpose-driven companies. Investors demand that companies disclose not only financial performance but also environmental, social, and governance (ESG) performance to properly assess risk and make investment decisions. And governments increasingly implement climate-related regulations, taxes, and policies, as well as workplace safety procedures, extended producer responsibility (EPR) schemes, anti-discrimination laws, and more.</p>
  <p>For businesses, it will be critical to consider a holistic view of their performance, one that integrates positive and negative impacts on the economy, society, and the environment. Research shows that a <a href="https://www.responsible-investor.com/storage/inline/ESG%20Study%202018%20-%20Digging%20deeper%20-%20112018.pdf">strong correlation exists between ESG performance and operational performance</a>.</p>
  <h2 id="measurement">Measurement</h2>
  <p>Redefining success to include sustainability requires measurements that capture this element of performance. For business leaders to make the appropriate decisions and set the strategy for a company’s long-term success, they need access to comprehensive data and metrics that go beyond financial measurements. This enables holistic steering and reporting, with the visibility required to mitigate negative ESG impact and increase positive ESG impact.</p>
  <p>As mentioned previously, SAP joined the VBA in an effort to transform the way businesses measure and value their societal impact. The VBA develops and tests methodologies that assign a monetary value to the impact of any decision, translating environmental and social impacts into comparable financial data. The VBA equips decision-makers with the knowledge to decide and act consciously.</p>
  <p>Profitability is a necessary condition for sustainability but alone is insufficient. Business can positively impact planet and people, but not if limited planetary resources run out. Unfortunately, the earth’s resources do not align with earnings cycles or CEO tenures, and sooner or later we will suffer the consequences.</p>
  <p>Paul Polman recognized this early on and launched Unilever’s <a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-sustainbility-unilever-ceo-idUSBRE8A11FH20121102">Sustainable Living Plan</a> (SLP) to help ensure that his business would be around 50, 100, or 200 years from now. The SLP shifted Unilever’s focus from solely meeting investor’s quarterly earnings to putting environmental and social impact top of mind. Similarly, Kering developed an <a href="https://www.kering.com/en/sustainability/measuring-our-impact/our-ep-l/what-is-an-ep-l/">Environmental Profit and Loss Account</a> to effectively measure its environmental footprint and convert it into monetary value. Utilizing this measurement tool provides a holistic approach to reporting that guides business decisions and respects natural resources.</p>
  <p>Unilever and Kering know that the successful businesses of the future will integrate sustainability into core business operations today.</p>
  <p>By adopting a long-term perspective, redefining success, and adjusting how we measure it, we can inspire a paradigm shift from profit maximization to value optimization, altering the status quo at our own companies and throughout the world. Innovation, business model transformation, and cross-industry collaboration will fuel this change. Wherever your business is today, this transition is a journey.</p>
  <p>You may not be there yet, but it’s time to start by putting this question front and center: “Can a company that is not sustainable be successful long-term?”</p>
  <p>At SAP, we believe it cannot.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Daniel Schmid is chief sustainability officer of SAP SE.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/chasing-zero</category>
            <category>news-tag/economics</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[When Value Chains Become Value Networks, Business Becomes Sustainable]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2021/08/value-networks-sustainable-business</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2021/08/value-networks-sustainable-business</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 05 Aug 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Supported by SAP Business Network, value networks can achieve sustainability goals much better than any company on its own. Learn how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/executive-blog</category>
            <category>news-tag/chasing-zero</category>
            <category>news-tag/economics</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Why Doing Business As Usual Can Cost Us Dearly]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2021/07/earth-overshoot-day-business-as-usual-can-cost-us-dearly</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2021/07/earth-overshoot-day-business-as-usual-can-cost-us-dearly</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[On Earth Overshoot Day, SAP CEO Christian Klein discusses how SAP can help protect our planet and create a better future for our children.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_12a8d26c316039df7af71f2f7c159ffbf8a65b64f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_12a8d26c316039df7af71f2f7c159ffbf8a65b64f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_12a8d26c316039df7af71f2f7c159ffbf8a65b64f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Why Doing Business As Usual Can Cost Us Dearly" src="./media_12a8d26c316039df7af71f2f7c159ffbf8a65b64f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="why-doing-business-as-usual-can-cost-us-dearly">Why Doing Business As Usual Can Cost Us Dearly</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>I am a proud dad of two young kids. Since they were born, the world has experienced a global <a href="/covid-19">pandemic</a>, increasing social unrest, numerous political conflicts, and countless natural disasters from heat waves and wildfires to record flooding.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Oftentimes, when we talk about sustainability, we think about it in terms of the distant future. But looking at the past few years alone, it becomes clear that we don’t need solutions in, say, five years. We need them now.</p>
  <p>It’s not about what we are doing to make the world better by the time our children are grown up, but about what can we do to make things better right now. What are we doing to make an impact by the time they learn to ride a bike, have their first day in kindergarten, leave school, and enter their first job?</p>
  <p><strong>We need to act now to ensure that our children have a sustainable future.</strong></p>
  <p>We might think that our individual actions don’t matter. But changes – both big and small –in the way we live our lives can help reduce our own personal carbon footprint, and also encourage other individuals, businesses, and policy makers to act for the good of the planet. Because at the end of the day, everything counts. Every day we act, every step we take, every decision we make can help move the needle. And vice versa: Every step we don’t take today will take us three steps back in the future.</p>
  <p>Today is <a href="/2021/07/earth-overshoot-day-2021">Earth Overshoot Day 2021</a>. It marks the date when humanity has exhausted nature’s budget for the year. From this day forward, we are using an unsustainable amount of the world’s resources. The exact date each year is calculated based on 3 million statistical data points from 200 countries, and the team at Global Footprint Network <a href="https://www.overshootday.org/about-earth-overshoot-day/">explains the process here</a> in more detail.</p>
  <p>This year’s date is almost as early as in 2019, when it fell on July 26, after being momentarily pushed back in 2020 by lockdowns due to the coronavirus pandemic. So for more than 40 years, we have been using up our planet’s resources in excess. Our desire for every aspect of our lives to become better, faster, and newer is not only stealing from a planet that cannot keep up with the demands of almost 8 billion people, but also costing our future generations an Earth on which they can live and prosper.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="chasing-zero-aspire-to-a-world-with-zero-emissions-zero-waste-and-zero-inequality">Chasing Zero: Aspire to a world with zero emissions, zero waste, and zero inequality</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/purpose-and-sustainability.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="covid-19-reset">COVID-19 Reset</h2>
  <p>The graphic above shows what is possible in extreme situations such as with the numerous lockdowns and restrictions due to the COVID-19 pandemic.</p>
  <p>Just a few examples: Due to beach closures in Florida, female turtles laid more eggs. In Japan — one of my favorite countries to visit — the Nara deer left the park to find food because the tourists that would normally feed them were no longer there. Air and water quality improved as tourism ground to a halt. For the first time in 30 years, Indians in the city of Jalandhar and the surrounding area could see the Himalayas.</p>
  <p>These examples show that our planet could recover relatively quickly if given the chance. However, life in many parts of the world is returning to a new version of normal with more and more people receiving vaccinations. While this is good for humanity, it also has an impact on nature.</p>
  <h2 id="our-responsibility">Our Responsibility</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-more-from-saps-chief-sustainability-officer-about-earth-overshoot-day-2021">Read more from SAP's Chief Sustainability Officer about Earth Overshoot Day 2021</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/07/earth-overshoot-day-2021">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The private sector for sure has its part to play if we are to combat climate change. Businesses should not focus exclusively on profit maximization, but at turning things around, in the here and now, for current and future generations.</p>
  <p>Without any doubt, sustainability is about more than protecting our environment. It is about ensuring the balance between economic growth, environmental care, and social welfare. That said, carbon neutrality is a major driver and key indicator of sustainability.</p>
  <p>At SAP, we set our goal to become carbon-neutral in our own operations by the end of 2023, two years earlier than previously stated. The SAP approach is of first avoiding, second reducing, and third compensating for emissions. You can read more about <a href="/2021/03/sap-carbon-neutrality-goal-2023">our goal for 2023 here</a>.</p>
  <p>But in addition to pursuing our own targets, we also want to help our customers become more sustainable. Because we are convinced: It’s time to build sustainability into the fabric of how we do business. We need to make it a standard dimension of corporate management just like productivity or growth.</p>
  <p>We’ve <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/sustainability.html">developed various solutions</a> to help businesses embed operational, experiential, and financial data and insights to drive sustainability at scale. With our sustainability portfolio, we support companies on their entire journey across the full spectrum of sustainability – from carbon neutrality to social impact and economic progress.</p>
  <p>Additionally, we will drive multi-year innovation roadmaps to ultimately provide our customers with end-to-end visibility around sustainability, integrated into their core business processes. To get to our vision of <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/purpose-and-sustainability.html">Chasing Zero</a>, we must act now with the goal of zero waste, zero emissions, and zero inequality.</p>
  <p>Given the significance of global supply chains in tackling sustainability, the SAP community truly has the power to protect our planet and create a future our children want to be part of. So, let’s give our planet the chance to recover and #MoveTheDate together.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Christian Klein is CEO of SAP SE.</em><br><em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/pulse/why-doing-business-usual-can-cost-us-dearly-christian-klein/">This piece was originally published on LinkedIn</a>.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/blog/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/blog/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/blog/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/blog/article-read-more</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/executive-blog</category>
            <category>news-tag/chasing-zero</category>
            <category>news-tag/climate-action</category>
            <category>non-sap-event/earth-overshoot-day</category>
            <category>news-tag/economics</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[CFOs Turn On Sustainability Reporting and ESG Metrics in Enterprise Software Suites]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/cfo-sustainability-reporting-esg-metrics-enterprise-software</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/cfo-sustainability-reporting-esg-metrics-enterprise-software</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[An updated approach to holistic steering and reporting that considers ESG metrics is necessary in today's world. Learn why.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_165b223f05b5705112f166ca7c1546bbdc6a85d00.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_165b223f05b5705112f166ca7c1546bbdc6a85d00.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_165b223f05b5705112f166ca7c1546bbdc6a85d00.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="CFOs Turn On Sustainability Reporting and ESG Metrics in Enterprise Software Suites" src="./media_165b223f05b5705112f166ca7c1546bbdc6a85d00.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="cfos-turn-on-sustainability-reporting-and-esg-metrics-in-enterprise-software-suites">CFOs Turn On Sustainability Reporting and ESG Metrics in Enterprise Software Suites</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sustainability-management-by-sap-enabling-tomorrow-starts-today">Sustainability Management by SAP: Enabling Tomorrow Starts Today</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/06/sapphire-now-sustainability-management-by-sap">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><em>Ubi concordia, ibi victoria.</em> Where there is harmony, there is victory. This Latin proverb is particularly relevant to my vision for holistic steering and reporting.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Connecting financial and non-financial metrics is key to comprehensively analyzing all dimensions of a company’s performance and working toward their integration and harmonization. This in turn provides the foundation for better balanced management decisions and drives business success while creating a positive impact on people and the planet.</p>
  <p>In the 15th century, <a href="https://www.npr.org/sections/money/2012/10/04/162296423/the-accountant-who-changed-the-world">Luca Pacioli</a>, an Italian monk, musician, and mathematician, discovered the concept of double-entry bookkeeping, which became the basis of modern accounting. However, over 500 years later, accounting could use an addendum. Today, tracking and reporting must include economic performance along with societal and environmental performance. Moving beyond traditional balance sheets and profit and loss statements provides meaningful and holistic insight into the total value creation of a business entity.</p>
  <p>These demands make sustainability a CFO imperative. Globally, business leaders are recognizing that a separate sustainability strategy will no longer suffice. Instead, companies must ensure their entire business strategy is sustainable. Companies that embed sustainability into core business processes consistently <a href="https://www.mckinsey.com/~/media/McKinsey/Business%20Functions/Sustainability/Our%20Insights/Profits%20with%20purpose/Profits%20with%20Purpose.ashx">outperform</a> their competitors and will only continue to do so in the future. Measuring business sustainability enables companies to gain higher profits which result from greater cost efficiency and revenue growth by addressing economic, social, and environmental considerations in a holistic, integrated manner.</p>
  <p>The business community sees value in considering <a href="https://insights.sap.com/redefine-success-sustainability-reporting/">environmental, social, and governance (ESG)</a> issues in strategic and operational decision making, but it still needs to execute on this vision. The journey has just begun.</p>
  <p>Digital technologies support and accelerate this journey by playing a fundamental role in delivering the visibility and velocity required to inform and drive better business decisions through embedded, validated, real-time data.</p>
  <p><strong>Visibility</strong> into relevant metrics across every line of business equips companies with the insights required to comply with new regulations, safeguard their license to operate, meet increasing stakeholder expectations, cut costs, and recognize opportunities for innovation and business transformation.</p>
  <p>The deployment of digital technology solutions also enables the <strong>velocity</strong> required to execute large-scale transformations, based on holistic steering and reporting. Technology’s ability to quickly and effectively measure and value green and social dimensions will help accelerate the shift towards an inclusive, low-carbon, and circular economy.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="the-quest-to-redefine-business-success-through-sustainability">The Quest to Redefine Business Success Through Sustainability</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://insights.sap.com/redefine-success-sustainability-reporting/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Moving forward, a digital transformation architecture and road map that enables sustainability efforts will become fundamental to every company’s business strategy.</p>
  <p>To help our customers power organization-wide sustainability practices in reporting, SAP recently announced a portfolio of new sustainability-specific products, including the <a href="/2021/06/sapphire-now-sustainability-management-by-sap">SAP Sustainability Control Tower</a> solution, which will enable companies to report against metrics, such as the <a href="https://www.weforum.org/reports/measuring-stakeholder-capitalism-towards-common-metrics-and-consistent-reporting-of-sustainable-value-creation">Stakeholder Capitalism Metrics</a>, supported by World Economic Forum (WEF) Metrics, <a href="https://www.value-balancing.com/en/press/new-sustainability-measurement-methodology-developed-by-the-value-balancing-alliance-successfully-tested-for-the-first-time-2.html">Value Balancing Alliance</a>, and more. This solution offers a greater degree of granularity in reporting and a higher level of transparency around ESG performance. End-to-end visibility and real-time data provide business leaders with insights to identify levers and options for driving corrective and enhanced action that take financial, social, and environmental valuation into account.</p>
  <p>At SAP, we have been measuring our progress holistically and connecting financial and non-financial data since 2012, when we merged our sustainability and annual reports into an integrated report. However, full visibility into the entire value chain and the capability to scale across business networks requires an actionable and <a href="https://insights.sap.com/redefine-success-sustainability-reporting/">standardized methodology</a>.</p>
  <p>In 2019, this recognition inspired SAP to become a <a href="/2019/08/value-balancing-alliance-sap-founding-member">founding member of the Value Balancing Alliance</a> (VBA) and contribute our experience, along with 20 other like-minded, multinational companies, to shape a “new accounting” system. The alliance aims to develop a standard for measuring, monetizing, and comparing the value of contributions made by businesses to the economy, society, and the environment. Assigning a monetary value or a “social cost” to various categories creates a comparable, inclusive data set that can guide business leaders as they make strategic decisions to impact long-term sustainable change.</p>
  <p>The first pilot program took place last year and included 11 companies across seven industries. At SAP we <a href="https://www.sap.com/integrated-reports/2020/en/connectivity/approach.html">focused on our complete operations and supply chain</a>, testing specific indicators, and translating non-financial metrics into comparable financial terms. Based on SAP’s 2019 data, we found the negative impact of our GHG emissions was monetized at €182 million, and a positive impact from our global employee training programs was valued at €1.3 billion. Such insights allow us to compare the potential costs and benefits of climate initiatives and training programs. The results of the pilot program provide evidence that the VBA can help companies optimize their value chains, achieve better business outcomes, and enable information sharing that supports large scale systemic change across regions and industries.</p>
  <p>As a global community, we have reached a tipping point. The successful businesses of tomorrow — those equipped to navigate the world’s most pressing challenges — will consider financial and non-financial metrics before making critical business decisions. Through the power of digital technologies, we can ensure the visibility and velocity required to effectively expand the scope of corporate reporting and execute sustainable business steering at scale. With an updated approach to holistic steering and reporting, one that considers ESG metrics alongside traditional financial metrics, business, society, and the planet can all emerge victorious.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Luka Mucic is chief financial officer and a member of the Executive Board of SAP SE.</em><br><em><a href="https://impactalpha.com/unlock-the-business-value-of-esg-metrics-with-digital-solutions/">This article first appeared in ImpactAlpha</a>.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/chasing-zero</category>
            <category>news-tag/economics</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Allbirds’ Runaway Success Leaves a Small Carbon Footprint]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/allbirds-carbon-footprint</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/allbirds-carbon-footprint</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[By avoiding shortcuts and sticking to its values, Allbirds' success story shows that what’s good for the planet is also good for business.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_182517a31877b68b9a4412352f8b8f5624ac8815e.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_182517a31877b68b9a4412352f8b8f5624ac8815e.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_182517a31877b68b9a4412352f8b8f5624ac8815e.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Allbirds’ Runaway Success Leaves a Small Carbon Footprint" src="./media_182517a31877b68b9a4412352f8b8f5624ac8815e.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="allbirds-runaway-success-leaves-a-small-carbon-footprint">Allbirds’ Runaway Success Leaves a Small Carbon Footprint</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="is-your-company-chasing-zero">Is your company Chasing Zero?</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/purpose-and-sustainability.html#chasing-zero">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>In a highly competitive and crowded category such as sportswear, it is extremely hard for any new player to break in. Understanding new market needs and creating differentiation in response to these needs requires fresh insights and viewpoints.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>From its earliest days as a pilot project on Kickstarter, <a href="https://www.allbirds.com/">Allbirds Inc.</a> positioned itself as a challenger brand by identifying sustainability as the core differentiator. This would help it appeal to an emerging class of consumers who were increasingly environmentally, economically, and socially conscious.</p>
  <p>But putting this differentiation into practice is easier said than done. It required a revolutionary approach in the entire shoe-making value chain. This could help ensure a superior product that delivered on sought-after attributes such as quality, comfort, fit, reliability, and price, yet made fully with eco-friendly practices.</p>
  <p>Allbirds co-founders and co-CEOs Tim Brown and Joey Zwillinger both like to say, “Mother nature made us do it.” Brown was an all-star athlete and footballer from New Zealand that was familiar with the unique qualities of merino wool. Zwillinger was an engineer and an expert in renewables – both unlikely entrepreneurs but with a clear vision.</p>
  <p>Less than a year after officially launching, Allbirds became a certified B Corporation, dedicated from its inception to making the most sustainable footwear possible while actively working to minimize its environmental impact. The California-based company crafts running shoes, and now even apparel and accessories, using planet-friendly natural materials such as merino wool and eucalyptus tree fibers ­– forsaking the synthetic materials commonly used in competing products.</p>
  <p>Innovating a quality running shoe that is comfortable to wear and treads lightly on the planet has made Allbirds something of a runaway success. In its first two years, the company sold more than one million pairs of its green sneakers and expanded its e-commerce operations into brick-and-mortar stores.</p>
  <p>Today, several factories feed into Allbirds’ nine distribution centers around the world, which supply its 25 physical retail stores, with the potential to reach 2.5 billion customers through digital commerce. To ensure that consumers can gain full visibility into the environmental impact across the supply chain, the company labels every product it makes with its individual carbon footprint, holding themselves accountable to their mantra to “create better things in a better way.”</p>
  <p>This kind of rapid success requires a strategic and thoughtful approach to managing the complexity of building a socially responsible global supply value chain. Allbirds confronts the challenge head on by developing meaningful, multi-year relationships with its suppliers to ensure ethical and humane manufacturing practices and demanding full transparency into its partners’ supply chains. This safeguards social responsibility across sourcing and procurement.</p>
  <p>With a long-term outlook from the beginning, Allbirds’ founders made the decision early on to invest in a single software platform. Allbirds wanted to invest in an enterprise resource planning (ERP) system that could help the company manage the entirety of its business in the present and continue to do so as it evolved and grew, all while keeping its commitment to sustainability at the forefront.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-s4hana-powering-industry-transformation">SAP S/4HANA: Powering industry transformation</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/s4hana-erp.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“We were really deliberate in making technology investments that would scale with our business,” said Zwillinger. “We needed to recognize how customers want to be served and offer an immersive cross-channel experience on mobile, Web, and in the store. To do this, we needed robust and connected real-time digital technologies, giving us visibility into our inventory. We also needed to personalize that experience for our customers, whether it’s online, pick-up in store, or ship-from-store, as well as be able to merchandize our products in a personalized way on our digital platforms.”</p>
  <p>Meeting these wide-ranging needs and more, Allbirds adopted <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/s4hana-erp.html">SAP S/4HANA</a> as the foundational business infrastructure to help underpin its fast-growing business, track its inventory in real time, and trim waste.</p>
  <p>In addition to supporting sales growth, managing marketing, and engaging customers through social media, Allbirds relies on SAP solutions to help it achieve specific business goals. This includes creating one financial system of record for all transactions throughout its global operations and embracing new cloud technologies to help it become a more diverse, capable, and responsible global employer.</p>
  <p>And with connected technologies across its operations, Allbirds can calculate and monitor its carbon footprint from design and delivery to supporting ongoing innovation to deliver new products and services that delight customers everywhere.</p>
  <p>By avoiding shortcuts and sticking to its values, Allbirds’ success story shows that what’s good for the planet is also good for business.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>To learn more about how Allbirds created a niche in the sportswear category by focusing on sustainability, <a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2021/06/1eeb6453-e87d-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">watch the interview</a> between Zwillinger and Julia White, SAP Chief Marketing and Solutions Officer, or read this <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/06/5818f54c-e87d-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">business transformation study</a>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Vivek Bapat is part of Purpose and Sustainability Marketing at SAP.</em><br><em><a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2021/06/29/allbirds-runaway-success-leaves-a-small-carbon-footprint/?sh=1d968f6f6e47">This story originally appeared on SAP BrandVoice on Forbes</a>.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/chasing-zero</category>
            <category>industry/consumer-goods-cpg</category>
            <category>news-tag/economics</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Helping Consumers, Retailers, and the Environment]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2021/07/sap-intelligent-returns-management-consumers-retailers-environment</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2021/07/sap-intelligent-returns-management-consumers-retailers-environment</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The new SAP Intelligent Returns Management solution closes the gap between retailers’ front and back offices. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1baefa14c9e60892428339451246c056fcc953f5f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1baefa14c9e60892428339451246c056fcc953f5f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1baefa14c9e60892428339451246c056fcc953f5f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Helping Consumers, Retailers, and the Environment" src="./media_1baefa14c9e60892428339451246c056fcc953f5f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="helping-consumers-retailers-and-the-environment">Helping Consumers, Retailers, and the Environment</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="give-shoppers-and-consumers-the-products-and-personalized-shopping-experiences-they-want-with-sap">Give shoppers and consumers the products and personalized shopping experiences they want with SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/retail.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Our customers face new market conditions, competition and challenges every day, so they rely on us to deliver the technology and solutions to help them survive and thrive in this dynamic and increasingly digital environment. SAP’s deep industry domain knowledge has enabled us to deliver the best and most innovative business process support for our customers for almost 50 years.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>By continuously evolving our enterprise resource planning (ERP) solutions, we are helping our customers modernize business processes and helping them adjust to a new IT reality at the same time. As <a href="/author/thomassaueressig">I’ve said before</a>, this reality combines flexibility, agility, and choice for our customers: Flexibility through a modular yet integrated approach to enterprise software, agility through business processes that can be adapted as needed, and choice for customers to operate their systems on the infrastructure of their choice. And we can certainly add the need for collaborative, networked, and sustainable solutions here.</p>
  <p>One of my favorite examples of how SAP is helping customers adapt and modernize their business processes comes from the retail sector and relates to the impact of the <a href="/covid-19">COVID-19</a> pandemic. E-commerce has surged during the pandemic as consumers faced lockdowns and sought the relative safety of online shopping. This surge in e-commerce has had dramatic implications for traditional retailers that have had to pivot quickly from primarily in-store sales to online platforms but have also had to deal with much higher levels of returns.</p>
  <p>Consumers are more likely to return something when bought online compared to offline purchases. This is particularly true in fashion retail because there is a much higher probability that a particular size doesn’t fit or the color is not quite what the consumer was expecting. Online customers also often bracket-purchase — ordering several similar items or sizes to ensure that one is the right fit and return the others.</p>
  <p>This represents a significant problem for traditional retailers that were not used to dealing with such high levels of returns and that, in the past, often outsourced the handling of returns. Returns — or reverse logistics, as the process is sometimes called — is a costly and time-consuming part of the daily life of the supply chain.</p>
  <p>Companies need to make decisions on where to return the stock, how to handle the stock when returned, and whether the customer will receive a refund or a replacement. Typically, these operations were optimized for time in order to keep customers happy, even if this meant destroying returned goods.</p>
  <p>Retailers know that the return experience can break or build customer loyalty and trust, and that’s why they aim to process returns and provide refunds to customers as quickly as possible. But destroying — and even storing — returned items is potentially bad for the environment and represents a monetary loss. According to UK’s online retail association, <a href="https://www.imrg.org/uploads/media/default/0001/09/aee8f77eb4d47ccae59293c2518ea67641e5a89d.pdf?st">69% of shoppers confirm that the quality of the returns service strongly influences the retailers where they will shop</a>.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="solve-complex-business-challenges-with-greater-ease-and-speed-using-ai-solutions-from-sap">Solve complex business challenges with greater ease and speed using AI solutions from SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Recognizing these problems, SAP has developed an innovative solution that we call <strong>SAP Intelligent Returns Management</strong>, a returns optimization solution that guides products from customers’ hands to the final dispositioning steps, maximizing both the customer experience and company margins. It uses routing and dispositioning decisions driven by artificial intelligence (AI) to maximize our customers’ sales and profits.</p>
  <p>SAP Intelligent Returns Management benefits consumers, retailers, and other stakeholders — and it helps customers operate more sustainably. Consumers benefit because we help our customers make the returns process easy, and that delivers the intended consumer experience. Our retail customers know that brand loyalty is fragile and can be lost quickly if a returns process is anything but straightforward and smooth. They need to optimize their return process to be efficient and ensure a great customer experience. When goods arrive at their return centers, retailers want to be able to make fast decisions about what to do with them: Should they dispose of the goods? Should they do a quality check and re-certify them for sale, or send them to an agent such as outlet or reseller?</p>
  <p>Our solution intelligently recommends return options for consumers optimizing for both the customer experience and the retailer and recommends disposition decisions for warehouse teams to limit value leakage. But it also provides business leaders with newfound visibility into the end-to-end returns process, enabling them to make data-based decisions.</p>
  <p>Particularly, retailers can use the embedded analytics to understand what is selling and what is not. Does a particular item always come back because it does not meet expectations in terms of size or look? Is a particular color not selling or is a style out of fashion? Whatever the reason, they can inform the design team and stem a problem at the source by not offering products that do not meet expectations, and thereby be more sustainable.</p>
  <p>SAP has offered a returns solution in the past, but it was a back-end, logistics solution. Now, with SAP Intelligent Returns Management sitting at the intersection of cloud ERP and SAP’s industry cloud, we have closed the gap between front office and back office. That’s the biggest advantage our solutions bring to fashion retailers and the like.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Thomas Saueressig is a member of the Executive Board of SAP SE for SAP Product Engineering.</em><br><em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/pulse/helping-consumers-retailers-environment-thomas-saueressig/">This story was originally published on LinkedIn</a>.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/blog/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/blog/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/blog/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/blog/article-read-more</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/executive-blog</category>
            <category>news-tag/chasing-zero</category>
            <category>industry/consumer-goods-cpg</category>
            <category>news-tag/economics</category>
            <category>news-tag/enterprise-resource-planning</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
            <category>product/sap-intelligent-returns-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Decarbonization Depends on the Data]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/06/decarbonization-depends-on-data</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/06/decarbonization-depends-on-data</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn how digitalization, data transparency, and collaborative action are key to meeting decarbonization targets in the automotive industry.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10d619ba9f35d98eba2a2b782fbc8fb3ca9f169de.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10d619ba9f35d98eba2a2b782fbc8fb3ca9f169de.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_10d619ba9f35d98eba2a2b782fbc8fb3ca9f169de.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Decarbonization Depends on the Data" src="./media_10d619ba9f35d98eba2a2b782fbc8fb3ca9f169de.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="decarbonization-depends-on-the-data">Decarbonization Depends on the Data</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>The race to zero carbon emissions among car manufacturers <a href="http://www.automobilsport.com/cars-tuning--37,222545,Way-to-Zero-Volkswagen-presents-roadmap-for-climate-neutral-mobility,news.htm">is in full swing</a>. Earlier this month, the world’s largest producer, Volkswagen Group (VW), indicated it would <a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/volkswagen-electric-emissions/insight-how-low-can-you-go-volkswagen-throws-down-the-emissions-gauntlet-idUSL1N2ML25I">support more ambitious CO2 emissions targets</a>, catching European rivals off guard and putting them under pressure to follow suit.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>But the race to “net zero” for the automobile industry is still in the first lap, and the route promises to be long and arduous. Greenhouse gas emissions from the industry account for more than 9% of global emissions – equaling those of the entire European Union. To achieve their individual sustainability targets, companies are dependent on each other for reliable and verifiable data.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="is-your-company-chasing-zero-learn-more">Is your company Chasing Zero? Learn more.</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="http://sap.com/ChasingZero">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="decarbonization-is-all-about-the-data">Decarbonization Is All About the Data</h2>
  <p>Becoming carbon neutral requires managing the carbon footprint of individual products in the supply chain, and to achieve this companies need transparency into the carbon footprints of their upstream suppliers – referred to as <a href="https://ghgprotocol.org/sites/default/files/standards_supporting/FAQ.pdf">scope 3 emissions</a>. The problem is that only 21% of business executives are satisfied with the quality of their environmental data, <a href="/2021/04/sustainability-study-from-sap-actions-challenges">according to a global research study from SAP</a>.</p>
  <p>But more accurate carbon footprint data is on the way. “Until now, companies have been using averages to calculate carbon footprint at a product level because there’s been a lack of accurate, granular emissions data and no consistent methodology,” said John Revess, director Net Zero Transformation at the World Business Council for Sustainable Development (WBCSD). “To remain a part of global supply chains, it will be necessary for companies to accurately calculate the carbon footprint of their products based on measured values,” predicted Revess. As a member of WBCSD, SAP and other companies are defining a <a href="https://www.wbcsd.org/Programs/Climate-and-Energy/Climate/SOS-1.5/Resources/Value-Chain-Carbon-Transparency-Pathfinder-Enabling-decarbonization-through-Scope-3-emissions-transparency">Value Chain Carbon Transparency Pathfinder</a> for the exchange of carbon emissions data.</p>
  <p>“To meet our decarbonization goals, we depend on credible data from our suppliers on the carbon footprints of the components we build our vehicles with,” said Ralf Pfitzner, global head of Sustainability at Volkswagen, at the <a href="https://events.sap.com/sap-sustainability-summit/en/home">SAP Sustainability Summit</a>.</p>
  <p>The two-day online meeting focused on how companies are applying new technologies to reduce their environmental footprint and manage limited resources. “We decided to join SAP in the co-innovation of a digital carbon tracking tool and database, and this is really exciting because there is obviously a demand,” said Pfitzner.</p>
  <p>Volkswagen and SAP are working together toward decarbonization in other ways. In 2020, their CEOs Herbert Diess and Christian Klein joined the <a href="https://www.volkswagenag.com/en/news/2021/03/European-CEO-Alliance-advocates-for-ambitious-climate-strategy.html#:~:text=The%20CEO%20Alliance%20considers%20itself,chain%20and%20rapid%20build%2Dup">CEO Alliance for Europe’s Recovery, Reform, and Resilience</a>. The Alliance’s 10 European business leaders have committed 100 billion to decarbonizing their companies and products and are calling for far-reaching climate protection measures.</p>
  <h2 id="massive-investments-necessary-in-electrification-and-digitalization">Massive Investments Necessary in Electrification and Digitalization</h2>
  <p>VW is <a href="https://www.volkswagen-newsroom.com/en/press-releases/volkswagen-group-raises-investments-in-future-technologies-to-eur-73-billion-6607">investing a hefty €73 billion</a> to help put its decarbonization challenges in the rear-view mirror. The underlying reasons for <a href="/2021/04/sustainability-study-from-sap-actions-challenges">companies’ investments in environmental issues</a> varies, spanning industry regulations (29%) to society’s approval of their organization (27%) and strengthening company reputation (26%). Uncertainty as to how to embed sustainability into business processes and IT systems is seen as the greatest barrier to implementing plans for action, <a href="/2021/04/sustainability-study-from-sap-actions-challenges">one study concludes</a>.</p>
  <p>Despite the challenges, VW’s Pfitzner is optimistic about achieving the company’s decarbonization targets. VW’s head of sustainability expects digitalization to play a major role in this transformation. “Beyond green electricity, there are plenty of opportunities where digitalization will help us reduce our carbon footprint, for example by hooking the manufacturing data into the cloud and having more efficient programming of robots,” he said.</p>
  <p>Pfitzner reiterated <a href="https://www.volkswagenag.com/en/news/stories/2019/12/what-volkswagen-is-doing-for-the-environment.html">VW’s 2050 goal of carbon neutrality</a> along the entire lifecycle of its cars, emphasizing the need for intermediate milestones. “The coming decades will be essential for the transformation of transport and the car industry. By 2030, we intend to reduce the lifecycle carbon footprint of our passenger car portfolio by 30% compared to 2018,” said Pfitzner.</p>
  <h2 id="no-carbon-neutrality-in-isolation">No Carbon Neutrality in Isolation</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sustainability-actions-still-challenging-to-implement-according-to-new-study-from-sap">Sustainability Actions Still Challenging to Implement, According to New Study from SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/04/sustainability-study-from-sap-actions-challenges">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Although nearly two-thirds of the global economy is covered by net zero targets, achieving them will require systems thinking and collaborative action among businesses of a type and scale that has never been done before, <a href="https://www2.deloitte.com/uk/en/pages/press-releases/articles/deloitte-announces-senior-partner-appointments-in-climate-change-and-transport.html">said Hannah Routh</a>, partner, Deloitte UK. “The proof will be in the implementation,” she predicted.</p>
  <p>“No business or country can become net zero in isolation,” said Routh. “Whether you are looking at energy supply, transportation, infrastructure, government, or communities, they all need to act in a coordinated way.”</p>
  <p>One of the biggest challenges for companies, says Routh, is embedding climate transformation into their business strategies and decision-making processes. This requires data transparency, she emphasizes, noting that there is no shortage of data, but the quality and usability of the data must be ensured.</p>
  <p>Nicolas Peter, BMW’s chief financial officer, agrees. “Digitalization helps in a significant way to increase data quality, and, from an auditor’s perspective, data quality is key in order to perform his responsibility in the audit process,” he said at SAP’s Sustainability Summit. Peter left no doubts that BMW is counting on new technologies to help it <a href="https://www.wemeanbusinesscoalition.org/blog/bmw-joins-growing-list-of-automakers-committed-to-bold-climate-action/">achieve its climate targets</a>: “The trend to sustainability has to be accompanied by digitalization. There is no alternative,” said Peter.</p>
  <h2 id="digitalization-supports-decarbonization">Digitalization Supports Decarbonization</h2>
  <p>“CEOs need transparency into their supply chains,” said Thomas Saueressig, head of Product Engineering and member of the Executive Board of SAP SE. “Through its strategic initiative <a href="https://community.sap.com/topics/sustainability/climate21">Climate 21</a>, SAP is launching new solutions that help customers reduce their emissions and manage their carbon footprint.”</p>
  <p>A new integrated set of solutions announced at the SAP Sustainability Summit includes SAP Product Footprint Management, which treats greenhouse gases like a ‘currency’ in the value chain. “Our sustainability management solutions enable companies not only to optimize their production facilities according to top line and bottom line, but also according to greenhouse gas emissions,” said Saueressig. As part of several joint sustainability initiatives with Accenture, <a href="/2021/04/sap-and-accenture-sustainability-better-business">SAP and Accenture are working</a> to develop new SAP solutions that address sustainability and enhance existing core technologies.</p>
  <h2 id="the-need-for-speed">The Need for Speed</h2>
  <p>Setting data quality issues aside, the most important factor for transforming businesses to net-zero is speed, said Deloitte’s Routh. “I think the world can master this, but my concern is whether it can do it quickly enough. The businesses that are going to succeed are the ones that understand and embrace the urgency.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/automotive</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-emissions</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-footprint</category>
            <category>news-tag/chasing-zero</category>
            <category>news-tag/climate-21</category>
            <category>news-tag/climate-change</category>
            <category>news-tag/economics</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Launches Chasing Zero]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/05/chasing-zero-launch</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/05/chasing-zero-launch</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP's new Chasing Zero series features executive thought leadership and unique insights into sustainability-related transformation.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_113f2308f10670c1d9eb45f0e2ab7e83fb6637d2f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_113f2308f10670c1d9eb45f0e2ab7e83fb6637d2f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_113f2308f10670c1d9eb45f0e2ab7e83fb6637d2f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Launches Chasing Zero" src="./media_113f2308f10670c1d9eb45f0e2ab7e83fb6637d2f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-launches-chasing-zero">SAP Launches Chasing Zero</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>We live in an industrial age linear model of “take, make, waste,” in which more than <a href="https://www.ellenmacarthurfoundation.org/">91%</a> of raw materials, including fossil fuels, are not reusable and are therefore wasted.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>What’s worse is that this model also contributes to more than two-thirds of global greenhouse emissions, creating a vicious cycle of economic, social, and environmental inequality.</p>
  <p>If we are to create a sustainable future, we must effect massive change.</p>
  <p>Imagine a future that looks greener, cleaner, and more equal than the world we live in today. A world of zero emissions, zero waste, and zero inequality.</p>
  <p>At SAP, we dare to not just dream about this aspiration, but to power the technology and innovation that is required to activate this bold vision into reality. Technology that can enable businesses to fundamentally rethink how they manage their carbon footprints, design new business processes that create opportunity rather than generate waste, and provide the transparency and regulatory compliance to hold ourselves accountable to the highest standards of economic, social, and environmental governance.</p>
  <p>Inspired by the notion that sustainable businesses can effectively lead the way to this ambition, we are launching a new series, <strong>Chasing Zero</strong>.</p>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1dc3d958ff2abef450ff9891b7ad8ebf38aeff5c5.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1dc3d958ff2abef450ff9891b7ad8ebf38aeff5c5.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1dc3d958ff2abef450ff9891b7ad8ebf38aeff5c5.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Chasing Zero by SAP" src="./media_1dc3d958ff2abef450ff9891b7ad8ebf38aeff5c5.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://youtu.be/aGf1DyDA9h0">Chasing Zero by SAP</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Chasing Zero will feature executive thought leadership and provide unique points of view and insights into sustainability-related transformation from some of the most forward-thinking companies in the world. It will highlight best practices from the global SAP ecosystem of leading thinkers and academics, as well as customers and partners.</p>
  <p>To learn more, visit <a href="http://sap.com/ChasingZero">sap.com/ChasingZero</a>. There you can fill out a submission form to share how your company is also chasing Zero.</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Watch the <a href="https://youtu.be/aGf1DyDA9h0">anthem video about the Chasing Zero series</a>.</li>
    <li>Engage in the conversation by following #ChasingZero and #SAP4Good.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>Together, let’s start “chasing zero” to enable a better tomorrow.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Vivek Bapat is senior vice president of Purpose and Sustainability Marketing at SAP</em>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/chasing-zero</category>
            <category>news-tag/economics</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Restoring Our Earth: Healthy Planet, Healthy People]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/earth-day-2021-healthy-planet-people</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/earth-day-2021-healthy-planet-people</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[On Earth Day 2021, SAP Chief Sustainability Officer Daniel Schmid discusses taking action for a more just, healthy, prosperous life for all.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ad06d3f8794643fa0fa33c96e5afe476df36f629.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ad06d3f8794643fa0fa33c96e5afe476df36f629.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1ad06d3f8794643fa0fa33c96e5afe476df36f629.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Restoring Our Earth: Healthy Planet, Healthy People" src="./media_1ad06d3f8794643fa0fa33c96e5afe476df36f629.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="restoring-our-earth-healthy-planet-healthy-people">Restoring Our Earth: Healthy Planet, Healthy People</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="catch-up-on-the-virtual-sap-sustainability-summit">Catch up on the virtual SAP Sustainability Summit</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://events.sap.com/sap-sustainability-summit/en/home">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>One year after the 50th anniversary of Earth Day in 2020, we have come a long way: <a href="https://news.un.org/en/story/2020/12/1078612">The race to zero is on</a>. Countries representing more than 65% of global carbon dioxide emissions and more than 70% of the world economy, have made ambitious commitments to carbon neutrality.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The European Union, Japan and the Republic of Korea, together with more than 110 other countries, have pledged carbon neutrality by 2050; China stated it will become carbon neutral before 2060. The U.S. has rejoined the Paris Agreement. On a corporate level, more than 480 companies, including SAP, have meanwhile signed the <a href="https://www.unglobalcompact.org/take-action/events/climate-action-summit-2019/business-ambition/business-leaders-taking-action">Business Ambition for 1.5°C commitment</a>, setting a net-zero target in line with a 1.5°C future.</p>
  <p>Yet, the urgency and importance to act are as high as ever. The United Nations Environment Program (UNEP) <a href="https://www.unep.org/emissions-gap-report-2020">Emissions Gap Report 2020</a> made it very clear: despite a dip in greenhouse gas emissions from the <a href="/covid-19">COVID-19</a> economic slowdown, the world is still heading for a catastrophic temperature rise above 3°C this century. Hope continues to lie in a green pandemic recovery, which UNEP believes could cut 25% off the greenhouse emissions expected in 2030.</p>
  <p>As more than 1 billion people in over 192 countries participate in <a href="https://www.earthday.org/press-release/climate-action-takes-center-stage-at-global-leaders-summit-and-during-worldwide-parallel-earth-day-events/">Earth Day activities</a> today, <a href="https://www.whitehouse.gov/briefing-room/statements-releases/2021/03/26/president-biden-invites-40-world-leaders-to-leaders-summit-on-climate/">President Biden has invited 40 world leaders to a Leaders Summit on Climate</a>. It is a major milestone on the road to the UN Climate Change Conference 2021 (<a href="https://ukcop26.org/">COP26</a>) in November, where world leaders will report back on progress since the 2015 Paris Agreement and are expected to come together to drive ambitious climate outcomes forward.</p>
  <p>It has been rightfully emphasized how important it is for our collective well-being to address the climate crisis. During the past year, however, evidence has been increasing how interrelated taking care of the environment is with taking care of ourselves.</p>
  <p>Earlier this month, the UNEP announced “<a href="https://www.unep.org/news-and-stories/story/one-health-approach-critical-tackle-health-inequality-and-emerging-diseases">One Health</a>,” a cross-cutting approach that carries out programs, policies, legislation, and research uniting human, animal, and environmental health.</p>
  <p>Julian Blanc, a UNEP wildlife expert sees a clear interdependency: “Many zoonoses that have become pandemics have been linked to environmental factors like deforestation and are exacerbated by climate change. We will not succeed in securing human health while we continue to ignore environmental health.”</p>
  <p>The close link between climate change and health is also in spotlight at the <a href="https://www.who.int/news-room/events/detail/2021/11/06/default-calendar/2021-global-conference-on-health-and-climate-change">2021 Global Conference on Health &#x26; Climate Change</a> convening at the margin of COP26. According to the World Health Organization (WHO), which is co-organizing the event, air pollution alone costs an estimated US$ 5.11 trillion in welfare losses globally each year and causes one out of eight deaths globally. A new study by the Harvard University published in <a href="https://www.seas.harvard.edu/news/2021/02/deaths-fossil-fuel-emissions-higher-previously-thought">Environmental Research</a> beginning of February 2021, increases estimates of the numbers killed by air pollution even to one out of five.</p>
  <p>Shouldn’t this reframe everything? It makes climate change seem a lot less abstract and distant; rather an immediate and direct threat to our health and that of our children — a massive wake-up call!</p>
  <p>So as we mark Earth Day 2021 with the theme “Restore our Earth,” let’s recognize that for us to be healthy people, we need a healthy planet. This means taking steps to act now and reshape our economy to be more restorative, low-carbon, circular, <em>and</em> inclusive.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-about-saps-commitment-to-making-sustainability-profitable-and-profitability-sustainable">Learn about SAP's commitment to making sustainability profitable and profitability sustainable</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/purpose-and-sustainability.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>At SAP, our opportunity to create the biggest positive environmental, social, and economic impact within the planetary boundaries is to <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/sustainability.html#climate-action">provide digital solutions and services that enable our more than 400,000 customers to become more sustainable</a>. With nearly 50 years of experience in resource optimization, we focus on those areas in which we can most effectively contribute: solutions for holistic steering and reporting, <a href="https://insights.sap.com/what-is-circular-economy/">a circular economy</a>, climate action, and socially responsible value chains.</p>
  <p>Acknowledging that <a href="https://insights.sap.com/government-business-civil-society-fast-track-circularity/">collaboration is key</a>, we partner and co-innovate with customers, governments, and non-governmental organizations (NGOs) around the world to advocate for practical problem solving.</p>
  <p>At the upcoming <a href="https://events.sap.com/sap-sustainability-summit/en/home">SAP Sustainability Summit from April 28-29</a>, we will announce new partnerships and explore opportunities, proven practices, and future solutions with our customers and broader ecosystem, as well as see how traditional business decision making is being transformed with sustainability indicators integrated. In the spirit of Earth Days’ theme “Restore our Earth,” we will restore 100sqm of diverse forest for every summit attendee.</p>
  <p>At the same time, we remain committed to lead by example in our own sustainable business operations and practices. In March, when we released our <a href="http://www.sapintegratedreport.com">Integrated Report 2020</a>, we announced our objective to become <a href="/2021/03/sap-carbon-neutrality-goal-2023">carbon-neutral in our own operations by 2023 – two years earlier than previously envisaged</a>. By accelerating toward carbon-neutral operations, SAP is taking the lead in considering the impact of COVID-19 on carbon emissions. The pandemic has taught businesses how to work with customers and colleagues effectively in a virtual setting. We anticipate the development toward more remote work and less business travel to continue and are adjusting our carbon neutrality target to uphold our ambition level.</p>
  <p>The pandemic has changed the world of work in ways we could not have imagined. While some see a silver lining in the climate impacts, we cannot deny the toll it continues to take on people, our employees. Looking at these impacts as part of our holistic steering and reporting, it was clear that the <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/purpose-and-sustainability/mental-health.html">care and well-being of our people</a> required even stronger focus in 2021 with a broad portfolio of benefits and offerings help our people maintain balance and thrive mental, emotional, physical, and social health. For example, we are implementing a <a href="/2021/03/mental-health-day-sap-employees">Mental Health Day</a>, a company-sponsored global holiday for all employees, scheduled for April 27 next week. Work will grind to a halt on that day, giving everyone time off to do something for themselves and their families, thereby offering employees a chance to recharge.</p>
  <p>Let’s take Earth Day 2021 as both a reminder and inspiration of what’s at stake and how important it is that we join forces to create a more just, healthy, and prosperous life for all people, respecting the boundaries of our one planet.</p>
  <p>At SAP, we are as committed as ever to live up to <a href="http://www.sap.com/sustainability">our purpose to help the world run better and improve people’s lives with sustainability at its core</a>. I invite everyone to join us on this journey.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>null</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Daniel Schmid is chief sustainability officer of SAP SE.</em><br><em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/pulse/restoring-our-earth-healthy-planet-people-daniel-schmid/">This piece was also published on LinkedIn</a>.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/chasing-zero</category>
            <category>non-sap-event/earth-day</category>
            <category>news-tag/economics</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reimagining an Industry-Wide Paradigm Shift Toward a Circular Economy]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2021/04/industry-wide-shift-to-a-circular-economy</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2021/04/industry-wide-shift-to-a-circular-economy</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 19 Apr 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Technology can make the shift to a circular economy possible, with innovative business models driving new sources of growth. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b7aaad0a3370f26330596ee7a95766f2be5855bd.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b7aaad0a3370f26330596ee7a95766f2be5855bd.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1b7aaad0a3370f26330596ee7a95766f2be5855bd.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Reimagining an Industry-Wide Paradigm Shift Toward a Circular Economy" src="./media_1b7aaad0a3370f26330596ee7a95766f2be5855bd.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="reimagining-an-industry-wide-paradigm-shift-toward-a-circular-economy">Reimagining an Industry-Wide Paradigm Shift Toward a Circular Economy</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="catch-up-on-the-virtual-sap-sustainability-summit">Catch up on the virtual SAP Sustainability Summit</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://events.sap.com/sap-sustainability-summit/en/home">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>The use of raw materials, including biomass, fossil fuels, metals, and non-metallic minerals, is expected to almost double between 2017 and 2060, increasing <a href="https://read.oecd-ilibrary.org/environment/global-material-resources-outlook-to-2060_9789264307452-en#page21">from 89 gigatons to 167 gigatons</a>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>These staggering numbers stem from the predicted spike in consumption created by the combination of a growing population and higher per capita income. If this consumption spike comes true, there will be massive consequences on our planet.</p>
  <p>Increasingly <a href="https://insights.sap.com/blank-canvas/">socially conscious consumers, employees, and citizens</a> have expressed disapproval over the consumption and production model, which is powered by the economic business practices of the industrial age: “take, make, waste.” Managing the waste aspect of this industrial age approach requires even more resources and energy that in turn contributes to increased emissions and hazardous environmental issues. It’s literally waste creating more waste!</p>
  <p>There is a clear case to shift from linear models to a more sustainable, <a href="https://insights.sap.com/what-is-circular-economy/">circular business model</a> of “resource, recovery, reuse.” According to the Ellen McArthur Foundation, of which SAP is a contributing member, the implementation of circular business practices could reduce up to <a href="https://www.ellenmacarthurfoundation.org/our-work/activities/climate-change">45% of carbon emissions</a> and 90% of <a href="https://insights.sap.com/circularity-creates-value-from-waste/">wasted materials</a>.</p>
  <p>Businesses are listening. Concerned by the potentially negative impacts on their operating costs, brand reputation, and employee retention, many companies are sharing bold aspirations and investments to reduce waste and emissions across their supply chains. These investments are also a generational opportunity to create innovative business models that can drive new sources of growth. Whether the industry is consumer products or agribusiness, technology offers the most effective way to achieve circularity at scale. There are <strong>three main ways that technology can enable circularity</strong>.</p>
  <p>First, a business must start by <strong>eliminating surplus from its own operations</strong> to keep products and materials in use and regenerate natural systems. An inspiring example of this is <a href="/2020/04/indoor-farming-ever-revolutionize-food-chain">&#x26;ever</a>, a Hamburg-based farming company offering vertical farming solutions in cities with limited space. It uses <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">SAP Business Technology Platform</a> to optimize production and manage the needs and capacities of its farms to help ensure minimal waste in its own business processes.</p>
  <p>Second, a company can reduce waste by <strong>gaining detailed visibility into material flows</strong> across its supply chain and that of its immediate trading partners. <a href="https://www.green-token.io/#Industries">GreenToken by SAP</a> offers an effective solution to aid in this process. The solution is supported by blockchain technology and provides a new level of transparency into raw material supply chains. This unique offering goes beyond tracking the final packaged good and provides visibility into the sourcing of all raw materials, including plastics, agriculture, and metals. Innovative solutions like GreenToken make sustainable sourcing and purchasing feasible and accelerates the transition to a circular economy.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="accelerate-business-outcomes-with-sap-business-technology-platform">Accelerate business outcomes with SAP Business Technology Platform</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Third, a business can activate circular practices by <strong>addressing specific problems and opportunities</strong> throughout its industry business network. For example, with the aim of reducing the use of single-use plastics across an entire industry cluster, SAP launched the <a href="/topics/plastics-cloud">Plastics Cloud</a><u>,</u> a new global marketplace for suppliers of recycled plastics and plastic alternatives. Through SAP’s involvement in the World Economic Forum’s <a href="https://www.weforum.org/projects/global-plastic-action-partnership">Global Plastic Action Partnership</a>, we are piloting this innovative technology solution through close collaboration with the Ghanaian Ministry of Environment, Science, Technology, and Innovation. In a country where only <a href="/2020/10/minimize-plastic-waste-in-ghana-domestic-recycling">five percent of plastics are recycled</a>, the Plastics Cloud reimagines the production, use, and reuse of plastics, helping the environment and improving the lives of Ghanaian waste pickers.</p>
  <p>I am excited about the potential SAP has to help businesses run more productively, revolutionize their business models, and deliver growth to realize the vision of a circular economy across industries.</p>
  <p>As business leaders, we must embrace sustainability as a business priority. This requires embedding sustainability across our business processes, using it as selection criteria for our vendors, and inspiring an <a href="https://insights.sap.com/government-business-civil-society-fast-track-circularity/">industry-wide paradigm shift</a>. Together, we can be on the forefront of a future with zero waste, one with a circular economy that thrives not at the expense of people and planet, but in unison.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>Learn more about our efforts to productively manage limited resources by attending the virtual <a href="https://events.sap.com/sap-sustainability-summit/en/home">SAP Sustainability Summit</a>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Julia White is <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/leadership/julia-white.html">chief marketing and solutions officer</a> and a member of the Executive Board of SAP SE.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/blog/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/blog/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/blog/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/blog/article-read-more</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/executive-blog</category>
            <category>news-tag/chasing-zero</category>
            <category>news-tag/circular-economy</category>
            <category>news-tag/economics</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Path to a Low-Carbon Future is Circular]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2021/04/low-carbon-future-circular-path</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2021/04/low-carbon-future-circular-path</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is uniquely positioned to help build a low-carbon future and create the foundation for a circular economy. Learn why.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/executive-blog</category>
            <category>news-tag/chasing-zero</category>
            <category>news-tag/circular-economy</category>
            <category>news-tag/economics</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Carbon Accounting: You Can’t Manage What You Don’t Measure]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2021/03/carbon-accounting-manage-measure</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2021/03/carbon-accounting-manage-measure</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Hear from SAP CEO Christian Klein about turning carbon accounting into an investment strategy that can also drive profit and sustainability.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/executive-blog</category>
            <category>news-tag/chasing-zero</category>
            <category>news-tag/economics</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>