<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-topic/technology/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[German National Team Relies on SAP Technology at the European Championship]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/german-national-team-dfb-sap-technology-european-championship</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/german-national-team-dfb-sap-technology-european-championship</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The coaches and analysts of the German Football Association (DFB) use SAP Sports One to analyze opponents and share tactics with players.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>topic/data-analytics</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>product/sap-sports-one</category>
            <category>industry/sports-entertainment</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Game On: Business Builders Prepares Future Business Leaders for a Data-Driven World]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/business-builders-sap-university-alliances</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/business-builders-sap-university-alliances</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Business Builders, built from a partnership between SAP University Alliances and HEC Montréal, is where education meets real-world needs.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-university-alliances</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bonprix Catwalks Onto Business Intelligence with SAP]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/bonprix-business-intelligence-sap</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/bonprix-business-intelligence-sap</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Leading international fashion company Bonprix has successfully completed implementation of SAP BW/4HANA and SAP Datasphere. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
            <category>product/sap-datasphere</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Four SAP Customers Are Successfully Driving Transformation in Their Businesses]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-sapphire-sap-customers-drive-business-transformation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-sapphire-sap-customers-drive-business-transformation</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In their SAP Sapphire keynote, Scott Russell and Thomas Saueressig talked to four customers about using SAP to deliver high-value results.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c4521f798d991573b94b36fd1f60cfe20d3399cf.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c4521f798d991573b94b36fd1f60cfe20d3399cf.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1c4521f798d991573b94b36fd1f60cfe20d3399cf.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="How Four SAP Customers Are Successfully Driving Transformation in Their Businesses" src="./media_1c4521f798d991573b94b36fd1f60cfe20d3399cf.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="how-four-sap-customers-are-successfully-driving-transformation-in-their-businesses">How Four SAP Customers Are Successfully Driving Transformation in Their Businesses</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>This week at SAP Sapphire, four industry-leading companies joined SAP Executive Board Members Scott Russell and Thomas Saueressig on stage in Orlando to discuss how they are using SAP technology to deliver high-value results for their businesses.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="taking-business-to-the-next-level-in-the-era-of-ai">Taking Business to the Next Level in the Era of AI</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/events/sapphire/news-guide.html">Read the news guide</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Russell told the crowd that customer stories and conversations is what SAP Sapphire is all about, saying that what makes the event special is having “a collective group that comes together, both here in the room and virtually, and being able to understand how SAP can bring out your best.”</p>
  <p>Russell emphasized that the news from SAP Sapphire is a “demonstration of our commitment to continually innovate, to continually strive to bring more creative value to your business.”</p>
  <p>He noted that a perfect example of this is the announcement that <a href="/2024/06/sap-enters-agreement-to-acquire-walkme">SAP has entered into an agreement to acquire WalkMe</a>, a leader in digital adoption platforms. Reflecting on the acquisition, Russell said “We are obsessed not only about great applications and great platforms to deliver value for your business, we also care passionately about the transformation journey to get there.”</p>
  <p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/live/ZZ1yFoALzAs?si=mbPWUzgttHga-_PR">Embed from www.youtube.com</a></p>
  <p>As Chief Revenue Officer, Russell noted that every day 300 million people log on to SAP cloud applications to run their businesses. “And obviously we can never take that for granted,” he said. “You have choice, you have options. We strive to be at our best to help you be at yours. The way we measure success is in your terms, because ultimately [as a] market leader in business AI, we hold ourselves to the highest standards. Why? Because that’s what you expect.”</p>
  <p>A big part of the transformation journey many customers are taking is moving to the cloud with RISE with SAP. “We are super proud of our cloud journey and [that] we are helping you transform your business,” Russell said. “More than 6,000 customers have already moved to RISE with SAP. Of those 6,000 customers in the last 12 months, over 1,000 have already gone live.”</p>
  <h2 id="puretech-scientific-speed-and-scalability-is-key">PureTech Scientific: Speed and Scalability is Key</h2>
  <p>Russell was first joined on stage by Brian Hardee, CIO of <a href="https://www.puretechscientific.com/">PureTech Scientific LLC</a>, a global leader in the production of glycolic acid used in a variety of industries and applications. As a recent carve-out by a private equity owner from a much larger global manufacturer, PureTech had to quickly migrate its operations to its own systems. But without an IT team of its own this was initially a daunting challenge. The new company chose SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition because of its many benefits.</p>
  <p>“For us, it was an easy choice because first, we have no IT team,” Hardee said. “We have no internal training team, and we also had a very tight timeline with respect to the exit. So, we needed a solution that would enable us to move forward with speed, efficiency, and scalability. I could be confident that the infrastructure was being managed and secure. And that left us with an awesome choice for growth as well.”</p>
  <p>Scalability and rapid implementation were key factors in the choice of GROW with SAP, Hardee noted: “It was a great fit and gave us a platform for scalability for future bolt-ons, acquisitions, and so forth. So that’s the main reason. And SAP has an awesome suite of tools that enable that rapid implementation. And there was no other way we were going to do it without an internal IT team and without the access to the training material and the testing and so on.”</p>
  <p>And speaking of rapid implementation, PureTech went live on SAP in just 15 weeks, standardizing a business with an 85-year history on a common platform. Hardee gave some advice on how to make a project successful: “Use the tool set that SAP provides – SAP Activate methodology does work! And if you have the opportunity, sign up for the SAP Preferred Success program because it gives you a direct line to someone in SAP so that if you or your integrator doesn’t know the answer, SAP can point you to the right direction very quickly. So that helps with the speed of transformation.”</p>
  <h2 id="tropicana-brands-group-all-about-agility-and-time">Tropicana Brands Group: All About Agility and Time</h2>
  <p>Tropicana is a household name to many consumers, known chiefly for its juice and other beverage products. But while the brand is more than 75 years old, <a href="https://www.tropicanabrandsgroup.com/">Tropicana Brands Group</a> is just a bit over two years old, having been recently spun-off as a stand-alone group.</p>
  <p>Jeff Lischett, CIO of the US$3 billion organization, joined Russell to talk about how his company relied on RISE with SAP to make its “Project Harvest” IT separation and transformation project successful.</p>
  <p>Lischett noted that speed and agility was the key value proposition for the project. “We needed a platform that was able to accelerate, move with us, pivot with us, as we were going through this in a very accelerated timeline,” he said. “When you bring the technology and couple it with the unified business architecture powered by SAP, the choice for us was clearly RISE with SAP. Tropicana really needed a fit for purpose. Where we came from was going to be entirely different than where we were going, and this modern ERP, in terms of leaner, simpler, more streamlined ways of working, was really at the core of what we needed across the value chain.”</p>
  <p>Tropicana Brands Group took its European business operations live on SAP just 11 months after it started the design work, followed by North America three months later. “That was pressure testing!” Lischett said. “In just over a year, we had a fully implemented, end-to-end digital core and technology foundation for Tropicana Brands. We have a technology and a platform now that is really going to – no pun intended – rise to meet the challenge of our growth ambition.”</p>
  <p>“Ruthless prioritization” and change management were key to the project’s success, Lischett said. “I’m the biggest evangelist and advocate of change management,” he said. “You need it. You need it at the front, you need it during, you need it at the end. One thing that I would’ve probably done slightly differently is [to have] stayed with it longer at the end.”</p>
  <p>Tropicana is already seeing the impact of the project and specifically its focus on a clean core. “The most impactful value we’ve seen [goes] back to that clean core,” Lischett said. “Just in the months that followed, the ability to … bring the development forward, to build on top of the core that we have with enhancements and optimizing at a speed ratio that you just haven’t seen.”</p>
  <p>When asked about what role AI will play in his company, Lischett focused mainly on the human side of the technology. “Ironically, from the standpoint of being a technologist … AI in my mind, in terms of how I lead it, [needs to be] human-centered first and foremost, ensuring that we’ve got the right culture, responsible use, and effective use,” he said. “The gift of time is really the value creator that I see in AI and being able to work more efficiently and being able to take that time and translate it into what matters to you.”</p>
  <h2 id="responsibly-enabling-critical-systems">Responsibly Enabling Critical Systems</h2>
  <p>Russell handed over the stage to Saueressig, who recently launched the <a href="/2024/04/cloud-transformation-adoption-revolution-expectations-outcomes-meet">new Customer Services &#x26; Delivery Board area</a>. Saueressig noted that 25% of the world’s commerce already runs through more than 6,000 RISE with SAP customers worldwide, and that SAP supports the most critical business processes on the planet.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <picture>
          <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1dc5f09272052858aaeb01a0eec06423efb162249.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
          <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1dc5f09272052858aaeb01a0eec06423efb162249.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
          <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1dc5f09272052858aaeb01a0eec06423efb162249.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
          <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_1dc5f09272052858aaeb01a0eec06423efb162249.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="683">
        </picture>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>With that comes “the responsibility and the accountability to provide you with the most reliable and secure infrastructure,” Saueressig said. “That’s the reason why we co-engineered together with our partners from AWS, Microsoft Azure, Google Cloud Platform, and many others, to ensure that you have the highest level of quality and availability.”</p>
  <p>Echoing the theme of speed and adaptability, he noted that fast adoption of technology is critical. “Today, it’s not about the big fish that eats the small fish, it’s about the fast fish that eats the slow,” he cited. “At the end of the day, [our] ambition is to transform your system landscape to create a more flexible architecture, which enables fast adoption of innovations and ultimately, value realization. … And we take our responsibility seriously to really help you thrive in this ever-changing environment.”</p>
  <h2 id="fresenius-se-from-complexity-to-standardization">Fresenius SE: From Complexity to Standardization</h2>
  <p>Ingo Elfering, CIO of global healthcare conglomerate <a href="https://www.fresenius.com/">Fresenius</a>, knows something about speed: his team migrated 29 system landscapes containing more than 134 systems in less than 15 months. He joined Saueressig on stage to provide some insights into his company’s transformation project.</p>
  <p>As a company that has grown through many acquisitions, Fresenius had a highly heterogenous IT landscape. “We never quite integrated them,” Elfering said. “So, a really complex landscape …, [with] all sorts of interfaces and other applications attached to it. That was our starting point.”</p>
  <p>Fresenius’ management realized the company needed to change and become more efficient and effective to set itself up for ongoing success. It went all-in, doing four major transformations at the same time. As Elfering noted, “We not only did the RISE with SAP migration, we also did a complete cloud migration of our data centers worldwide; an outsourcing with a partner to become a more global team; and a global change of our network, including a whole bunch of security additions into our space.”</p>
  <p>Since it works in the healthcare and pharmaceutical space, Fresenius has a lot of regulatory requirements that it must adhere to, making the project more challenging than it might be in other industries. “You do a lot more technical documentation, testing, and so forth. So, from that perspective, regulations like GxP, good manufacturing or critical infrastructure, they were new to SAP in that instance in RISE with SAP. And we did it together. And I find that quite remarkable.”</p>
  <p>The <a href="/2023/06/fresenius-rise-with-sap-moves-sap-systems-cloud">new system has now been live</a> for just over a year and the company has seen many benefits. “We have a better speed on the underlying systems,” Elfering said. “We have a new infrastructure stack that works well. The main benefit for us will come as we [reinvent] the company. … We have some systems that doubled and tripled in size. So, it’s possible to leverage SAP quite quickly in these types of environments. From that perspective, I’m very happy with where we are. … We now have all the foundations in place to be able to execute our next phase of changes, our consolidation, our simplification, and in the cloud.”</p>
  <p>Finally, Elfering believes that healthcare is an area where AI can make a significant difference. “Healthcare always has been data-rich and insights-poor. … And the only way to get there, in our opinion at least, is to be on a cloud-based infrastructure in the first place. Because otherwise you don’t have the same performance or capabilities.”</p>
  <h2 id="clean-core-drives-agility">Clean Core Drives Agility</h2>
  <p>The idea of a “clean core” and a unified, simplified system underlies all these customer transformation stories. And it’s even more important in the context of agility and adaptability when it comes to taking advantage of the latest innovations in AI.</p>
  <p>“It’s super important for us to be clear that the clean core is not just for the sake of the clean core,” Saueressig said. “It’s a means to get to an innovation- and upgrade-ready system to be able to embrace these innovations. Because at the end of the day, legacy systems often have this technical depth that limits agility.”</p>
  <p>Saueressig admitted that even SAP has struggled with this, noting that the company had millions of lines of custom code in its systems. An internal analysis of all SAP customers showed that more than 65% of their custom code was unused in the past 12 months. “Code is also a liability, not just an asset,” he said. “And this is something we need to actively work against.”</p>
  <h2 id="hitachi-high-tech-corporation-clean-and-simple-benefits">Hitachi High-Tech Corporation: Clean and Simple Benefits</h2>
  <p>Saueressig invited Takuya Sakai, general manager of the Digital Transformation Business Group at <a href="https://www.hitachi-hightech.com/">Hitachi High-Tech</a>, on the stage to talk more about the benefits of system simplification and clean core. In 2019, Hitachi High-Tech <a href="https://www.sap.com/asset/dynamic/2023/07/d237f8b9-7e7e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">initiated a project</a> to simplify its business processes and digitize its management information. With its existing business processes fragmented across overseas sales offices, headquarters, and manufacturing sites, the organization needed to change to accelerate its business and set itself up for future growth. It chose SAP S/4HANA to help it build its new foundation for ongoing growth.</p>
  <p>Hitachi was running SAP R/3 but had significantly customized it with 9,000 add-ons across four instances, resulting in a lot of custom code. This resulted in many errors every day and large operational costs every year, Sakai said. And with the cost of validating so many add-ons, the company only did a major version update once in 12 years.</p>
  <p>To move to a more standardized and flexible system, Hitachi High-Tech adopted a two-tier architecture model. Taking advantage of development flexibility, the company deployed SAP S/4HANA Cloud Private Edition for its headquarters and group companies in Japan and SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition for its overseas sales offices. The adoption of SAP S/4HANA Cloud allows Hitachi High-Tech to take advantage of the functionality offered by SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP) for application development, data management, automation, integration, analytics, and AI.</p>
  <p>With the new system, Hitachi High-Tech reduced its 9,000 add-ons to just 750, allowing it to easily upgrade its ERP core. “Upgrading our old ERP took about a year and a half from the planning stage,” Sakai said. “However, with clean core, we can now do an upgrade every year in about 40 days. An upgrade every year keeps the clean core fresh and means new features can be delivered to our business quickly, like AI or process automation.”</p>
  <p>But achieving – and keeping – a clean core “requires patience,” Sakai said. Executives must understand the purpose of the transformation project and employees must overcome the pain that comes with a transformation project. “This is the most difficult thing,” he said. “The IT department must properly understand the new technology and suggest how to use it correctly. Then together we embark on the journey to the transformation.”</p>
  <h2 id="supporting-business-transformation-and-accelerating-time-to-value">Supporting Business Transformation and Accelerating Time to Value</h2>
  <p>Accelerating and improving time-to-value for customers is very important to SAP, according to Saueressig.</p>
  <p>“We are now bringing together all of our assets … in a seamless, end-to-end tool chain,” he said. “We want to holistically support your business transformation according to the dimensions of applications, data, processes, and people, which means we bring together and fully integrate SAP LeanIX for the IT landscapes and architecture, SAP Signavio for process management, SAP Cloud Application Lifecycle Management for application management and operational aspects, SAP BTP for integrations, and SAP Build for extensions, but also our telemetry tools, which we can leverage in the cloud.”</p>
  <p>Saueressig’s passion and ambition is to help customers drive innovation adoption. He noted that RISE with SAP is more than just a technical migration: it’s an offering for holistic business transformation as a service to accelerate value realization.</p>
  <p>“Ultimately, we want to help you to bring the best out of our entire holistic portfolio,” he said. “We want to help you to transform, realize agility at scale, achieve more across the entire value chain, and fundamentally transform operations with sustainability at the core. And this is something where I feel that we have a huge opportunity together to make that a reality.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-news-and-coverage-from-sap-sapphire-in-2024">Get the latest news and coverage from SAP Sapphire in 2024</h3>
        <p><em><a href="/topics/sap-sapphire">Read more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/grow-with-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[End-to-End Innovation Is Key to Bringing Out Your Best]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-sapphire-innovation-key-to-bring-out-your-best</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-sapphire-innovation-key-to-bring-out-your-best</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In their keynote, Juergen Mueller and Muhammad Alam demoed and discussed the latest innovations out of SAP Sapphire in 2024.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e38256295162fd6aa4582f624a1a9f11f0f8543b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e38256295162fd6aa4582f624a1a9f11f0f8543b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1e38256295162fd6aa4582f624a1a9f11f0f8543b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="End-to-End Innovation Is Key to Bringing Out Your Best" src="./media_1e38256295162fd6aa4582f624a1a9f11f0f8543b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="end-to-end-innovation-is-key-to-bringing-out-your-best">End-to-End Innovation Is Key to Bringing Out Your Best</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>In their SAP Sapphire Orlando keynote, Executive Board Members Muhammad Alam, SAP Product Engineering, and Juergen Mueller, chief technology officer, shared how the latest SAP innovations will help businesses drive true, end-to-end digital transformation and address their toughest business challenges.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="taking-business-to-the-next-level-in-the-era-of-ai">Taking Business to the Next Level in the Era of AI</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/events/sapphire/news-guide.html">Read the news guide</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In the keynote, which featured several real-world product demos by SAP employees, Alam and Mueller touted the value of SAP’s best-of-breed solutions with an outlook of what the next 50 years of innovation by SAP may look like.</p>
  <p>Who better to inspire the keynote than Hasso Plattner, co-founder and recently retired chairman of the SAP Supervisory Board, who both Alam and Mueller invoked during the session. To spell out SAP’s legacy and vision for the future, Mueller quoted <a href="/2024/05/hasso-plattner-olaf-scholz-farewell-tributes">Plattner’s farewell message</a>: “Keep innovating, keep pushing boundaries, and keep making a difference in the lives of our customers and the world at large.”</p>
  <h2 id="keep-innovating">Keep Innovating</h2>
  <p>To kick off his first SAP Sapphire appearance as the head of SAP Product Engineering, Alam began by describing the importance of harnessing innovation to deliver an end-to-end picture across all business functions and unlock true value.</p>
  <p>Simply put, businesses exist to build and deliver products and services to customers, he explained. But the materials, assets, people, and processes that come together to achieve this task is far from simple. “The reality is that each part of the business is deeply and intricately connected to all the others,” Alam said, meaning a pain point in one area impacts the rest. That’s why SAP’s modular cloud ERP approach is so successful: “We allow our customers to drive true digital transformation as opposed to running systems integration projects disguised as digital transformation,” he added.</p>
  <p>Alam presented <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/grow.html">GROW with SAP</a> as an example of this composability and extensibility, as it can work for and scale to many sizes and types of business. And now, SAP Sales Cloud and Concur Expense are natively integrated into GROW with SAP, making the offering even more comprehensive. Sinit Foto, product manager for UX, Cloud ERP at SAP, joined Alam on stage to show how GROW with SAP and SAP Business AI can help achieve integrated processes, demoing use cases such as communicating with customers about sales quotes, creating expense reports, and supporting financial analyses. In fact, Alam announced that SAP is implementing the demoed application internally to manage sales worldwide. And Mueller emphasized: “We are committed to helping you in this transformative AI moment by creating business outcomes that were unthinkable before. That’s why we’re embedding SAP Business AI deeply in our processes and analytics.”</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <picture>
          <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ab1b55bf13f95fe3a6b47084f96d918d20d0b6d4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
          <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ab1b55bf13f95fe3a6b47084f96d918d20d0b6d4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
          <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1ab1b55bf13f95fe3a6b47084f96d918d20d0b6d4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
          <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_1ab1b55bf13f95fe3a6b47084f96d918d20d0b6d4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="683">
        </picture>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="keep-pushing">Keep Pushing</h2>
  <p>AI was woven throughout the entire keynote, with both Alam and Mueller discussing <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence.html">SAP’s strategy and product enhancements in this space</a>. AI must be high value, easy to adopt into the flow of work, and trustworthy for it to truly transform how we do business, Alam said. “Equally important is whether it’s done in a way where it keeps your data secure and private – and is executed in a responsible manner,” he added. “And that is really the core promise of SAP Business AI.”</p>
  <p>There’s no doubt that AI is a powerful technology, which is why it’s essential that businesses view it as a “responsibility” not just an “opportunity,” Alam said. Megan Fife, executive solution advisor for SAP SuccessFactors, showed how SAP executes on its responsible, reliable, and relevant business AI by demoing how SAP’s AI copilot Joule in SAP SuccessFactors HCM can help fill skills gaps and collaborate across teams, among other meaningful tasks. Key to this endeavor is <a href="/2024/06/joule-microsoft-copilot-unified-work-experience">SAP’s expanded partnership with Microsoft announced earlier in the day</a>, which Scott Guthrie, executive vice president of Cloud and AI at Microsoft, discussed with Alam on stage.</p>
  <p>Mueller echoed the importance of responsible AI, saying that the technology depends highly on data that is reliable and that allows customers to look at their business end-to-end. Here, SAP Datasphere and SAP Spend Control Tower – which was demoed by Orla Cullen, product marketing manager for Data and Analytics at SAP – can help simplify data management and view and manage spend and sustainability data holistically.</p>
  <p>This transformation is supported by <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform.html">SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP)</a>, and Mueller demonstrated the newest generative AI features in SAP Analytics Cloud, SAP Integration Suite, and SAP Build solutions. He showed how Joule can help create and summarize financial reports for controlling teams; generate integration flows between SAP and non-SAP applications; and create custom skills and content based on specific business needs. Greater insights, faster reaction times, and increased productivity are the result. Soon, Mueller added, it will even be possible to enhance and extend Joule’s knowledge by creating custom skills using SAP Build and having the copilot interact with data housed in SAP and non-SAP systems, helping businesses run even more efficiently.</p>
  <p>SAP BTP is the key to being “innovation-ready,” maintaining a clean core, and tailoring standard offerings to unique needs, Mueller explained. More than 24,000 companies running live on SAP BTP, including Blue Diamond Growers and Lufthansa Technik, can attest to this.</p>
  <p>“SAP BTP’s extensibility and enterprise automation capabilities can help businesses turn process insights into actual improvements,” Mueller said. Cecilia Huergo, product manager for SAP BTP, showed this in her demo on how identifying improvement opportunities, realizing needed changes while maintaining a clean core, and gaining an up-to-date view of your IT landscape can be enabled with the combined power of SAP Signavio solutions, SAP LeanIX,, SAP BTP, and ABAP Cloud.</p>
  <h2 id="keep-making-a-difference">Keep Making a Difference</h2>
  <p>The innovations demoed and discussed in Alam and Mueller’s keynote, in addition to <a href="/2024/06/sap-sapphire-news-business-ai-enterprise-cloud-portfolio-cutting-edge-partnerships">the many others announced at SAP Sapphire in 2024</a>, are just the latest steps forward in SAP’s journey to bringing out the best in its customers. “The future is here, and it’s defined by those who innovate first,” Mueller said. “And we are here to give you the right tools at hand, such that you can be a leader not just today, but also tomorrow.”</p>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d468a3b0b7b4a96babee63b887b0c66d1bdc61b2.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d468a3b0b7b4a96babee63b887b0c66d1bdc61b2.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1d468a3b0b7b4a96babee63b887b0c66d1bdc61b2.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Why AI Means Being In The Cloud" src="./media_1d468a3b0b7b4a96babee63b887b0c66d1bdc61b2.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://youtu.be/EnxihshouTE">Why AI Means Being In The Cloud</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Gillian Hixson is an integrated communications specialist at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-news-and-coverage-from-sap-sapphire-in-2024">Get the latest news and coverage from SAP Sapphire in 2024</h3>
        <p><em><a href="/topics/sap-sapphire">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/grow-with-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Enters into Agreement to Acquire WalkMe, Driving Business Transformation by Enhancing the Customer Experience and Enriching SAP Business AI Offerings]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-enters-agreement-to-acquire-walkme</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-enters-agreement-to-acquire-walkme</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is entering into an agreement to acquire WalkMe, a leader in digital adoption platforms. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17c02c58752a8aaaec6051673cfe2308da8b06446.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17c02c58752a8aaaec6051673cfe2308da8b06446.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_17c02c58752a8aaaec6051673cfe2308da8b06446.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Enters into Agreement to Acquire WalkMe, Driving Business Transformation by Enhancing the Customer Experience and Enriching SAP Business AI Offerings" src="./media_17c02c58752a8aaaec6051673cfe2308da8b06446.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-enters-into-agreement-to-acquire-walkme-driving-business-transformation-by-enhancing-the-customer-experience-and-enriching-sap-business-ai-offerings">SAP Enters into Agreement to Acquire WalkMe, Driving Business Transformation by Enhancing the Customer Experience and Enriching SAP Business AI Offerings</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) and WalkMe Ltd. (NASDAQ: WKME) announced today that the companies have entered into a definitive agreement under which SAP will acquire WalkMe, a leader in digital adoption platforms (DAPs).</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>WalkMe’s solutions help organizations navigate constant technology change by providing users with advanced guidance and automation features that enable them to execute workflows seamlessly across any number of applications. This results in higher adoption of the underlying application and as such drives value realization.</p>
  <p>The Executive and Supervisory Boards of SAP SE and the board of directors of WalkMe have approved the transaction for US $14.00 per share in an all-cash transaction, representing an equity value of approximately US $1.5 billion. The offer price represents a 45% premium to WalkMe’s closing share price on June 4, 2024.</p>
  <p>The envisioned combination complements SAP’s Business Transformation Management portfolio around SAP Signavio and SAP LeanIX solutions to help customers on their transformation journeys.</p>
  <p>“Applications, processes, data and people are the four key elements of a successful business transformation,” said Christian Klein, CEO and member of the Executive Board of SAP SE. “By acquiring WalkMe, we are doubling down on the support we provide our end users, helping them to quickly adopt new solutions and features to get the maximum value out of their IT investments.”</p>
  <h2 id="walkme-focus-on-analyzing-adoption-and-business-transformation">WalkMe: Focus on Analyzing Adoption and Business Transformation</h2>
  <p>“We are thrilled to join forces with SAP. This acquisition marks a significant milestone in our journey, providing us with the resources and customer base necessary to enhance our product offerings and expand our market reach,” said Dan Adika, CEO of WalkMe. “By leveraging SAP’s extensive ecosystem, we are poised to unlock substantial growth opportunities and deliver even greater value to our customers. Together, we look forward to a future filled with innovation and exceptional service.”</p>
  <p>WalkMe helps organizations boost enterprise productivity and lower risk by enabling consistent, effective and efficient use of software and the workflows it enables. Its DAP works on top of an organization’s application landscape, detects where people encounter friction and provides the tailored support and automation they need to complete the job to be done, right in the flow of work, across any application. Importantly, WalkMe will continue to fully support non-SAP applications.</p>
  <p>Soon, WalkMe will launch the WalkMe<sup>X</sup> copilot, which will use WalkMe’s contextual awareness and AI to suggest the best next step for any workflow, anywhere. WalkMe<sup>X</sup> has the capability to always be on, serving as an overlay to any application, including copilots from different vendors that companies use in their landscapes. Integrating the strength of WalkMe’s adoption capabilities with SAP’s copilot Joule will boost AI assistant and productivity gains for all SAP customers. Additionally, integrating distinctive e-learning features in the SAP Enable Now solution with WalkMe will form the center of SAP’s people-centric transformation approach going forward.</p>
  <p>The acquisition is subject to customary closing conditions, including the receipt of WalkMe shareholder approval and necessary regulatory clearances, and is expected to close in the third quarter of 2024. The impact of the transaction on SAP’s non-IFRS earnings per share for fiscal 2024 is expected to be immaterial.</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>About WalkMe</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>WalkMe (NASDAQ: WKME), headquartered in Tel Aviv, Israel, pioneered DAP innovations and solutions so companies can effectively navigate the constant change brought on by technology. With WalkMe, organizations drive enterprise productivity and reduce risk by ensuring consistent, responsible, and efficient adoption of software and the workflows it powers. Our AI-driven platform sits on top of an organization’s tech stack, identifies where people experience friction, and delivers the personalized guidance and automation needed to get the job done, right in the flow of work. Customers like IBM, Nestle, ThermoFisher Scientific, and the U.S. Dept. of Defense trust WalkMe to create the people-centric experiences required to boost the effectiveness of their workflows and maximize software ROI.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>About SAP</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As a global leader in enterprise applications and business AI, SAP (NYSE:SAP) stands at the nexus of business and technology. For over 50 years, organizations have trusted SAP to bring out their best by uniting business-critical operations spanning finance, procurement, HR, supply chain, and customer experience. For more information, visit <a href="http://www.sap.com">www.sap.com</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Note to editors:</strong><br>To preview and download broadcast-standard stock footage and press photos digitally, please visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/photos">www.sap.com/photos</a>. On this platform, you can find high resolution material for your media channels.</p>
  <p><strong>For customers interested in learning more about SAP products:</strong><br>Global Customer Center: +49 180 534-34-24<br>United States Only: 1 (800) 872-1SAP (1-800-872-1727)</p>
  <p><strong>For more information, financial community only:</strong><br>Anthony Coletta, +49 6227-7-60437, <a href="mailto:investor@sap.com">investor@sap.com</a>, CEST</p>
  <p><strong>For more information, press only:</strong><br>Joellen Perry, +1 650-445-6780, <a href="mailto:joellen.perry@sap.com">joellen.perry@sap.com</a>, PT<br>Daniel Reinhardt, +49 6227-7-40201, <a href="mailto:daniel.reinhardt@sap.com">daniel.reinhardt@sap.com</a>, CEST<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p><strong>For WalkMe Investor Relations:</strong><br>John Streppa, <a href="mailto:investors@walkme.com">investors@walkme.com</a></p>
  <p><strong>Additional Important Information and Where to Find It</strong> In connection with the proposed transaction, WalkMe will prepare a proxy statement to be delivered to its shareholders and furnished to the Securities and Exchange Commission (the “SEC”). INVESTORS AND SECURITY HOLDERS ARE STRONGLY ADVISED TO READ THE PROXY STATEMENT WHEN IT BECOMES AVAILABLE AND OTHER RELEVANT DOCUMENTS FILED OR FURNISHED TO THE SEC IN CONNECTION WITH THE PROPOSED TRANSACTION OR INCORPORATED BY REFERENCE THEREIN, BECAUSE THE PROXY STATEMENT AND SUCH OTHER RELEVANT DOCUMENTS WILL CONTAIN IMPORTANT INFORMATION ABOUT THE PROPOSED TRANSACTION AND THE PARTIES TO THE PROPOSED TRANSACTION. This press release is not a substitute for the proxy statement or any other document that may be filed or furnished by WalkMe with the SEC.</p>
  <p>The proxy statement and other related documents filed or furnished to the SEC regarding the proposed transaction may be obtained for free from the SEC’s website (<a href="http://www.sec.gov/">www.sec.gov</a>), WalkMe’s website at <a href="http://www.walkme.com">www.walkme.com</a> or by directing such request to WalkMe’s Investor Relations.</p>
  <p><strong>Forward-Looking Statements</strong><br>This press release contains “forward-looking statements” within the meaning of the “safe harbor” provisions of the Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995 and other applicable securities laws. All statements other than statements of historical fact, including statements regarding the proposed acquisition of WalkMe by SAP, the expected timing for completing the proposed transaction and the terms thereof, future financial and operating results, benefits and synergies of the transaction, future opportunities for the combined businesses and any other statements regarding events or developments that may occur in the future, may be “forward-looking statements” for purposes of federal and state securities laws. These forward-looking statements involve a number of risks and uncertainties that could significantly affect the financial or operating results of SAP, WalkMe or the combined company. Words such as “expects,” “anticipates,” “intends,” “plans,” “believes,” “estimates,” “predicts,” “seeks,” “targets,” “would,” “will,” “should,” “may” and variations of such words and similar expressions are intended to identify such forward-looking statements. Such statements are based on management’s expectations as of the date they are first made, are not guarantees of future performance and involve certain risks, uncertainties and assumptions that are difficult to predict. Neither SAP nor WalkMe can give any assurances that the expectations in such forward-looking statements will be attained and, therefore, actual outcomes and results may differ materially from what is expressed or forecasted in such forward-looking statements. For example, these forward-looking statements could be affected by factors including, without limitation, risks associated with the ability to consummate the proposed transaction, the satisfaction of the conditions to the consummation of the proposed transaction, including the receipt of certain regulatory approvals, and the timing of the closing of the proposed transaction; the occurrence of any event, change or other circumstance that could give rise to the termination of the proposed transaction; the potential that WalkMe shareholders may not approve the transaction; the ability to successfully integrate operations and employees; the ability to realize anticipated benefits and synergies of the proposed transaction as rapidly or to the extent anticipated by financial analysts or investors; the potential impact of the announcement of the proposed transaction on operating results, business generally and business relationships, including with employees, customers, suppliers and competitors; unanticipated restructuring costs may be incurred or undisclosed liabilities assumed; actual or threatened legal proceedings that have been or may be instituted against SAP or WalkMe in connection with the proposed transaction or otherwise; the ability and costs related to retaining key personnel and clients; risks related to diverting management’s attention from ongoing business operations; delays, challenges, costs, fees, expenses and charges related to the proposed transaction; actions by competitors; general adverse economic, political, social and security conditions in the regions and industries in which SAP and WalkMe operate, including relating to Israel’s ongoing war with Hamas and other terrorist organizations in the Middle East and general hostilities; exposure to inflation, currency rate and interest rate fluctuations and risks associated with doing business locally and internationally, as well as fluctuations in the market price of SAP and WalkMe’s traded securities; natural catastrophes, any pandemic, epidemic or outbreak of infectious disease, warfare, protests and riots, and terrorist attacks; and those additional risks and factors discussed in reports filed or furnished with the SEC by SAP and WalkMe, including SAP’s and WalkMe’s most recent Annual Reports on Form 20-F and in any subsequent reports on Form 6-K, each of which is on file with or furnished to the SEC and available at the SEC’s website at <a href="http://www.sec.gov/">www.sec.gov</a>. Reports filed or furnished with the SEC by SAP are also available on SAP’s website at <a href="http://www.sap.com/investors/en.html">www.sap.com/investors</a> and by WalkMe on WalkMe’s website at <a href="http://www.walkme.com">www.walkme.com</a>. Moreover, other risks and uncertainties of which SAP or WalkMe are not currently aware or may not currently consider material may also affect each of the companies’ forward-looking statements and may cause actual results and the timing of events to differ materially from those anticipated. The forward-looking statements made in this press release are made only as of the date hereof or as of the dates indicated in the forward-looking statements, even if they are subsequently made available by SAP or WalkMe on their respective websites or otherwise. Neither SAP nor WalkMe undertakes any obligation to update or supplement any forward-looking statements to reflect actual results, new information, future events, changes in its expectations or other circumstances that exist after the date as of which the forward-looking statements were made.</p>
  <p>© 2024 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE and affiliated entities in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p>Please consider our <a href="https://www.sap.com/corporate/en/legal/privacy.html">privacy policy</a>. If you receive this press release in your e-mail and you wish to unsubscribe to our mailing list please contact <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a> and write Unsubscribe in the subject line.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/investor-relations</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>product/sap-leanix</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-signavio</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP's New AI Innovations and Partnerships Deliver Real-World Results]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/ai-innovations-partnerships-sap-sapphire</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/ai-innovations-partnerships-sap-sapphire</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Explore the AI capabilities and ecosystem innovations presented at SAP Sapphire in 2024, all aimed at delivering real-world results.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>news-topic/financial-management</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/abap-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/accenture</category>
            <category>news-tag/ai-ethics</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/aws</category>
            <category>news-tag/bcg</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Generative AI Innovations Take Center Stage at SAP Sapphire in 2024]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-sapphire-generative-ai-center-stage</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-sapphire-generative-ai-center-stage</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A series of generative AI innovations and partnerships announced at SAP Sapphire showcase how SAP is taking business to the next level.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_183c39d6e19efd7774c87954a8bbf7838320ef779.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_183c39d6e19efd7774c87954a8bbf7838320ef779.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_183c39d6e19efd7774c87954a8bbf7838320ef779.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Generative AI Innovations Take Center Stage at SAP Sapphire in 2024" src="./media_183c39d6e19efd7774c87954a8bbf7838320ef779.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="generative-ai-innovations-take-center-stage-at-sap-sapphire-in-2024">Generative AI Innovations Take Center Stage at SAP Sapphire in 2024</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>SAP CEO Christian Klein kicked off SAP Sapphire this week with an upbeat keynote that highlighted the company’s latest business AI innovations, products, and partnerships, which he said will change how people work.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="taking-business-to-the-next-level-in-the-era-of-ai">Taking Business to the Next Level in the Era of AI</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/events/sapphire/news-guide.html">Read the news guide</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“This year is a very special Sapphire,” Klein said. “We are entering a new phase of AI, with endless possibilities for us all.”</p>
  <p>Klein and Chief Marketing and Solutions Officer Julia White used the keynote to outline how AI will deliver real business benefits for different corporate functions and “Bring Out Your Best,” this year’s event theme.</p>
  <h2 id="delivering-on-an-ai-promise">Delivering on an AI Promise</h2>
  <p>Klein emphasized how SAP has delivered on its promise to infuse generative AI throughout its business portfolio, has enabled customers to exploit the potential of business AI, and has positioned the Joule copilot as the new front end for SAP applications.</p>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11a9e312c5b8efe848ea7622ac6bcc8c38c9e5913.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11a9e312c5b8efe848ea7622ac6bcc8c38c9e5913.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_11a9e312c5b8efe848ea7622ac6bcc8c38c9e5913.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Sapphire Opening Keynote: Bring Out the Best in Your Business | 2024" src="./media_11a9e312c5b8efe848ea7622ac6bcc8c38c9e5913.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://youtu.be/gOVQhhm5yO0?si=wkpDopYq0gPK6kWn">SAP Sapphire Opening Keynote: Bring Out the Best in Your Business | 2024</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Together, the two also announced the next evolution and new capabilities in both RISE with SAP and GROW with SAP. Since it was launched over three years ago, more than 6,000 customers have selected RISE with SAP. During his keynote, Klein announced that RISE with SAP will now include a dedicated enterprise architect to guide customers through the RISE with SAP Methodology as well as an integrated tool chain to help manage the process, system, and data landscape holistically across the RISE with SAP life cycle.</p>
  <p>Meanwhile White, broadcasting live from the central showcase on the SAP Sapphire show floor, announced that cloud ERP offering GROW with SAP will now include SAP Sales Cloud and Concur Expense at no additional charge. Whether its managing your finances or managing your expenses, GROW with SAP has you covered, she said.</p>
  <h2 id="ai-momentum">AI Momentum</h2>
  <p>Building on SAP’s business AI momentum, Klein and White also announced a series of expanded partnerships to help companies make the most out of this decisive AI moment. The expanded partnerships include deals with Amazon Web Services (AWS) and Google Cloud. Klein also announced the integration of Microsoft 365 Copilot with Joule, delivering what he described as a “truly differentiated employee experience.”</p>
  <p>Together onstage with customers and SAP Chief AI Officer Philipp Herzig, they showcased how SAP is infusing generative AI throughout the application portfolio and enabling customers to thrive in the AI era.</p>
  <p>“The business AI innovations we’re announcing will not only change how people work with SAP solutions, but how people work overall,” said Klein ahead of his keynote address.</p>
  <h2 id="new-joule-capabilities">New Joule Capabilities</h2>
  <p>Klein announced Joule for consulting capabilities and Joule for ABAP developer capabilities, which will help SAP’s 6-million-strong consultant and developer community to accelerate projects by 30% and implement SAP solutions faster than ever before.</p>
  <p>During his keynote he described business AI as being “an inflection point” and added, “Today’s AI announcements and partnerships build on our commitment to deliver revolutionary technology that drives real-world results, helping customers unleash the agility and ingenuity they need to succeed in today’s fast-moving business landscape.”</p>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16cdfc9fd1fdbbf5cdc9cd5193401b9dfcafd1805.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16cdfc9fd1fdbbf5cdc9cd5193401b9dfcafd1805.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_16cdfc9fd1fdbbf5cdc9cd5193401b9dfcafd1805.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Why Joule Will Change the Way You Work" src="./media_16cdfc9fd1fdbbf5cdc9cd5193401b9dfcafd1805.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://youtu.be/a9j2Q6VVCfM?si=9cdzuqQ27TZ_J3uj">Why Joule Will Change the Way You Work</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“SAP is the only tech company who can infuse AI capabilities right into your business processes and workflows,” he said, saluting the achievements of the 40,000 SAP employees in the Product Development organization.</p>
  <h2 id="shout-out-to-sap-developers">Shout Out to SAP Developers</h2>
  <p>“No other tech company can offer a more powerful platform to transform enterprises to rewrite how business is run.” SAP developers have transformed SAP’s portfolio “from an ERP system that enabled transactions in real time, to a system with modular applications and embedded AI so that you can run intelligent, connected, and sustainable enterprises.”</p>
  <p>“We promised this to you, and we delivered,” Klein told audiences online and the 14,000 customers and partners attending SAP Sapphire in person this week in Orlando. “Now we are using the power of generative AI across our stack to once again revolutionize how businesses run and end users will work in the future.”</p>
  <p>After announcing generative AI copilot Joule in September 2023, Klein confirmed that it will become the new front-end and UX for SAP applications and “will turn your words into action.” Joule is ready for prime time, he declared, “and going forward, it will be embedded out of the box for all our cloud customers.”</p>
  <h2 id="joule-key-to-higher-productivity">Joule: Key to Higher Productivity</h2>
  <p>He predicted that Joule will also become the biggest productivity engine for every SAP end user, and that by the end of the year, 80% of the most used tasks will be managed via Joule and the 300 million end users of SAP products will be 20% more productive.</p>
  <p>While AI is a powerful technology facilitating huge opportunities for business and employees, the SAP CEO emphasized that it is also crucial to offer responsible AI. To that end, he announced that SAP is among the first tech companies to adhere to UNESCO’s AI principles.</p>
  <p>Klein wrapped up the keynote by emphasizing that SAP does not view AI as an end in itself, but rather as a tool to help the world run better and improve people’s lives. “You have my commitment that we will continue to listen to your needs, we will continue to deliver great innovations and we will continue to deliver great outcomes for your company.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-news-and-coverage-from-sap-sapphire-in-2024">Get the latest news and coverage from SAP Sapphire in 2024</h3>
        <p><em><a href="/topics/sap-sapphire">Read more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Putting Sustainability at the Heart of ERP]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sustainability-erp-sap-business-ai-sap-sapphire</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sustainability-erp-sap-business-ai-sap-sapphire</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP’s ERP-centric, cloud-based, AI-enabled approach is redefining how companies manage sustainability. Learn how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_19f549b1c60b71d253752564f5659b7cd5b69ae91.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_19f549b1c60b71d253752564f5659b7cd5b69ae91.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_19f549b1c60b71d253752564f5659b7cd5b69ae91.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Putting Sustainability at the Heart of ERP" src="./media_19f549b1c60b71d253752564f5659b7cd5b69ae91.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="putting-sustainability-at-the-heart-of-erp">Putting Sustainability at the Heart of ERP</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Sustainability has evolved from a boardroom buzzword to a critical driver of business success and strategic differentiation. To thrive, companies are going to need to understand how to operate in a modern, low-carbon, circular economy. SAP solutions will support them by embedding sustainability into every aspect of their operations.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-sapphire-taking-business-to-the-next-level-in-the-era-of-ai">SAP Sapphire: Taking Business to the Next Level in the Era of AI</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/events/sapphire/news-guide.html">Read the news guide</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>At our customer flagship event, <a href="/topics/sap-sapphire">SAP Sapphire</a>, we’re discussing how we support customers with their biggest challenges, looking at future trends, and unveiling the latest product innovations.</p>
  <p>This makes the event the perfect opportunity to highlight how we are redefining the way companies manage sustainability through our ERP-centric, cloud-based, AI-enabled approach.</p>
  <h2 id="erp-centric">ERP-Centric</h2>
  <p>For true business model transformation, sustainability needs to be at the core of how companies operate. At SAP, we integrate sustainability data into cloud ERP business processes, which helps companies connect financial and non-financial information and thus treat carbon like money. This makes all decisions financially <em>and</em> environmentally sound while enabling customers to record real impacts and report audit-ready environmental, social, and governance (ESG) metrics seamlessly.</p>
  <h2 id="cloud-based">Cloud-Based</h2>
  <p>Instant access to fast-evolving innovations is only possible through the cloud. Our modern cloud-based solutions ensure that businesses can quickly adopt new functionality and stay ahead in a rapidly changing environment.</p>
  <h2 id="ai-enabled">AI-Enabled</h2>
  <p>Business AI is revolutionizing the way we approach sustainability. At SAP, AI takes complex sustainability tasks reliant on sustainability data and ERP data and makes them automated and auditable. It enables companies to improve operational efficiency, foster greater transparency around supply chain emissions, design and plan more effectively, and automate time-consuming tasks. SAP Business AI is built on the data and processes that run the business world, including sustainability related information from both inside and outside the company’s walls, making our solutions smarter, faster, and more effective.</p>
  <p>With SAP Business AI, we support our customers’ efforts to optimize for sustainable impact. This year at SAP Sapphire, we are thrilled to announce two new AI-driven sustainability use cases:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Emission Factor Mapping with AI:</strong> Available in SAP Sustainability Footprint Management, this feature enhances the accuracy and speed of carbon footprint calculations through automated, intelligent suggestions. By reducing the manual effort involved in mapping emission factors, businesses can achieve more precise measurements and make informed decisions faster.</li>
    <li><strong>ESG Report Generation with AI:</strong> This capability allows for the automatic generation of ESG reports based on the data within SAP Sustainability Control Tower. This not only streamlines the reporting process but also helps ensure that the data is reliable and actionable, providing a clear picture of a company’s sustainability performance.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>Our comprehensive approach to carbon management is becoming a reality as we introduce new sustainability tracking, monitoring, and reporting features within the SAP cloud ERP portfolio as well as a new solution that will help customers manage sustainability commitments and comply with global regulations.</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Advanced Carbon Calculator Engine:</strong> This powerful tool featured in SAP Sustainability Control Tower and SAP Sustainability Footprint Management integrates ERP data from SAP S/4HANA Cloud and other sources and embeds results back into business processes for informed decision-making. As such, it allows customers to meet Greenhouse Gas Protocol reporting standards, offering advanced, granular calculations of both product and corporate carbon footprints.</li>
    <li><strong>SAP Green Ledger</strong> will be released at the end of 2024. The solution will help customers connect their emissions data and financial data, allowing customers to easily understand the correlation between emissions and finances, model sustainable business scenarios, and then act with decisions that are both financially and environmentally sound.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>At SAP, we believe that the future of business is inextricably linked to sustainability. This is why sustainability is a key pillar of our growth strategy. Businesses must recognize that sustainable practices are not just ethical choices, but strategic financial decisions that drive innovation, reduce costs, and mitigate risks.</p>
  <p>Moreover, sustainable transformation opens up significant economic opportunities. By transforming their operations around sustainability, businesses can create a modern, low-carbon, circular economy that benefits both the environment and their bottom line, enhancing overall resilience.</p>
  <p>This transformation aligns business success with global sustainability goals, paving the way for a more sustainable, valuable, and prosperous future.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Sophia Mendelsohn is chief sustainability and commercial officer at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-news-and-coverage-from-sap-sapphire-in-2024">Get the latest news and coverage from SAP Sapphire in 2024</h3>
        <p><em><a href="/topics/sap-sapphire">Read more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-footprint-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Joule to Integrate with Microsoft Copilot for a Unified Work Experience]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/joule-microsoft-copilot-unified-work-experience</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/joule-microsoft-copilot-unified-work-experience</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is bringing its generative AI copilot Joule together with Microsoft Copilot for Microsoft 365 for deep bi-directional integration.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>news-tag/microsoft</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Expands Business AI Portfolio with Meta Open-Source Models]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-business-ai-meta-open-source-models</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-business-ai-meta-open-source-models</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is integrating Meta Llama 2 and Meta Llama 3 models into generative AI hub to enable customers to create dashboards based on rich content.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP’s Partnership with Mistral AI, One of the Leading LLM Makers]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-mistral-ai-leading-llm-maker-partnership</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-mistral-ai-leading-llm-maker-partnership</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The collaboration between SAP and Mistral AI is a symbiotic combination of AI expertise and technology. Learn about the partnership.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP and Accenture Collaborate on Getting to Value Faster with SAP Business AI]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/accenture-sap-sapphire-business-ai</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/accenture-sap-sapphire-business-ai</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP and Accenture are working together to help their customers make SAP Business AI and data their No. 1 competitive advantage.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/accenture</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>product/sap-leanix</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-signavio</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Infuses Business AI Throughout Its Enterprise Cloud Portfolio and Partners with Cutting-Edge AI Leaders to Bring Out Customers’ Best]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-sapphire-news-business-ai-enterprise-cloud-portfolio-cutting-edge-partnerships</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-sapphire-news-business-ai-enterprise-cloud-portfolio-cutting-edge-partnerships</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New SAP Business AI innovations and collaborations with partners are igniting ingenuity. Read the news from SAP Sapphire Orlando in 2024.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18ff27978e1178b1dce994986e74f4cc1f6087f26.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18ff27978e1178b1dce994986e74f4cc1f6087f26.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_18ff27978e1178b1dce994986e74f4cc1f6087f26.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Infuses Business AI Throughout Its Enterprise Cloud Portfolio and Partners with Cutting-Edge AI Leaders to Bring Out Customers’ Best" src="./media_18ff27978e1178b1dce994986e74f4cc1f6087f26.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-infuses-business-ai-throughout-its-enterprise-cloud-portfolio-and-partners-with-cutting-edge-ai-leaders-to-bring-out-customers-best">SAP Infuses Business AI Throughout Its Enterprise Cloud Portfolio and Partners with Cutting-Edge AI Leaders to Bring Out Customers’ Best</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>SAP Business AI Innovations and Collaborations with Partners including Google Cloud, Meta, Microsoft, Mistral AI and NVIDIA Ignite Ingenuity</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <table>
          <thead>
            <tr>
              <th>Text Large</th>
            </tr>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td><strong><em>ORLANDO</em></strong> — At its annual SAP Sapphire conference, SAP unveiled generative AI innovations and partnerships that showcase how the company is taking business to the next level in the era of AI.</td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="taking-business-to-the-next-level-in-the-era-of-ai">Taking Business to the Next Level in the Era of AI</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/events/sapphire/news-guide.html">Read the news guide</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>By infusing Business AI across an enterprise cloud portfolio that powers the world’s most mission-critical processes and partnering with companies pushing the edge of what’s possible with AI, SAP is igniting a new wave of insight and ingenuity in global business.</p>
  <p>“The Business AI innovations we’re announcing at SAP Sapphire in 2024 will redefine the way businesses run,” says Christian Klein, CEO and member of the Executive Board of SAP SE. “Today’s AI announcements and partnerships build on our commitment to deliver revolutionary technology that drives real-world results, helping customers unleash the agility and ingenuity they need to succeed in today’s fast-moving business landscape.”</p>
  <h2 id="ai-that-means-business">AI That Means Business</h2>
  <p>As SAP embeds Business AI across its enterprise solutions, it puts rich insights at users’ fingertips, empowering them to deliver better outcomes and elevate the creative problem-solving humans do best. Examples include AI-generated reports in SAP SuccessFactors solutions that give people managers responsibly sourced insights for compensation-related discussions as well as forecasting capabilities in SAP Sales Cloud solutions that predict combinations of salespeople and products most likely to drive sales. Meanwhile, the SAP Business Technology Platform is adding large language models from Amazon Web Services, Meta and Mistral AI to its generative AI hub. This capability in the SAP AI Core infrastructure makes it easier to build generative AI use cases for SAP applications.</p>
  <p>SAP’s generative AI copilot Joule, which quickly sorts and contextualizes data from multiple systems to advance automation and improve decision-making, is expanding throughout the company’s solution portfolio. Joule launched in <a href="/2023/09/joule-new-generative-ai-assistant">SAP SuccessFactors solutions last fall</a> and is now embedded into SAP S/4HANA Cloud solutions and others including SAP Build and SAP Integration Suite. Further expansion by year-end will include SAP Ariba and SAP Analytics Cloud solutions. At Sapphire, SAP also announced <a href="/">plans to further broaden Joule’s scope</a> by integrating it with Microsoft Copilot to surface even richer insights. This deep, bi-directional integration gives users a unified experience built right into the flow of work, enabling seamless access to information from interactions with business applications in SAP and Microsoft 365.</p>
  <p>Reflecting Business AI’s increasing importance, SAP is redoubling its commitment to the principles of relevant, reliable, and responsible AI it pioneered. At Sapphire, SAP is adopting the 10 guiding principles of the UNESCO Recommendation on the Ethics of Artificial Intelligence, which aim to ensure that AI technologies are developed and used in ways that respect human rights, promote fairness and contribute to sustainable development.</p>
  <h2 id="partnerships-that-scale-innovation">Partnerships That Scale Innovation</h2>
  <p>SAP is partnering with best-in-class technology leaders to push the limits of what generative AI can do at an enterprise level. In addition to our expanded collaborations with <a href="/2024/05/aws-sap-generative-ai-new-innovation">AWS</a> and Microsoft, partnerships with Google Cloud, Meta, Mistral AI and NVIDIA ensure SAP can harness the power of AI-ready technology to innovate at speed and deliver richer real-world results.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Google Cloud</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP and Google Cloud are expanding their partnership, using Business AI to help enterprises better predict and mitigate supply-chain risks to minimize disruptions and maintain optimal inventory levels. The companies will integrate Joule and the SAP Integrated Business Planning for Supply Chain solution with Google Cloud’s Gemini models AI assistant and Google Cloud Cortex Framework’s data foundation.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Meta</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP will leverage Meta Llama 3 to generate scripts that render highly customized analytics applications in SAP Analytics Cloud. Meta’s next-generation AI model excels at language nuances and contextual understanding, making it an ideal candidate for translating enterprise business requirements into tangible outcomes.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Mistral AI</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP will also add <a href="/">new large language models from Mistral AI</a>, a global company headquartered in Paris specializing in generative AI, to the generative AI hub capability in SAP AI Core.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>NVIDIA</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP and NVIDIA Corporation advance a <a href="https://blogs.nvidia.com/blog/sap-sapphire-ai-omniverse/">cross-product partnership</a> to embed cutting-edge technologies into enterprise-ready business applications:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>As SAP trains Joule to serve as an AI assistant for the RISE with SAP solution implementations, NVIDIA’s state-of-the-art AI models sift through SAP consulting assets to provide relevant and precise answers to implementation-related questions;</li>
    <li>As SAP embeds Joule in the ABAP Cloud model to generate ABAP code for SAP developers, NVIDIA’s accelerated infrastructure will run, scale, and manage SAP’s generative AI model for ABAP code generation;</li>
    <li>As SAP infuses generative AI into the SAP Intelligent Product Recommendation solution, NVIDIA Omniverse Cloud APIs enable the simulation of complex manufacturing products and configurations as industrial digital twins.</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="cloud-technology-that-drives-agility-and-sustainability">Cloud Technology That Drives Agility and Sustainability</h2>
  <p>Business success in the era of AI means being in the cloud. SAP is making the move easier than ever with initiatives that help customers find partners with the expertise needed for complex SAP S/4HANA Cloud transformations. Further cloud innovations at SAP Sapphire include features that help the world’s organizations measure, manage and execute their sustainability strategies. SAP Sustainability Control Tower and SAP Sustainability Footprint Management solutions now track carbon footprints at scale and help businesses meet regulatory standards.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><a href="https://www.sap.com/events/sapphire/news-guide.html">Learn more in the 2024 SAP Sapphire News Guide</a>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Visit the <a href="/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-news-and-coverage-from-sap-sapphire-in-2024">Get the latest news and coverage from SAP Sapphire in 2024</h3>
        <p><em><a href="/topics/sap-sapphire">Read more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>About SAP</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As a global leader in enterprise applications and business AI, SAP (NYSE:SAP) stands at the nexus of business and technology. For over 50 years, organizations have trusted SAP to bring out their best by uniting business-critical operations spanning finance, procurement, HR, supply chain, and customer experience. For more information, visit <a href="http://www.sap.com">www.sap.com</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Note to editors:</strong><br>To preview and download broadcast-standard stock footage and press photos digitally, please visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/photos">www.sap.com/photos</a>. On this platform, you can find high resolution material for your media channels.</p>
  <p><strong>For customers interested in learning more about SAP products:</strong><br>Global Customer Center: +49 180 534-34-24<br>United States Only: 1 (800) 872-1SAP (1-800-872-1727)</p>
  <p><strong>For more information, press only:</strong><br>Joellen Perry, +1 (650) 445-6780, <a href="mailto:joellen.perry@sap.com">joellen.perry@sap.com</a> PT<br>Marcus Winkler, +49 6227-767497, <a href="mailto:marcus.winkler@sap.com">marcus.winkler@sap.com</a> CET<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>This document contains forward-looking statements, which are predictions, projections, or other statements about future events. These statements are based on current expectations, forecasts, and assumptions that are subject to risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results and outcomes to materially differ. Additional information regarding these risks and uncertainties may be found in our filings with the Securities and Exchange Commission, including but not limited to the risk factors section of SAP’s 2023 Annual Report on Form 20-F.<br>© 2024 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.<br>Please consider our <a href="https://www.sap.com/corporate/en/legal/privacy.html">privacy policy</a>. If you receive this press release in your e-mail and you wish to unsubscribe to our mailing list please contact <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a> and write Unsubscribe in the subject line.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/abap-cloud</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-sales-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-footprint-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[AWS and SAP Unlock New Innovation with Generative AI]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/aws-sap-generative-ai-new-innovation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/aws-sap-generative-ai-new-innovation</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP and AWS are making it easier for customers to embed generative AI into their entire portfolio of business-critical applications.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_104d1ffe68c31e9f2e51bfd7af2878774eaaff54a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_104d1ffe68c31e9f2e51bfd7af2878774eaaff54a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_104d1ffe68c31e9f2e51bfd7af2878774eaaff54a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="AWS and SAP Unlock New Innovation with Generative AI" src="./media_104d1ffe68c31e9f2e51bfd7af2878774eaaff54a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="aws-and-sap-unlock-new-innovation-with-generative-ai">AWS and SAP Unlock New Innovation with Generative AI</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Generative AI hub in SAP AI Core integrates with foundation models in Amazon Bedrock to deliver generative AI-driven insights and streamline manual processes for enterprise customers</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <table>
          <thead>
            <tr>
              <th>Text Large</th>
            </tr>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td><strong><em>SEATTLE and WALLDORF</em></strong> — Amazon Web Services (AWS), an Amazon.com company (NASDAQ: AMZN), and <a href="https://www.sap.com/index.html">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced an expanded, strategic collaboration to transform modern cloud enterprise resource planning (ERP) experiences and help enterprises drive new capabilities and efficiencies with generative artificial intelligence (AI).</td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
        <p>Together, AWS and SAP are striving to make it easier for customers to adopt the RISE with SAP solution on AWS, to improve the performance and efficiency of SAP workloads running in the cloud and to embed generative AI into an enterprise’s entire portfolio of business-critical applications.</p>
        <p>“AWS was the first cloud provider certified to support the SAP portfolio and today, thousands of enterprise companies run SAP solutions on AWS to get the most out of their mission-critical applications,” said Matt Garman incoming CEO at AWS. “Now, AWS and SAP are making it faster and easier for companies to apply generative AI to their core business data to become more efficient, responsive and sustainable.”</p>
        <p>“Partnerships like this collaboration with AWS are critical as we embed generative AI solutions across our ERP applications so that customers can drive innovation at an accelerated pace,” said Christian Klein, Chief Executive Officer of SAP SE. “In addition to delivering modern cloud ERP to our joint customers, we are excited to support Amazon on their own transformation journey as they adopt RISE with SAP for pioneering areas such as Project Kuiper, Amazon’s satellite initiative intended to increase global broadband access.”</p>
        <h2 id="generative-ai-models-from-amazon-bedrock-available-on-the-generative-ai-hub-in-sap-ai-core">Generative AI Models from Amazon Bedrock Available on the Generative AI Hub in SAP AI Core</h2>
        <p>The generative AI hub in SAP AI Core infrastructure provides customers with secure access to a broad range of large language models (LLMs) that can easily be integrated into SAP business applications. With the integration of generative AI models from Amazon Bedrock such as the Anthropic Claude 3 model family and Amazon Titan, SAP customers will be able to access high-performing LLMs and other foundation models (FMs) to build applications customized with their own data. Tens of thousands of customers use Amazon Bedrock to easily, quickly and securely build and scale generative AI applications using FMs from leading AI companies such as AI21 Labs, Anthropic, Cohere, Meta, Mistral AI, Stability AI and Amazon.</p>
        <p>With this integration, SAP customers may accelerate the adoption of generative AI and modernize key business processes built on SAP solutions. These innovations can be used in embedded use cases within RISE with SAP and the intelligent scenario lifecycle management functionality as an integration component or side-by-side directly on SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP). SAP and AWS plan to expand the use of Bedrock capabilities in the generative AI hub to further enable embedded AI functionality within SAP’s portfolio of cloud solutions and applications. This includes additional use cases across finance and product lifecycle management.</p>
        <h2 id="sap-to-use-aws-chips-to-train-and-deploy-future-sap-business-ai-offerings">SAP to Use AWS Chips to Train and Deploy Future SAP Business AI Offerings</h2>
        <p>SAP’s use of <a href="/2023/11/sap-hana-cloud-now-supports-aws-graviton">AWS Graviton3 chips to support SAP HANA Cloud</a> helps to deliver performance gains, cost savings and energy efficiency to SAP. By using Graviton3-based Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (EC2) instances, SAP has realized up to 30% better compute for analytical workloads and an estimated 45% reduction in carbon footprint for SAP HANA Cloud. Now SAP and AWS are collaborating on the next generation of Graviton4 for SAP HANA Cloud and additional SAP applications to continue to improve performance and efficiency. Based on the success of running SAP HANA Cloud on AWS Graviton, SAP plans to use AWS Graviton to support SAP solutions and applications such as SAP BTP, SAP Datasphere, SAP Analytics Cloud and the SAP Cloud ALM solution.</p>
        <p>SAP plans to use <a href="https://aws.amazon.com/machine-learning/inferentia/">AWS Trainium</a> and <a href="https://aws.amazon.com/machine-learning/inferentia/">AWS Inferentia</a> chips, purpose built for AI and machine learning (ML) workloads, for training and deploying future SAP Business AI offerings. Using Trainium and Inferentia2-based instances in a proof of concept, SAP engineers trained and fine-tuned generative AI LLMs in two days versus 23 days with comparable Amazon EC2 instances. By leveraging Trainium’s specialized architecture designed for efficient ML model training, SAP can accelerate the development process while maintaining high levels of accuracy and reliability.</p>
        <h2 id="increased-performance-for-rise-with-sap-on-aws">Increased Performance for RISE with SAP on AWS</h2>
        <p>Thousands of customers have selected RISE with SAP on AWS to run their largest, most complex, global SAP solution implementations. Now generally available, the next-generation Amazon EC2 High Memory U7i instances offer up to 32TiB of memory in a single instance and provide customers the memory and flexibility they need to support expanding SAP HANA database requirements. Amazon EC2 High Memory U7i instances are the first DDR5 memory-based 8-socket offering by a leading cloud provider to improve the performance of memory-intensive applications such as SAP S/4HANA Cloud as part of RISE with SAP.</p>
        <h2 id="amazons-project-kuiper-selects-rise-with-sap">Amazon’s Project Kuiper Selects RISE with SAP</h2>
        <p>Amazon companies, including Twitch, Zappos.com and Zoox Inc., already use SAP software on AWS to support their operations. And now Project Kuiper—Amazon’s satellite broadband network—is deploying RISE with SAP to support its complex supply chain and manufacturing operations and get the best performance and most value out of its mission-critical SAP software. Running SAP solutions on AWS allows Kuiper to take advantage of the latest SAP capabilities embedded in RISE with SAP to help drive impactful transformation, accelerating company decisions and enhancing overall performance and productivity.</p>
        <p>Hundreds of millions of people lack adequate internet access and Project Kuiper’s goal is to help close the digital divide by delivering fast, affordable broadband to a wide variety of customers operating in places without reliable internet connections. Delivering on that vision requires Kuiper to build satellites at an unprecedented rate. RISE with SAP allows the Project Kuiper team to leverage the most reliable and scalable infrastructure to run a modern, cloud ERP as a managed service, so they can focus on innovation instead of IT management.</p>
        <p>To learn more about the SAP and AWS partnership, tune in to the <a href="https://www.sap.com/events/sapphire.html">SAP Sapphire conference</a>, June 3-5, in Orlando.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="join-experts-speakers-and-peers-at-sap-sapphire-in-2024">Join experts, speakers and peers at SAP Sapphire in 2024</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/events/sapphire.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Visit the <a href="/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP at <a href="https://x.com/sapnews">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>About Amazon Web Services</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Since 2006, Amazon Web Services has been the world’s most comprehensive and broadly adopted cloud. AWS has been continually expanding its services to support virtually any workload, and it now has more than 240 fully featured services for compute, storage, databases, networking, analytics, machine learning and artificial intelligence (AI), Internet of Things (IoT), mobile, security, hybrid, media, and application development, deployment, and management from 105 Availability Zones within 33 geographic regions, with announced plans for 18 more Availability Zones and six more AWS Regions in Malaysia, Mexico, New Zealand, the Kingdom of Saudi Arabia, Thailand, and the AWS European Sovereign Cloud. Millions of customers—including the fastest-growing startups, largest enterprises, and leading government agencies—trust AWS to power their infrastructure, become more agile, and lower costs. To learn more about AWS, visit <a href="https://cts.businesswire.com/ct/CT?id=smartlink&#x26;url=https%3A%2F%2Faws.amazon.com%2F&#x26;esheet=53904515&#x26;newsitemid=20240304438993&#x26;lan=en-US&#x26;anchor=aws.amazon.com&#x26;index=12&#x26;md5=74b48ab611b237d4b1c4af457e844e2a">aws.amazon.com</a>.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>About Amazon</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Amazon is guided by four principles: customer obsession rather than competitor focus, passion for invention, commitment to operational excellence, and long-term thinking. Amazon strives to be Earth’s Most Customer-Centric Company, Earth’s Best Employer, and Earth’s Safest Place to Work. Customer reviews, 1-Click shopping, personalized recommendations, Prime, Fulfillment by Amazon, AWS, Kindle Direct Publishing, Kindle, Career Choice, Fire tablets, Fire TV, Amazon Echo, Alexa, Just Walk Out technology, Amazon Studios, and The Climate Pledge are some of the things pioneered by Amazon. For more information, visit <a href="https://cts.businesswire.com/ct/CT?id=smartlink&#x26;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.aboutamazon.com%2F&#x26;esheet=53552459&#x26;newsitemid=20230913559977&#x26;lan=en-US&#x26;anchor=amazon.com%2Fabout&#x26;index=4&#x26;md5=a9213abaf1405cdcf6f92fbf73419565">amazon.com/about</a> and follow @AmazonNews.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>About SAP</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As a global leader in enterprise applications and business AI, SAP (NYSE: SAP) stands at the nexus of business and technology. For over 50 years, organizations have trusted SAP to bring out their best by uniting business-critical operations spanning finance, procurement, HR, supply chain, and customer experience. For more information, visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/">www.sap.com</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Note to editors:</strong><br>To preview and download broadcast-standard stock footage and press photos digitally, please visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/photos">www.sap.com/photos</a>. On this platform, you can find high resolution material for your media channels.</p>
  <p><strong>For customers interested in learning more about SAP products:</strong><br>Global Customer Center: +49 180 534-34-24<br>United States Only: 1 (800) 872-1SAP (1-800-872-1727)</p>
  <p><strong>For more information, press only:</strong><br>Scott Malinowski, +1 (781) 852-3822, <a href="mailto:scott.malinowski@sap.com">scott.malinowski@sap.com</a>, ET<br><a href="mailto:SAP%20Press%20Room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a><br>Amazon.com, Inc. Media Hotline<br><a href="mailto:Amazon-pr@amazon.com">Amazon-pr@amazon.com</a><br><a href="https://cts.businesswire.com/ct/CT?id=smartlink&#x26;url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fpr&#x26;esheet=52838073&#x26;newsitemid=20220829005779&#x26;lan=en-US&#x26;anchor=www.amazon.com%2Fpr&#x26;index=11&#x26;md5=f7f322f746ba4e16da9b2e92d74e349a">www.amazon.com/pr</a></p>
  <p>This document contains forward-looking statements, which are predictions, projections, or other statements about future events. These statements are based on current expectations, forecasts, and assumptions that are subject to risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results and outcomes to materially differ. Additional information regarding these risks and uncertainties may be found in our filings with the Securities and Exchange Commission, including but not limited to the risk factors section of SAP’s 2023 Annual Report on Form 20-F.<br>© 2024 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.<br>Please consider our <a href="https://www.sap.com/corporate/en/legal/privacy.html">privacy policy</a>. If you receive this press release in your e-mail and you wish to unsubscribe to our mailing list please contact <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a> and write Unsubscribe in the subject line.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-business-ai-revolutionary-technology-real-world-results">SAP Business AI: Revolutionary technology, real-world results</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/aws</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Retaining Customers Through Support Experience and Efficiency]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/retaining-customers-through-support-experience-and-efficiency</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/retaining-customers-through-support-experience-and-efficiency</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A smooth support experience and efficient support teams combine to delight and retain customers when it comes to customer support. Learn how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/built-in-support</category>
            <category>news-tag/incident-solution-matching</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-for-me</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[NEC Leverages RISE with SAP and AI to Build Business AI in Move to the Cloud]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/nec-move-to-cloud-rise-with-sap-business-ai</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/nec-move-to-cloud-rise-with-sap-business-ai</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[NEC is migrating to SAP S/4HANA Cloud and adopting a clean-core approach to create a sustainable society through digital transformation.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/aws</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How SAP BTP Becomes the Trusted Platform for Business AI]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/sap-btp-strategy-paper-trusted-platform-business-ai</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/sap-btp-strategy-paper-trusted-platform-business-ai</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP BTP will further evolve to become the trusted business AI platform for SAP-centric landscapes. Learn more in the SAP BTP strategy paper.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-build</category>
            <category>product/sap-integration-suite</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Customer Support at SAP: Where Artificial Intelligence Meets Application Integration]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/customer-support-ai-meets-application-integration</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/customer-support-ai-meets-application-integration</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Customer Support is owning and driving end-to-end customer support experiences powered by AI. Read to find out how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a24c027bda61c9797c1244107749e253bbea24a8.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a24c027bda61c9797c1244107749e253bbea24a8.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1a24c027bda61c9797c1244107749e253bbea24a8.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Customer Support at SAP: Where Artificial Intelligence Meets Application Integration" src="./media_1a24c027bda61c9797c1244107749e253bbea24a8.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="customer-support-at-sap-where-artificial-intelligence-meets-application-integration">Customer Support at SAP: Where Artificial Intelligence Meets Application Integration</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>On April 1, 2024, SAP <a href="/2024/04/cloud-transformation-adoption-revolution-expectations-outcomes-meet">formed</a> Customer Services &#x26; Delivery – a new Board area that will focus on maximizing innovation adoption and customer value in the cloud.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>This is good news – not just for customers but also for the ecosystem. In recent months, SAP had already identified that when engineering teams deliver innovations, there is a corresponding need to provide customers with guidance on how they can swiftly adopt and consume innovation. Customer Services &#x26; Delivery was created to bring together the offerings that help customers tap the value of SAP’s integrated portfolio.</p>
  <p>By virtue of its function, the Customer Support organization fits into this strategic setup quite naturally. To learn more about how Customer Support is owning and driving end-to-end customer support experiences powered by AI, I met with Stefan Steinle, executive vice president and head of Customer Support, SAP SE.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Q: How would you describe the role of Customer Support in SAP’s success?</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><strong>A:</strong> Customer support is a differentiating factor among companies that are equally positioned in functional richness, usability, quality, deployability, or configurability. While signing up a new customer is considered a huge win, being able to delight and retain the customer is equally important.</p>
  <p><a href="https://support.sap.com/en/index.html">Support at SAP</a> has been singularly impactful in advancing SAP’s customer success stories by proactively responding to customer needs and building long-term relationships. In addition to helping customers solve day-to-day problems, we are business partners who proactively work with customers toward achieving their business goals.</p>
  <p>The Customer Support group encompasses much more than bug fixes. In addition to regular ticket resolutions, we use SAP Cloud ALM to help guide customers in application lifecycle management by enabling their transformation to the cloud and the operation of hybrid environments. We help customers help themselves through self-services and we proactively consult with our engineering teams to improve SAP products based on support-related feedback and learnings. Thanks to our support engineers, SAP has delivered over 1,000 improvements in the last 12 months.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Q: How is SAP’s AI story shaping up when it comes to Customer Support? What is the AI strategy for Customer Support?</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><strong>A:</strong> With our focus on value realization, the push to enhance support with AI has never been higher. To start with, we have invested in digitalizing mission-critical business processes with AI.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="revolutionize-your-business-with-generative-ai-innovations-from-sap">Revolutionize your business with generative AI innovations from SAP</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>There are three parts toward bringing these business processes into the fold of AI-powered offerings. With the help of SAP Signavio Process Transformation Suite, we can measure metrics around the customer’s business processes to gauge efficiency, bottlenecks, and opportunities for improvement. Alternatively, customers can use this as a blueprint to review these metrics themselves. The next layer delivers business transformational AI services. And finally, we have a platform that provides tools to support a closed-loop approach for AI innovation in services and support.</p>
  <p>Coming to the AI strategy for Customer Support, we believe that any innovations in AI must be in lockstep with application integration, meaning AI developments can only bring business value when they are infused and integrated into the applications used in a business process or scenario.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Q: In the context of Customer Support, could you give some examples of how AI brings business value?</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><strong>A:</strong> While the real-world applications are countless, we could broadly classify them into three groups.</p>
  <p>We use AI to correct – this means we use AI for the support experience, for personalization, and for data-driven decisions. We use AI to connect – here you find the platform, tools, and applications along customer touchpoints. We use AI to catalyze – this covers self-service, issue resolutions, and predictive and preventative support.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Q: How does SAP realize this?</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><strong>A:</strong> We do this by taking advantage of our AI development platform that can bring all the data of services and support into one place. This platform helps bring endless possibilities based on the unique needs of customers’ businesses. On our part, we ensure that we explore the power of AI across business contexts.</p>
  <p>By building AI models, we have the power to transform business in the way we want. We can plug these models into support systems and portals to extract the full value of AI in support. By collecting data and events from support systems and portals, we can even train AI models that can deliver value later. By processing the context and history of the customer, we can provide highly personalized support experiences – at runtime.</p>
  <p>I could go on, but at this point I would urge you to follow the Customer Support tracks at <a href="https://www.sap.com/events/sapphire.html">SAP Sapphire &#x26; ASUG Annual Conference Orlando on June 3–5, 2024</a>, to learn about the technologies and strategies that are shaping the future of Customer Support and business transformation. Be sure to bookmark your favorite topics from this guide: <a href="https://community.sap.com/t5/technology-blogs-by-sap/your-ultimate-guide-for-sap-sapphire-2024-orlando/ba-p/13699589">Your Ultimate Guide for SAP Sapphire Orlando in 2024</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Renuka Abraham is part of Customer Support at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="join-experts-speakers-and-peers-at-sap-sapphire-in-2024-to-explore-innovations-that-can-help-turn-your-visions-into-reality">Join experts, speakers, and peers at SAP Sapphire in 2024 to explore innovations that can help turn your visions into reality</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/events/sapphire.html">Register today</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Maximizing Efficiency: Integrating AI into Corporate Processes & Information Technology]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/benjamin-blau-interview-ai-corporate-processes-information-technology</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/benjamin-blau-interview-ai-corporate-processes-information-technology</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Chief Process and Information Officer Benjamin Blau discusses his new role, his organization, and the impact of AI. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Signavio Again Leads the 2024 SPARK Matrix™ for Digital Twin of an Organization]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/sap-signavio-leads-2024-spark-matrix-digital-twin-organization</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/sap-signavio-leads-2024-spark-matrix-digital-twin-organization</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Signavio is a Leader in the 2024 SPARK Matrix for Digital Twin of an Organization (DTO) for the fourth consecutive year. Read more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/business-process-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/business-process-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-twin</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-signavio</category>
            <category>product/sap-signavio-process-explorer</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[AI-Enabled Recruitment Is the Name of the Game for FC Bayern with SAP SuccessFactors]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/fc-bayern-sap-successfactors-ai-enabled-recruitment</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/fc-bayern-sap-successfactors-ai-enabled-recruitment</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[FC Bayern is leveraging the SAP SuccessFactors HCM suite and SAP Business AI capabilities to drive excellence on and off the pitch.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>industry/media: industry/sports-entertainment</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>industry/sports-entertainment</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Three Key Actions Procurement Can Take to Increase Supply Chain Visibility]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/three-actions-procurement-increase-supply-chain-transparency</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/three-actions-procurement-increase-supply-chain-transparency</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Procurement’s transparency into the supply chain is paramount for informed decision-making and mitigating risk. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-spend</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>topic/spend-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[IBM and SAP Plan to Expand Collaboration to Help Clients Become Next-Generation Enterprises with Generative AI]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/ibm-and-sap-generative-ai-new-value-generation-partnership</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/ibm-and-sap-generative-ai-new-value-generation-partnership</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New Value Generation partnership from SAP and IBM includes new generative AI capabilities and industry-specific cloud solutions. Read the news]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1aeeb46bbfcb4f664eb2a3c5eaebfbd24570cce9b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1aeeb46bbfcb4f664eb2a3c5eaebfbd24570cce9b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1aeeb46bbfcb4f664eb2a3c5eaebfbd24570cce9b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="IBM and SAP Plan to Expand Collaboration to Help Clients Become Next-Generation Enterprises with Generative AI" src="./media_1aeeb46bbfcb4f664eb2a3c5eaebfbd24570cce9b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="ibm-and-sap-plan-to-expand-collaboration-to-help-clients-become-next-generation-enterprises-with-generative-ai">IBM and SAP Plan to Expand Collaboration to Help Clients Become Next-Generation Enterprises with Generative AI</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>New Value Generation partnership initiative focused on delivering greater client productivity and innovation with new generative AI capabilities and industry-specific cloud solutions</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <table>
          <thead>
            <tr>
              <th>Text Large</th>
            </tr>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td>
                <p><strong><em>WALLDORF and ARMONK</em></strong></p>
                <hr>
                <p>IBM (NYSE: <a href="http://www.ibm.com/investor">IBM</a>) and <a href="http://sap.com">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced their vision for the next era of their collaboration, which includes new <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/generative-ai.html">generative AI</a> capabilities and industry-specific cloud solutions that can help clients unlock business value.</p>
              </td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="unlock-new-capabilities-with-generative-ai">Unlock new capabilities with generative AI</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/generative-ai.html">Learn how</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“IBM and SAP’s shared approach to generative AI, built on an open ecosystem, trust and purpose-built models, will help empower clients to optimize business outcomes,” said John Granger, Senior Vice President, IBM Consulting. “Our new Value Generation partnership initiative will enable clients to accelerate the path to innovation, competitive advantage and become a next generation enterprise through generative AI.”</p>
  <p>“It makes perfect sense to expand our partnership with IBM to help more customers accelerate their cloud journey leveraging RISE with SAP and realize the transformative benefits of generative AI for business in the cloud,” said Scott Russell, Chief Revenue Officer &#x26; Executive Board Member, Customer Success of SAP SE. “This expanded partnership will help more of our joint customers reach new heights by innovating through the cloud, data and business AI to grow and transform their businesses.”</p>
  <p><a href="https://www.ibm.com/consulting">IBM Consulting</a> and SAP aim to accelerate transformation enabled by RISE with SAP by supporting clients in the following key areas:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Next-Generation AI Business Processes</strong>: Together, the companies are exploring opportunities to build new generative AI capabilities for RISE with SAP and infuse AI into SAP business processes across industry-specific cloud solutions and line of business applications. Initially, IBM plans to extend AI capabilities across SAP’s portfolio of cloud solutions and applications, all of which are underpinned by SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP). This includes RISE with SAP, the GROW with SAP solution, financial solutions for the office of the CFO, supply chain management solutions, solutions for human capital management, SAP Customer Experience solutions and intelligent spend management solutions. IBM also plans to leverage SAP Signavio and SAP Business AI solutions to help define next-generation business processes through a proof-of-concept adoption program.</li>
    <li><strong>Next-Generation Industry Innovation</strong>: IBM and SAP plan to build intelligent industry use cases, enabled by data-driven insights, into end-to-end business processes to fuel next-generation industry innovation. These use cases will initially focus on the industrial manufacturing, consumer packaged goods (CPG), retail, defense, automotive and utilities industries. This includes IBM’s recent work with SAP to develop new AI solutions for the CPG and retail industries. As part of this initiative, IBM has begun the development of an extensive portfolio of over 100 AI solutions across industry, line-of-business and product delivery. In addition, IBM plans to develop prescriptive industry value maps that define next-generation business processes and opportunities for impact with AI. Clients will be able to access all of these new AI solutions through the global <a href="https://www.ibm.com/about/innovation-studio">IBM Innovation Studios</a> and <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/innovation.html">SAP Experience Center</a> sites.</li>
    <li><strong>Next-Generation Platform Architecture and Customer Adoption Approach</strong>: Next-generation enterprises require next-generation platform architectures and a modernized approach to customer adoption. Through the Value Generation partnership initiative, IBM intends to provide next-generation reference architectures that enable a clean core approach. To do this, IBM plans to leverage SAP BTP, SAP Signavio and LeanIX solutions. These new reference architectures will help define standards across data, process, systems and device integration, process orchestration and automation. IBM consultants supporting clients on SAP projects can also leverage IBM Consulting Advantage, IBM’s AI services platform, and its portfolio of proprietary methods, assets and Assistants to bring more repeatability and consistency to client delivery. With IBM Consulting Advantage, IBM consultants can transform the way they deliver SAP solutions to boost productivity and mitigate risk by leveraging generative AI to help complete tasks like generation of user stories, test scripts, training and change management content and code creation.</li>
    <li><strong>Next-Generation Ecosystem Expansion</strong>: IBM and SAP plan to partner around their respective employee network groups and “next-gen” communities, such as the business women’s networks at IBM and SAP, the <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/innovation/next-gen-innovation-platform/university-alliances.html">SAP University Alliances</a> program and the <a href="https://jobs.sap.com/content/Military-Veterans/?locale=en_US">Veterans to Work</a> program of SAP and Veterans at IBM to increase the SAP solutions experience in the consulting workforce and develop the next generation of talent. The companies also plan to explore new ways to collaborate on social impact programs, such as training at- risk youth in the IT sector and accelerating the integration of social businesses into global supply chains.</li>
    <li><strong>watsonx Planned Availability on the Generative AI Hub</strong>: IBM Granite Model Series are expected to be accessible for use across SAP’s portfolio of cloud solutions and applications – which is underpinned by the generative AI hub in SAP AI Core. The generative AI hub facilitates relevant, reliable and responsible business AI and provides instant access to a broad range of large language models (LLMs). This expands on IBM and SAP’s collaboration around <a href="https://newsroom.ibm.com/2023-05-02-SAP-to-Embed-IBM-Watson-Artificial-Intelligence-into-SAP-R-Solutions">embedding IBM Watson AI technology into SAP solutions</a>. To further highlight watsonx.ai Granite capabilities, IBM Consulting plans to build extensions using the model on the generative AI hub for select customers.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>This initiative will build on the companies’ over 50-year collaboration based on deep technology, industry and domain expertise and demonstrates the two organizations’ joint commitment to continue to evolve to put clients first and meet market demand.</p>
  <p>IBM Consulting accelerates business transformation for our clients through hybrid cloud and AI technologies, leveraging our open ecosystem of partners. With deep industry and business expertise spanning strategy, experience design, technology, and operations, we have become the trusted partner to the world’s most innovative and valuable companies, helping modernize and secure their most complex systems. Our 160,000 consultants embrace an open way of working and apply our proven, collaborative engagement model, IBM Garage, to scale ideas into outcomes. As the only major global systems integrator inside a technology company, we don’t just advise – we invent and build what’s next together with our clients. Find out more at <a href="http://ibm.com/consulting">IBM.com/consulting</a>.</p>
  <p>To learn more about the Value Generation partnership initiative, visit <a href="https://www.ibm.com/info/sap-value-generation">ibm.com/info/sap-value-generation</a>.</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>About IBM</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>IBM is a leading provider of global hybrid cloud and AI, and consulting expertise. We help clients in more than 175 countries capitalize on insights from their data, streamline business processes, reduce costs and gain the competitive edge in their industries. More than 4,000 government and corporate entities in critical infrastructure areas such as financial services, telecommunications and healthcare rely on IBM’s hybrid cloud platform and Red Hat OpenShift to effect their digital transformations quickly, efficiently and securely. IBM’s breakthrough innovations in AI, quantum computing, industry-specific cloud solutions and consulting deliver open and flexible options to our clients. All of this is backed by IBM’s commitment to trust, transparency, responsibility, inclusivity and service.</p>
  <p>Visit <a href="http://www.ibm.com/">www.ibm.com</a> for more information.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>About SAP</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As a global leader in enterprise applications and business AI, SAP (NYSE:SAP) stands at the nexus of business and technology. For over 50 years, organizations have trusted SAP to bring out their best by uniting business-critical operations spanning finance, procurement, HR, supply chain, and customer experience. For more information, visit <a href="http://www.sap.com">www.sap.com</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Note to editors:</strong><br>To preview and download broadcast-standard stock footage and press photos digitally, please visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/photos">www.sap.com/photos</a>. On this platform, you can find high resolution material for your media channels.</p>
  <p><strong>For customers interested in learning more about SAP products:</strong><br>Global Customer Center: +49 180 534-34-24<br>United States Only: 1 (800) 872-1SAP (1-800-872-1727)</p>
  <p><strong>For more information, press only:</strong><br>Scott Malinowski, SAP, +1 (781) 852-3822, <a href="mailto:scott.malinowski@sap.com">scott.malinowski@sap.com</a><br><a href="mailto:SAP%20Press%20Room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a><br>Jamee Nelson, IBM, <a href="mailto:jamee.nelson@ibm.com">jamee.nelson@ibm.com</a></p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-the-power-of-sap-partners-who-drive-customer-success-delivering-trusted-advice-and-deep-product-knowledge">Learn more about the power of SAP partners, who drive customer success, delivering trusted advice and deep product knowledge</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/partners.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>This document contains forward-looking statements, which are predictions, projections, or other statements about future events. These statements are based on current expectations, forecasts, and assumptions that are subject to risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results and outcomes to materially differ. Additional information regarding these risks and uncertainties may be found in our filings with the Securities and Exchange Commission, including but not limited to the risk factors section of SAP’s 2023 Annual Report on Form 20-F.<br>© 2024 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.<br>Please consider our <a href="https://www.sap.com/corporate/en/legal/privacy.html">privacy policy</a>. If you received this press release in your e-mail and you wish to unsubscribe to our mailing list please contact <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a> and write Unsubscribe in the subject line.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/ibm</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Insights from SAP MaxAttention Summit 2024]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/sap-maxattention-summit-2024</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/sap-maxattention-summit-2024</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[At SAP MaxAttention Summit 2024, attendees saw insightful keynotes and informative sessions on important topics. Learn more about the event.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a6ba5cbc59466e687fdce42c949f974636cc5961.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a6ba5cbc59466e687fdce42c949f974636cc5961.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1a6ba5cbc59466e687fdce42c949f974636cc5961.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Insights from SAP MaxAttention Summit 2024" src="./media_1a6ba5cbc59466e687fdce42c949f974636cc5961.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="insights-from-sap-maxattention-summit-2024">Insights from SAP MaxAttention Summit 2024</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>At SAP MaxAttention Summit 2024, attendees received in-depth information about SAP Business AI, clean core with SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP), updates on enterprise architecture, and more.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-maxattention-premium-level-engagement-and-personalized-service">SAP MaxAttention: Premium-level engagement and personalized service</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/services-support/premium-support/maxattention.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The event was held April 23-25 in Heidelberg, Germany, and customers on-site experienced insightful keynotes and sessions from SAP Executive Board Members Thomas Saueressig and Muhammad Alam, as well as SAP Chief Artificial Intelligence Officer Philipp Herzig and other experts.</p>
  <p><a href="https://events.sap.com/sap-maxattention-summit/en/speaker">SAP and customer speakers</a> presented important updates on topics that also included Business Transformation as a Service, RISE with SAP, and SAP BTP. Attendees also benefited from interactive “eXpert eXchange” sessions and opportunities to network and share their experiences and best practices.</p>
  <p>The SAP MaxAttention program offers premium-level engagement and personalized service for customers to move business-wide transformational change from boardroom plans to business reality with a tailored, premium experience. Program participants get premium access to trusted SAP experts, tools, and methodologies that can help deliver expected outcomes successfully with SAP solutions.</p>
  <h2 id="replays">Replays</h2>
  <p>Watch the replays to see more:</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Thomas Saueressig’s Keynote</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_178255e3659f21f565eabcbac4e43ebe78f781309.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_178255e3659f21f565eabcbac4e43ebe78f781309.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_178255e3659f21f565eabcbac4e43ebe78f781309.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Innovate to Deliver: The Journey to Business Transformation with SAP" src="./media_178255e3659f21f565eabcbac4e43ebe78f781309.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://youtu.be/pbJr7apkyik?si=CHU6OedRF23m56-D">Innovate to Deliver: The Journey to Business Transformation with SAP</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Muhammad Alam’s Keynote</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1bbc78a928fe6754f20ff39c432c291de3e19223c.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1bbc78a928fe6754f20ff39c432c291de3e19223c.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1bbc78a928fe6754f20ff39c432c291de3e19223c.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Thriving Through Uncertainty with SAP’s End-to-End Portfolio Strategy" src="./media_1bbc78a928fe6754f20ff39c432c291de3e19223c.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://youtu.be/6pHCx2pZ_4g?si=pikTl3MmUMabZ_jL">Thriving Through Uncertainty with SAP’s End-to-End Portfolio Strategy</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Philipp Herzig’s Executive Session</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1676dfa8c313d07603d26caf19b4994a98b400a61.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1676dfa8c313d07603d26caf19b4994a98b400a61.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1676dfa8c313d07603d26caf19b4994a98b400a61.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="The Future is now - Embrace it with SAP Business AI" src="./media_1676dfa8c313d07603d26caf19b4994a98b400a61.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://youtu.be/GHLRyjmMtvQ?si=C4ZylXj-CDzV2iho">The Future is now – Embrace it with SAP Business AI</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-maxattention</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-maxattention-summit</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Defining the AI Opportunity for SAP and Our Partners]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/sap-partners-ai-opportunity</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/sap-partners-ai-opportunity</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP and partners are seizing the AI opportunity, providing new solutions backed by expertise, business process knowledge, and SAP system data.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a591bef8055a8ff0903470a566a95b31994c8267.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a591bef8055a8ff0903470a566a95b31994c8267.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1a591bef8055a8ff0903470a566a95b31994c8267.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Defining the AI Opportunity for SAP and Our Partners" src="./media_1a591bef8055a8ff0903470a566a95b31994c8267.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="defining-the-ai-opportunity-for-sap-and-our-partners">Defining the AI Opportunity for SAP and Our Partners</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Artificial intelligence is by far the disruptor of the decade. It can search, summarize, and analyze vast data stores, putting data-driven insights at employees’ fingertips in a matter of minutes. It can also generate content, anything from text to software code, streamlining workflows and saving precious time and money.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>And that’s just the surface. We are still learning just how far reaching the implications could be in the workplace.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-business-ai-revolutionary-technology-real-world-results">SAP Business AI: Revolutionary technology. Real-world results.</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As we explore this new realm and AI’s vast potential, SAP has adjusted its strategy with the goal of becoming not only the leading enterprise application provider but also the No. 1 business AI company. The foundation is now available with SAP Business AI that offers SAP customers a reliable, relevant, and responsible AI solution portfolio.</p>
  <p>A key element of that strategy is leveraging SAP partners’ expertise. The trusted relationships our partners have developed with our joint customers are essential to communicating the value of AI solutions from SAP and finding the best SAP products to meet their business objectives. It also poses a great opportunity for partners to expand their business.</p>
  <p>But first, let’s take a step back and explore why SAP is best positioned to deliver on the business AI opportunity.</p>
  <h2 id="saps-ai-advantage">SAP’s AI Advantage</h2>
  <p><strong>Deep Business Process Knowledge</strong><br>Before AI can make operations faster, data-driven, and more effective, organizations must optimize business processes. SAP brings a deep understanding of business processes to AI applications, enabling solutions that orchestrate workflows, data sharing, and automation for the greatest efficiency and productivity.</p>
  <p><strong>SAP Data</strong> AI solutions require data to train their algorithms to provide accurate, relevant, real-world outputs. SAP can draw on business data from thousands of customer systems across the value chain, helping to address our customers’ challenges and drive their digital transformation.</p>
  <p><strong>Focus on Application Creation</strong> SAP is partnering with technology providers to make the most of the AI opportunity by creating value with new applications. For example, large language models (LLMs) will become solution differentiators. LLMs perform a range of natural language processing tasks. Combining LLMs with AI solutions automates insight delivery, freeing users from the need to wait for help from their IT or data science departments. It allows companies to focus on data insights, rather than devoting focus to the technology that produces them.</p>
  <p><strong>Strong Partner Ecosystem</strong><br>SAP recognizes that it cannot reach the full addressable market alone. That is why our more than 25,500 partner ecosystem is a huge advantage when offering business AI solutions. Working together, we can drive innovation, accelerate AI road maps, and expand AI capabilities beyond its own limitations.</p>
  <p>I cannot underscore enough how important that fourth component is to our AI strategy. It is a linchpin to our success. That’s why we must ensure we are creating win-win scenarios for our partners that benefit us both for the long term.</p>
  <h2 id="partner-opportunities">Partner Opportunities</h2>
  <p>While AI offers a range of benefits to SAP customers, it also represents a significant business opportunity for SAP partners. As a part of the SAP ecosystem, partners can provide advanced functionality out of the box with embedded AI capabilities within SAP applications. They must also take advantage of the virtually endless opportunities that AI offers regardless of the chosen SAP partner business model:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Sell:</strong> Partners that resell SAP solutions can leverage the embedded AI portfolio from SAP to accelerate RISE with SAP and GROW with SAP deals. Sell partners can also enhance the appeal of the cloud with AI capabilities exclusive to SAP cloud solutions and enlarge deals with AI units from SAP required for premium AI capabilities.</li>
    <li><strong>Service:</strong> Service partners can drive adoption of SAP’s AI portfolio and custom AI capabilities built on SAP by bundling them with services and support. This approach enables customers to gain value through customized generative AI use cases built on the foundation of SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP), including the generative AI hub, and accelerate their cloud migrations and business transformation, backed by partners’ expertise.</li>
    <li><strong>Innovate:</strong> Partners also have the opportunity to develop innovative AI solutions and extensions to enhance the SAP portfolio. Partners can build customer-specific and repeatable use cases with AI services from SAP on SAP BTP and augment customer business processes.</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="take-the-next-step">Take the Next Step</h2>
  <p>Ready to expand your partnership with SAP to build on the AI opportunity? <a href="https://partneredge.sap.com/en/products/aic/about.html">Explore our AI portfolio</a> and visit <a href="https://partneredge.sap.com/en/partnership/manage/expand.html">SAP Partner Portal site to learn more</a>. If you’re not currently an SAP partner, there’s never been a better time to explore the benefits of becoming a part of the SAP ecosystem.</p>
  <p>If you’re ready to start your SAP partnership journey and provide businesses in your market with reliable, effective AI solutions, <a href="https://www.sap.com/partners/partner-program.html">get started here today</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Karl Fahrbach is chief partner officer at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="win-more-customers-and-grow-revenue-with-the-help-of-saps-award-winning-partner-program-and-portfolio-of-industry-leading-solutions">Win more customers and grow revenue with the help of SAP’s award-winning partner program and portfolio of industry-leading solutions</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/partners/partner-program.html">Explore how</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Path to AI with Clean Core]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/the-path-to-ai-with-clean-core</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/the-path-to-ai-with-clean-core</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP's Claudio Muruzabal shares about his Customer Advisory role and how SAP customers are winning with intelligent technology, like AI.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1df14be7df416024e279a8fbc6ac26cd297e9f468.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1df14be7df416024e279a8fbc6ac26cd297e9f468.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1df14be7df416024e279a8fbc6ac26cd297e9f468.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="The Path to AI with Clean Core" src="./media_1df14be7df416024e279a8fbc6ac26cd297e9f468.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="the-path-to-ai-with-clean-core">The Path to AI with Clean Core</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>From cloud to generative AI, the list of new and emerging technologies continues to grow in our era of digital intelligence. Yet it’s also the era of inflation, geopolitical tension, supply chain disruption, and countless other challenges. How are businesses supposed to make sense of all these technologies – let alone transform their businesses with them – while simply trying to survive during such a challenging time?</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>That’s where Claudio Muruzabal, chief business officer of SAP SE, steps in.</p>
  <p>Muruzabal is responsible for supporting the Customer Advisory, Solution Area and Services Sales, and Customer Success Management &#x26; Engagement teams at SAP. For more than eight years, he has played an important role in understanding not only an increasingly complex technology landscape but also how businesses actually use the technology at their disposal. He supports teams that help bring SAP customers closer to their goals by leveraging SAP solutions. This begins with advising customers through honest conversations about how they can apply the intelligent capabilities now included in many SAP solutions, such as generative AI.</p>
  <p>I sat down with Muruzabal to find out more about his role, how SAP customers are winning with intelligent technology, and the growing impact of customer success management at SAP.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Q: AI is all the rage today, so let’s start there. What are the biggest opportunities for businesses to use AI?</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><strong>Muruzabal</strong>: Opportunity is everywhere for <a href="/topics/ai">AI</a>. And it’s bigger than just automating processes to increase efficiency, which is what was talked about for the longest time. At SAP, we’re seeing how AI can support relevant business processes to instill innovation and competitiveness. While many players in the industry are focused on developing AI engines and large language models, we are focused on accelerating business value through generative AI. I could talk all day about how AI is transforming data analytics and decision-support systems as well as supply chain optimization, predictive maintenance, and HR. Every day we are discovering new opportunities for customers to leapfrog their competition when they combine the power of generative AI with the context of their business data and processes.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>What are some examples of how SAP customers are using AI, and what value have they realized so far?</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-business-ai-revolutionary-technology-real-world-results">SAP Business AI: Revolutionary technology, real-world results</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>There’s really so much to get excited about when it comes to how our customers are using the AI capabilities included with their SAP solutions. Across industries, workers everywhere are using natural language to instantly get the data insights they need using the SAP Analytics Cloud solution. I like how busy recruiters can tap into generative AI with SAP SuccessFactors solutions to create compelling job descriptions and interview questions in less time. Joule, our AI assistant and copilot, can support end users in getting the right answers on how to get the most of our cloud solutions. With Joule already embedded across the portfolio – generally available in SAP SuccessFactors HCM, SAP Start, and SAP S/4HANA Cloud – we are all excited about the opportunities for our customers.</p>
  <p>All industries can get this unique value, including professional soccer clubs FC Bayern Munich and Hertha BSC that are using a scouting prototype powered by AI to find and develop the next generation of star athletes.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>AI can solve a lot of problems, but what about the underlying foundational technology stack companies have today? What conversations are you having with businesses about their technology investments?</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Early on in our conversations with customers, it’s important to understand how businesses can set up their core, foundational enterprise technology platform running in the cloud. This is critical to establish a journey of innovation including <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence.html">SAP Business AI</a>. Coming back to the foundation, many of our customers have built numerous modifications on top of their core ERP. In order to build a true cloud operating model – essential to embrace innovation including AI – it is critical to move to a clean core model. This means that any modification to the ERP functionality offered by SAP is built outside of the core, using extensibility solutions. This is not a technical topic only. Although clean core contributes to the cost-efficient operation of the platform, the true contribution is bringing flexibility and adaptability to the business, converting the cloud operating model into a unique “innovation as a service” platform.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>What makes SAP unique and stand out to customers with its value proposition?</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP has the unique value of being the global leader in best of suite solutions built with more than 50 years of industry knowledge and ERP technology leadership. On top of this, our leading “best of breed” solutions, such as in HCM, customer experience, intelligent spend and business network, and more, can provide the best functionality and the right integration into the core. Only SAP can offer this value proposition. When we combined this with the cloud operating model – widely adopted by our RISE with SAP customers – we provide exponential value for the innovation as a service proposition.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>How can customers get the most from their investments? What kind of support is there to help them transform and innovate?</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Customer success management is essential in the cloud. It is the end-to-end engagement with our customers, from advisory to sales execution to onboarding, adoption, and consumption. We provide the tools, assets, and content to help accelerate adoption and consumption so as to maximize the value from first use of the solution to full and future use. SAP Preferred Success services can accelerate the time to value even more. To support this motion, deep <a href="/2024/02/driving-customers-business-outcomes-telemetry">telemetry</a> being built into our cloud solutions allows customers and our customer success management leaders to better understand how the solutions are being used while identifying opportunities to expand usage.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Where do advisory services fit into the customer journey?</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Customer advisory services might be the most essential part of the journey with a customer. Successful projects start with the right business case definition, anchored in the best understanding of the industry and business of our customers. With that in mind, our Customer Advisory teams support building the right technical solutions that can support an enterprise architecture. This is the first step in moving in the right direction of building the cloud operating model.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-sap-news-on-linkedin">Connect with SAP News on LinkedIn</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news">Stay up-to-date</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-engagement</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-success</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Signavio Is a Leader in the 2024 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Process Mining Platforms]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/sap-signavio-a-leader-2024-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-process-mining-platforms</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/sap-signavio-a-leader-2024-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-process-mining-platforms</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In the 2024 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Process Mining, SAP Signavio has again been recognized as a Leader. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_138b3ef0b5b24b564b18da25ef3b2cde982bba0f8.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_138b3ef0b5b24b564b18da25ef3b2cde982bba0f8.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_138b3ef0b5b24b564b18da25ef3b2cde982bba0f8.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Signavio Is a Leader in the 2024 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Process Mining Platforms" src="./media_138b3ef0b5b24b564b18da25ef3b2cde982bba0f8.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-signavio-is-a-leader-in-the-2024-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-process-mining-platforms">SAP Signavio Is a Leader in the 2024 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Process Mining Platforms</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>In the 2024 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Process Mining, SAP Signavio has once again been recognized as a Leader in the market based on Completeness of Vision and Ability to Execute.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="complimentary-copy-2024-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-process-mining-platforms">Complimentary copy: 2024 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Process Mining Platforms</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.signavio.com/downloads/analyst-reports/2024-gartner-magic-quadrant-process-mining/">Download yours here</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>This is the second year in a row that SAP Signavio has been positioned as a Leader in the report. We believe that this positioning implies that SAP Signavio is a key driver for SAP’s growth and long-term strategy.</p>
  <p>According to the Gartner Magic Quadrant research methodology, “Leaders execute well against their current vision and are well positioned for tomorrow.”</p>
  <p>Our solutions solve today’s real and diverse customer use cases — operational excellence, compliance, automation, transformation, etc.– and recognizes that we have a compelling vision for a future in which process automation and process AI open up new opportunities for our customers and partners.</p>
  <p>SAP Signavio continues to focus on ensuring the long-term success of all of our customers and partners.</p>
  <h2 id="revenue-nsw">Revenue NSW</h2>
  <p>In the Australian state of New South Wales, the tax collected by Revenue NSW accounts for more than 35% of finances, helping fund essential services, from healthcare to education and policing.</p>
  <p>With a vision to be the world’s most innovative and customer-centric revenue agency, Revenue NSW set out with a very specific objective: it wanted to analyze cases in which clients had overpaid land tax to identify why these overpayments occur and what experience clients received when obtaining refunds. This analysis would not only help reduce overpayment volumes and improve the client experience, but also enable the agency to work more efficiently for its diverse stakeholders.</p>
  <p>“As part of our Aspire 2032 strategy, our vision is to be the world’s most innovative and customer-centric revenue collection agency,” shared Jocelyn Yem, director of Strategy and Innovation at Revenue NSW.”‘Embrace Innovation’ is one of our strategic focus areas, where we can respond to our customers’ needs by embedding a culture of continuous improvement. SAP Signavio Process Intelligence has helped us achieve our first stage in this journey.”</p>
  <p>“SAP Signavio Process Intelligence has painted a clear picture of why clients pay too much land tax and how we can process refunds smoothly, along with a detailed road map to help us put these insights into action,” confirmed Sabrina Bazouni, director of Land Tax at Revenue NSW.</p>
  <h2 id="fujitsu-limited">Fujitsu Limited</h2>
  <p>Recognizing the wide-ranging effect of business process transformation solutions, Fujitsu Limited has embraced SAP Signavio solutions across its operations and portfolio.</p>
  <p>At one of its manufacturing plants in Japan, Fujitsu used the SAP Signavio Process Intelligence solution to gather process execution data directly from the shop floor into the continuous improvement model the company had been using for many years. Integrating process data into the Kaizen discussions delivered never-before-seen insights, which helped the company further optimize its shop-floor processes and transform their Kaizen from traditional to digital, using process mining to generate data-driven insights.</p>
  <p>This firsthand experience of the solutions has also allowed Fujitsu to enrich its customer offerings with new frameworks, insights, and tools that can help customers realign their organizations and make changes at speed.</p>
  <p>Having seen the potential of SAP Signavio solutions, Fujitsu now plans to extend its use both internally and externally. One such planned initiative involves combining the concepts of the digital twin on an organization and the intelligent enterprise, using business process transformation solutions as the mechanism of change.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Download a <a href="https://www.signavio.com/downloads/analyst-reports/2024-gartner-magic-quadrant-process-mining/">complimentary copy of the report here</a>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Dee Houchen is global head of Market Impact for SAP Signavio.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="optimize-and-transform-business-processes-fast-and-at-scale">Optimize and transform business processes fast and at scale</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-process-transformation.html">Learn how</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Gartner, Magic Quadrant for Process Mining Platforms, Marc Kerremans, David Sugden, Nick Duffy, 29 April 2024</p>
  <p>GARTNER is a registered trademark and service mark of Gartner, Inc. and/or its affiliates in the U.S. and internationally, and MAGIC QUADRANT is a registered trademark of Gartner, Inc. and/or its affiliates and are used herein with permission. All rights reserved. Gartner does not endorse any vendor, product or service depicted in its research publications, and does not advise technology users to select only those vendors with the highest ratings or other designation. Gartner research publications consist of the opinions of Gartner’s research organization and should not be construed as statements of fact. Gartner disclaims all warranties, expressed or implied, with respect to this research, including any warranties of merchantability or fitness for a particular purpose.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/business-process-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/magic-quadrant</category>
            <category>news-tag/process-mining</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-signavio</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Esports Powerhouse Team Liquid Wins Big with SAP Business AI]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/esports-powerhouse-team-liquid-wins-big-with-sap-business-ai</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/esports-powerhouse-team-liquid-wins-big-with-sap-business-ai</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With a generative AI model trained on SAP AI Core, Team Liquid is maximizing their chances at the League of Legends Championship Series.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/esports</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-sponsorships</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hannover Messe: What Can AI Do for Manufacturing?]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/hannover-messe-ai-manufacturing</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/hannover-messe-ai-manufacturing</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[At Hannover Messe 2024, SAP and its partners showed how they are embedding AI to help companies achieve excellence in manufacturing.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/catena-x</category>
            <category>news-tag/hannover-messe</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-x</category>
            <category>product/sap-digital-manufacturing</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>