<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/sap-anz/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Flexibility Is Non-Negotiable When It Comes to the Employee Experience]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/02/flexibility-non-negotiable-employee-experience</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/02/flexibility-non-negotiable-employee-experience</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Leading experts discuss how organizations are reinventing flexibility as a core part of transforming the employee experience.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_104d736bffd16956b265815dcd608601c0138cc0d.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_104d736bffd16956b265815dcd608601c0138cc0d.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_104d736bffd16956b265815dcd608601c0138cc0d.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Flexibility Is Non-Negotiable When It Comes to the Employee Experience" src="./media_104d736bffd16956b265815dcd608601c0138cc0d.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="flexibility-is-non-negotiable-when-it-comes-to-the-employee-experience">Flexibility Is Non-Negotiable When It Comes to the Employee Experience</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>The future of work is unfolding as we speak and it’s more flexible than we could have ever imagined when the global <a href="/topics/covid-19">pandemic</a> hit two years ago. A recent Mercer <a href="https://www.mercer.com.au/what-we-do/workforce-rewards-and-talent/rewards-and-employee-experience/salary-benchmarking-surveys/au-benefits-hr-policies-practices.html">research</a> report found that almost 60% of organizations in Australia were reinventing flexibility as a core part of transforming the employee experience.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“Employee benefits around health and well-being are a major topic within the Australian culture because people in this country expect more work-life balance,” said Chi Tran, head of Workforce Market Insights and Data at Mercer. “Organizations want to make sure they have the flexible programs in place to attract and retain people. We see well-being benefits becoming increasingly non-negotiable as a core component of an organization’s ability to deliver an effective employee experience.”</p>
  <p>The same study also showed that 97% of organizations had a health and wellness benefits program in place, and employees were more attracted to organizations that have a sense of purpose.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="workforce-trends-2022-how-companies-are-building-digital-dream-teams">Workforce Trends 2022: How Companies Are Building Digital Dream Teams</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2022/02/workforce-trends-2022">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="pandemic-puts-employee-wellness-at-center-stage">Pandemic Puts Employee Wellness at Center Stage</h2>
  <p>Like everything else, the pandemic has fast-tracked the future of work. Another Mercer poll revealed that respondents from one in two companies in Asia-Pacific saw indications of worsening employee burnout and pandemic fatigue. As a result, Tran said many organizations are taking a risk-based approach with data-driven prevention programs to reduce insurance premiums while addressing worker well-being, particularly mental health.</p>
  <p>“In addition to keeping responsive employee assistance programs in place, many companies are shifting to proactive strategies that bring people in with virtual wellness workshops on a more regular basis,” she said. “There’s no one-size-fits-all program. Organizations need to listen to their different employee cohorts, investing in benefits that will resonate with everyone’s unique needs.”</p>
  <h2 id="personalized-flexible-benefit-programs">Personalized, Flexible Benefit Programs</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="turn-employees-into-ambassadors-with-employee-experience-management">Turn employees into ambassadors with employee experience management</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm/employee-experience-management.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>One example is SAP’s global “Pledge to Flex” program designed to fit every​ employee’s ​role, style, and location while continuing to meet business and customer needs. At <a href="/australia/2021/12/01/lets-talk-how-to-find-and-keep-great-staff">SAP ANZ</a>, where the pandemic’s impact was nascent in 2020 but revved up through 2021, the company established a framework for employees to consider when determining their work style preferences.</p>
  <p>“We want people empowered to find the ideal working style that will meet their individual, team, and customer success responsibilities,” said Debbie Rigger, head of HR at SAP Australia and New Zealand “We have parents with young children or other caregiving responsibilities. We have early talent working at home out of their bedroom. We want them to ask themselves, ‘What is my role? Who are my stakeholders and what are their expectations? What family-related and other personal commitments do I have? Given all these factors, what do I need to do my best work?'”</p>
  <p>Looking ahead, Rigger expects to see the unexpected, meaning employee requests for things HR has never thought of before. In the meantime, the SAP ANZ team as doubled down on creating a safe in-person reentry experience for employees based on legislation and government guidance, as well as the company’s global policies.</p>
  <p>“This has been more of a re-education for employees about the options they have and being transparent about what’s possible when it comes to working schedules that span full-time, part-time, compressed hours, job sharing, and even geographies,” said Rigger. “Given the border closures, people have been interested in traveling within the country while also being able to work remotely for a specified time period. Through candid conversations with managers, employees determine how, when, and where they work based on their personal circumstances and the needs of the business.”</p>
  <h2 id="organizations-adjust-employee-experience-to-the-new-normal">Organizations Adjust Employee Experience to the New Normal</h2>
  <p>Flexible working practices are likely here to stay. <a href="https://www.idc.com/getdoc.jsp?containerId=US47290521">IDC</a> analysts predicted that by 2023, digital transformation and business volatility would drive 70% of G2000 organizations to deploy remote or hybrid-first work models, redefining work processes and engaging diverse talent pools. The beauty of being flexible is obvious during these times of rapid change and market uncertainty.</p>
  <p>Rigger said SAP ANZ was already exploring how to make the most of the company’s office spaces in compliance with local legislation guidance. Hybrid work models might demand new spacial configurations, not just for social distancing but for fundamentally changed workplace norms. From impermanent individual workstations to virtual tools that let people effectively brainstorm when they aren’t in the same room, organizations need to create that employee community again, bringing people back into a space so they can continue to be more productive.</p>
  <p>Companies still struggling with remote versus in-person work mandates are missing the point about addressing the opportunities the global pandemic continues to reveal. Innovative organizations will jump at this historic inflection point to redefine the future of work with benefits for both organizations and their employees.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Follow me @smgaler.</em><br><em>This also appeared on <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2022/01/25/flexibility-is-non-negotiable-when-it-comes-to-the-australian-employee-experience/?sh=ec159d522f5e">SAP BrandVoice on Forbes.</a></em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/future-of-work</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-anz</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Without More Flexible Hours and Locations, 54% of Workers to Quit]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/02/without-flexibility-54-percent-to-quit</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/02/without-flexibility-54-percent-to-quit</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Global talent marketplaces help business and HR leaders head off tech worker shortages and power massive growth from digitalization.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1de65b4f8c903741801eae2d7b08e181383eefa42.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1de65b4f8c903741801eae2d7b08e181383eefa42.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1de65b4f8c903741801eae2d7b08e181383eefa42.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Without More Flexible Hours and Locations, 54% of Workers to Quit" src="./media_1de65b4f8c903741801eae2d7b08e181383eefa42.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="without-more-flexible-hours-and-locations-54-of-workers-to-quit">Without More Flexible Hours and Locations, 54% of Workers to Quit</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>On the cusp of economic growth fueled by a huge wave of digitalization, organizations in Australia and New Zealand (ANZ) are transforming talent management strategies to find the tech workers they need.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>A recent EY study found that nine out of 10 respondents worldwide, including workers from ANZ, wanted flexibility in their working hours and location. Fifty-four percent of employees were prepared to quit if they weren’t offered some form of flexibility. According to Thomas Barlow, head of SAP Fieldglass Centre of Excellence, Australia and New Zealand, the talent challenge is acute when it comes to tech employees.</p>
  <p>“Technology permeates every part of an organization, requiring people with new skills in areas like data science, artificial intelligence (AI), machine learning, blockchain, robotics, and the Internet of Things (IoT). Organizations need to build a global workforce that meets digitalized business demands,” said Barlow. “Workers with specialized expertise typically operate in a highly flexible, agile way. They’re likelier to be more mobile, in charge of managing their own learning experiences and careers. They also may not be located nearby.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="put-employees-at-the-heart-of-everything-you-do-with-sap-successfactors-software">Put employees at the heart of everything you do with SAP SuccessFactors software</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="complete-talent-pool-data-creates-business-resilience">Complete Talent Pool Data Creates Business Resilience</h2>
  <p>The latest data from the <a href="https://www.abs.gov.au/">Australian Bureau of Statistics</a> revealed how <a href="/covid-19">pandemic</a> lockdowns have accelerated the skills shortage. <a href="https://www.businessinsider.com.au/australia-skills-shortage-wage-growth-2021-6">Business Insider Australia</a> reported one in four Australian businesses were struggling to find suitable staff to fill job vacancies. In a recent COVID-19 Resilience Ranking from <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/graphics/covid-resilience-ranking/">Bloomberg</a>, Australia dropped 21 points compared to over 50 other major economies worldwide. To meet this workforce challenge, leaders are turning to connected data.</p>
  <p>“As companies build more flexible, cross-border workforces, they need full transparency of all employees, including permanent and external workers,” said Barlow. “With complete workforce data, companies are better prepared to identify and deploy the right people with the right skills to support growth forecasts, or pivot quickly in case of unexpected disruptions like the pandemic.”</p>
  <p>AI-based talent pools like <a href="https://store.sap.com/dcp/en/product/display-0000056483_live_v1">WillHire</a> have emerged to help organizations quickly match open positions with pre-qualified candidates from the global external labor pool. Integrated with <a href="https://www.fieldglass.com/">SAP Fieldglass solutions</a> and available on <a href="https://store.sap.com/dcp/en/">SAP Store</a>, WillHire curates emerging talent who have the niche skills that support digital transformation.</p>
  <h2 id="global-people-strategy-is-core-to-business-execution">Global People Strategy Is Core to Business Execution</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="five-workplace-norms-innovative-hxm-leaders-are-replacing-right-now">Five Workplace Norms Innovative HXM Leaders Are Replacing Right Now</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/11/five-workplace-norms-innovative-hxm-leaders-are-replacing">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Historical talent strategies distinguished between permanent full-time employees and external workers who were typically hired to pitch in as a short-term business fix. With the advent of global marketplaces, talent strategies have transformed to flex with changing business demands.</p>
  <p>“Companies need to embrace fluidity, looking at talent from the perspective of business results, as opposed to permanent versus contract workers,” said Marc Havercroft, global chief customer officer at SAP SuccessFactors. “For example, organizations using <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm.html">SAP SuccessFactors solutions</a> and SAP Fieldglass solutions can easily see how many people work for the company irrespective of an end date on their contract. Data reveals where people are, what skills they have, and their work quality over time. Organizations can quickly identify gaps and find the additional specialists with the latest skills anywhere in the world.”</p>
  <p>One SAP customer, an established ANZ-based financial services organization, needed to digitally transform to attract the next generation of customers. Using both SAP SuccessFactors and SAP Fieldglass solutions, leaders sourced external tech experts to build digital services, pairing them with existing employees who shared their business knowledge while gaining new skills.</p>
  <p>At the other end of the spectrum, a native digital banking startup in ANZ relied on both SAP solutions to help guide talent investments in business specialists with go-to-market and customer upselling and engagement capabilities. These experts rounded out the existing team’s tech-centric skills.</p>
  <h2 id="employee-experience-attracts-global-talent-pool">Employee Experience Attracts Global Talent Pool</h2>
  <p>The same EY study found that worldwide, 72% of respondents believed remotely working would likely have a negative impact on their career opportunities. That percentage was higher (82%) among employees in Asia-Pacific. With greater visibility across the entire workforce, companies can create a strong employee experience in a hybrid ‘work-from-anywhere’ world.</p>
  <p>“Full transparency into an organization’s workforce capabilities and recruitment needs allows leaders to adopt a continuous learning culture with benefits to the business and employees,” said Havercroft. “People want to learn, making their work enjoyable and career secure. They want to be valued globally for their skills and knowledge, which is probably the biggest benefit of a global talent marketplace.”</p>
  <p>Business resiliency demands new talent management strategies to match recruitment programs with forecasted growth opportunities, factoring in skills and roles that might not exist yet but are surely on the horizon. For example, SAP’s recent acquisition of <a href="/2021/08/sap-acquires-swooptalent-intellectual-property-to-boost-talent-data-intelligence">SwoopTalent’s IP</a>, an AI-based talent data platform, will allow companies to explore ‘what-if’ scenarios, combining real-world total workforce data to improve ROI on talent investments and other decisions as businesses evolve. Massive growth from digitalization is all well and good. Just make sure you have the business and tech experts on hand to power it.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Follow me @smgaler.</em><br><em>This also appeared on <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2021/10/05/54-percent-of-workers-plan-to-quit-without-more-flexible-hours-and-locations/?sh=1148b4b83bab">SAP BrandVoice on Forbes.</a></em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-anz</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-store</category>
            <category>news-tag/talent-acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[AI Trends 2022: Spare Us the Hype, We Want Business Results]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/01/ai-trends-2022-spare-us-the-hype-we-want-business-results</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/01/ai-trends-2022-spare-us-the-hype-we-want-business-results</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The latest industry analyst predictions on AI trends show how smart, creative, and sincere artificial intelligence will become. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c8d8a4bb0d40b93cde54c85cab62756d51ea01fc.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c8d8a4bb0d40b93cde54c85cab62756d51ea01fc.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1c8d8a4bb0d40b93cde54c85cab62756d51ea01fc.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="AI Trends 2022: Spare Us the Hype, We Want Business Results" src="./media_1c8d8a4bb0d40b93cde54c85cab62756d51ea01fc.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="ai-trends-2022-spare-us-the-hype-we-want-business-results">AI Trends 2022: Spare Us the Hype, We Want Business Results</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>If you thought judgment, ethics, and even creativity were the unique purview of humans, think again.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The latest industry analyst predictions about artificial intelligence (AI) are out, and they’re certain to oust a ton of assumptions we’ve made to date. Read on to find out just how smart, creative, and sincere AI will become during the next few years.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="find-out-more-about-intelligent-technologies-from-sap">Find out more about intelligent technologies from SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/intelligent-technologies.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="creative-machines-are-the-future">Creative Machines Are the Future</h2>
  <p>Noting that South Africa granted the first patent to a creative AI system in 2021, <a href="https://www.forrester.com/predictions/">Forrester</a> researchers predicted creative AI systems will win dozens of patents in 2022. They were quick to point out that “AI will not own the products in the traditional sense – the developers of the AI systems…will still enjoy commercial benefits. But companies will experiment with creative AI, knowing that these innovations may be legally protected.”</p>
  <p><a href="https://www.forrester.com/blogs/meet-the-new-demand-for-creativity-with-ai/">Forrester</a> Analyst Diego Lo Giudice looked ahead to “AI 2.0,” which he saw fueling the development of new creative business applications, exceeding basic expectations of AI to free up workers for greater creativity. He predicted that AI would connect business processes across silos to boost business creativity and wrote that “AI’s new business models can optimize the convergence of the digital world with the physical world and drive the ‘anything as a digital service’ trend. The impact on customer experience could be huge.”</p>
  <h2 id="explainable-ai-is-not-your-typical-it-project">Explainable AI Is Not Your Typical IT Project</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="explore-the-entire-sap-institute-for-digital-government-research-series">Explore the entire SAP Institute for Digital Government research series</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://discover.sap.com/sap-institute-digital-gov/en-us/publications.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Explainability and ethics were among the most widely discussed AI-related issues. <a href="https://www.forrester.com/blogs/predictions-for-2022-successfully-riding-the-next-wave-of-ai/">Forrester</a> Analyst Srividya Sridharan saw the market for responsible AI solutions doubling as industries adopt “responsible AI solutions that help companies turn AI principles such as fairness and transparency into consistent practices.” And for those who fear these algorithms will run amok, <a href="https://www.idc.com/getdoc.jsp?containerId=US47913321">IDC</a> analysts predicted that by 2025, to reduce reputational risks, 40% of G2000 companies will be forced to redesign their approaches to algorithmic decision-making, providing better human oversight and explainability.</p>
  <p>AI explainability is one of topics that Ian Ryan is exploring as global head of the SAP Institute for Digital Government. It’s part of a research series for the Australian public sector on the value and impact of technologies for employees, citizens, and society at large. Ryan said that AI can help deliver citizen services with that coveted Amazon-like experience, provided organizations set value-based, measurable objectives.</p>
  <p>“Applications of AI consist of the person using it, the AI model itself, and the information that comes from reality; these three pieces have to be in sync, targeted towards driving a particular outcome,” said Ryan. “You need to train the AI model continuously, keeping it updated so it can support workers as situations evolve, engineering out any bias while preserving data protection.”</p>
  <p>For business value, AI algorithms cannot function as an inscrutable black box or operate autonomously. Ryan said organizations need to build explainability into complex AI models and involve targeted employees in AI model development.</p>
  <p>“AI supports employees by taking tasks away, allowing people to be more productive and focus on high-value activities,” he said. “Al can access huge amounts of seemingly disconnected data from different places and identify patterns in seconds, far faster than humans. Explainability provides the transparency people can trust, so they’ll share their data knowing the organization will protect it and deliver value.”</p>
  <p>Indeed, <a href="https://www.gartner.com/en/information-technology/insights/top-technology-trends">Gartner</a> analysts warned that while AI will help companies emerge from the <a href="/covid-19">pandemic</a> in a strong position, merely adopting AI won’t be enough. Companies need to operationalize updates to AI models, “using integrated data and model and development pipelines to deliver consistent business value from AI. It combines automated update pipelines with strong AI governance.”</p>
  <h2 id="ai-becomes-ubiquitous">AI Becomes Ubiquitous</h2>
  <p>Numerous analyst predictions tout the benefits of AI in strengthening human decisions. <a href="https://www.idc.com/getdoc.jsp?containerId=US48298421">IDC</a> researchers said that 85% of enterprises will combine human expertise with AI, machine learning, natural language processing, and pattern recognition to augment foresight across the organization, making workers 25% more productive and effective by 2026. <a href="https://www.idc.com/getdoc.jsp?containerId=US47913321">IDC</a> researchers saw 30% of organizations using forms of behavioral economics and AI- and machine learning-driven insights to nudge employees’ actions, leading to a 60% increase in desired outcomes by 2026.</p>
  <p>More near term, <a href="https://www.forrester.com/blogs/predictions-for-2022-successfully-riding-the-next-wave-of-ai/">Sridharan</a> expected traditional businesses will take a page out of digital-native practices during the pandemic with an AI-first approach to platform and digital transformation. He said that “the more AI inside, the more enterprises can shrink the latency between insights, decisions, and results.”</p>
  <p>Unlike many previous innovations, AI is not an isolated technology that organizations can surgically apply and wait for the magic to happen. AI is an extraordinarily powerful technology with profound ramifications for organizations and people as they discover its true business potential.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Follow me @smgaler.</em><br><em><a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2021/12/08/ai-trends-2022-spare-us-the-hype-we-want-business-results/?sh=11dd0d96601a">This blog also appeared on SAP BrandVoice on Forbes.</a></em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/forrester</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-anz</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[AI Startup Gives Sustainable Wastewater Management a High-Tech Refresh]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/ai-startup-gives-sustainable-wastewater-management-high-tech-refresh</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/ai-startup-gives-sustainable-wastewater-management-high-tech-refresh</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Streamwise D.I offers data from wastewater treatment systems to help close the gap between business exigencies and sustainability mandates.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ee75fdb9c9def28312cb07c8d850eb067400055c.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ee75fdb9c9def28312cb07c8d850eb067400055c.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1ee75fdb9c9def28312cb07c8d850eb067400055c.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="AI Startup Gives Sustainable Wastewater Management a High-Tech Refresh" src="./media_1ee75fdb9c9def28312cb07c8d850eb067400055c.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="ai-startup-gives-sustainable-wastewater-management-a-high-tech-refresh">AI Startup Gives Sustainable Wastewater Management a High-Tech Refresh</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Clean water is one of the highest sustainability priorities worldwide, and industrial manufacturers are turning to artificial intelligence (AI), machine learning, and Industrial Internet of Things (IIoT) technologies to meet the challenge. In Australia, startup <a href="https://streamwisedi.com/">Streamwise D.I.</a> has developed an AI-powered intelligence platform providing industrial-grade digitization for wastewater treatment.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“Manufacturers across a range of industries process water that is on the scale of megaliters per day,” said Abhyuday Bhartia, chief technology officer at Streamwise D.I. “Our devices and decision intelligence platform guide companies through collecting the right data and give them the tools to effortlessly find insights. This transparency lowers operational costs and risk while improving the organization’s ability to meet compliance regulations.”</p>
  <p>Streamwise D.I.’s blue chip customers include recognized brands in the food and beverage, mining, and chemicals industries, as well as municipal water authorities. Customers can gain business value early with smaller initial projects while making further improvements over time.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-how-sapio-foundries-supports-b2b-technology-startups-worldwide">Learn how SAP.iO Foundries supports B2B technology startups worldwide</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://sap.io/foundries/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="bubbling-up-process-inefficiencies">Bubbling Up Process Inefficiencies</h2>
  <p>The Streamwise D.I. platform collects real-time information from cameras, IoT-based sensors, and other instruments installed on machinery at the customer’s facilities. The data becomes a “digital twin” that feeds into a cloud-based dashboard, where it’s analyzed and shared as action items with designated team members. People have immediate access to the information through their mobile device or Web browser.</p>
  <p>“Within an hour of turning on the system, operations teams can quickly see water contaminant levels and if operations are out of compliance with regulations,” said Bhartia. “Over time, the algorithms calculate asset and process inefficiencies, as well as environmental compliance with that company’s municipal trade waste agreements.”</p>
  <p>Among the biggest regulatory mandates is the volume and type of chemicals that manufacturers use in wastewater treatment. The issue is as much about regulatory compliance as cost-savings.</p>
  <p>“Using the data, the operator can adjust mechanisms and treatment processes to stay in compliance and achieve great efficiencies,” said Bhartia. “With historical and real-time data, the platform can create what-if scenarios, and make automated operational control and management decisions. Companies may discover they’re using types and levels of chemicals that aren’t necessary.”</p>
  <p>One customer, an Australian cereal manufacturer, significantly lowered wastewater treatment operating costs by reducing unnecessary chemical usage. A dairy processing plant lowered trade waste charges by 26% and operator oversight by 80% for a total savings of over one-quarter of a million dollars each year.</p>
  <h2 id="data-reduces-operational-expenses">Data Reduces Operational Expenses</h2>
  <p>Addressing environment, sustainability, and corporate governance (ESG) imperatives also hinges on operational efficiencies. In monitoring and analyzing data from water treatment operations, Bhartia said that Streamwise D.I. delivers insights with far-reaching sustainable business impact.</p>
  <p>“Are operations working to their optimized efficiency? Are they working to agreed-upon specifications, or are they actually failing? Does equipment need maintenance or replacement?” he said. “Understanding and acting on all of these issues affects efficiencies for energy savings too.”</p>
  <h2 id="digital-intelligence-modernizes-wastewater-treatment">Digital Intelligence Modernizes Wastewater Treatment</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="can-artificial-intelligence-take-the-guesswork-out-of-the-customer-journey">Can Artificial Intelligence Take the Guesswork Out of the Customer Journey?</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/12/can-artificial-intelligence-take-the-guesswork-out-of-the-customer-journey">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Bhartia has been with Streamwise D.I. since it transitioned into a digital services platform. He agreed with the startup’s founder, Alastair Lockey, that AI had the power to modernize wastewater treatment, closing the gap between business exigencies and sustainability mandates.</p>
  <p>“Wastewater treatment systems are inefficient and extremely complex with unique environments and operations,” said Bhartia. “We knew intelligent digitalization could help simplify processes, providing operators with actionable insights to meet operational targets, budget objectives, and regulatory mandates. There’s enormous global potential to make a real difference for business and the environment worldwide.”</p>
  <h2 id="incredible-sustainability-partnership-with-sapio">Incredible Sustainability Partnership with SAP.iO</h2>
  <p>Streamwise D.I. was part of the energy and natural resource cohort of <a href="http://www.sap.io/">SAP.iO Foundry Singapore</a>. Bhartia found value in SAP’s hands-on product commercialization and go-to-market support.</p>
  <p>“It’s been an incredible opportunity working with SAP. We’ve learned so much from SAP’s experts, and their validation of our solution has provided us with greater market credibility and visibility,” he said. “Being integrated with <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/asset-intelligence-network.html">SAP Asset Intelligence Network</a> increases our collective sustainability impact for industrial water management customers globally.”</p>
  <p>Streamwise D.I. is available on <a href="https://store.sap.com/dcp/en/product/display-0000060292_live_v1/Streamwise%20D.I.%20Extender">SAP Store</a>.</p>
  <h2 id="tech-can-turn-back-the-water-pollution-tide">Tech Can Turn Back the Water Pollution Tide</h2>
  <p>Sustainable business demands technologies to head off increasingly dire predictions about our quality of life and very survival. The <a href="https://www.worldbank.org/en/news/feature/2019/08/20/quality-unknown">World Bank</a> said that around 80% of the world’s wastewater is returned to the environment without adequate treatment. These experts predicted that two-thirds of the world’s population could be water stressed by 2025. But they also made it clear that “change is possible…Increased awareness, strengthened prevention, and smart investments using new technology are needed to turn back the tide of water pollution.”</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Follow me @smgaler.</em><br><em>This blog also appeared on <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2021/11/15/ai-start-up-gives-sustainable-wastewater-management-a-high-tech-refresh/?sh=6d9783186155">SAP BrandVoice on Forbes</a>.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-anz</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-store</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-io</category>
            <category>news-tag/startups</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Digitalization Behind Australia’s $140B Critical Infrastructure Spend]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/digitalization-behind-australias-140b-critical-infrastructure-spend</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/digitalization-behind-australias-140b-critical-infrastructure-spend</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Digitized infrastructure connects partners and data across complex projects to meet deadlines and lower costs. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-anz</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[AGL Energy Digitally Transforms for a Brighter Future]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/agl-energy-digitally-transforms-for-brighter-future</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/agl-energy-digitally-transforms-for-brighter-future</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[AGL Energy digitally transforms to meet rising customer demands and competitive threats in a fast-changing industry. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-anz</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Vital Truths About Business Digitalization from High Performers in ANZ]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/vital-truths-business-digitalization-high-performers-anz</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/vital-truths-business-digitalization-high-performers-anz</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Leaders from high-performing ANZ organizations shared their digitalization experiences during a virtual SAPPHIRE NOW session. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14e9478cb963a97ba71af61b2a3ab178007a392e6.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14e9478cb963a97ba71af61b2a3ab178007a392e6.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_14e9478cb963a97ba71af61b2a3ab178007a392e6.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Vital Truths About Business Digitalization from High Performers in ANZ" src="./media_14e9478cb963a97ba71af61b2a3ab178007a392e6.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="vital-truths-about-business-digitalization-from-high-performers-in-anz">Vital Truths About Business Digitalization from High Performers in ANZ</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Having experienced the equivalent of 10 years of digital change in the past 18 months or so, organizations are addressing the realities of transformation as <a href="https://insights.sap.com/digitization-vs-digitalization/">digitalization</a> becomes the business norm.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Leaders from two high-performing organizations in ANZ recently shared their experiences with digitalization during a <a href="https://reg.sapevents.sap.com/flow/sap/sapphirenow2021/portal/page/sessions/session/1624909796224001c5ES">SAPPHIRE NOW session</a> hosted by Des Fisher, innovation principal at SAP ANZ. Here is a sampling of the far-ranging thoughts on the sustainable business realities behind innovating on cloud-based digital platforms.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="watch-replays-from-sapphire-now">Watch replays from SAPPHIRE NOW</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://reg.sapevents.sap.com/flow/sap/sapphirenow2021/portal/page/sessions/session/1624909796224001c5ES">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="digitalization-is-a-mindset-and-tech-transformation">Digitalization Is a Mindset and Tech Transformation</h2>
  <p>For Australian-based <a href="/australia/2021/06/30/stockland-settles-in-on-its-new-sap-core">Stockland</a>, digitalization involved transforming people’s mindsets along with systems company-wide. As one of the largest diversified real estate groups in Australia, the company owns, develops, and manages a large portfolio of retail town centers, workplace and logistics assets, residential communities, and retirement living villages. It’s replaced over 100 disparate, legacy software systems with SAP software, including <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/s4hana-erp.html">SAP S/4HANA</a> and <a href="https://www.ariba.com/">SAP Ariba solutions</a>, as well as embedded artificial intelligence (AI) and robotics.</p>
  <p>“We now have a single source of the truth,” said Tiernan O’Rourke, CFO at Stockland. “I’m absolutely convinced that in time we’ll look back and say that was one of the best things we did in the 70-year history of the company…Our digitization journey shows that unless you’re on the journey you’re going to struggle in business, not only in Australia, but globally.”</p>
  <p>Stockland began by defining digitalization in the company’s own terms. The digital platform was designed to strike a balance between achieving three objectives: organizational risk, governance, and business growth.</p>
  <p>“We first looked at what digitization meant to us and came at it by putting the company on the core SAP platform,” said O’Rourke. “We’re a tactile industry of property, bricks, and mortar. Getting people’s minds away from physical to digital was…one of the biggest obstacles to overcome.”</p>
  <h2 id="digital-backbone-drives-innovation">Digital Backbone Drives Innovation</h2>
  <p>Oil and gas provider OMV New Zealand recently won an <a href="/australia/2021/04/20/services-australia-agl-and-omv-new-zealand-win-sap-global-innovation-awards">SAP Innovation Award</a> for its groundbreaking digitalization that included digital twins and augmented reality (AR) in onshore and offshore inspections. Replacing paper-heavy processes with digitalized and integrated workflows based on the latest mobile solutions and wearable technologies will help OMV improve decision-making, performance, and efficiencies in inspections and maintenance. Its integrated workflow management relies on SAP S/4HANA, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/supply-chain-management/asset-management-eam.html">SAP Intelligent Asset Management</a>, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/asset-manager.html">SAP Asset Manager</a>, and HoloLens 2.</p>
  <p>“The use of automation and AI-driven technologies for creating intelligent digital twins is a key enabler for global scalability and accelerates creating the digital backbone of the company during digital transformation. Enhancing this technology with an augmented reality experience including mark-up annotations provides a solid basis for data insights, data-driven decision-making, and performance optimization,” said Farid Akbari, functional lead for Digital Transformation at OMV New Zealand. “This innovation project will change the way we are working and enable us to position ourselves among digital front-runners within our industry.”</p>
  <h2 id="digital-platforms-are-core-to-supplier-relationships">Digital Platforms Are Core to Supplier Relationships</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="anz-leaders-that-invested-early-in-digital-supply-chains-had-tremendous-results">ANZ Leaders That Invested Early in Digital Supply Chains Had Tremendous Results</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/09/anz-digital-supply-chains-tremendous-results">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Acknowledging that no business does business alone, O’Rourke said that Stockland’s deep supplier relationship management strategy is foundational to customer centricity.</p>
  <p>“If you don’t partner with best-in-breed, like-minded companies to help deliver premium services to customers, you won’t win,” he said. “We have 14% market share in residential business…because we evaluate every step of the customer journey, including supplier choice…You can’t know your suppliers unless you have deep relationships and are collaborating with them at a very granular level…Collaboration is an absolute threshold issue in business today.”</p>
  <h2 id="close-gap-between-dx-and-business-realities">Close Gap Between DX and Business Realities</h2>
  <p>When asked about some of the biggest digital transformation challenges, Akbari discussed the gap between innovation aspirations and reality. He pointed out that while everyone wants simplicity, getting there means answering difficult questions.</p>
  <p>“We asked ourselves if we had the right organization in place to achieve digital maturity,” he recalled. “Other questions were about managing resistance to change and how to actively support the change management process with tools that were changing the way we work…We asked how to build and retain skills over time as innovations like blockchain, the Internet of Things (IoT), and cloud computing continue [to emerge].”</p>
  <p>Akbari also warned organizations not to neglect core details such as infrastructure capabilities, technology integration, and resultant business process changes.</p>
  <p>“Often the business comes up with a good idea, but we’re not ready yet,” he said. “For example, AR had to be integrated into the environment…You also have to consider operational maturity…As a global gas and oil company, we have different maturity levels of all assets and have to map where we are for each asset and how we will achieve that automation level.”</p>
  <h2 id="sustainability-is-much-more-than-climate-change">Sustainability Is Much More Than Climate Change</h2>
  <p>While ESG (environmental, social, and governance) demands tend to emphasize climate change, O’Rourke urged companies to consider all aspects of sustainability, including diversity.</p>
  <p>“Everyone talks about climate change, but that’s just about the environment. To do business successfully…you’re going to have to be very balanced in the E, S, and G of ESG,” he said. “Everyone is focused on net zero carbon, and rightly so. But we can’t do that in isolation…We have to jump on [behavior change] proactively to get suppliers to work with us in a way allows us to operate effectively. On the diversity side, business has been playing lip service for so long and needs to get serious about focusing on this change.”</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Follow me @smgaler.</em><br><em><a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2021/08/24/vital-truths-about-business-digitalization-from-high-performers-in-anz/?sh=187392fa331b">This blog also appeared on SAP BrandVoice on Forbes.</a></em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digitalization</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-anz</category>
            <category>sap-award/sap-innovation-awards</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Five Ways Australian Market Leaders Create Winning Customer Experiences]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/five-ways-australian-market-leaders-create-winning-cx</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/five-ways-australian-market-leaders-create-winning-cx</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Leaders from two Australian-based companies shared their thoughts on winning CX strategies during a virtual SAPPHIRE NOW session.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-anz</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-customer-experience</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ANZ Leaders That Invested Early in Digital Supply Chains Had Tremendous Results]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/anz-digital-supply-chains-tremendous-results</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/anz-digital-supply-chains-tremendous-results</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[How supply chain leaders digitally transform to connect business and operational data for resilience and sustainability.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-supply-chain</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-anz</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Procurement Leaders Are Weathering the Staggering Costs of Supply Chain Disruption]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/intelligent-procurement-weathering-supply-chain-disruption</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/intelligent-procurement-weathering-supply-chain-disruption</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Intelligent procurement helps businesses boost productivity for pandemic recovery, despite supply chain disruptions. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_196f9210703d27951d296e2a2d1617191e5fdb21b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_196f9210703d27951d296e2a2d1617191e5fdb21b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_196f9210703d27951d296e2a2d1617191e5fdb21b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="How Procurement Leaders Are Weathering the Staggering Costs of Supply Chain Disruption" src="./media_196f9210703d27951d296e2a2d1617191e5fdb21b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="how-procurement-leaders-are-weathering-the-staggering-costs-of-supply-chain-disruption">How Procurement Leaders Are Weathering the Staggering Costs of Supply Chain Disruption</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Extreme weather, a global <a href="/covid-19">pandemic</a>, and continuous market uncertainties are just a few of the supply chain shocks businesses and their customers have been absorbing in the past few years. According to one survey, organizations best able to manage the pandemic were the ones that embraced digital transformation. What’s more, a large percentage of respondents regretted not accelerating to digital fast enough.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“Companies that recognize the role of technology in transforming their business models are the ones that have been able to thrive,” said Chris Willcocks, head of Intelligent Spend Management at SAP ANZ. “Customers are focused on driving visibility in their supply chains and through their data, becoming agile <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/intelligent-enterprise.html?source=blog-au-forbes-intelligent-enterprise&#x26;campaigncode=">intelligent enterprises</a>, increasing the resilience of their functions in business, and identifying and reducing risk.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="watch-a-replay-from-sapphire-now-to-learn-more-about-saps-intelligent-spend-strategy">Watch a replay from SAPPHIRE NOW to learn more about SAP’s intelligent spend strategy</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://reg.sapevents.sap.com/flow/sap/sapphirenow2021/portal/page/sessions/session/1616721417441001IcW3">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="intelligent-enterprises-innovate-with-business-networks">Intelligent Enterprises Innovate with Business Networks</h2>
  <p>Speaking with Baber Farooq, senior vice president of Intelligent Spend Management at SAP, during <a href="https://reg.sapevents.sap.com/flow/sap/sapphirenow2021/portal/page/sessions/session/1616721417441001IcW3">SAPPHIRE NOW</a>, Willcocks gave the virtual audience a glimpse into the future of procurement. It’s built on insights from quality data across supply chains, bringing buyers much closer to their suppliers. Noting that procurement doesn’t exist in a vacuum, Willcocks said that collaborative business networks are foundational to <a href="https://insights.sap.com/what-is-digital-transformation/">digital transformation</a>.</p>
  <p>“When you’re connected not only to your suppliers but to your customers and their customers, you make the move to being an intelligent enterprise,” he said.</p>
  <h2 id="autonomous-procurement-for-intelligent-spend">Autonomous Procurement for Intelligent Spend</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="what-are-the-essentials-for-successful-digital-transformation-now">What are the essentials for successful digital transformation now?</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://insights.sap.com/what-are-the-essentials-for-successful-digital-transformation-dx/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Just when the world needs to boost productivity to recover from the worldwide pandemic, markets are facing potentially dire shortages of both goods and labor. The answer lies in intelligent procurement, where people do the things that machines cannot replicate.</p>
  <p>“Procurement is at the heart of solving these [productivity] problems,” said Farooq. “That’s why we’re focused on automating more and more processes – what we call autonomous procurement. Intelligent spend is finding out what machines can do and letting machines do that, and getting people to focus on the things that people do, which is establishing strategic relationships with suppliers.”</p>
  <h2 id="digitalized-procurement-translates-to-business-innovation">Digitalized Procurement Translates to Business Innovation</h2>
  <p>In digitalizing forecasting, inventory management, and other collaboration points between buyers and suppliers, business networks have profoundly changed procurement. Teams have the time to be more productive, which translates to innovation.</p>
  <p>“I was talking to an automotive customer that said that over 90% of the innovation it has in its cars came from its suppliers,” said Farooq. “Another customer in Asia recently launched an initiative where it used SAP Business Network to help support the goal of paying all suppliers within seven days. The network allows you to foster that amazing relationship with the supplier because everything is digital…People can do what they do best, which is driving relationships and working on innovation.”</p>
  <p>Farooq challenged the audience to ask themselves, despite all the technological innovations the world has experienced in the past decade, if they had more time today for their work than they did 10 years ago.</p>
  <p>“Technology has come about to make people more productive, but it has to get out of the way,” he said. “The heart of artificial intelligence (AI) is to make businesses more effective…If we can make procurement organizations more productive, procurement organizations can make their entire business more productive, becoming a strategic advisor to the C-suite.”</p>
  <p>As for those organizations that regret not digitalizing fast enough to head off the worst business impacts from this pandemic, it’s not too late to prepare now for the next supply chain disruptions headed our way soon.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Follow me @smgaler.</em><br><em><a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2021/07/22/how-procurement-leaders-are-weathering-the-staggering-costs-of-supply-chain-disruption/?sh=11b0bdfc3316">This blog also appeared on SAP BrandVoice on Forbes.</a></em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-anz</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sustainable Business at Veolia ANZ: A Culture of Employee Engagement]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/veolia-anz-culture-of-employee-engagement</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/veolia-anz-culture-of-employee-engagement</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Aug 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Veolia ANZ builds a culture of employee engagement with SAP solutions as part of its sustainable business mission. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d9756ca8715dfa6172ff87e4a03e6f2be81050f0.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d9756ca8715dfa6172ff87e4a03e6f2be81050f0.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1d9756ca8715dfa6172ff87e4a03e6f2be81050f0.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Sustainable Business at Veolia ANZ: A Culture of Employee Engagement" src="./media_1d9756ca8715dfa6172ff87e4a03e6f2be81050f0.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sustainable-business-at-veolia-anz-a-culture-of-employee-engagement">Sustainable Business at Veolia ANZ: A Culture of Employee Engagement</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Sustainable business is one post-pandemic trend that’s here to stay, especially among global market leaders like <a href="https://www.veolia.com/anz/">Veolia ANZ</a>, a longtime champion of ecological transformation.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>With approximately 4,600 employees in Australia and 182,000 worldwide, Veolia ANZ has extended its sustainable business commitment to both customers and workers. The company’s COVID-19 crisis response team in Australia and New Zealand began using <a href="https://www.qualtrics.com/">Experience Management solutions from SAP and Qualtrics</a> this past year to stay connected with workers and address their challenges.</p>
  <p>“It’s critical that we constantly communicate with employees to understand their challenges and act quickly to address their needs,” said Alexandre Moreau, chief people and safety officer at Veolia ANZ. “We needed a quick and easy solution to keep people connected, whether it was managers and their teams or customers. Qualtrics helped us make sure that our people were okay and receiving the support they needed.”</p>
  <p>Sustainability is in Veolia’s DNA. The company’s business portfolio includes providing environmental solutions across water, waste management, and energy. With operations and treatment facilities nationwide, it serves customers of all sizes – from local cafes and food chains to industrial facilities. One of its business units helps municipal water customers provide safe drinking water for their communities and industrial clients to more sustainably manage water in their operations, while its energy division helps companies build energy resilience and become carbon neutral.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="put-employees-at-the-heart-of-everything-you-do-with-sap-successfactors">Put employees at the heart of everything you do with SAP SuccessFactors</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="listening-translates-employee-feedback-into-engagement">Listening Translates Employee Feedback Into Engagement</h2>
  <p>As a designated essential service during the <a href="/covid-19">pandemic</a>, Veolia ANZ provided the same level of support for customers despite significant challenges, including social distancing, schedule disruptions, and lockdowns. During the height of the crisis, it needed even more flexibility to respond to highly changeable situations. For example, workloads increased in the health sector because of pandemic-related activities. Meanwhile, some employees were working remotely, while others had to be in the field. The company used XM solutions from SAP and Qualtrics to stay in touch with employees.</p>
  <p>Kate Moonen, head of Marketing and Digital Experience at Veolia ANZ, was part of the company’s pandemic response team. Speaking during <a href="https://open.spotify.com/episode/1Xe6n7mvEGJCwKz4A7kOgl">The Best Run Podcast by SAP ANZ</a>, she discussed how short, but targeted surveys helped the company stay in touch with its diverse workforce that includes truck drivers, machine operators, engineers, lawyers, and sustainability experts in urban and remote locations.</p>
  <p>“We really wanted to understand that our people, particularly essential workers, were feeling supported,” she said. “Did they have enough PPE equipment to do their jobs safely? What were their concerns about their mental health and well-being? Based on that feedback, it helped our team formulate what we were going to communicate and what actions we needed to take to continue to support our people.”</p>
  <p>Initially, the team was surprised at the high employee engagement levels with the surveys. Over time, the company rolled out new activities based on the feedback. These included regularly scheduled, anywhere, any device communications with senior leadership through live webinars and question-and-answer sessions. In response to employee requests, executives also sent short video messages that employees could watch on their mobile phones, with personalized stories from company leaders about their lives outside of work and how they adapted to the changed working environment.</p>
  <p>“People felt they wanted to take the opportunity to be heard,” said Moonen. “We would often share regular communications with them about what came out of the latest pulse and what we were going to do about it. If you’re asking people for their time, it’s critical to demonstrate what you’re doing with that feedback to meet their needs.”</p>
  <h2 id="continuous-dialogue-through-employee-surveys">Continuous Dialogue Through Employee Surveys</h2>
  <p>Just like any aspect of sustainable business, employee engagement is not a one-and-done effort.</p>
  <p>“We’re seeing strong employee engagement every time we roll out a new survey,” said Moreau. “Instead of waiting a year to connect with employees, Qualtrics has given us a more agile response tool with a quick pulse check that our people appreciate and we can rely on for updated feedback to make better decisions. We want to know how people are feeling in a fast-changing business environment.”</p>
  <h2 id="go-digital-for-fast-action">Go Digital for Fast Action</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="the-future-of-business-has-feelings">The future of business has feelings</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/experience-management-xm.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Moreau said companies should be explicit about what employees have shared and how they’re taking action. Even if there isn’t an immediate answer, people appreciate the transparency.</p>
  <p>Moonen also advised employers not to overthink the survey process.</p>
  <p>“Sustainable business is all about agility,” she said. “Collecting the feedback and acting quickly is far more valuable than spending months iterating questions. Digital technology gives us the ability to constantly evolve and adapt as customer expectations, market conditions, and employee experiences shift.”</p>
  <h2 id="future-of-work-is-in-employee-experience">Future of Work Is in Employee Experience</h2>
  <p>In the wake of the pandemic, many employees yearn for a greater sense of belonging. They want more help with their individual career goals and to have pride in their workplace. Getting the employee experience right is part of every organization’s transformational journey to sustainable business.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Follow me @smgaler.</em><br><em><a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2021/07/08/sustainable-business-at-veolia-anz-we-make-sure-our-people-are-okay/?sh=5a8244291c0f">This blog also appeared on SAP BrandVoice on Forbes.</a></em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-engagement</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/experience-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/qualtrics</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-anz</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Australia’s Asset-Intensive Industries Save Millions Managing the External Workforce]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/australia-asset-intensive-industries-external-workforce</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/australia-asset-intensive-industries-external-workforce</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Organizations in asset-intensive industries can integrate data to holistically manage contingent workers for safety and savings. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/external-workforce-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-anz</category>
            <category>product/sap-erp</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[We Are All Neurodiverse in Some Way: Australia Expands Workplace Neurodiversity]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/australia-expands-workplace-neurodiversity</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/australia-expands-workplace-neurodiversity</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Aug 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Workplace neurodiversity programs bring greater innovation to teams for customer innovation and business growth. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1cd9a5552bc6cda9d7eb7cc33f8ef4e907a9ae0c4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1cd9a5552bc6cda9d7eb7cc33f8ef4e907a9ae0c4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1cd9a5552bc6cda9d7eb7cc33f8ef4e907a9ae0c4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="We Are All Neurodiverse in Some Way: Australia Expands Workplace Neurodiversity" src="./media_1cd9a5552bc6cda9d7eb7cc33f8ef4e907a9ae0c4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="we-are-all-neurodiverse-in-some-way-australia-expands-workplace-neurodiversity">We Are All Neurodiverse in Some Way: Australia Expands Workplace Neurodiversity</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div>As leaders realize that workforce diversity, equity, and inclusion (DEI) is good for employees and business, Australian-based organizations are exploring how to bring more neurodiversity into the workplace.</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>Forrester</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Globally, researchers found that diverse organizations were more profitable and innovative, and did a better job of retaining top talent. <a href="https://blogs.gartner.com/beyond-supply-chain-blog/the-future-of-work-a-view-from-the-top/?_ga=2.59126884.817088538.1623251479-581596103.1562588316">Gartner</a> analysts said that companies in many industries have tied DEI goals into numerous organizational activities such as employee pipelines and compensation and supply chain partnerships. However, an article in <em><a href="https://www.theage.com.au/business/workplace/coming-up-with-creative-solutions-companies-looking-to-hire-autistic-employees-20210304-p577xw.html">The Age</a></em> reported that although one in 59 people was on the autism spectrum, 32% of working age Australians with autism were unemployed. Experts explored the importance of creating neurodiverse workplaces during a recent episode of <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/neurodiversity-in-the-workplace/id1457146626?i=1000524594019">The Best Run Podcast by SAP ANZ</a>, hosted by Rushenka Perera, head of Marketing at SAP ANZ.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="bring-everything-you-are-and-become-everything-you-want-at-sap">Bring everything you are and become everything you want at SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/careers/your-career/autism-at-work-program.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="understanding-neurodiversity-beyond-labels">Understanding Neurodiversity Beyond Labels</h2>
  <p>Andrew Eddy, CEO of Untapped Holdings, said that neurodiversity was coined by a Sydney-based sociologist to describe the infinite neuro-cognitive variability across people. It’s currently used to describe people with neurological differences such as autism, ADHD, dyslexia, dyscalculia, dysgraphia, PTSD, and Tourette’s Syndrome. Untapped is a social enterprise focused on developing a neurodiverse employment ecosystem to increase opportunities for people with autism. Working with corporate partners, like SAP, as well as educators, researchers, parents, and students, Untapped created the Neurodiversity Hub initiative, working with universities and colleges to foster educational and employment inclusion.</p>
  <p>“Neurodiversity is really about extending the level of diversity that we have in the workplace because we are all neurodiverse in some way – we all have different ways of thinking,” he said. “See it as a way of intentionally broadening the diversity of thought and ways of thinking that we already have in the workplace, extending that further and being more inclusive of people that have those labels.”</p>
  <h2 id="neurodiverse-people-add-business-capabilities">Neurodiverse People Add Business Capabilities</h2>
  <p>According to Eddy, it’s important for organizations to look at neurodiversity from a business-capability perspective, rather than just through an inclusion and diversity lens.</p>
  <p>“We go into a company and talk to the business people and talent acquisition about the potential gaps in the capabilities of the business and how some of those gaps could be filled by a group of individuals who have some great talents, including loyalty – being very sticky employees – with a very focused approach to the way they do their work, a different way of seeing things, attention to detail, and great memory,” he said.</p>
  <h2 id="neurodiversity-impacts-entire-workforce">Neurodiversity Impacts Entire Workforce</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="employee-centered-experience-drives-business-agility-in-australia">Employee-Centered Experience Drives Business Agility in Australia</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/07/employee-centered-experience-business-agility-australia">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP expanded its global <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/careers/your-career/autism-at-work-program.html">Autism at Work</a> program to SAP ANZ, where neurodiverse people have joined the region’s finance, development and coding, and project management teams. The impact has been profound on both the business overall and numerous teams.</p>
  <p>“We wanted to diversify our talent and the benefits they could bring to our organization,” said Sehida Frawley, head of Services at SAP ANZ. “The positive benefits are not just what those individuals contribute to our business, but what it’s [also] done to change team working relationships…It’s influenced all of our communication skills, how you nurture and develop individuals and consider their different needs.”</p>
  <p>For example, after introducing neurodiverse interns into an SAP ANZ office, one manager’s adjusted communication strategies created a more open environment for the entire team to work more effectively together.</p>
  <h2 id="how-to-start-a-workplace-neurodiversity-program">How to Start a Workplace Neurodiversity Program</h2>
  <p>As more people identify as neurodivergent, some companies are responding with inclusive talent recruitment strategies, including graduate and internship programs. Establishing a sustainable neurodiversity program begins with upper management support.</p>
  <p>“You need to have that senior sponsorship, which is certainly something SAP has done, running this as an important program with passionate people like Sehida taking that role,” said Eddy. “The next thing is how do you start to change the culture…It’s not a choice to employ neurodiverse people. They’re already there. Many companies are expanding existing programs to have an employee resource group that’s focused on neurodiversity.”</p>
  <p>Eddy also recommended including neurodiverse awareness in employee training and education programs.</p>
  <h2 id="diversity-powers-innovation-for-customer-transformation">Diversity Powers Innovation for Customer Transformation</h2>
  <p>Neurodiverse workplaces are not just about doing something good. There is also the larger business impact. Frawley said that the Autism at Work program at SAP was driven by the company’s global diversity and inclusion mission, along with meeting the demands of a fiercely competitive talent marketplace.</p>
  <p>“Our business is about assisting our customers to innovate and transform…You can’t always have the same way of doing things and the same ideas,” she said. “It’s really important that we broaden our pool of talent so we can bring that diversity of thought and approach so we can innovate and transform…and drive that with our customers.”</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Follow me @smgaler</em><br><em><a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2021/06/29/we-are-all-neurodiverse-in-some-way-australia-expands-workplace-neurodiversity/?sh=393fabfd1020">This blog also appeared on SAP BrandVoice on Forbes</a>.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/autism-at-work</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-anz</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Australian Entrepreneur Turns Award-Winning Cloud Platform into Digital Career]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/06/australian-entrepreneur-digital-career</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/06/australian-entrepreneur-digital-career</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[After Blake Garrett won the Young ICT Explorers (YICTE) competition, he went on to found a cloud-based startup for educators. Learn more!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_104e832fe8b9d057bbf7af532ab0c9e841cf33686.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_104e832fe8b9d057bbf7af532ab0c9e841cf33686.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_104e832fe8b9d057bbf7af532ab0c9e841cf33686.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Australian Entrepreneur Turns Award-Winning Cloud Platform into Digital Career" src="./media_104e832fe8b9d057bbf7af532ab0c9e841cf33686.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="australian-entrepreneur-turns-award-winning-cloud-platform-into-digital-career">Australian Entrepreneur Turns Award-Winning Cloud Platform into Digital Career</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Blake Garrett, CEO of <a href="https://www.schoolbytes.education/">School Bytes</a>, never envisioned that winning a high school tech competition would lead to him founding a cloud-based company that streamlines daily administrative tasks for 440 educational institutions in Australia.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Fascinated by technology throughout his school years, Garrett had already been working on a solution to automate paper-based front office processes that he saw firsthand at Chatsworth High School. With his teacher’s encouragement, Garrett entered his project in the 2015 <a href="https://www.youngictexplorers.net.au/">Young ICT Explorers (YICTE)</a> competition, going on to win at the national level. He credited the valuable feedback from both judges and other entrants with helping him iterate and scale what has now become Sydney-based School Bytes.</p>
  <p>“I was always interested in programming and computers, and my experience with YICTE provided the chance to refine my presentation skills, meet tech industry experts, and learn from like-minded contestants,” said Garrett. “Seeing what others were working on and getting that exposure helped validate my ideas. I realized I could turn this into a viable business, and it ended up jump-starting my career.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-the-young-ict-explorers-competition">Learn more about the Young ICT Explorers competition</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.youngictexplorers.net.au/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="early-innovation-fun-leads-to-tech-careers">Early Innovation Fun Leads to Tech Careers</h2>
  <p>SAP ANZ launched YICTE 12 years ago to help stoke the region’s next generation of technology leaders. Since then, almost 8,000 students from 850 schools across Australia and New Zealand have participated in YICTE competitions. YICTE is supported by <a href="https://www.csiro.au/en/">CSIRO</a>, with help from universities, other corporate sponsors, and a long-running partnership with The Smith Family, Australia’s largest independent children’s education charity.</p>
  <p>“We want to get children in primary and high school interested in and excited about STEM careers,” said Pete Andrew, chief operating officer at <a href="https://www.sap.com/australia/index.html">SAP ANZ</a>. “The competition shows them how they can use technology to solve actual problems in the world while having fun and unleashing their creativity.”</p>
  <p>Andrew said that contest participants have pursued STEM studies, with some going on to university and internships at SAP ANZ. Similar to Garrett, others have founded <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2021/02/02/predictive-trendspotting-2021-how-to-genetically-sequence-the-lifecycle-of-a-trend/?sh=68d2fb266b0b">startups</a> of their own. Competition entries have evolved with community priorities, including sustainability, which was added as a prize category this year.</p>
  <p>“The increase in sustainability-related projects in the competition has been phenomenal. You can see the energy and passion these youths have for important topics like environmental change,” said Andrew. “Imagine being a nine-year-old interacting with your friends and presenting to a panel of judges your creative ideas to create a more sustainable future for our planet. From SAP’s perspective, this aligns with our <a href="/2021/03/sap-carbon-neutrality-goal-2023">carbon-neutral commitment</a> and <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/purpose-and-sustainability.html">corporate vision</a>.”</p>
  <h2 id="students-do-well-through-doing-good">Students Do Well Through Doing Good</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="find-out-more-about-saps-corporate-social-responsibility-partnerships">Find out more about SAP’s Corporate Social Responsibility partnerships</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/csr.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>YICTE Accelerator is among The Smith Family programs designed to help young people break the cycle of poverty through education. As part of the program, the charity provides teachers with resource support and professional development, so they can encourage students from disadvantaged backgrounds to explore career paths in tech. Students who participate in the competition are energized by developing digital tech projects that solve social issues while finding innovative solutions to real-world issues personally, locally, or nationally.</p>
  <p>“Being able to creatively solve problems in their own communities is incredibly motivating for students,” said Judy Barraclough, acting CEO at The Smith Family. “For children who might not have Internet access or computers, the YICTE Accelerator program is a wonderful chance for them to develop digital skills, showcasing their initiative and innovation. I’ve talked with many children who’ve participated, and they are committed to their own achievement so they can give back and change the experience of others in their communities.”</p>
  <p>According to <a href="https://www.educationandemployers.org/wp-content/uploads/2014/06/its_who_you_meet_final_26_06_12.pdf">research out of the UK</a>, children who have at least four exposures to career-based activities or insights during their schooling are much likelier to participate in employment beyond school. Barraclough had high praise for the partnerships that make this possible for the charity.</p>
  <p>“We depend on the support of partners like SAP to bring students incredible access to resources and professionals in the tech industry,” she said.</p>
  <h2 id="digital-transformation-through-education">Digital Transformation Through Education</h2>
  <p>Garrett’s passion for technology has come full circle. Following his YICTE competition win during the last year of high school, two schools interested in his solution immediately reached out to Garrett. School Bytes is a sponsor in this year’s virtual YICTE competition, providing judging and financial support for other aspiring youths. His advice to anyone thinking about a career in tech was simple.</p>
  <p>“Just go for it and keep iterating. One of the most exciting aspects of being in high tech is the constant change,” said Garrett. “Bringing administrative tasks into a modular, cloud subscription-based model provides schools with incredible time-saving efficiencies when it comes to managing events, sports, logistics and payments, and professional learning for teacher accreditation. To this day, we continue evolving with innovations like bringing machine learning and artificial intelligence (AI) into our solutions.”</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Follow me: @smgaler</em><br><em>This blog also appeared on <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2021/05/24/australian-entrepreneur-turns-award-winning-cloud-platform-into-digital-career/?sh=43a286993918">SAP BrandVoice on Forbes</a>.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-education</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-anz</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Creating a Data-Driven Culture for Customer Experience Excellence]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/05/customer-experience-excellence-data-driven-culture</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/05/customer-experience-excellence-data-driven-culture</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Experts from two ANZ market leaders shared how orgs can seek customer experience excellence and overcome challenges amid market disruption.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-anz</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-customer-experience</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>