<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/mental-health-well-being/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mindfulness: The Surprising Business Model]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/mindfulness-the-surprising-business-model</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/mindfulness-the-surprising-business-model</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Global Mindfulness Practice is bringing its successful formula to customers around the world. Read to learn about SLB's experience.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/mental-health-well-being</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-global-mindfulness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Future of Work Beyond Flex Work]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/future-of-work-beyond-flex-work</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/future-of-work-beyond-flex-work</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The future of work will go beyond flex work; we are just scratching the surface when it comes to the many opportunities. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1fe50fe3db75fc6d5437a22dc37e75d23a81dacf4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1fe50fe3db75fc6d5437a22dc37e75d23a81dacf4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1fe50fe3db75fc6d5437a22dc37e75d23a81dacf4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="The Future of Work Beyond Flex Work" src="./media_1fe50fe3db75fc6d5437a22dc37e75d23a81dacf4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="the-future-of-work-beyond-flex-work">The Future of Work Beyond Flex Work</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>For many, the introduction into a new world of work was driven by a focus on employee safety and business continuity in response to the pandemic. As we move forward into a post-pandemic era, organizations can finally shift their focus from crisis management to strategically thinking about the future of work. Now is the time to switch gears.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>It’s the heyday of flex-work models, but the future of work is so much more, with opportunities ready to be tackled along the spectrum of workforce transformation, new people practices, and next-generation HR models.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="the-mission-and-vision-of-saps-chief-future-of-work-officer">The Mission and Vision of SAP's Chief Future of Work Officer</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2022/07/christian-schmeichel-sap-chief-future-of-work-officer">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="saps-holistic-future-of-work-agenda-shaping-the-next-world-of-work">SAP’s Holistic Future of Work Agenda: Shaping the Next World of Work</h2>
  <p>Managing the future of work holistically is a strategic imperative to build a resilient, agile, and innovative organization that is future-fit for the digital age. As global provider of leading-edge human experience management (<a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/what-is-hxm-suite.html">HXM</a>) software, SAP has been putting its focus on designing a holistic future of work agenda that empowers its more than 100,000 people across the globe to thrive while creating value for its customers.</p>
  <p>The agenda is SAP’s north star to reimagine work at its core. It considers business elements and strategic HR components along three dimensions to create a sustainable work experience for its global and diverse workforce:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Future of Workforce</strong>, aiming to define a target picture for a future-proof workforce at SAP</li>
    <li><strong>Future of People Practices</strong>, making new, flexible, and healthy work “work” for everyone</li>
    <li><strong>Future of HR</strong>, reimagining the way how HR functions need to operate in future along a strategic HR master plan</li>
  </ul>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e04b008630c7dc9c8f6a1874d5435820627aa597.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e04b008630c7dc9c8f6a1874d5435820627aa597.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1e04b008630c7dc9c8f6a1874d5435820627aa597.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Infographic: SAP&#x27;s Future of Work agenda" src="./media_1e04b008630c7dc9c8f6a1874d5435820627aa597.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1986" height="1129">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p><em>Click to enlarge</em></p>
  <h2 id="future-proof-the-workforce">Future-Proof the Workforce</h2>
  <p>Accelerated digitalization and technology advances fuel the need for skill transformations across large portions of today’s workforce. The shift of skills as well as demographic changes result in a shortage of available talent, emphasizing the necessity of a clear understanding of future workforce demands. At the same time, this increases the competition for available talent in the market.</p>
  <p>SAP’s workforce transformation is based on scenario modeling to provide a clear understanding of what our workforce will need to look like five to 10 years down the road and how it will be composed. From these projections, we can derive a strategy to define the target picture with the right mix of permanent employees, gig workers, as well as the use of technology and <a href="/topics/artificial-intelligence">artificial intelligence</a> (AI). HR leaders play a crucial role by engaging in systematic resource planning in line with business strategy requirements.</p>
  <p>To future-proof their workforce, organizations need to prioritize continuous employee development through up- and reskilling. One example of this commitment is SAP’s internal talent marketplace, which offers project work, fellowships, or mentoring opportunities. Employees can take on respective assignments and apply their expertise where it is most needed while also acquiring new skills on the job: a win-win for everybody.</p>
  <h2 id="leading-edge-people-practices">Leading-Edge People Practices</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="what-is-human-experience-management">What is human experience management?</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/what-is-hxm-suite.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>People are the heartbeat of every organization. To meet ever-changing employee needs, organizations need to create innovative and effective strategies to attract, develop, engage, and retain top talent, as well as constantly challenge and evolve their people and workplace practices.</p>
  <p><strong>Empowerment Through Flexibility</strong> Flexibility is in more demand than ever, making it a strong lever for outstanding employee experience. With <a href="/topics/pledge-to-flex">Pledge to Flex</a>, SAP offers a hybrid work model that empowers employees to decide with their managers when, where, and how they work best in alignment with customer and business requirements.</p>
  <p>There is measurable success to the advantages of flexibility: SAP’s recent global future of work pulse survey revealed that over 80% of the workforce feel at least as or even more productive, satisfied, and engaged through hybrid work. The grand majority also believes that flexibility increases SAP’s attractiveness as employer.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c1940cbbe88ce3898664f0813f29bbe2f1039fc3.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c1940cbbe88ce3898664f0813f29bbe2f1039fc3.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1c1940cbbe88ce3898664f0813f29bbe2f1039fc3.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Infographic: Pledge to Flex continuum" src="./media_1c1940cbbe88ce3898664f0813f29bbe2f1039fc3.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1994" height="1127">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p><em>Click to enlarge</em></p>
  <p>Providing the best setup for every team with the right balance between office and remote work is one of the key elements in making hybrid work “work” for everyone. At the same time, the office remains the number one place to meet and support cultural affiliation, networking, and onboarding of new joiners.</p>
  <p>To promote SAP’s hybrid work approach with Pledge to Flex, we launched the internal “I’m In” campaign, encouraging employees to find the right ratio of in-office and remote work. At SAP, we see that a combination of splitting time between remote work and two to three days of in-person office work per week seems to be a good practice, given that it fosters team spirit, engagement, and excitement about the organization.</p>
  <p><strong>Enablement for a Successful Transition</strong> To navigate the added level of complexity in a hybrid landscape and build a routine, enablement and trainings are key. SAP supports employees, managers, and teams with hands-on tools and resources to balance team and individual needs while keeping customer requirements front and center.</p>
  <p>One example is the Flex Team Workshop, allowing leaders and team members to jointly determine the hybrid work setup that best fits their needs in terms of productivity, collaboration, work-life balance, and, of course, business and customer requirements. Additionally, the Meeting Workout toolkit is a gamified approach to review and declutter meetings, making each interaction more valuable to everyone. And with “Lighten the Load” and “Are you OK?,” SAP runs powerful personalized programs to enhance employee health and people sustainability, while providing stress relief.</p>
  <p>Leadership becomes more demanding in the new world of work. Leaders need to become even stronger facilitators when communicating direction and strategy in a hybrid environment. Critical skills to adjust to the evolving role of management include communicating and listening with empathy and being agile when connecting with people. Modern leadership today also includes to keep teams engaged and tackle Zoom fatigue in times of unprecedented change.</p>
  <h2 id="next-generation-hr">Next-Generation HR</h2>
  <p>A data-driven and agile HR approach is the foundation to bringing the future of workforce and people practices to life. With the help of leading-edge technology, the HR function can evolve while addressing the demand for scalable and flexible services to meet changing needs of employee and the business quickly and efficiently.</p>
  <p>Besides technological advancements, the required skills for the future HR function will evolve as well. SAP focuses on a set of key themes:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Experience management in HR, emphasizing the needs of employees, managers, or applicants from a HR consumer point of view</li>
    <li>Data-driven HR, leveraging advanced analytics to solve talent and organization related business problems and support decision-making</li>
    <li>Digital HR to reap the fruits of technological advances across the entire employee life cycle</li>
    <li>Agile HR, applying an agile mindset, values, principles, practices, and tools when serving the business</li>
  </ul>
  <p>Capabilities like digital savviness, analytical skills, data interpretation, and an agile mindset will become must-have skills for successful HR work in the new era.</p>
  <h2 id="stay-curious-and-keep-learning">Stay Curious and Keep Learning</h2>
  <p>Looking ahead, it is fair to say that we are just scratching the surface when it comes to the many opportunities to shape the future of work. With an industry-leading hybrid work model in place, SAP built a strong foundation to tackle the workplace evolution as part of a holistic future of work agenda.</p>
  <p>Getting the triad of future workforce planning, people practices, and next generation HR teams right sets the path to make organizations more future-ready while the world around us is changing at breakneck speed. In the end it all comes down to continuously learning and discovering what works best for the creation of outstanding employee experiences while driving sustainable business success — truly exciting times for HR!</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Dr. Christian Schmeichel is chief future of work officer at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/future-of-work</category>
            <category>news-tag/mental-health-well-being</category>
            <category>news-tag/pledge-to-flex</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Organizations Are Using SAP SuccessFactors Solutions to Prepare for What’s Next]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/organizations-using-sap-successfactors-2023-hr-meta-trends</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/organizations-using-sap-successfactors-2023-hr-meta-trends</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Organizations are using SAP SuccessFactors solutions to get ahead – and stay ahead – of the curve. Read about our 2023 HR meta-trends.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/mental-health-well-being</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-work-zone</category>
            <category>news-tag/well-being-at-work</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Working with Cancer: Creating a Recovery-Forward Culture]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/working-with-cancer-pledge-recovery-forward-culture</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/working-with-cancer-pledge-recovery-forward-culture</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP CEO Christian Klein recently signed the Working with Cancer Pledge to support people working with cancer in the best possible way.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/future-of-work</category>
            <category>news-tag/mental-health-well-being</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pledge to Flex: Empowerment in the Future of Work]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/pledge-to-flex-empowerment-new-world-of-work</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/pledge-to-flex-empowerment-new-world-of-work</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Success in the new world of work requires a flexible and trust-based working environment. Learn what SAP is doing.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/future-of-work</category>
            <category>news-tag/mental-health-well-being</category>
            <category>news-tag/pledge-to-flex</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-apphaus</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Take: This Holiday Season, Workers Need a Culture that Supports Healthy Habits]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/the-take-healthy-habits-at-work</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/the-take-healthy-habits-at-work</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Get SAP's take on how employees benefit from a culture that supports healthy habits at work, like rest and micro-breaks.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/perspective</category>
            <category>news-tag/future-of-work</category>
            <category>news-tag/mental-health-well-being</category>
            <category>news-tag/people-sustainability</category>
            <category>news-tag/the-take</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Drive Key Business Outcomes through People Sustainability]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/drive-key-business-outcomes-people-sustainability</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/drive-key-business-outcomes-people-sustainability</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[HR has both the opportunity and responsibility to ensure that people are at the center of work. Learn more about people sustainability.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/mental-health-well-being</category>
            <category>news-tag/people-sustainability</category>
            <category>news-tag/well-being-at-work</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How SAP SuccessFactors Innovation Can Help You Tackle Your Toughest Challenges]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/sap-successfactors-innovation-tackle-2022-hr-trends</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/sap-successfactors-innovation-tackle-2022-hr-trends</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Take on 2022 HR trends like hybrid work, diversity and inclusion, well-being, and the race for talent with SAP Successfactors solutions.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-technologies</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/mental-health-well-being</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-employee-central</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-opportunity-marketplace</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-performance-goals</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-recruiting</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-work-zone</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Holistic Future of Work Agenda for SAP: Mission and Vision of Chief Future of Work Officer Christian Schmeichel]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/christian-schmeichel-sap-chief-future-of-work-officer</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/christian-schmeichel-sap-chief-future-of-work-officer</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[What kind of work environment can SAP employees expect in the future? SAP's Chief Future of Work Officer Christian Schmeichel explains.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/future-of-work</category>
            <category>news-tag/mental-health-well-being</category>
            <category>news-tag/pledge-to-flex</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Employees Worldwide Take a Day Off for Their Mental Health]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/sap-mental-health-day-2022</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/sap-mental-health-day-2022</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Mental Health Day 2022 an additional paid day off for all employees to take space for reflection and collectively recharge.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/future-of-work</category>
            <category>news-tag/mental-health-well-being</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Deloitte Is Beating Burnout at Scale]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/how-deloitte-is-beating-burnout-at-scale</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/how-deloitte-is-beating-burnout-at-scale</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In trying to address overwork issues before they impact mental health, professional services company Deloitte is a pioneer. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/deloitte</category>
            <category>news-tag/mental-health-well-being</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-original-series-forward</category>
            <category>news-tag/well-being-at-work</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Five Dimensions to Create a Robust Employee Well-Being Strategy]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/five-dimensions-to-create-robust-employee-well-being-strategy-telus</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/five-dimensions-to-create-robust-employee-well-being-strategy-telus</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[TELUS has developed a strategy that includes five interlocking dimensions that align with emerging industry best practices. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e9ef10a46e14836a5b028351769a9327d59a02b0.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e9ef10a46e14836a5b028351769a9327d59a02b0.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1e9ef10a46e14836a5b028351769a9327d59a02b0.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Five Dimensions to Create a Robust Employee Well-Being Strategy" src="./media_1e9ef10a46e14836a5b028351769a9327d59a02b0.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="five-dimensions-to-create-a-robust-employee-well-being-strategy">Five Dimensions to Create a Robust Employee Well-Being Strategy</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>What does it mean to have a robust employee well-being strategy?</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Just ask TELUS, a leading communications and information technology company with $16 billion in annual revenue and 15.2 million customer connections spanning wireless, data, IP, voice, television, entertainment, video and security, healthcare, and agriculture. TELUS connects people to what matters most to improve lives and build a better future – and it starts with supporting and enabling its employees.</p>
  <p>TELUS’ employees have long depended on the company’s technology, devices, and services to work from home – well before remote work became all the rage. Since 2006, TELUS’ employees have enjoyed flexible work arrangements, with approximately 75% of its Canadian workforce spending a portion of time working remotely.</p>
  <p>In response to the global health <a href="/covid-19">pandemic</a>, 95% of TELUS employees work from home, including 99% of domestic call center employees. As a result, the company has achieved higher levels of workplace satisfaction and productivity, as employees are empowered to find new ways to fit work into their evolving lives.</p>
  <p>Just as TELUS was ahead of its time with its flexible work styles, the company is proving to be a pioneer in supporting employee well-being.</p>
  <p>According to Sandy McIntosh, TELUS’ executive vice president, People and Culture, and chief human resources officer, “without a robust people strategy, you won’t have a business that will thrive or succeed.”</p>
  <p>Under McIntosh’s leadership, well-being has become an ongoing cultural commitment and business imperative. TELUS has developed a strategy that recognizes the whole person and includes five interlocking dimensions that align with emerging industry best practices from the National Standard for Psychological Health and Safety in the Workplace, the Mental Health Commission of Canada, and the World Health Organization:</p>
  <ol>
    <li><strong>Physical</strong>: The company offers physical fitness and well-being centers, as well as virtual fitness classes and apps, virtual care solutions, nutritional counseling, health coaching, and more. TELUS also hosts biannual well-being challenges for employees and household family members to promote healthy habits.</li>
    <li><strong>Psychological</strong>: TELUS understands its employees are all somewhere on the well-being continuum and that each person’s situation is dynamic. The company offers industry-leading benefits coverage for mental health support and 24/7 support to mental health counselors and therapists through its Employee and Family Assistance Program and virtual care. In 2020, TELUS launched custom mental health training for leaders and over 90% have completed it. In May 2021, the company extended the reach by introducing similar training to all employees.</li>
    <li><strong>Social</strong>: TELUS creates opportunities to connect employees at work, home, and in the community through initiatives like TELUS Days of Giving, as well as supportive resources, collaboration tools, and employee resource groups that offer mentoring, networking, peer support, volunteering, and coaching.</li>
    <li><strong>Environmental</strong>: TELUS helps employees maintain healthy workspaces at home and in offices. In fact, TELUS is reimagining its offices for the future of work with work styles and well-being top of mind, offering a mix of private and collaborative spaces to support whitespace and brainstorming.</li>
    <li><strong>Financial</strong>: TELUS supports all aspects of its employees’ financial well-being, offering competitive salaries and benefits and financial literacy resources, including a financial well-being hub where employees can find tools to help them reach their financial and life goals.</li>
  </ol>
  <p>“Our job as leaders is to come at well-being from all five dimensions because well-being is not just mental and it’s not just physical,” said McIntosh. “Leaders have a responsibility to make sure that employees understand their financial situation, that the environment is appropriate, and their social connections are healthy. If you understand all of that and keep pressing the gas on all levers, you create a magical place where people want to be,” McIntosh explained.</p>
  <p>For TELUS, it’s deeper than providing technology and tools. The company is working to create a common language, build leadership competencies and practices, and use data insights to shift mindsets and behaviors.</p>
  <p><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm/hxm-suite.html">SAP SuccessFactors Human Experience Management (HXM) Suite</a> provides TELUS with the technology to create a company culture dedicated to flexible work that in turn supports employee well-being. With cloud-based tools, employees can tap into engaging, individualized experiences. The company knows that a better employee experience will empower the workforce to provide better experiences to customers.</p>
  <p>Very rarely does a superior or business leader say an employee must give up the things they love. But McIntosh says that employees often feel this way, especially after they have been promoted or move into a new role. Employees who quit a beloved hobby or stop exercising because they feel they don’t have the time may soon see the rest of their lives – including their performance at work – begin to free-fall.</p>
  <p>“Nobody explicitly says to you, ‘Stop doing these things,’” said McIntosh. “But also, unfortunately, nobody explicitly says to you, ‘Keep doing these things.’ We have to, as leaders, overtly come out and say, ‘Is your self-care in check?’”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="watch-forward-a-new-series-about-a-better-human-experience-at-work">Watch Forward, a new series about a better human experience at work</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="http://www.sap.com/HXMForward">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="making-good-on-a-commitment-to-employee-well-being">Making Good on a Commitment to Employee Well-Being</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="put-employees-at-the-heart-of-everything-you-do-with-sap-successfactors">Put employees at the heart of everything you do with SAP SuccessFactors</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm/hxm-suite.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>At TELUS, team member well-being initiatives aren’t designed to simply make the company look good. Rather, they exist to make employees feel good and perform at their best.</p>
  <p>“We’re really focused on helping leaders understand we don’t mean fluffy stuff,” said McIntosh. “We don’t mean every Friday we’re having a pizza party. We mean that you understand that you’re leading other human beings.”</p>
  <p>Take, for example, one TELUS benefit that provides employees, including their dependents, with up to CAD5,000 per year to spend on psychologists, psychotherapists, and social workers – a benefit unmatched by its peers. TELUS also enables its team members to connect with registered mental health clinicians through a range of virtual care solutions and provides a free, unlimited subscription to the leading mental fitness app Calm.</p>
  <p>“Human beings are complex, and we need to look at all five dimensions and put all of these ingredients together,” said McIntosh.</p>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div>To learn more, <a href="https://www.sap.com/HXMForwardAdamGrant">watch Sandy McIntosh’s interview</a> in an episode of Forward with Adam Grant.</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>Carolyn Judge Phillip is VP of Corporate Marketing for SAP SuccessFactors. <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2021/10/14/5-dimensions-to-create-a-robust-employee-well-being-strategy/?sh=3d0c882a5e18">This also appeared on SAP BrandVoice on Forbes.</a></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/mental-health-well-being</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-original-series-forward</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
            <category>news-tag/well-being-at-work</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Four Essential Leadership Qualities for Modern Times]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/four-essential-leadership-qualities-for-modern-times</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/four-essential-leadership-qualities-for-modern-times</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In this new age of work, leaders need to adapt their leadership strategies if they are to continue to engage and inspire their teams.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11fc60b50473239cda925a21876f7cc901f507e86.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11fc60b50473239cda925a21876f7cc901f507e86.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_11fc60b50473239cda925a21876f7cc901f507e86.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Four Essential Leadership Qualities for Modern Times" src="./media_11fc60b50473239cda925a21876f7cc901f507e86.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="four-essential-leadership-qualities-for-modern-times">Four Essential Leadership Qualities for Modern Times</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Steve Jobs, Satya Nadella, Bill Gates. What do these three people have in common? Of course, they have all made their mark on the technology world, but they are also exceptional leaders. All three possess a clear vision, demonstrate the courage required to realize that vision, and display integrity, honesty, and humility even in the most challenging times.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As someone operating in a leadership position, I often look to these three for inspiration. Leading teams can be complex in our digital age, where remote working is commonplace and seldom do you get the opportunity to sit with colleagues or clients face-to-face.</p>
  <p>There’s no doubt that in this new age of work, leaders need to adapt their strategies if they are to continue to engage their teams and inspire high performance. Taking some of the lessons I have learned from other leaders, I wanted to outline four vital qualities leaders need to succeed in modern times.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="simplify-digital-transformation-with-sap-services-and-support">Simplify digital transformation with SAP Services and Support</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/support.html#services-support-offerings">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="authenticity">Authenticity</h2>
  <p>All the leaders I mentioned have one thing in common: their credibility. I believe it’s essential to start from a place of authenticity. How you manage people should sit comfortably with who you are. For less experienced leaders especially, who may still be growing in confidence, don’t attempt to be someone you are not. Not only will this be difficult to maintain, but it could also be transparent to others.</p>
  <p>Authenticity is vital for another reason. Like your team, you will have tough days, you may feel exposed, and you will wish you had approached certain things differently. These things are what make us human. It may seem counterintuitive, but acknowledging our weaknesses takes strength and often earns more respect.</p>
  <p>And it’s in times of adversity and through shared experiences that we can connect more deeply with our teams. Humor is also an excellent coping mechanism and a way to forge bonds.</p>
  <h2 id="approachability">Approachability</h2>
  <p>Influential leaders are like magnets and draw people to them. Some tough and powerful personalities may be revered but, conversely, can also be feared. This fear can become a barrier that could inhibit your people from being open about their mistakes or seeking your advice. If you want to build a reputation for openness, greet everyone, make time to chat – even if virtually – and give them your full attention. And this applies to people you don’t work with directly, including catering and cleaning staff. Why? Because it says that everyone matters to you.</p>
  <h2 id="innovation">Innovation</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="leading-large-what-the-marketplace-wants-from-leaders-today">Leading Large: What the Marketplace Wants from Leaders Today</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://insights.sap.com/social-responsibility-of-business/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Innovation starts with having a vision, possessing an adaptive mindset, and being purpose-driven. It also demands collaborative leadership behavior to enable the exploration of ideas. Good leaders create and empower interdisciplinary teams and foster a culture of agile learning.</p>
  <p>Also, creating a culture where everyone feels their contributions and ideas are valued and welcomed helps innovation. Often, some of the quietest or most introverted people have the most brilliant ideas. Unless they are encouraged and empowered to speak up, their contributions will be lost.</p>
  <h2 id="empathy">Empathy</h2>
  <p>Empathy calls for compassion in communication and being an engaged and active listener. According to research referenced by <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/tracybrower/2021/09/19/empathy-is-the-most-important-leadership-skill-according-to-research">Forbes</a>, empathy is a critical leadership skill. It’s necessary because people are experiencing multiple layers of stress, including the impact of <a href="/covid-19">the pandemic</a>. And when people are stressed, research also shows they find it harder to concentrate, take longer to finish tasks, and can compromise their physical and mental health.</p>
  <p>How can you lead with empathy? You will be more successful when you not only consider how others might be feeling but when you reach out to them personally. For example, a simple inquiry <a href="/2021/03/mental-health-in-the-workplace">can go a long way</a>: “I’ve noticed you’ve not been yourself lately, is there anything you would like to talk about or that I can do to help?” You don’t need to be an expert in mental health – just pay attention and take your cues from your team members on how best to respond.</p>
  <p>Creating opportunities for people to feel heard and understood makes a tremendous difference. But of course, strong leadership requires action too, and how this plays out will depend on the circumstances. At SAP, we believe a healthy business starts with healthy people. We promote a caring culture where our employees can stay healthy and balanced in a highly competitive environment. SAP’s <a href="https://www.sap.com/corporate/en/purpose/mental-health.html">global health and well-being programs</a> are integral to our investment in our people.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Guido Schlief is senior vice president and head of Services for Middle &#x26; Eastern Europe at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/covid-19</category>
            <category>news-tag/leadership</category>
            <category>news-tag/mental-health-well-being</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[COVID-19: a Disruptor and a Navigator]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/world-mental-health-day-2021-covid-19-disruptor-navigator</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/world-mental-health-day-2021-covid-19-disruptor-navigator</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[For World Mental Health Day 2021, SAP is encouraging everyone to lighten the load of their stress and do something for their health.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_13e1a4d973b6b0a5399a97a75c8743b66dff33dea.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_13e1a4d973b6b0a5399a97a75c8743b66dff33dea.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_13e1a4d973b6b0a5399a97a75c8743b66dff33dea.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="COVID-19: a Disruptor and a Navigator" src="./media_13e1a4d973b6b0a5399a97a75c8743b66dff33dea.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="covid-19-a-disruptor-and-a-navigator">COVID-19: a Disruptor and a Navigator</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Without question, COVID-19 is a disruptor that is challenging organizations and employees alike. It is also an unprecedented test and navigator to every aspect of how we live and how we build a successful future of work. Marking World Mental Health Day on October 10 is a good reminder to prioritize our holistic well-being — as individuals and organizations.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="mapping-the-course-in-uncharted-waters">Mapping the Course in Uncharted Waters</h2>
  <p>The world we currently work and live in is mostly uncharted. As humans, we like to stay in our comfort zone and these enforced changes to societal living are causing stress for many. While employee stress poses a real risk for organizations, finding the best strategies as organizations and individuals to cope with stress is also an opportunity to explore and shape the future of work.</p>
  <p>The recent Deloitte Human Capital Trends <a href="https://hbr.org/sponsored/2021/04/thriving-in-the-future-of-work-means-focusing-on-your-people">survey</a> revealed that 96% of respondents believe organizations are responsible for employees’ well-being. SAP has been a front-runner in <a href="https://www.sap.com/docs/download/investors/2019/sap-2019-integrated-report.pdf#page=75">connecting a healthy culture with business success</a> since 1972, putting customers and employees at the very center of any decision. Earlier in 2021, SAP was one of the first organizations to announce its <a href="/2021/06/pledge-to-flex-future-of-work-at-sap">Pledge to Flex</a>, an entirely flexible and trust-based promise to provide a setup that fits every role, style, and location.</p>
  <h2 id="employees-charting-future-of-work">Employees Charting Future of Work</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-more-stories-about-saps-focus-on-mental-health-and-well-being-365-days-a-year">Read more stories about SAP's focus on mental health and well-being 365 days a year</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/topics/mental-health-well-being">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>One thing is certain: the blurred line between work and private life is individualizing the future of work. Research from McKinsey estimated there will be <a href="https://www.mckinsey.com/featured-insights/future-of-work/the-future-of-work-after-covid-19">four to five times more remote work than before the pandemic</a>, which will prompt a large shift in the geography of work, workspaces, and soft skills needed to stay healthy and balanced in an autonomous virtual world.</p>
  <p>Today, employers are at a critical time in strengthening employee’s sense of belonging, job satisfaction, and ownership of self-care, and at the same time provide the leadership framework of navigation to ensure sustainable business success.</p>
  <p>“I am proud of the innovative KPIs around measuring healthy culture and health-related productivity loss that allow us to chart and track our course in the future of work,” says Christian Schmeichel, chief future of work officer at SAP. “Understanding and respecting people’s needs in regard to their health and well-being pays off as it keeps them happy and productive.”</p>
  <h2 id="beacons-and-early-warning-signals">Beacons and Early Warning Signals</h2>
  <p>Balancing the demands of work and private life is challenging, and stress symptoms can affect our body, thoughts, and feelings. Left unmanaged or out of control, stress can contribute to many health problems. Add an inactive lifestyle and maybe a sub-optimal work set-up at home, and you have the perfect storm for musculoskeletal pain, risk of toxic stress, presenteeism, burnout, or mental health challenges.</p>
  <p>In the UK, stress, depression, or anxiety and musculoskeletal disorders accounted for about two-thirds of days lost due to work-related ill health before the pandemic (<a href="https://www.hse.gov.uk/statistics/dayslost.htm">HSE</a>), while the <a href="https://www.healthline.com/health-news/people-feeling-more-stress-now-than-any-point-since-the-pandemic-began#Experiencing-collective-trauma">American Psychological Association’s survey “Stress in America 2021”</a> reports people are experiencing their highest levels of stress since the beginning of the pandemic.</p>
  <h2 id="setting-sail-to-lighten-the-load">Setting Sail to ‘Lighten the Load’</h2>
  <p>Tightening the sails from <a href="/2020/10/are-you-ok-mental-health-initiative">Are You OK? mental health initiative</a>, SAP is setting course for a six-week “get moving” campaign, helping employees create self-awareness and take action for their health. SAP is proud to continue partnering and supporting <a href="https://osha.europa.eu/en/highlights/lighten-load-eu-osha-launches-healthy-workplaces-campaign-2020-2022">EU-OSHA healthy workplaces</a> campaigns.</p>
  <p>Its current campaign, “Lighten the Load,” empowers people to prevent, alleviate, or recover from the stresses we feel on our own shoulders every day. The employee campaign has over 40 live events for employees to discover and experience new ways to lighten their load by signing up for physical activity challenges, demonstrations, and practice sessions with ergonomic, physiotherapy, and physical fitness experts. We wish for our employees to discover their way to lighten the load and reach their full potential in work and private life.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="a-healthy-business-starts-with-healthy-people-visit-sapcommentalhealth">A healthy business starts with healthy people: visit sap.com/mentalhealth</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/purpose-and-sustainability/social-responsibility/mental-health.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="on-world-mental-health-day-2021-do-something-for-your-health">On <a href="https://www.who.int/campaigns/world-mental-health-day/2021">World Mental Health Day 2021</a>, do something for your health.</h3>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Natalie Lotzmann is chief medical officer and global head of Health and Well-Being at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="pledge-to-flex-the-future-of-work-at-sap-is-100-flexible-and-trust-based">Pledge to Flex: The Future of Work at SAP Is 100% Flexible and Trust Based</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/06/pledge-to-flex-future-of-work-at-sap">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/covid-19</category>
            <category>news-tag/future-of-work</category>
            <category>news-tag/mental-health-well-being</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Setting Our Minds to Being Kind]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/setting-our-minds-to-being-kind</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/setting-our-minds-to-being-kind</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[For the second year in a row, SAP stands proud with Born This Way Foundation and its #BeKind21 campaign to foster kindness worldwide.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_12ba02c059d9104e356e1deda2511e1412227046c.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_12ba02c059d9104e356e1deda2511e1412227046c.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_12ba02c059d9104e356e1deda2511e1412227046c.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Setting Our Minds to Being Kind" src="./media_12ba02c059d9104e356e1deda2511e1412227046c.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="setting-our-minds-to-being-kind">Setting Our Minds to Being Kind</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>One of my favorite quotes ever shared is from Maya Angelou: “People will forget what you said, people will forget what you did, but people will never forget how you made them feel.”</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>We have reached a critical point in humanity where we need to collectively take pause – as individuals, communities, companies, societies at large – and think about how our actions, or lack thereof, make others feel. We must ask ourselves the tough questions: Are we making people feel valued? Appreciated? Loved? Heard? Empowered? Inspired? Confident? Hopeful? In order to create a sustainable future where our economy, environment, and society prosper for years to come, everyone must search within themselves and do their part to create a better world for all.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="kindness-is-the-contagion-that-brings-us-together">Kindness Is the Contagion That Brings Us Together</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2020/09/bekind21-campaign-kindness-contagious">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="bekind21-in-2021">#BeKind21 in 2021</h2>
  <p>For the <a href="/2020/09/bekind21-campaign-kindness-contagious">second year</a> in a row, SAP stands proud with <a href="https://bornthisway.foundation/">Born This Way Foundation</a> (BTWF) and its <a href="https://bornthisway.foundation/bekind21/">#BeKind21 campaign</a>. BTWF was founded by Lady Gaga and her mom, Cynthia Germanotta. The foundation supports the mental health of young people, with a mission of creating a kinder, braver world. At SAP, our purpose is to help the world run better and improve people’s lives. With a caring work culture grounded in psychological safety, SAP aspires to a world with zero inequality where people genuinely care about each other and feel a sense of belonging. We see it as our responsibility to <a href="http://www.sap.com/mentalhealth">lead by example</a> in removing the stigma around mental health disorders in the workplace, and kindness is a powerful lever to help get us there.</p>
  <h2 id="the-science-of-kindness">The Science of Kindness</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="a-healthy-business-starts-with-healthy-people">A healthy business starts with healthy people</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="http://www.sap.com/mentalhealth">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Kindness has the power to turn darkness into light, cold into warmth, loneliness into connection. Acts of kindness – whether random or deliberate, small or large, simple or complex – make everyone involved feel good: the giver, the recipient, and even the observer. <a href="https://www.mayoclinichealthsystem.org/hometown-health/speaking-of-health/the-art-of-kindness">Science shows</a> that kindness benefits our minds and our bodies. In fact, it tends to be contagious.</p>
  <p>The healing powers of kindness are well documented and recognized by the world’s foremost <a href="https://www.cedars-sinai.org/blog/science-of-kindness.html">medical experts</a>. Did you know that performing – and even witnessing – small, simple acts of kindness can produce oxytocin, also known as “the love hormone,” and can improve our overall health and well-being? Kindness is also known to release dopamine, a feel-good brain chemical, and boost serotonin, a neurotransmitter that helps regulate mood. Similar to the type of high we feel when we exercise, being kind can lead to a “<a href="https://www.psychologytoday.com/us/blog/emotional-nourishment/201711/why-random-acts-kindness-matter-your-well-being">helper’s high</a>.”</p>
  <p>Imagine if we could spread kindness farther, wider, and faster than the speed of <a href="/covid-19">COVID-19</a>. Do we have the power – as all of humankind – to counter the negative effects of the pandemic by killing it with kindness? I believe we do if we set our minds to it.</p>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div>.<a href="https://twitter.com/ZequeMa?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@ZequeMa</a> 🇦🇷 is kicking off <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/BeKind21?src=hash&#x26;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#BeKind21</a> by showing kindness to his best friend and donating to a charity that helps others like him! <a href="https://twitter.com/SAPLatinAmerica?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@SAPLatinAmerica</a> <a href="https://t.co/Rq1a4pK8Fx">pic.twitter.com/Rq1a4pK8Fx</a></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div>— Life at SAP (@LifeatSAP) <a href="https://twitter.com/LifeatSAP/status/1433006798819180545?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">September 1, 2021</a></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="join-us-lifeatsap">Join Us @LifeatSAP</h2>
  <p>From September 1st through the 21st, we’re curating acts of kindness from SAP employees all around the world and sharing them on our social channels.</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Follow along with us on <a href="https://www.instagram.com/lifeatsap/">Instagram</a>, <a href="https://twitter.com/LifeatSAP">Twitter</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/lifeatsap">Facebook</a>, or through the hashtags #LifeAtSAP and #BeKind21.</li>
    <li>Make the #BeKind21 pledge. Sign up and <a href="https://bornthisway.foundation/current-programs/bekind21/">generate your own #BeKind21</a> calendar to share on your personal accounts with the hashtags #LifeAtSAP and #BeKind21.</li>
  </ul>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Julie Barrier is global vice president of Purpose and Sustainability Marketing at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/covid-19</category>
            <category>news-tag/life-at-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/mental-health-well-being</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Let’s Talk: The Most Important Thing You Can Do for Mental Health in Your Workplace]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/03/mental-health-in-the-workplace</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/03/mental-health-in-the-workplace</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[An important first step to fostering positive mental health in the workplace is destigmatizing conversations around the topic. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e073d12d42a05889c3c308804d3833b0e44dd074.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e073d12d42a05889c3c308804d3833b0e44dd074.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1e073d12d42a05889c3c308804d3833b0e44dd074.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Let’s Talk: The Most Important Thing You Can Do for Mental Health in Your Workplace" src="./media_1e073d12d42a05889c3c308804d3833b0e44dd074.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="lets-talk-the-most-important-thing-you-can-do-for-mental-health-in-your-workplace">Let’s Talk: The Most Important Thing You Can Do for Mental Health in Your Workplace</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>The <a href="/covid-19">COVID-19</a> public health crisis has given new urgency to the discussion around mental health in the workplace. Since March 2020, employees have been coping with unprecedented levels of social disconnection, financial worries, insomnia, and anxiety about health and safety.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>It is no secret that employees who are laboring under strain and emotional exhaustion carry this stress into the workplace, where it surfaces as reduced motivation, performance, and cognitive capabilities.</p>
  <p>“Mental health was already identified as a critical employee concern prior to COVID-19,” says Dr. Autumn Krauss, chief scientist at SAP SuccessFactors. An organizational psychologist with a specialization in occupational health psychology, Krauss works with organizations to develop strategies that support employee well-being in a holistic sense. This includes mental health in the workplace, a topic that is receiving heightened attention in these challenging times. “I do see the issue being more serious and pervasive as mental health concerns have been exacerbated by the pandemic,” she says.</p>
  <p>Even before the pandemic, the economic impact of poor mental health has been staggering. The <a href="https://www.who.int/teams/mental-health-and-substance-use/mental-health-in-the-workplace">World Health Organization</a> (WHO) estimates that the loss of productivity from depression and anxiety cost the global economy 1 trillion dollars each year. However, there is hope in even the smallest actions. The WHO found that for every dollar invested in treatment for common mental health disorders, there is a return of four dollars in improved health and productivity.</p>
  <p>Employers may be unclear about their role, or what their contribution should be, when it comes to supporting the mental health needs of their workforce. It can be difficult for managers to gauge how their employees are actually coping with stress, especially while many employees are working from home offices and have limited options to use vacation days. What’s an appropriate response? What’s off-limits?</p>
  <h2 id="sap-offers-employees-a-mental-health-day">SAP Offers Employees a Mental Health Day</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="mental-health-day-sap-offers-employees-a-chance-to-recharge">Mental Health Day: SAP Offers Employees a Chance to Recharge</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/03/mental-health-day-sap-employees">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>When a recent employee pulse survey, powered by Qualtrics, revealed that one-third of SAP employees have stress levels that are higher than their satisfaction levels – with 61% reporting that they were working slightly above capacity – SAP responded by <a href="/2021/03/mental-health-day-sap-employees">allocating a Mental Health Day</a> on April 27 as a way to encourage employees to unwind and recharge.</p>
  <p>SAP’s Mental Health Day is a company-sponsored global holiday for all employees to unplug from the office and reconnect with their families and other important areas of their lives that may be neglected, including physical health, hobbies, and social connections.</p>
  <p>“As an SAP employee, I appreciate the recognition by our executive leadership on the importance of employee well-being and their investment in our mental health by allocating a working day to this cause across our entire global SAP workforce,” says Krauss. She advocates for sustaining the benefits from the company-wide holiday by fostering new ways of thinking and acting that promote mental health and well-being every day – so that “it’s just the way we do things around here.”</p>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11e6606515ad688ba0daa1b85dc1daedcc732ca86.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11e6606515ad688ba0daa1b85dc1daedcc732ca86.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_11e6606515ad688ba0daa1b85dc1daedcc732ca86.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Announces Global Mental Health Day" src="./media_11e6606515ad688ba0daa1b85dc1daedcc732ca86.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://youtu.be/OOrsZNcBrcA">SAP Announces Global Mental Health Day</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="resetting-company-culture-creating-a-safe-environment-to-speak-up">Resetting Company Culture: Creating a Safe Environment to Speak Up</h2>
  <p>Setting aside a day for employee mental health is just one strategy employers can take to support the well-being of their workforces. Each company’s approach will be as unique as its culture.</p>
  <p>Regardless of the company’s size, geography, or demographics, however, the single most important thing managers can do to support their employees’ emotional well-being is to remove the stigma around mental health. This helps ensure that important conversations about employees’ mental health can happen as naturally as discussions about training and upskilling. It is imperative that employees feel it is safe to speak up and seek the help they need without fear of repercussions or consequences to their reputation or advancement opportunities.</p>
  <p>When employees feel that they can be authentic about who they are, the result is often improved engagement, better performance, and better employee retention. This, however, requires a cross-organization commitment, with all managers on board in providing a psychologically safe environment for employees.</p>
  <p>“I’m a firm believer that fostering positive mental health at work is not HR’s job,” Krauss says. “<a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm/hxm-suite.html">HR can provide resources</a> for individuals to build better personal coping skills and get support, but HR would have no visibility into employees’ everyday behavior and how it might be changing as a first sign that they could be struggling with their well-being.”</p>
  <p>Therefore, when crafting a mental health strategy, employers are advised to take a preventative approach, rather than a reactive approach, so that employees get the help they need <em>before</em> the appearance of serious negative mental health symptoms, such as depression and burnout. The overarching goal should be to not only reduce negative mental health, but also to foster positive mental health.</p>
  <p>Krauss argues that it is the organizations’ responsibility to create the team norms, work environment, and culture that foster positive mental health. Employees should feel encouraged to raise their hands early if they are struggling and feel confident that their managers will recognize their distress, even if they don’t raise their hands.</p>
  <p>Rather than relying solely on individual-focused policies, initiatives, or benefits, destigmatizing mental health in many organizations will require a reset of corporate culture starting at the executive level. As Krauss emphasizes, “This is only achieved by managers role modeling that they are investing in their own well-being, and well-being is important enough for a continuous dialogue with their team members.”</p>
  <h2 id="join-the-conversation-on-sap-purpose-network-live">Join the Conversation on SAP Purpose Network Live</h2>
  <p>Connect with the experts who are moving business in new directions. Join <a href="https://events.sap.com/sap-purpose-network-live/en/home">SAP Purpose Network Live</a> for an open discussion on the importance of fostering a company culture that supports the mental health of its employees and how to kick-start the conversation around mental health in your organization.</p>
  <h3 id="starting-the-conversation-arounddestigmatizing-mental-health-in-the-workplace"><a href="https://events.sap.com/sap-purpose-network-live/en/agendas">Starting the Conversation AroundDestigmatizing Mental Health in the Workplace</a></h3>
  <ul>
    <li>Thursday, March 25, 2021</li>
    <li>11:30 a.m. ET | 5:30 p.m. CET | 11:30 p.m. SGT</li>
    <li><strong>Speakers:</strong>
      <ul>
        <li>Waheeda Rahman White, director, Engagement, Inclusion and Mental Health, Bell</li>
        <li>Laurie Ruettimann, author and HR consultant, Punk Rock HR</li>
        <li>Dr. Autumn D. Krauss, chief scientist, SAP SuccessFactors HR Research Team, SAP</li>
        <li>Kim Lessley, moderator, global director, Solution Marketing, SAP</li>
      </ul>
    </li>
  </ul>
  <p><strong><a href="https://webinars.sap.com/starting-the-conversation-mental-health-workforce/en/registration.aspx">Register here</a></strong></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/mental-health-well-being</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mental Health Day: SAP Offers Employees a Chance to Recharge]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/03/mental-health-day-sap-employees</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/03/mental-health-day-sap-employees</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP has scheduled a mental health day for all employees in reponse to the difficulties of dealing with health challenges amid COVID-19.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/covid-19</category>
            <category>news-tag/in-focus</category>
            <category>news-tag/mental-health-well-being</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Make 2021 Count: Your Guide to Creating the Best Employee Experience]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/create-best-employee-experience</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/create-best-employee-experience</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Companies that do more for employee well-being see real business impact. Read to learn how you can improve your employee experience.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/mental-health-well-being</category>
            <category>news-tag/well-being-at-work</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>