<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/deloitte/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Business Technology Platform Helps Deloitte and Its Customers Gain Competitive Market Advantage]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/sap-btp-helps-deloitte-gain-competitive-market-advantage</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/sap-btp-helps-deloitte-gain-competitive-market-advantage</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[For Deloitte, the flexibility, volume of services available, and continuous evolving of the platform are what make SAP BTP special.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1abc228ba68990b2059c06dc6b90a8a59783abd7a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1abc228ba68990b2059c06dc6b90a8a59783abd7a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1abc228ba68990b2059c06dc6b90a8a59783abd7a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Business Technology Platform Helps Deloitte and Its Customers Gain Competitive Market Advantage" src="./media_1abc228ba68990b2059c06dc6b90a8a59783abd7a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-business-technology-platform-helps-deloitte-and-its-customers-gain-competitive-market-advantage">SAP Business Technology Platform Helps Deloitte and Its Customers Gain Competitive Market Advantage</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Jon Baukham, a director in Technical Services at <a href="https://www2.deloitte.com/uk/en/explore/home.html?icid=site_selector_uk">Deloitte</a>, is clear on the role SAP Business Technology Platform (<a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform.html">SAP BTP</a>) plays in his company’s long-term strategy.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“One of our key differentiators is how we put innovation at the core of what we do,” he says. “Our experience with SAP BTP, the opportunities it provides for innovation, and the value we have leveraged for our customers is intrinsic to us as a business. So many organizations, large and small, deliver transformation projects. But what does ‘good’ look like and how can that be delivered? These are the questions we always ask ourselves. Developing solutions that solve real business challenges, across industries and lines of business, and demonstrating how they can be applied to a customer’s business is pivotal in strengthening existing relationships and winning new customers.”</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="innovate-with-agility-sap-btp-with-premium-plus-package-for-rise-with-sap">Innovate with Agility: SAP BTP with Premium Plus Package for RISE with SAP</h3>
        <p><em><a href="/2023/10/sap-btp-with-premium-plus-package-for-rise-with-sap">Read the feature</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Baukham, who’s an SAP technical architect by profession, specializing in SAP BTP, was – together with colleagues – instrumental in collaborating with SAP on the platform’s development, helping in the very early days of its inception to shape it into the platform known and used today by partners worldwide.</p>
  <p>Indeed, Baukham’s team made a name for itself by developing web-based user interfaces on top of what were then SAP’s fairly basic solutions and, therefore, became involved in the very early discussions about how to update and move SAP forward.</p>
  <p>“We recognized the platform as being the best way to innovate around the core to give our clients something that met their very specific needs,” he says. “The platform has now evolved and that approach is now standard, but in the early days it wasn’t.”</p>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16bad37eec38740fc8d301bfd613671a464ae60b3.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16bad37eec38740fc8d301bfd613671a464ae60b3.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_16bad37eec38740fc8d301bfd613671a464ae60b3.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Deloitte - an SAP BTP Story" src="./media_16bad37eec38740fc8d301bfd613671a464ae60b3.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=76mqQ231k2Q">Deloitte – an SAP BTP Story</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>He says that <a href="/topics/business-technology-platform">SAP BTP</a> is a way for the team to “demo the art of the possible,” delivering a completely different user-experience or bringing a different vision to SAP solutions. It’s a platform that allows customers to leverage their investment in SAP and gives them an advantage in the market, whether through finding more efficient ways of working or identifying and opening up new revenue streams.</p>
  <p>“Meeting with a client and talking about integration and databases is not going to cut it with the people in the room that are there to make business decisions and who ultimately will be using the technology. They’re not interested,” he says. “It’s more helpful to discuss SAP BTP and how it can be the platform for continuous innovation and for delivering real benefits to a business. We change the conversation so that it’s about the benefits the tech can bring, where we can see things need to be improved, either based on other customers’ similar challenges or from the experience of our vast network of SAP consultants.”</p>
  <p>SAP BTP is “the platform where we can do things differently,” he continues, and is “central” to many conversations with existing or prospective customers. While the team can use SAP BTP to manage the standard things – like integrating SAP solutions to other systems, closing any gaps that have been identified, or looking at analytics – Baukham is clear that the real benefit comes from how the platform is used holistically. “This isn’t about focusing on one particular area, but how you can use all the surfaces together to deliver a much better experience. This is about putting the users first: it has to be easy to use otherwise people avoid using it.”</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-btp-data-and-analytics-ai-application-development-automation-and-integration-in-one-unified-environment">SAP BTP: Data and analytics, AI, application development, automation, and integration in one unified environment</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In client discussions, Deloitte covers all aspects of the platform. “Regardless of where clients are on their SAP journey – whether they’re on a legacy system or ready to do a transformation – we look at whether they need a UI refresh, whether they need to simplify some apps to make it easier for transformation, whether it’s greenfield, brownfield, or selective. We look at where SAP BTP lays in that,” Baukham explains. “But we also then have the conversations around what’s next – once the transformation is complete, how can we help them to address other pain points that may not have been solved. Do we bring in more analytics so they have the data on hand to make decisions quicker? Do we look at the smarter technologies, the bots that can help to perform some of the more mundane tasks more easily? If they’re doing the same processes or making the same kind of decisions, do they need someone to do that or can machine learning do that for them instead? We’ve always been good at pushing the boundaries and exploring what’s possible. When augmented reality first came out, a lot of competitors were using it for gimmicky things. What we did was to take CEO reports and explain and display them in 3D so people could interact with them. What we do is to try to turn these new technologies into a business case: how you can use these technologies through SAP BTP to enhance your experience?”</p>
  <p>The three things Baukham likes best about SAP BTP are the flexibility, the sheer volume of services available that can all integrate smoothly with SAP, and the fact that the platform is continually evolving. “Because it moves forward and embraces new tech, you don’t feel it’s ever going to get old. It grows with the times,” he says.</p>
  <p>He also says it’s inspiring to see how the platform can be used in different ways. While it is largely used to support internal processes, for some of Deloitte’s customers it has been used to help deliver external services, opening up completely new revenue streams.</p>
  <p>“It’s a completely different way of looking at SAP BTP,” Baukham says. “They’re looking at the layer underneath the analytics, the federation of data across multiple sources. While you’re not looking to replicate that – that data stays where it is – you can still model it through some common data models, KPIs, and dashboards and some of our customers have done that and brought real benefit to their end customers. In both cases, we put ourselves in the shoes of their end customers to develop a new approach. That’s down to the innovative nature of SAP BTP and the way you can make it work for you.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-sap-news-delivered-to-your-inbox-once-a-week">Get the latest SAP news delivered to your inbox once a week</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/nl/sap-news-center-newsletter/index.html">Sign up now</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/deloitte</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Smart Factory @ Wichita: Experience the Future of Manufacturing]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/09/the-smart-factory-wichita-future-of-manufacturing</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/09/the-smart-factory-wichita-future-of-manufacturing</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[At The Smart Factory @ Wichita, visitors learn about digital transformation and Industry 4.0 in an immersive experience. Read about it here.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/deloitte</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-4-0</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Power and Scale of a Global Sustainability Ecosystem]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/01/global-sustainability-ecosystem-power-scale</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/01/global-sustainability-ecosystem-power-scale</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Hear from the SAP sustainability ecosystem about tackling challenges and delivering a path to innovation no individual competitor can match.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d6145a5beac2544e30db5fc832b0b98396b71881.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d6145a5beac2544e30db5fc832b0b98396b71881.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1d6145a5beac2544e30db5fc832b0b98396b71881.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="The Power and Scale of a Global Sustainability Ecosystem" src="./media_1d6145a5beac2544e30db5fc832b0b98396b71881.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="the-power-and-scale-of-a-global-sustainability-ecosystem">The Power and Scale of a Global Sustainability Ecosystem</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>According to a recent <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/10/92351eae-017e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">SAP and Alpha Sense survey</a>, most businesses have not embedded sustainability into their core strategies. In some cases, corporations see sustainability management as a regulatory and compliance challenge rather than a strategic opportunity for economic and social growth.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Therefore, businesses run different technologies and end up operating in silos, which prevent them from connecting financial outcomes with non-financial metrics. Additionally, companies can view sustainability as an after-the-fact reporting activity without any influence in its executive decisions.</p>
  <p>Today, more than ever, businesses need to holistically manage their business models across their supply chains, operations, and people agenda.</p>
  <p>At the recent COP26 climate conference, <a href="/2021/11/cop26-reflections-enabling-business-action-and-planetary-ambition">business and government leaders agreed on the urgency</a> to reinvent their business models to accelerate sustainable business performance. Business leaders want to meet regulatory requirements, improve efficiency in their processes, and create responsible products and services.</p>
  <p>As the leading enterprise resource management company, SAP has committed to help customers in their digital transformation to make sustainability profitable and profitability sustainable.</p>
  <p>In this digital transformation, SAP’s approach is based on providing visibility and transparency to make sustainable decisions from the CEO’s office to the end user, connecting business processes to embed sustainability into all business functions — from carbon accounting to gender equality — and providing a global ecosystem of partners than can help SAP to scale impact through businesses of all sizes and across all industries around the world.</p>
  <p>Providing a global ecosystem to help businesses is core to SAP’s DNA.</p>
  <p>Julia White, chief marketing and solutions officer and member of the Executive Board at SAP SE, points out: “<a href="/">Sustainability is a team sport</a>. No company or organization can do it alone. We work with many of the world’s best companies who support our vision and work together with us every day to deliver sustainable outcomes for our customers.”</p>
  <p>Working with SAP, <a href="https://www.sap.com/partner.html">partners</a> advance market development for sustainable solutions. They turn ideas and imperatives into compelling paths to action that leverage SAP solutions. Together, we advocate with thought leadership and galvanize collective efforts and methodologies in industry forums like the World Economic Forum, World Business Council on Sustainable Development, and United Nations Organizations.</p>
  <p>SAP and its ecosystem accelerate sustainable innovation as a central element of the intelligent enterprise. Through co-innovation as well as solution and content partnerships, SAP brings more complete solutions to market faster, benefiting our customers and the planet. More broadly, SAP serves as a key player in a thriving ecosystem of sustainability innovation — helping customers more easily capitalize on emerging solutions that tie closely to their digital core. With its robust network, SAP can deliver a path to sustainability innovation that no other individual competitor can match.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <table>
          <thead>
            <tr>
              <th colspan="2">Promo</th>
            </tr>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td>
                <h3 id="choose-both-profitability-and-sustainability-with-sap">Choose both profitability and sustainability with SAP</h3>
              </td>
              <td><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/purpose-and-sustainability/economics.html">Learn more</a></strong></td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
        <h2 id="accenture">Accenture</h2>
        <p>“With fewer than 2,000 working days left to 2030, the time to rewire business top to bottom to meet the UN Sustainable Development Goals is now. We are proud to expand our work with SAP, which includes launching SDG Ambition with UN Global Compact that over 700 companies have joined. By committing to put sustainability at the center of all we do and everyone we work with, together we can show companies how to tackle climate change, build circular economy practices, businesses, human rights and supply chains, and focus on data-driven measurement as well as accurately report ESG performance when delivering their commitments.”</p>
        <p><em>– Peter Lacy, Global Sustainability Services Lead, Chief Responsibility Officer and</em><br><em>Member of the Global Management Committee, Accenture</em></p>
        <h2 id="bearingpoint">BearingPoint</h2>
        <p>“Helping our clients meet their decarbonization targets has been one of our proven market offerings for more than 10 years. At BearingPoint, we not only calculate the product and corporate footprint of our clients, we also enable them to optimize the climate impact of every product across the entire life cycle. Providing end-to-end CO2 as a service is our core enabler for our clients. We at BearingPoint, as co-development partner for SAP Product Footprint Management, believe that together with SAP we can bring our vision to life: managing the ‘green line’ as equally as the financial bottom line. As partners, we go beyond business, making a positive impact on the climate.”</p>
        <p><em>– Donald Wachs, Head of IP-Assets and</em><br><em>Member of Management Committee, BearingPoint</em></p>
        <h2 id="capgemini">Capgemini</h2>
        <p>“Our ambitions are to act on climate change by being carbon neutral across our own operations by 2025 and across our supply chain by 2030, becoming a net-zero business well ahead of 2050, and to lead to low-carbon economic transition by helping our clients achieve their environmental commitments and save 10m tons of CO2eq globally by 2030. We cannot do this without our partner ecosystem. We are a strategic partner of SAP; by combining our deep industry knowledge, our human energy, and SAP’s world-class portfolio of enterprise and sustainability solutions, we commit to delivering on our promise to co-create a greener tomorrow with our clients.”</p>
        <p><em>– Aiman Ezzat, CEO, Capgemini</em></p>
        <h2 id="deloitte">Deloitte</h2>
        <table>
          <thead>
            <tr>
              <th colspan="2">Promo</th>
            </tr>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td>
                <h3 id="sap-cloud-for-sustainable-enterprises-taking-action-together">SAP Cloud for Sustainable Enterprises: Taking Action Together</h3>
              </td>
              <td><strong><a href="/">Learn more</a></strong></td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
        <p>“The climate change emergency is unfolding in front of our eyes, touching all corners of the globe. The future of our people, planet, and profession depends on the business community taking measurable, decisive action on the climate crisis. Through our WorldClimate strategy, Deloitte will embed climate-smart considerations into our own operations, encourage our professionals to act on climate change at work and at home, and engage our broader ecosystem – including SAP – to create solutions that facilitate the transition to a low-carbon economy.”</p>
        <p><em>– Punit Renjen, Global CEO, Deloitte</em></p>
        <h2 id="ey">EY</h2>
        <p>“Sustainability is one of the defining issues of our time, and today there is an unprecedented opportunity to create value for all. Together with SAP and stakeholders around the globe, the EY organization is committed to making business work for sustainability and making sustainability work for business. Enterprises and people are inspired now more than ever to do the right thing — to collaborate, innovate, be inclusive, and accelerate to a more sustainable and equitable future.”</p>
        <p><em>– Steve Varley, Global Vice Chair – Sustainability, EY</em></p>
        <h2 id="ibm">IBM</h2>
        <p>“With five generations in the workplace, we are witnessing the birth of an era where technological innovation is being used to create social, economic, environmental, and business opportunities for all. Businesses of all sizes need to move from ambition to action and embrace radical thinking, like IBM’s commitment to achieve net-zero greenhouse gas emissions by 2030. We are partnering with SAP to operationalize sustainability for our customers and society using ethical innovation to build a world that is responsible, equitable, and leaves no one behind in net-zero transition. We are committed to furthering our decades-long work to address the global climate crisis.”</p>
        <p><em>– Sheri R. Hinish, Global Executive Partner, Enterprise Sustainability and</em><br><em>Sustainable Supply Chain Practice Leader, IBM</em></p>
        <h2 id="pwc">PwC</h2>
        <p>“PwC’s global sustainability network in over 60 countries is supporting organizations to deliver ESG-related outcomes across the globe. PwC works with clients to help them create their strategy, set targets, measure impact, and report on key performance indicators relevant to internal and external ESG drivers. Together with SAP, PwC is leveraging its ESG expertise to integrate and build strategic ESG solutions leveraging SAP technology. Organizations will benefit from these integrated solutions to help set and manage net-zero targets, define ESG strategies, and mitigate climate and ESG risks to deliver transparent investor-grade ESG reporting.”</p>
        <p><em>– Michael Rasch, Global SAP Alliance Leader, PwC Germany</em></p>
        <p><em>Bernd Schmalzridt is senior director of Global Business Development for Sustainability at SAP.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/accenture</category>
            <category>news-tag/capgemini</category>
            <category>news-tag/deloitte</category>
            <category>news-tag/ey</category>
            <category>news-tag/ibm</category>
            <category>news-tag/pwc</category>
            <category>product/sap-cloud-for-sustainable-enterprises</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Deloitte Is Beating Burnout at Scale]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/how-deloitte-is-beating-burnout-at-scale</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/how-deloitte-is-beating-burnout-at-scale</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In trying to address overwork issues before they impact mental health, professional services company Deloitte is a pioneer. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/deloitte</category>
            <category>news-tag/mental-health-well-being</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-original-series-forward</category>
            <category>news-tag/well-being-at-work</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Announces New SAP Process Insights Solution for Quick and Easy Understanding of How Well Processes Perform]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/06/sapphire-now-new-sap-process-insights</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/06/sapphire-now-new-sap-process-insights</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Process Insights is the newest in the business process intelligence portfolio from SAP and Signavio. Read the news from SAPPHIRE NOW.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/business-process-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/deloitte</category>
            <category>news-tag/ey</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>