<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/sap-customer-experience/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Digital Hub Innovations Win Silver and Bronze at 2024 Stevie® Awards]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-digital-hub-innovations-win-2024-stevie-awards</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-digital-hub-innovations-win-2024-stevie-awards</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Three SAP digital hub tools won 2024 Stevie Awards for Sales & Customer Service. Read to learn more about the recognition.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-engagement</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-customer-experience</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Customer Engagement Lessons from Competitive Racing]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/digital-customer-engagement-competitive-racing</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/digital-customer-engagement-competitive-racing</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP executes digital customer engagement via digital hubs. Read to find out how competitive racing teams, like Mercedes-AMG, can benefit.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-engagement</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/mercedes</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-customer-experience</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[More Than Just the Numbers: Insights from 2023 Cyber Week]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/cyber-week-2023-insights</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/cyber-week-2023-insights</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Black Friday marks the beginning of the holiday shopping season. Learn about SAP customers' successes during Cyber Week 2023.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a6045a889e543a1e87aa3bb1f359ec62eca3fa7e.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a6045a889e543a1e87aa3bb1f359ec62eca3fa7e.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1a6045a889e543a1e87aa3bb1f359ec62eca3fa7e.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="More Than Just the Numbers: Insights from 2023 Cyber Week" src="./media_1a6045a889e543a1e87aa3bb1f359ec62eca3fa7e.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="more-than-just-the-numbers-insights-from-2023-cyber-week">More Than Just the Numbers: Insights from 2023 Cyber Week</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Black Friday marks the beginning of the holiday shopping season and there have been great stories of record-breaking volumes, many from SAP customers that experienced success during Cyber Week, the Monday before Black Friday to Cyber Monday.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Through Cyber Week, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm/commerce-cloud.html">SAP Commerce Cloud</a> customers achieved over a 35% year-over-year (YoY) increase in the number of orders processed, an astounding amount of $110 million in peak gross merchandising value (GMV) per minute, and a 9.3% YoY increase in overall site traffic. Essential for driving site traffic and increasing conversions is customer engagement, and on Cyber Weekend, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm/commerce-cloud.html">SAP Emarsys Customer Engagement</a> supported customers with a nine percent YoY increase of overall send volume across all channels. What’s more, SAP Commerce Cloud customers achieved a 5.04% higher conversion rate versus 2022, and retailers saw a 5.2% higher conversion rate during Cyber Week.</p>
  <p>This success was possible due to the reliability, scalability, and intelligence of <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm.html">SAP Customer Experience solutions</a> for individually curated shopping journeys across the globe.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="unlock-business-agility-and-transform-customer-experiences-with-sap-commerce-cloud">Unlock business agility and transform customer experiences with SAP Commerce Cloud</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm/commerce-cloud.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>But at SAP, it is not just about the numbers. Deriving insights from data is at the heart of SAP and the start to the holiday shopping season provided a treasure trove of learnings and understanding about how people are shopping and how retailers can <a href="/topics/crm-customer-experience">optimize their experiences</a>.</p>
  <p>By serving some of the largest brands in the world through this holiday season, here is what we learned.</p>
  <h2 id="insight-one-the-definition-of-holiday-season-is-expanding">Insight One: The Definition of “Holiday Season” Is Expanding</h2>
  <p>Traditionally, Black Friday is considered as a starting point for the holiday shopping season. However, recent research has revealed the holiday shopping is starting sooner and extending over the course of several weeks.</p>
  <p>According to <a href="https://go.criteo.com/">Criteo</a>, an SAP commerce media partner, the longest path to purchase during the holidays is <a href="https://c-grid.criteo.com/holiday-season-success-2023">about 45 days</a>. This includes Singles Day, originated in China, on November 11 and El Buen Fin, Mexico’s version of Cyber Weekend from November 17 to November 20.</p>
  <p>In 2023, SAP Emarsys Customer Engagement saw a spike on Singles Day, nearly surpassing 1 billion customer engagements — for example, email, SMS, mobile push, and web push — two weeks ahead of Black Friday. This figure was then eclipsed not once but twice during El Buen Fin, which saw overall an approximate 30% YoY increase in messages delivered.</p>
  <p>When looking at just email growth during this season, the growth of volume for the entire month of November was nearly twice what it was for Cyber Weekend. This not only underscores that holiday shopping is starting earlier, but how brands are scaling up sooner and avoiding sharp peaks, which is a win for deliverability too.</p>
  <p>Newly emerging celebrations and extended shopping seasons also mean a higher and longer strain on e-commerce sites. However, SAP Commerce Cloud prepared the customers to combat this challenge during these peak sales times leading up to Cyber Week, and delivered 100% uptime. In fact, customers that ran holiday sales events during El Buen Fin achieved 112% growth in conversion rate, with 10% higher traffic volume compared to the regular daily average of 2023.</p>
  <h2 id="insight-two-email-still-reigns-but-omnichannel-engagement-is-rapidly-growing">Insight Two: Email Still Reigns, But Omnichannel Engagement Is Rapidly Growing</h2>
  <p>While overall 2023 holiday sales are expected to <a href="https://nrf.com/media-center/press-releases/2023-holiday-reach-record-spending-levels">increase between three and four percent</a>, online sales are expected to double and <a href="https://nrf.com/media-center/press-releases/2023-holiday-reach-record-spending-levels">increase between seven and nine percent</a>. More digitally advanced customer journeys and increasingly tech-savvy buyers present an exciting opportunity for businesses to engage with shoppers more often and on their preferred channels.</p>
  <p>Aiming to capitalize on this opportunity and remain top of mind with shoppers, SAP Emarsys customers sent a record number of omnichannel messages, resulting in a nine percent YoY increase in customer engagements from 2022. Email remained the top promotional channel in terms of volume and saw a respectable 10% YoY increase.</p>
  <p>In addition to email, brands are also now investing heavily in omnichannel engagement strategies to meet customers where they prefer to shop. Mobile messages like SMS (35% YoY increase) and in-app (15% YoY increase) were utilized effectively alongside email, as were Web channel engagements, like Web push, which saw a whopping 74% increase in usage in 2023.</p>
  <h2 id="insight-three-personalization-proves-less-is-more">Insight Three: Personalization Proves Less is More</h2>
  <p>It is important to acknowledge that success does not equate to the quantity of messages, but also the quality. Bucking the notion that more is simply better, marketers using SAP Emarsys increased utilization of data-driven segmentation by 20% compared to Cyber Weekend 2022, enabling more targeted offers and personalized messages. While conversion rates would naturally be expected to dip given the extra volume, this targeted and personalized approach contributed to minimal or no change compared to baseline conversion rates during a typical weekend.</p>
  <p>Similarly, AI-powered product recommendations, delivered across channels, and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/marketing.html#ecommerce">intelligent shopping assistants from SAP Customer Experience solutions</a> also helped consumers find the right product or best deal among the seemingly limitless choices — with confidence and ease.</p>
  <p>With consumers shopping for an extended period on more channels, brands have both an obligation to meet them where they are in their journey and an opportunity to earn their business and loyalty by investing in data-driven, omnichannel strategies that better match them with personalized offers on the items they wish to buy.</p>
  <h2 id="insight-four-b2b-shoppers-share-the-holiday-fever-during-cyber-week">Insight Four: B2B Shoppers Share the Holiday Fever During Cyber Week</h2>
  <p>Black Friday is usually seen as an influential opportunity to create a revenue boost for retailers. However, SAP has the privilege of working with many B2B commerce companies in addition to a large number of retailers.</p>
  <p>According to our data, other industries outside of retail also experience the benefits of Black Friday and Cyber Monday pushes. While the retail industry had the highest volume of orders, consumer products and wholesale distribution came in close behind. Additionally, the chemicals industry saw a huge spike in AOV over the weekend and achieved a GMV increase of 51% YoY, while life sciences industry saw more than 120% YoY GMV growth.</p>
  <p>These data points indicate that Cyber Week trends are no longer limited to retailers, as various industries now achieve bigger sales volume and revenue during this period. Moving forward, organizations across all industries must put their best foot forward during Cyber Weekend activities to support profitable growth.</p>
  <h2 id="insight-five-black-friday-isnt-just-about-the-us-thanksgiving-holiday-anymore">Insight Five: Black Friday Isn’t Just About the U.S. Thanksgiving Holiday Anymore</h2>
  <p>The data from SAP Commerce Cloud also reflects the globalization trend. While North America led the biggest GMV number on Black Friday, the Europe, Middle East, and Africa (EMEA) region is comparable. In fact, the highest number of orders, about 800,000, was placed in EMEA. Additionally, the Asia Pacific and Japan (APJ) region on Cyber Monday achieved over 130% growth in conversion rate compared to last year.</p>
  <p>SAP Emarsys customers were also ready to leverage this trend and engage with customers around the world. On Cyber Monday, total send volumes saw significant YoY increases in multiple regions: by 20% in EMEA, over 27% in Middle and Eastern Europe (MEE), and over 15% in Asia.</p>
  <p>The data also highlighted differences in how consumers shop and buy in different regions. Unsurprisingly email continued to be the most used channel across the board, though EMEA proved to be the only region, outside of the Americas, that saw high growth in email volume year-on-year with a 13% increase.</p>
  <p>The MEE region saw a slight decrease in the use of email (-12% YoY) in favor of SMS, mobile push, and in-app messages. In APJ, where a mobile-first mindset is often the norm, usage of in-app (58% YoY growth) and mobile push (176% YoY growth) went up significantly compared to email growth (two percent YoY). Even in EMEA, SMS (53% YoY growth) and in-app (388% YoY growth) mobile messages outpaced email growth, underscoring the importance of an omnichannel strategy.</p>
  <p>This data illustrates the global influence of Black Friday, what used to be considered an U.S.-specific sales event. For businesses across the globe, it is crucial to recognize this shift and consider customer behaviors, so they can adapt and evolve their commerce and channel engagement strategies to gain customer loyalty and boost profitability.</p>
  <h2 id="next-step">Next Step</h2>
  <p>As market trends evolve, organizations must proactively adopt strategies for profitable and sustainable growth. With the right blend of modern technologies, agile business processes, and customer centric strategies, businesses significantly benefit from extended shopping season, through personalized omnichannel engagements, increased conversions, and lifelong customer loyalty.</p>
  <p>Moreover, with the right choice of cloud technologies, organizations can remain secure and compliant, while delivering reliable, scalable, and personalized experiences that are optimized for their industries.</p>
  <p>To learn more about how SAP Customer Experience solutions can help, please <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm.html">visit us at sap.com/crm</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Balaji Balasubramanian is senior vice president and global head of Commerce and Industry Cloud at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><em>*All data presented here is approximate and is based on various assumptions. All data is unaudited and is subject to adjustment. All financial figures are in USD. Data represents online and offline sales made by SAP global merchants.</em></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-commerce</category>
            <category>news-tag/e-commerce</category>
            <category>product/sap-commerce-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-customer-experience</category>
            <category>product/sap-emarsys-customer-engagement</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Debuts New CX Generative AI Capabilities to Enhance Customer Experiences and Boost Business Operations]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/new-cx-generative-ai-capabilities</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/new-cx-generative-ai-capabilities</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[From SAP Customer Experience LIVE, SAP has announced new generative AI capabilities for the CX solution portfolio. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>product/sap-customer-data-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-customer-experience</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-customer-experience-live</category>
            <category>product/sap-emarsys-customer-engagement</category>
            <category>product/sap-sales-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-service-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How PILLER Increased Customer Service with SAP Customer Experience Solutions]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/piller-increased-customer-service-sap-cx</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/piller-increased-customer-service-sap-cx</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With the help of SAP, PILLER was able to share information and optimize business processes across sales, service, and marketing.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_183ba6c7acd6d09f1a49eb03d61c336ed1830707f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_183ba6c7acd6d09f1a49eb03d61c336ed1830707f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_183ba6c7acd6d09f1a49eb03d61c336ed1830707f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="How PILLER Increased Customer Service with SAP Customer Experience Solutions" src="./media_183ba6c7acd6d09f1a49eb03d61c336ed1830707f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="how-piller-increased-customer-service-with-sap-customer-experience-solutions">How PILLER Increased Customer Service with SAP Customer Experience Solutions</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><a href="https://www.piller.de/">PILLER Blowers &#x26; Compressors</a> produces high-performance blowers and compressors and customized solutions to meet specific requirements of various industries. Its global network of wholly owned subsidiaries and joint ventures enables it to serve an international customer base.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>To increase customer service quality, the company wanted to share information and optimize business processes across its sales, service, and marketing activities.</p>
  <h2 id="moving-from-manual-processes-to-integrated-activities">Moving from Manual Processes to Integrated Activities</h2>
  <p>At PILLER, different departments were using their own IT solutions.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-customer-experience-solutions-help-connect-customer-data-improve-loyalty-and-grow-your-business">SAP Customer Experience solutions help connect customer data, improve loyalty, and grow your business</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The service department had manual processes, such as Microsoft Excel spreadsheets, to dispatch service technicians. The technicians were logging into a central server to retrieve data and recording customer support by e-mails and conversations. The sales department had a basic access environment due to custom-made products with individual serial numbers. There was no master data; tailored sales quotes were done on paper, posing challenges for data updating and quality. The marketing department was conducting its business, like capturing trade-fair leads or planning and executing campaigns, by hand and with spreadsheets. All these manual activities were time intensive and prone to human error.</p>
  <p>To enable the marketing, sales, and service teams to perform to the best of their abilities, PILLER wanted solutions that allowed it to share important information. It wished to harmonize all customer-related processes, from initial contact and order management to delivery of spare parts and follow-up.</p>
  <p>“For new products or customers, it’s important that real-time master data in our core software is mirrored in our sales, service, and marketing systems. We can do this by integrating SAP Customer Experience solutions and SAP Field Service Management with SAP S/4HANA,” said Frank Münzner, in-house SAP consultant for Lead to Cash at PILLER Blowers &#x26; Compressors GmbH.</p>
  <h2 id="adopting-cloud-solutions-to-achieve-innovative-customer-service">Adopting Cloud Solutions to Achieve Innovative Customer Service</h2>
  <p>PILLER employed the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm/sales-cloud.html">SAP Sales Cloud</a> solution to help address the needs of its sales team and integrate functionalities, such as managing quotes and orders, in one place. The solution offers a search capability and a modern, intuitive user interface.</p>
  <p>The company is using the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/field-service-management.html">SAP Field Service Management mobile app</a> to help create service tickets, which are the single point of customer contact, with product serial numbers and metadata. Integrating this mobile app with the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm/service-cloud.html">SAP Service Cloud</a> solution can enable technicians to receive service ticket information on an Apple iPad, so they can have everything they need to carry out their work. This can also translate to good customer support.</p>
  <p>By deploying the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm/marketing.html">SAP Marketing Cloud</a> solution and integrating it with SAP Sales Cloud, PILLER now proactively shares data, such as service tickets, lead opportunities, and customer contacts, between the sales and marketing teams. This lets the company contact a customer with a warranty option or service cost reduction, for example.</p>
  <p>PILLER has now integrated the three SAP Customer Experience solutions for sales, service, and marketing and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/field-service-management.html">SAP Field Service Management</a> with <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/s4hana.html">SAP S/4HANA</a>, the company’s enterprise resource planning (ERP) software.</p>
  <p>PILLER partnered with <a href="https://www.fis-gmbh.de/en/">FIS Global</a> to gain advice about new functionalities and implementation support, while <a href="https://www.ibsolution.com/en/">IBsolution</a> provided guidance around leveraging the potential in terms of business transformation and digitization.</p>
  <h2 id="gaining-comprehensive-customer-visibility-with-integrated-solutions">Gaining Comprehensive Customer Visibility with Integrated Solutions</h2>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="resolve-customer-issues-faster-with-proactive-ai-enabled-field-service-management-software-from-sap">Resolve customer issues faster with proactive, AI-enabled field service management software from SAP</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/field-service-management.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The major advantage in connecting the SAP Customer Experience portfolio, SAP Field Service Management, and SAP S/4HANA is that real-time data can be available across all these solutions. While master data, such as for a new product, customer, or material, is entered and kept in SAP S/4HANA as the core software, it’s automatically pushed into the other integrated solutions.</p>
  <p>This is helping PILLER deliver highly efficient and innovative customer service and business models. The company gains a comprehensive view of worldwide customers in real time while interacting with them at each stage of their journey in a targeted manner.</p>
  <p>There are now customer-related processes across departments, sites, and systems as well as consistent communication throughout the company, thanks to standardized forms and templates. The business is achieving agile sales with faster response times and better allocation of target groups. It’s also making decisions for customer management based on facts and analyses.</p>
  <p>Other benefits the company achieved were:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>360-degree view of customers worldwide in real time</li>
    <li>90% less paper with digital processes</li>
    <li>30% reduction in effort by using digital processes</li>
  </ul>
  <p>“We’ve always combined tradition with innovation when manufacturing our blowers. With SAP Customer Experience solutions, our customer management operations are superior to those of our competitors. We’re able to keep a close eye on processes and respond quickly and accordingly,” said Thomas Henzler, CIO at PILLER Blowers &#x26; Compressors GmbH.</p>
  <h2 id="rolling-out-customer-centric-solutions">Rolling Out Customer-Centric Solutions</h2>
  <p>Combining <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm.html">SAP Customer Experience solutions</a> and the SAP Field Service Management mobile app with SAP S/4HANA is helping deliver real-time data for integrated processes.</p>
  <p>The integration of the SAP Field Service Management mobile app with SAP Service Cloud is being piloted with three service technicians and garnering positive feedback so far.</p>
  <p>Watch an <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm/sales-cloud.html?video=189daad3-437e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b">overview video</a> of SAP Sales Cloud to help build lasting customer relationships and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm/service-cloud.html?pdf-asset=983be5bb-b27d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff&#x26;page=1">learn more about SAP Service Cloud</a> to maximize customer lifetime value with connected service. Read about the benefits companies achieved with <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/customer-stories/topcon.html">SAP Customer Experience solutions</a>. View a <a href="https://www.sap.com/sea/products/scm/field-service-management/features.html?video=66ec8033-617e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b">solution demo</a> and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/field-service-management/features.html?video=f83398c5-247e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b">overview video</a> to learn how to maximize productivity and asset uptime with SAP Field Service Management. <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/field-service-management.html?video=14f5efa9-427e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b">Learn what benefits other enterprises achieved</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Karin Fent is senior director of Global Customer Success Digital Supply Chain at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-sap-news-delivered-to-your-inbox-once-a-week">Get the latest SAP news delivered to your inbox once a week</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/nl/sap-news-center-newsletter/index.html">Sign Up</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/field-service-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-customer-experience</category>
            <category>product/sap-marketing-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>product/sap-sales-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-service-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Named a Leader in 2023 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Digital Commerce]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/sap-named-a-leader-in-2023-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-digital-commerce</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/sap-named-a-leader-in-2023-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-digital-commerce</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[This is the ninth time in a row SAP has been rated a leader by Gartner in the Magic Quadrant for Digital Commerce. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/magic-quadrant</category>
            <category>product/sap-commerce-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-customer-experience</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[What Is Customer Loyalty?]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/what-is-customer-loyalty</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/what-is-customer-loyalty</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Effectively measuring and learning from customer behavior with loyalty solutions is the key to taking customer loyalty to the next level.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1095042ae655d1c2458fed3b507068ee0b10d7433.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1095042ae655d1c2458fed3b507068ee0b10d7433.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1095042ae655d1c2458fed3b507068ee0b10d7433.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="What Is Customer Loyalty?" src="./media_1095042ae655d1c2458fed3b507068ee0b10d7433.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="what-is-customer-loyalty">What Is Customer Loyalty?</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>What makes you stick with a brand – is it the quality of the product or service? Is it the support you receive when something goes wrong? Is it the availability in the market or the compatibility with other products? Is it the rewards you are offered for being a loyal customer?</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>When I’m in the market for new sport shoes, I stick to the brand that I know is the most comfortable for me. There’s nothing worse than buying a pair of sneakers and going jogging with them for the first time, only to realize in the first few minutes of your run that they don’t fit properly.</p>
  <p>On the other hand, if I’m shopping for groceries, it’s how healthy the product is, then the selection, freshness, and price that matter the most. Time is also a factor – the quicker I can find exactly what I need, the better.</p>
  <p>But what happens if another sport shoe manufacturer sets up a loyalty program, allowing me to collect points and offering discounts? Or, what if a new grocery store opens that allows me to save even more time by eliminating the checkout counter? Would that make me change my buying behavior?</p>
  <p>What I’m talking about is loyalty in the context of <a href="/topics/crm-customer-experience">customer experience</a>. It’s different for every industry. How can you as a supplier or service provider ensure that you are offering the best experience possible to your customers?</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="intelligent-cx-solutions-from-sap-help-connect-customer-data-and-improve-loyalty">Intelligent CX solutions from SAP help connect customer data and improve loyalty</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="loyalty-is-a-very-noisy-space">Loyalty Is a Very Noisy Space</h2>
  <p>Recently, I spoke to Riad Hijal, head of Commerce Solution Management at SAP Customer Experience. “Loyalty is a very noisy space. I think for retailers, for example, to be successful and ultimately drive customer lifetime value through loyalty, they need to cut through that noise,” he said. “We as consumers are faced with dozens of rewards or loyalty accounts – most of them aren’t really driving any kind of real modification in behavior. We don’t buy more just because we have a loyalty account with someone and are collecting points; we are merely using it as a discount mechanism. That’s how to do loyalty wrong.”</p>
  <p>Loyalty requires a reimagination of the loyalty experience and underlying process. To stand out from the crowd, companies need to be leveraging measurement. In addition, what are the themes that we need to focus on to rethink loyalty to truly drive long-term customer value? What does the measurement look like? According to Hijal, historically, efficient and tangible measurement has been lacking in loyalty programs due to the complexity of the topic.</p>
  <h2 id="what-should-loyalty-solutions-really-be-offering">What Should Loyalty Solutions Really Be Offering?</h2>
  <p>By leveraging data and analytics, a loyalty platform helps businesses understand why customers regard certain experiences as more memorable and important than others. This allows businesses to dig deeper into the different elements of behavior-driven customer loyalty.</p>
  <p>And, the truth is, data is siloed within a multitude of systems within your organization. As a company, you need to be able to reconcile all of it, across both transactional and behavioral dimensions so that you can understand which customers are truly profitable and worth your focus. With SAP Customer Data Platform, for example, which is part of RISE with SAP, you can prioritize your customers with intelligent insights delivered by the platform. See more about SAP Customer Data Platform in <a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2023/04/8ad02f10-6e7e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">this video</a>.</p>
  <p>As such, there are key capabilities necessary for modern experiential loyalty platforms. These are rewards and incentive management, personalization, gamification, communication and engagement, feedback and surveys, data-driven insights, and integration and convenience.</p>
  <h2 id="puma-and-mention-me-an-industry-cloud-solution">PUMA and Mention Me: An Industry Cloud Solution</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="watch-how-rise-with-sap-can-help-you-prioritize-your-customers">Watch how RISE with SAP can help you prioritize your customers</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2023/04/8ad02f10-6e7e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As a leading sports brand, PUMA wanted to transform its fan base to a key growth-driver by not only attracting new customers, but also improving brand awareness and loyalty. Mention Me, an industry cloud partner solution, in combination with SAP Emarsys Customer Engagement, helped PUMA launch referral programs in six European countries.</p>
  <p>PUMA has integrated Mention Me with SAP Emarsys Customer Engagement, its customer relationship management (CRM) platform. This helps equip PUMA to serve seamless customer journeys that drive more referrals, such as sending reward reminders and encouraging referrers to introduce more friends. PUMA is also able to feed first-party referral data into the CRM platform in real time – growing its database and giving a whole new level of insight. The combination of these solutions is giving the company remarkable growth, increasing its ROI through referral to six times its investment just nine months after launching the campaigns. <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2023/05/0227ee79-727e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Learn more about this transformation</a>.</p>
  <h2 id="valora-revolutionizing-convenience-store-shopping">Valora: Revolutionizing Convenience Store Shopping</h2>
  <p>Valora wanted to better meet customer needs by combining the convenience of a physical store with the simplicity of a digital business model. This was the beginning of its newest brand of cashier-free convenience store – avec box. To help realize the project, Valora chose SAP Customer Experience solutions, used the rich knowledge available with SAP Services and Support, and worked with Webtiser AG and Pagnos GmbH on a proof of concept. The goal was to start with a single store, using a minimal viable product collaboration approach, then scale the solution further.</p>
  <p>Now, Valora is winning new customers by offering them an even more convenient and flexible shopping experience – without the hassle of waiting in line at the cash register. Plus, with customers registering with the avec app, Valora is able to get new insight into what customers want. Not only does make it possible to give personalized recommendations, but it is also now easier than ever for Valora to reward customer loyalty and keep people coming back for more. <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/04/9c274ed9-dc7d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff.html">Read the full story here</a>.</p>
  <h2 id="measurement-is-key">Measurement Is Key</h2>
  <p>Effectively measuring and then learning from customer behavior with loyalty solutions to improve reward experiences is the key to taking customer loyalty to the next level. “Since loyalty is such a mature space, measurement is key,” said Hijal. “Most loyalty programs are abundant and don’t achieve much, but focusing on measurement is what the next generation of loyalty programs is all about.”</p>
  <p>Speaking of next generation, SAP Customer Experience solutions are also artificial intelligence (AI)- and machine learning-fueled. These types of insights can help you make each customer feel like they are your only customer. They can help you engage and understand consumers on their terms while respecting their privacy preferences during the customer journey, to retain and upsell using machine learning and smart automation.</p>
  <p>So, the next time I’m in the market for sports shoes, maybe the AI-fueled loyalty program will be able to convince me to try something new…and stick with it.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Sven Denecken is senior vice president and chief marketing and solutions officer for SAP Industries and CX.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-customer-data-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-customer-experience</category>
            <category>product/sap-emarsys-customer-engagement</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP CX Is a TrustRadius 2023 Top Rated Award Winner]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/06/sap-cx-trustradius-2023-top-rated-award</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/06/sap-cx-trustradius-2023-top-rated-award</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[TrustRadius has named SAP Customer Experience (SAP CX) as the winner of its 2023 Top Rated award under multiple CX market categories.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/trustradius</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Direct-to-Consumer Imperative for Today’s Consumer Product and Retail Brands]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/the-d2c-imperative-consumer-product-retail-brands</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/the-d2c-imperative-consumer-product-retail-brands</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[When faced with the D2C imperative, SAP is uniquely positioned to help consumer product and retail brands drive profitable results.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/consumer-goods-cpg</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-customer-experience</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Delivers the Future of Intelligent Customer Experience for Utilities]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/future-intelligent-cx-for-utilities</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/future-intelligent-cx-for-utilities</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[An industry-first approach to CX for utilities allows for involving end customers in the energy transition journey. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>product/sap-commerce-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-customer-experience</category>
            <category>product/sap-emarsys-customer-engagement</category>
            <category>product/sap-sales-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-service-cloud</category>
            <category>industry/utilities</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Delivers New Approach to Composability, Helping Businesses Drive Profitability and Move Fast on Their Own Terms]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/sap-delivers-new-approach-to-composability</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/sap-delivers-new-approach-to-composability</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is introducing a new composability offering in SAP Commerce Cloud. Read to learn about this unique, composable approach.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/commerce</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-commerce</category>
            <category>news-tag/e-commerce</category>
            <category>product/sap-commerce-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-customer-experience</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP CX: Delivering Growth with Intelligent Industry-Tailored Solutions]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2023/03/sap-cx-intelligent-industry-tailored-solutions</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2023/03/sap-cx-intelligent-industry-tailored-solutions</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The aligned SAP CX portfolio takes an industry-first approach to accelerate value to customers with end-to-end, integrated business processes.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18e5bbb7b48fb7e47ef274203aba2e61d2fc2bbe7.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18e5bbb7b48fb7e47ef274203aba2e61d2fc2bbe7.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_18e5bbb7b48fb7e47ef274203aba2e61d2fc2bbe7.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Customer Experience: Delivering Growth with Intelligent Industry-Tailored Solutions" src="./media_18e5bbb7b48fb7e47ef274203aba2e61d2fc2bbe7.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-customer-experience-delivering-growth-with-intelligent-industry-tailored-solutions">SAP Customer Experience: Delivering Growth with Intelligent Industry-Tailored Solutions</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>SAP’s unmatched industry expertise has been a cornerstone of our leadership for the past 50 years and will continue as the foundation for success. As we work with business leaders to manage their digital transformation and navigate their pathways to sustainable growth, they trust us to not just understand and deliver industry standards, but industry specifics.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Our customers have also been clear with us: they need greater agility in their business processes while also reducing the costs of integrating a patchwork of solutions from multiple vendors. From finance to supply chain to commerce, the user and customer experiences need to be seamless. This requires the underlying applications to service the user and customer journeys in real time.</p>
  <p>SAP has the rare combination of unmatched industry depth as well as the breadth of business process solutions to meet this moment. While our ERP has always had deep industry capabilities, we have now aligned the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm.html">SAP Customer Experience</a> (CX) portfolio to an industry-first approach to accelerate value to customers by enabling end-to-end, integrated business processes.</p>
  <p>Some voices across the market are recasting SAP’s commitment to an industry-first strategy to suggest that SAP is no longer committed to key needs of our customers, starting with our CX portfolio. Let us be clear: SAP will continue to deliver customer experience (<a href="/topics/crm-customer-experience">CX/CRM</a>) solutions. Now we’ll focus on adding an industry lens, delivering industry-tailored CX solutions and bringing the front office together with the back office to provide the unmatched value customers expect from SAP solutions.</p>
  <p>Together with our global ecosystem, we can solve the most relevant challenges of customers in all industries. In fact, today, 80% of industry solutions are ecosystem-led. With this approach, customers will get solutions that natively connect the cloud ERP through to the last mile of a customer’s experiences spanning e-commerce, sales, service, and marketing — all with the industry-specific best practices they rely on from SAP and our ecosystem.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="explore-cx-and-crm-solutions-that-work-for-your-customers">Explore CX and CRM solutions that work for your customers</h3>
        <p><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm/solutions.html">Learn more</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Here are just a few examples of where industry-first CX has bridged gaps often seen between business process-led ERP and experience delivery:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Retail:</strong> Maintaining optimal inventory levels in stores and distribution centers is crucial to ensure customers get the products they want. Predictive replenishment uses artificial intelligence (AI) to help retailers automate the restocking process, drawing on the deep retail expertise built into our customer experience product and our cloud ERP. Retailers benefit by reducing their environmental footprint while avoiding both overstock and out-of-stock situations and delivering personalized customer service if things go wrong.</li>
    <li><strong>Consumer Products:</strong> By automating 80% of the trade claims process and enhancing cash flow by about a month, consumer product companies free up billions of dollars tied up in settlement processes as well as hours of time for key account managers. SAP uniquely sits at the intersection of accounts receivables (finance, ERP) and revenue growth management (sales, service, and marketing), which allows us to provide not only native integrations but also faster time to value and lower TCO in this space than any other vendor.</li>
    <li><strong>Automotive:</strong> SAP improves production planning and forecasting based on real-time demand; we boost logistics optimization thanks to end-to-end integration from dealership sales and service to group production and logistics processes. Dealers can also optimize sales strategy and marketing spend as well as improving upsell, retention, and overall customer lifetime value thanks to data aggregated from the front and back office into SAP’s customer data platform. This enables dealers to strategically upsell subscription services or entertainment system software updates while updating customers on production progress, delivery, warranty, and service notifications.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>SAP CX customers including Pizza Hut, Carhartt, and smart Europe are among those already benefiting from our unique industry depth. We are excited about the additional value we can deliver to our customers with our industry-focused approach to delivering holistic, integrated business process solutions together with our ecosystem. Examples include the retail solutions <a href="https://events.sap.com/noam-nrf/en/videopage.aspx?v=oluBrjrC1Rn9L3WV043aZMFVlhreKw4xK%2FqQRqxWlTTCvgEhZalDo0E7G5%2FOzPee0p9owH7y6I%2FAATgMBsvHh%2B02mKjH8DsP">we showcased at NRF 2023</a>, from customer engagement to inventory fulfillment to sustainable manufacturing. We will demonstrate this same industry value for manufacturing at the Hannover Messe in April.</p>
  <p>Stay tuned for more exciting updates in the coming months.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Thomas Saueressig is a member of the Executive Board of SAP SE, SAP Product Engineering.</em><br><em>Julia White is chief marketing and solutions officer and a member of the Executive Board of SAP SE.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/blog/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/blog/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-customer-data-from-demand-to-delivery-with-sap-software">Connect customer data from demand to delivery with SAP software</h3>
        <p><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm.html">Learn more</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>sidebar</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/blog/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/blog/article-read-more</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/executive-blog</category>
            <category>industry/automotive</category>
            <category>industry/consumer-goods-cpg</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-customer-experience</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Revolution in Product Discovery with Zoovu Apps on SAP Store]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/revolution-in-product-discovery-zoovu-sap-store</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/revolution-in-product-discovery-zoovu-sap-store</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Zoovu humanizes product discovery, making products easier to find, evaluate, and buy by bringing context to your search. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-commerce</category>
            <category>news-tag/e-commerce</category>
            <category>product/sap-commerce-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-cpq</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-digital-commerce</category>
            <category>product/sap-sales-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-store</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Commerce Cloud Black Friday and Cyber Monday Results Show Shoppers’ Willingness to Spend]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/sap-commerce-cloud-black-friday-cyber-monday-holiday-shopping-results</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/sap-commerce-cloud-black-friday-cyber-monday-holiday-shopping-results</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Commerce Cloud enabled brands to maximize traffic and conversions of holiday shopping during Black Friday and Cyber Monday this year.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1af5de22ea9202f9d958b920f3c3d1359aa1f6ee5.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1af5de22ea9202f9d958b920f3c3d1359aa1f6ee5.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1af5de22ea9202f9d958b920f3c3d1359aa1f6ee5.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Commerce Cloud Black Friday and Cyber Monday Results Show Shoppers’ Willingness to Spend" src="./media_1af5de22ea9202f9d958b920f3c3d1359aa1f6ee5.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-commerce-cloud-black-friday-and-cyber-monday-results-show-shoppers-willingness-to-spend">SAP Commerce Cloud Black Friday and Cyber Monday Results Show Shoppers’ Willingness to Spend</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>‘Tis the season to be shopping, and retailers around the world have been gearing up for what is still the most important time of the year for shoppers – the holidays. While Black Friday and Cyber Monday usually kick off the official holiday season, we’ve seen many retailers start as early as the beginning of November to capture more market share sooner and stay ahead of the curve.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>But Cyber Week still reigns supreme for shoppers as the year’s most important shopping weekend. This year, <a href="/topics/sap-commerce-cloud">SAP Commerce Cloud</a> powered over <strong>US$8.3 billion in digital commerce gross merchandise value</strong> (GMV) for Cyber Week. Specifically, our retail customers saw a <strong>22.3% increase in average order value</strong> (AOV) year over year.</p>
  <p>The National Retail Federation (NRF) is predicting <a href="https://nrf.com/media-center/press-releases/nrf-predicts-healthy-holiday-sales-consumers-navigate-economic">6% to 8% growth in sales</a> compared with the same period last year, which is significantly lower than the 13% growth the year prior. We believe some of that growth can be attributed to <a href="https://www.bls.gov/cpi/">inflation, which was at 7.7%</a> as of late October.</p>
  <p>Inflation – coupled with a looming recession – has affected shopper spending habits, but not in the ways most people would expect. Many insiders and analysts predicted that shoppers would be buying less and paying more, but with <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/11/13/retailers-biggest-holiday-wish-is-to-get-rid-of-all-that-excess-inventory.html">retailers sitting on lots of inventory</a> this season, deals and promotions have been plentiful. In addition, shoppers aren’t necessarily shopping less, but instead <a href="https://nrf.com/research-insights/holiday-data-and-trends/winter-holidays">spreading out their purchases by buying earlier</a>. To help with cash flow, many shoppers are dipping into savings, relying on credit cards, or taking advantage of buy-now-pay-later options at checkout to be sure that they can still make the holidays work for themselves and their loved ones.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="reinvent-simplify-and-strengthen-your-e-commerce-business-with-sap">Reinvent, simplify, and strengthen your e-commerce business with SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm/e-commerce-platforms.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="shoppers-are-looking-for-deals-and-promotions">Shoppers Are Looking for Deals and Promotions</h2>
  <p>These spending trends are reflected in shoppers’ online behaviors as well, evidenced by movement in site traffic. For Black Friday, overall site traffic for SAP Commerce Cloud customers increased 23% versus last year. For these same customers on Cyber Monday, overall site traffic increased 53%.</p>
  <p>In addition to site traffic, retail customers leveraging SAP Commerce Cloud saw Black Friday conversion rates of 3.4 times more versus last year, as well as Cyber Monday conversion rates 2.9 times more versus last year.</p>
  <p>What’s more impressive are the site traffic metrics and conversion rates when we zoom in on our business-to-consumer (B2C) retail customers running sales events, which show that shoppers are actively looking for deals and will buy if the deals are attractive enough. Black Friday traffic for retailers running SAP Commerce Cloud that executed sales events was 33% higher year over year, versus a 16% increase for the total data set. Conversion rates during these events were even more impressive, with an explosive 209% higher year over year for those that ran them, compared to a 4% increase for the total data set. On Cyber Monday, traffic for retailers running sales events using SAP Commerce Cloud was 58% higher year over year, versus a 40% increase for the total data set. Conversion rates were similarly great, coming in at 382% higher year over year for those that ran sales events, compared to 5% less year over year for the whole data set.</p>
  <h2 id="what-to-expect-and-key-recommendations-for-brands">What to Expect and Key Recommendations for Brands</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-how-sap-commerce-cloud-integrates-each-customers-digital-activities-to-deliver-a-personalized-shopping-experience">Learn how SAP Commerce Cloud integrates each customer's digital activities to deliver a personalized shopping experience</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/oth/commerce-retail/index.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>EMarketer’s Insider Intelligence <a href="https://www.insiderintelligence.com/content/cyber-monday-projected-biggest-online-shopping-day-ever">predicts the remainder of the season will grow at 7%</a>, and with the current <a href="https://data.oecd.org/leadind/consumer-confidence-index-cci.htm">consumer confidence index at 96.5</a>, it’s hard to say if spending will persist throughout the rest of the holiday shopping season into the new year.</p>
  <p>Despite the current uncertainty, retailers can stay agile to cater to shoppers’ needs, meeting and exceeding their expectations while responding to dynamic market conditions. Having the right levers to pull at any time is key to successful holiday sales growth, so they should leverage their technology to monitor changing shopping behaviors and identify and convert on growth opportunities by quickly adding new touchpoints and experiences. Finally, they can ensure the last-mile journey for shoppers is frictionless by ensuring inventory levels will meet demand and fulfillment is not backlogged, ultimately avoiding the dreaded post-holiday returns that can eat into the growth they worked so hard for.</p>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div>To learn more about SAP Commerce Cloud, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm/commerce-cloud.html?source=social-Global-LINKEDIN_COMPANY-MarketingCampaign-CRM_and_Customer_Experience-SAPCX-BFCM_Card1-ComProduct-spr-8313917272-account_name&#x26;campaigncode=CRM-YA22-BSC-1440506&#x26;sprinklrid=8313917272">visit the solution page</a>.</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>All data presented here is approximate and is based on various assumptions. All data is unaudited and is subject to adjustment. All financial figures are in USD. Data represents online and offline sales made by SAP global merchants.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/e-commerce</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
            <category>product/sap-commerce-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-customer-experience</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Announces Winners of the SAP Global SAP Customer Experience Partner Excellence Awards 2022]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/sap-customer-experience-partner-excellence-awards-2022-winners</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/sap-customer-experience-partner-excellence-awards-2022-winners</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Six global awards for partner excellence in the SAP Customer Experience LoB during SAP CX LIVE: Exec Connect in London.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-customer-experience</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-customer-experience-live</category>
            <category>sap-award/sap-global-lob-partner-excellence-awards</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Customer Experience Helps Marketing and Sales Teams Win Together]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/sap-customer-experience-account-engagement-marketing-and-sales-teams-win</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/sap-customer-experience-account-engagement-marketing-and-sales-teams-win</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The new account engagement option for SAP Customer Experience helps marketing and sales teams accelerate performance and grow revenue.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-engagement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-customer-experience</category>
            <category>product/sap-emarsys-customer-engagement</category>
            <category>product/sap-sales-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Why Is CX Critical for Future-Proofing B2B Sales?]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/future-proof-b2b-sales-cx-critical</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/future-proof-b2b-sales-cx-critical</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[To future-proof your B2B sales, SAP Sales Cloud can connects experiences to outcomes that matter for your customer. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-customer-experience</category>
            <category>product/sap-sales-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Digital Strategy Behind Moen’s Customer Experience Magic]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/09/moen-customer-experience-digital-strategy</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/09/moen-customer-experience-digital-strategy</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Moen, North America's leading faucet maker, is digitalizing on a cloud-based platform to get closer to customers and innovate business models.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-customer-experience</category>
            <category>product/sap-sales-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-service-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Named a Leader in 2022 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Digital Commerce]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/2022-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-digital-commerce-sap-a-leader</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/2022-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-digital-commerce-sap-a-leader</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP been named a leader in the 2022 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Digital Commerce for the eighth time. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/magic-quadrant</category>
            <category>product/sap-commerce-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-customer-experience</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bridge the Coder Talent Gap to Accelerate the Innovation of Personalized Experiences]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/bridge-coder-talent-gap-lcnc-accelerate-innovation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/bridge-coder-talent-gap-lcnc-accelerate-innovation</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP partners are tapping into a new community of innovators by joining the low-code/no-code (LCNC) movement. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/low-code-no-code</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-commerce-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-customer-experience</category>
            <category>product/sap-intelligent-rpa</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-partneredge</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-partneredge-build</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Creating a More Sustainable World with SAP’s Focus on Green Customer Experiences]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/green-customer-experiences-more-sustainable-world</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/green-customer-experiences-more-sustainable-world</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Green customer experiences increase loyalty, facilitate eco-conscious behaviors, promote sustainable consumption, and meet market demands.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-customer-experience</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP and Icertis Expand Partnership to Deliver Enterprise Contract Intelligence]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/01/sap-icertis-expand-partnership</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/01/sap-icertis-expand-partnership</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[An expanded cooperation with Icertis will help SAP customers take advantage of market-leading innovations for contract management.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_138c442285c71c51b7df821b9cafb8724bb18d76f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_138c442285c71c51b7df821b9cafb8724bb18d76f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_138c442285c71c51b7df821b9cafb8724bb18d76f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP and Icertis Expand Partnership to Deliver Enterprise Contract Intelligence" src="./media_138c442285c71c51b7df821b9cafb8724bb18d76f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-and-icertis-expand-partnership-to-deliver-enterprise-contract-intelligence">SAP and Icertis Expand Partnership to Deliver Enterprise Contract Intelligence</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF and BELLEVUE, Wash.</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com">SAP SE</a> (NYSE:SAP) and <a href="http://www.icertis.com">Icertis</a> today announced an expanded partnership for enhanced contract management to help companies increase efficiency, minimize risk and realize the full intent of their agreements.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The partnership, which includes a financial investment from SAP in Icertis, will lead to a joint product road map and deeper technological integration to deliver enterprise-wide value, including faster negotiations, greater compliance and AI-powered business insights and automation.</p>
  <p>“The expanded cooperation with Icertis will help our customers take advantage of market-leading innovations for contract management from Icertis while managing core business processes with SAP solutions,” said Christian Klein, CEO and member of the Executive Board, SAP SE. “This partnership is a great complement to our portfolio, with multiple touchpoints to SAP systems across ERP, finance, procurement, sales and HR.”</p>
  <p>This expanded partnership builds on the existing relationship between SAP and Icertis, which began in 2020 to transform the <a href="https://www.icertis.com/news/icertis-integrates-with-sap-ariba/?utm_source=hootsuite&#x26;utm_medium=&#x26;utm_term=&#x26;utm_content=&#x26;utm_campaign=Increase%20CLM%20Leadership">source-to-pay</a> and <a href="https://www.icertis.com/news/icertis-partners-with-sap-sales-cloud/">lead-to-cash</a> processes through the integration of Icertis Contract Intelligence (ICI) with SAP Ariba and SAP Customer Experience solutions. The enhanced partnership further leverages each company’s technology to deliver even more value to a growing list of joint customers. Customers will have the opportunity to benefit from ICI capabilities for smart contract creation, online negotiation, AI-assisted risk identification, obligation management and contract-driven insights for decision support while operating their core source-to-pay and lead-to-cash processes within SAP solutions.</p>
  <p>“With this partnership, SAP and Icertis customers will be able to derive end-to-end value across the enterprise, so the intent of every contract is correctly memorialized and fully realized,” said Samir Bodas, CEO of Icertis. “Partnering with SAP to bring our AI-powered, best-of-breed contract intelligence to the market is another affirmation of Icertis’ strategy to become the contract intelligence platform of the world. It is also a testament to SAP’s forward-looking vision for the intelligent and networked enterprise.”</p>
  <p>As part of the expanded partnership, Icertis Contract Intelligence (ICI) for SAP Ariba solutions and ICI for SAP Customer Experience solutions are now SAP Endorsed Apps, premium certified by SAP with added security, in-depth testing and measurements against cloud operations best practices.</p>
  <p>“SAP’s focus on the intelligent enterprise has enabled many organizations to move into the digital-first world, and the contracting process in SAP Ariba solutions has done much for the buying community,” said Mickey North Rizza, Program Vice President Enterprise Applications and Digital Commerce, IDC. “Icertis is named a leader in the IDC MarketScape: Worldwide Contract Life-Cycle Management Software for Corporate Legal 2021. With Icertis’ flexible platform and enhanced CLM capabilities, SAP can now manage the trading partner relationship for the enterprise in a much more integrated, innovative and tailored manner.”</p>
  <p>Contracts are the foundation of commerce, governing the rights and obligations between parties. Traditional contract management is often manual and siloed, creating inefficiency and risk while leaving value unrealized. ICI helps structure and connect data within contracts across an enterprise, enabling businesses to increase efficiencies, identify and mitigate potential risk, and drive bottom-line value throughout the contract lifecycle.</p>
  <p>Icertis solutions including <a href="https://store.sap.com/dcp/en/product/display-0000055732_live_v1/Icertis%20Contract%20Intelligence%20%28ICI%29%20for%20SAP%20Ariba">ICI for SAP Ariba solutions</a> and <a href="https://store.sap.com/dcp/en/product/display-0000059213_live_v1/Icertis%20Contract%20Intelligence%20%28ICI%29%20for%20SAP%20Customer%20Experience">ICI for SAP Customer Experience solutions</a> are available in <a href="https://store.sap.com/dcp/en/">SAP Store</a>, the digital marketplace for solutions from SAP and its partners. SAP Store provides customers with real-time access to more than 1,800 innovative solutions from SAP as well as partner solutions that complement and extend their SAP applications.</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="/">SAP News Center</a> and follow SAP on Twitter at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="standardize-source-to-contract-processes-across-the-organization">Standardize source-to-contract processes across the organization</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/spend-management/strategic-sourcing-and-contracts.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="about-icertis">About Icertis</h3>
  <p>With unmatched technology and category-defining innovation, Icertis pushes the boundaries of what’s possible with contract lifecycle management (CLM). The AI-powered, analyst-validated Icertis Contract Intelligence (ICI) platform turns contracts from static documents into a strategic advantage by structuring and connecting the critical contract information that defines how an organization runs. Today, the world’s most iconic brands and disruptive innovators trust Icertis to govern the rights and commitments in their 10 million+ contracts worth more than $1 trillion, in 40+ languages and 90+ countries.</p>
  <p><strong>About SAP</strong></p>
  <p>SAP’s strategy is to help every business run as an intelligent enterprise. As a market leader in enterprise application software, we help companies of all sizes and in all industries run at their best: SAP customers generate 87% of total global commerce. Our machine learning, Internet of Things (IoT), and advanced analytics technologies help turn customers’ businesses into intelligent enterprises. SAP helps give people and organizations deep business insight and fosters collaboration that helps them stay ahead of their competition. We simplify technology for companies so they can consume our software the way they want — without disruption. Our end-to-end suite of applications and services enables business and public customers across 25 industries globally to operate profitably, adapt continuously, and make a difference. With a global network of customers, partners, employees, and thought leaders, SAP helps the world run better and improve people’s lives. For more information, visit <a href="http://www.sap.com">www.sap.com</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Note to editors:</strong><br>To preview and download broadcast-standard stock footage and press photos digitally, please visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/photos">www.sap.com/photos</a>. On this platform, you can find high resolution material for your media channels. To view video stories on diverse topics, visit <a href="http://www.sap-tv.com">www.sap-tv.com</a>. From this site, you can embed videos into your own Web pages, share video via email links, and subscribe to RSS feeds from SAP TV.</p>
  <p><strong>For customers interested in learning more about SAP products:</strong><br>Global Customer Center: +49 180 534-34-24<br>United States Only: 1 (800) 872-1SAP (1-800-872-1727)</p>
  <p><strong>For more information, press only:</strong>:<br>Kelly Sheldon Murray, SAP, +1 (978) 708-6821, <a href="mailto:kelly.murray@sap.com">kelly.murray@sap.com</a><u>,</u> ETGeraldine Lim, SAP, +1 (415) 418-0945, <a href="mailto:geraldine.lim@sap.com">geraldine.lim@sap.com</a>, PT<br><a href="mailto:SAP%20Press%20Room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a><br>Liza Colburn, Director of Corporate Communications, Icertis,<br><a href="mailto:CorpComm@icertis.com">CorpComm@icertis.com</a>, +1 (781) 562-0111</p>
  <p>This document contains forward-looking statements, which are predictions, projections, or other statements about future events. These statements are based on current expectations, forecasts, and assumptions that are subject to risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results and outcomes to materially differ. Additional information regarding these risks and uncertainties may be found in our filings with the Securities and Exchange Commission, including but not limited to the risk factors section of SAP’s 2020 Annual Report on Form 20-F.<br>© 2022 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.<br>Please consider our <a href="https://www.sap.com/corporate/en/legal/privacy.html">privacy policy</a>. If you received this press release in your e-mail and you wish to unsubscribe to our mailing list please contact <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a> and write Unsubscribe in the subject line.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-customer-experience</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Digital Process Automation: Kicking Off a New Generation of Operating Models]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/01/digital-process-automation-kicking-off-a-new-generation-of-operating-models</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/01/digital-process-automation-kicking-off-a-new-generation-of-operating-models</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn how SAP partners utilize digital process automation to help customers boost business agility and better respond to changing markets.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b382846fa5ed04adb96fe59e3d91f97ff1e22c71.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b382846fa5ed04adb96fe59e3d91f97ff1e22c71.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1b382846fa5ed04adb96fe59e3d91f97ff1e22c71.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Digital Process Automation: Kicking Off a New Generation of Operating Models" src="./media_1b382846fa5ed04adb96fe59e3d91f97ff1e22c71.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="digital-process-automation-kicking-off-a-new-generation-of-operating-models">Digital Process Automation: Kicking Off a New Generation of Operating Models</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>More and more, we’re living in a culture of digital innovation and experimentation – and digital process automation represents the latest domain of experimentation. For SAP partners, this is an opportunity to address every conceivable area of need – from job roles to customer experiences and business processes – with SAP Business Technology Platform.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The concept of process automation may not be new, but it’s now fueling a wide assortment of business scenarios that go beyond simple processes, tasks, and workflows. Companies are now digitalizing their operations – reaching into their vendor networks, business partners, and customers – to address organizational needs more holistically and strategically.</p>
  <p>At SAP, many of our partners are using <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">SAP Business Technology Platform</a> (SAP BTP) to help customers take advantage of this trend to build applications that drive revenue growth. By embedding modern automation capabilities in line-of-business systems, they can improve information usability and process efficiency with automation capabilities such as verification workflows, approval processes, content integration, or the retirement of outdated materials and inventory.</p>
  <p>These examples are only a small glimpse into the automation use cases that SAP BTP can support. Through its operational layer, the platform provides a portfolio of low-code development tools and prebuilt content that can enable our partners and their customers to drive critical improvements with automation.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-business-processes-applications-data-and-experiences-with-sap-btp">Connect business processes, applications, data, and experiences with SAP BTP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="setting-the-foundation-for-performance-improvement">Setting the Foundation for Performance Improvement</h2>
  <p>When first considering automation, most organizations often think about their processes. Why? To increase their operational efficiency, make better decisions, improve performance and customer satisfaction, and, better yet, allow employees to focus on more strategic work.</p>
  <p>SAP BTP supports this entry into the automation world by providing <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-process-intelligence.html">business process intelligence</a>, empowering users with a low-code and no-code platform, workflow capabilities, robotic process automation (RPA), and machine learning. Our customers can transform their business safely and predictably with proven methodologies for project and process governance and a simulation engine that evaluates the impact of change.</p>
  <p>With these capabilities, organizations can adopt a range of use cases. For example, <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2020/04/ce197ac4-927d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff.html">Uniper</a> has automated job requisitioning, streamlined processes for requesting and approving time off, and accelerated role authorization, registration, and authentication. In return, the energy market powerhouse realized 50% time savings on plant inspections and 10 times faster data entry for job requisitions.</p>
  <p>Meanwhile, companies such as <a href="https://www.sap.com/bin/sapdxc/inm/attachment.8577/pitch-deck.pdf">Villeroy &#x26; Boch Group</a> have offloaded rule-based tasks, including the checking, classification, and processing of thousands of documents. This approach freed up employees to focus on nonroutine activities that help maximize business value and improve customer experiences.</p>
  <h2 id="cultivating-a-portal-that-unifies-work-experiences">Cultivating a Portal That Unifies Work Experiences</h2>
  <p>When using legacy workflows or out-of-date portals, maintaining a cohesive operation of multiple departments, suppliers, partners, and service providers can be difficult. But SAP BTP can help companies overcome that challenge by providing quick and intuitive mobile access to essential functions, documentation, and resources – everything a business needs to support organizational processes and strengthen information management company-wide.</p>
  <p>The platform delivers an expanding set of services that enable customers and partners to maximize the value of existing SAP applications – combining access to external data and systems through integration. Our partners can then leverage their expertise and knowledge to extend those digital assets to develop capabilities that, for example, introduce automation into complex processes and workflows and connect internal and external stakeholders.</p>
  <p>By pulling all these innovations together into a user-friendly portal, the entire business can collaborate and access information anytime and anywhere and use that intelligence to take decisive action on risks and opportunities. Administrative processes and workflows are further simplified with a streamlined user interface, while systems and data are kept secure with authentication.</p>
  <p>By adopting this use case for SAP BTP, food exporter <a href="https://dam.sap.com/mac/u/a/kM72htV.htm">SunRice</a> teamed up with SAP partner Bourne Digital Pty. Ltd. to extend existing systems and enhance its growers’ portal.</p>
  <h2 id="inspiring-lasting-connections-between-people-and-business">Inspiring Lasting Connections Between People and Business</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="harness-your-intellectual-property-and-take-it-to-market-as-an-sap-partner">Harness your intellectual property and take it to market as an SAP partner</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/partner/become/partneredge-build.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>On a journey to modernization, most companies choose to overhaul their aging legacy systems, cumbersome processes, and paper-based reporting to improve operational efficiency so they can adapt quickly to changing market conditions.</p>
  <p>One approach that many customers follow is migrating to <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/s4hana-erp.html">SAP S/4HANA Cloud</a> and implementing the <a href="https://www.sapstore.com/solutions/42339/SAP-Workflow-Management">SAP Workflow Management</a> service and the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/cloud-analytics.html">SAP Analytics Cloud</a> solution, all of which are part of SAP BTP. With the help of a partner, customers can embed analytics capabilities into existing business applications and establish enterprise-wide governance to help optimize the management of general ledgers, revenue, and expenses. Then, they can quickly transform their enterprise resource planning (ERP) data to automate tasks such as financial and management reporting.</p>
  <p>The benefits of system automation can quickly add up as individual process efficiencies are combined, resulting in reduced administration and reporting times, consolidation of financial results, and elimination of manual processes. Business planners can also leverage strategic dashboards generated by SAP Analytics Cloud to gain near-real-time insights into critical performance indicators. Additionally, with the inclusion of SAP S/4HANA Cloud, they can analyze scenarios, create forecasts, and predict future growth.</p>
  <p>Emulating the above path, <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2020/09/3c1db458-ad7d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff.html">Taronga Conservation Society Australia</a> and its software partner Bluetree Pty. Ltd. automated financial and management reporting, streamlined data-driven decision-making, and delivered a superior user experience.</p>
  <h2 id="improving-the-customer-experience-from-lead-to-order">Improving the Customer Experience from Lead to Order</h2>
  <p>Automating lead-to-order processes is particularly interesting to companies that characterized their customer experiences with fast response times, little to no fulfillment errors, and inventory accuracy. Yet, even more compelling is the opportunity to enhance order visibility, efficiency, and integration from early marketing touchpoints to deal closure and beyond – accelerating customer loyalty and fueling profitable business growth.</p>
  <p>SAP customers can adopt this use-case scenario with a <a href="https://api.sap.com/package/com.ibm.bpm.ep.lto.iworkflowforleadtoorder/overview">lead-to-order intelligent workflow API package</a> – developed and maintained by one of our partners, IBM. The package spans multiple solutions such as SAP S/4HANA Cloud and the <a href="https://www.sap.com/canada/products/crm/products.html#active_tab=item_1602592296240">SAP Customer Experience portfolio</a>, which spans sales automation and configure, price, and quote (CPQ) solutions.</p>
  <p>Similar chatbot-enabled scenarios enable organizations to benefit from the automatic and rapid dissemination of relevant sales intelligence, price optimizations, and a real-time outlook into sales and pipeline performance. Furthermore, they can create lead and CPQ processes integrated with customer self-services, providing a collaborative customer experience beginning with the first interaction.</p>
  <h2 id="taking-business-intelligence-to-the-next-level">Taking Business Intelligence to the Next Level</h2>
  <p>The more companies digitally transform, the more agile, efficient, and innovative they expect to be. And of course, they see digital process automation as a critical milestone in their journey to becoming an intelligent enterprise.</p>
  <p>But this form of digitalization is much more than automating basic processes and workflows. It also expands existing systems and data and adapts them to meet new regulatory requirements, innovative business functions, emerging customer expectations, and more.</p>
  <p>By using SAP BTP as their unified and open platform for innovation, partners can help customers increase their business agility while adapting and responding to changing requirements and conditions. Furthermore, the addition of intelligent automation can boost customer satisfaction as new efficiencies are gained through the redirection of resources toward higher-value activities and the reinvention of workflows that enable a continuous stream of process improvements.</p>
  <p>Most importantly, our partners and customers are supported by the business, industry, and technical knowledge of a global ecosystem. Together, with SAP BTP and our enablement services, they can optimize the use of our back-end technology and understand our application life cycle and road map – all with a focus on shaping their unique vision of an intelligent enterprise.</p>
  <p>To learn more about how SAP partners are helping businesses succeed with a unified technology platform, <a href="/author/jagdishsahasrabudhe">explore my other articles</a>. If you’re interested in software partnership opportunities with SAP, check out <a href="https://www.sap.com/partner/become/partneredge-build.html">SAP PartnerEdge, Build</a>. If you’re already a partner, check out these exciting initiatives: <a href="https://events.sap.com/hack2build/en/home">Hack2Build</a> and <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/innovation/coil.html">SAP Co-Innovation Lab</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Jagdish Sahasrabudhe is CTO of Global Partner Organization at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-partneredge</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-partneredge-build</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-workflow-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Named a Leader in 2021 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Configure, Price and Quote Application Suites]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/sap-a-leader-magic-quadrant-cpq-application-suites</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/sap-a-leader-magic-quadrant-cpq-application-suites</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[For the fourth consecutive year, SAP is again a Leader in the 2021 Gartner Magic Quadrant for CPQ Application Suites. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1003a8ab55898d80871e8dfdb899389a2c8a7fc26.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1003a8ab55898d80871e8dfdb899389a2c8a7fc26.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1003a8ab55898d80871e8dfdb899389a2c8a7fc26.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Named a Leader in 2021 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Configure, Price and Quote Application Suites" src="./media_1003a8ab55898d80871e8dfdb899389a2c8a7fc26.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-named-a-leader-in-2021-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-configure-price-and-quote-application-suites">SAP Named a Leader in 2021 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Configure, Price and Quote Application Suites</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-cpq-deliver-the-perfect-solution-for-your-customers-with-fast-and-accurate-quotes">SAP CPQ: Deliver the perfect solution for your customers with fast and accurate quotes</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/cpq.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced it has been positioned as a Leader in the 2021 <a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/cx/gartner-mq-cpq/index.html">Gartner Magic Quadrant for Configure, Price and Quote Application Suites</a>.<sup>1</sup> This is the fourth consecutive year SAP has been positioned as a Leader in this Gartner Magic Quadrant.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/cpq.html">SAP CPQ</a> solution helps streamline the sales-quote-to-cash process, leading to more signed deals, higher margins and a better experience for both sales and customers.</p>
  <p>“Customers expect a buying process that is quick and simple, no matter how complicated the product or service might be,” said Sameer Patel, chief marketing and solution officer for SAP Customer Experience. “The last mile of the transaction is extremely critical in the buying process and serves as an opportunity for brands to stand out from the competition and deliver on the customers expectation of a great experience. With SAP CPQ, sales teams and partners have the power to quickly build a quote for the right solution, at the right price, every single time.”</p>
  <p>SAP CPQ is part of the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm.html">SAP Customer Experience</a> portfolio, which goes beyond traditional CRM solutions by bringing together customer data, experiential and operational data, and machine learning. SAP Customer Experience offers organizations a complete platform to address all customer interactions using a common data model and functionality from commerce, marketing, sales and service to address their business needs.</p>
  <p>To learn more, <a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/cx/gartner-mq-cpq/index.html">download a complimentary copy</a> of the Gartner Magic Quadrant for CPQ Application Suites.</p>
  <p>Recently, SAP was also named a Leader in the <a href="/2021/09/gartner-magic-quadrant-for-digital-commerce-sap-a-leader">2021 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Digital Commerce<sup>2</sup></a> for the seventh time and as a Leader in the <a href="/2021/08/sap-leader-2021-gartner-magic-quadrant-sales-force-automation">2021 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Sales Force Automation</a><sup>3</sup> for the third consecutive year. Additionally, Emarsys, now part of SAP, was recently named a Leader for the third time in the <a href="/2021/07/emarsys-personalization-engines-magic-quadrant">2021 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Personalization Engines</a>.<sup>4</sup></p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Visit the <a href="http://news.sap.com/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP on Twitter at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Media Contact:</strong> Samantha Finnegan, +1 (415) 377-0475, <a href="mailto:samantha.finnegan@sap.com">samantha.finnegan@sap.com</a>, ET<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>1. Gartner, “Magic Quadrant for Configure, Price and Quote Application Suites,” <a href="https://www.gartner.com/analyst/61052">Mark Lewis</a>, <a href="https://www.gartner.com/analyst/84153">Dayna Ford</a>, October 21, 2021.<br>2. Gartner, “Magic Quadrant for Digital Commerce,” Jason Daigler, Yanna Dharmasthira, Sandy Shen, Penny Gillespie, Mike Lowndes, Aditya Vasudevan, August 31, 2021.<br>3. Gartner, “Magic Quadrant for Sales Force Automation,” Adnan Zijadic, Ilona Hansen, Melissa Hilbert, Steve Rietberg, August 4, 2021.<br>4. Gartner, “Magic Quadrant for Personalization Engines,”<a href="https://www.gartner.com/analyst/88875">Jason McNellis</a>, <a href="https://www.gartner.com/analyst/67591">Claire Tassin</a>, <a href="https://www.gartner.com/analyst/46806">Jennifer Polk</a>, July 19, 2021.</p>
  <p><em>Gartner does not endorse any vendor, product or service depicted in its research publications, and does not advise technology users to select only those vendors with the highest ratings or other designation. Gartner research publications consist of the opinions of Gartner’s research organization and should not be construed as statements of fact. Gartner disclaims all warranties, expressed or implied, with respect to this research, including any warranties of merchantability or fitness for a particular purpose.</em><br><em>Gartner and Magic Quadrant are registered trademarks of Gartner, Inc. and/or its affiliates in the U.S. and internationally and is used herein with permission. All rights reserved.</em></p>
  <p>Any statements contained in this document that are not historical facts are forward-looking statements as defined in the U.S. Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995. Words such as “anticipate,” “believe,” “estimate,” “expect,” “forecast,” “intend,” “may,” “plan,” “project,” “predict,” “should” and “will” and similar expressions as they relate to SAP are intended to identify such forward-looking statements. SAP undertakes no obligation to publicly update or revise any forward-looking statements. All forward-looking statements are subject to various risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results to differ materially from expectations. The factors that could affect SAP’s future financial results are discussed more fully in SAP’s filings with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (“SEC”), including SAP’s most recent Annual Report on Form 20-F filed with the SEC. Readers are cautioned not to place undue reliance on these forward-looking statements, which speak only as of their dates.<br>© 2021 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/magic-quadrant</category>
            <category>product/sap-cpq</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-customer-experience</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Hires Ritu Bhargava as Chief Product Officer for SAP Customer Experience; Bob Stutz Retiring After a Trailblazing Career in the Tech Industry]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/ritu-bhargava-chief-product-officer-sap-customer-experience-bob-stutz-retires</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/ritu-bhargava-chief-product-officer-sap-customer-experience-bob-stutz-retires</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Ritu Bhargava will join SAP as chief product officer for SAP Customer Experience, taking over from Bob Stutz as he retires.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1054e2db604c9269de0e5d81811610399237f7250.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1054e2db604c9269de0e5d81811610399237f7250.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1054e2db604c9269de0e5d81811610399237f7250.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Hires Ritu Bhargava as Chief Product Officer for SAP Customer Experience; Bob Stutz Retiring After a Trailblazing Career in the Tech Industry" src="./media_1054e2db604c9269de0e5d81811610399237f7250.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-hires-ritu-bhargava-as-chief-product-officer-for-sap-customer-experience-bob-stutz-retiring-after-a-trailblazing-career-in-the-tech-industry">SAP Hires Ritu Bhargava as Chief Product Officer for SAP Customer Experience; Bob Stutz Retiring After a Trailblazing Career in the Tech Industry</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="understand-your-customers-and-engage-them-with-hyper-personalized-experiences">Understand your customers and engage them with hyper-personalized experiences</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced that Ritu Bhargava will join SAP on November 15, 2021, to become chief product officer for SAP Customer Experience.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP’s vision is to help companies enable a cohesive customer experience (CX) across the entire customer lifecycle. With its CX portfolio, SAP is bringing together customer, experience and operational data to deliver unique value to customers.</p>
  <p>“During the last months, all businesses have been challenged with the need to reinvent the experience for their customers — to make it personalized, seamless and outstanding”, said Christian Klein, CEO of SAP SE. “Companies understand that if they are not competing on experience, they don’t stand a chance. Delivering meaningful experiences at scale has become key to stay competitive.”</p>
  <p>“Ritu brings extensive experience in the enterprise applications and CX space, a strong market focus from both a business and an engineering perspective, and an employee-focused and customer-first mindset,” said Thomas Saueressig, member of the Executive Board of SAP SE. “I couldn’t think of a better match to strengthen our stellar CX team.”</p>
  <p>Bhargava joins SAP from Salesforce, where she held various technology leadership positions over the past ten years, most recently heading Salesforce Sales Cloud engineering as a senior vice president. She started her career working as an SAP developer before she went on to work at Oracle for ten years, responsible for financial applications in various roles. Bhargava holds a bachelor’s degree in economics and psychology from Lady Shriram College, Delhi University, and an MBA in finance and IT from the University of Lincolnshire, UK. She co-chairs the West Coast Advisory Board for Asian University for Women, a Bangladesh-based nonprofit dedicated to women’s education and leadership development.</p>
  <p>Bhargava is taking over from Bob Stutz, one of the world’s leading experts on customer experience and recognized by Ad Age as one of the Top 25 Marketing Technology Trailblazers, who is retiring after a career of more than 25 years in the tech industry.</p>
  <p>“Since Bob rejoined SAP in 2019, he has done a tremendous job in driving our CX business forward,” said Saueressig. “There is hardly another tech leader who has shaped CRM and CX in such a unique way over the past 25 years. His visibility in the tech industry and his passion for making every customer experience a great experience is unmatched. We are very happy to have had him onboard over the past few years, and I’m incredibly grateful for everything he has done for our customers and the entire ecosystem.”</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="http://news.sap.com/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP on Twitter at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Media Contact:</strong> Marcus Winkler, +49 6227 7-67497, <a href="mailto:marcus.winkler@sap.com">marcus.winkler@sap.com</a>, CET<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>Any statements contained in this document that are not historical facts are forward-looking statements as defined in the U.S. Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995. Words such as “anticipate,” “believe,” “estimate,” “expect,” “forecast,” “intend,” “may,” “plan,” “project,” “predict,” “should” and “will” and similar expressions as they relate to SAP are intended to identify such forward-looking statements. SAP undertakes no obligation to publicly update or revise any forward-looking statements. All forward-looking statements are subject to various risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results to differ materially from expectations. The factors that could affect SAP’s future financial results are discussed more fully in SAP’s filings with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (“SEC”), including SAP’s most recent Annual Report on Form 20-F filed with the SEC. Readers are cautioned not to place undue reliance on these forward-looking statements, which speak only as of their dates.<br>© 2021 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-customer-experience</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[CPG Companies Use AI to Build High-Performance Sales Teams]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/cpg-companies-use-ai-build-high-performance-sales-teams</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/cpg-companies-use-ai-build-high-performance-sales-teams</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[When salespeople don‘t meet expectations, an AI-based tool from Datoin surfaces problems so teams and their managers can fix them fast.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>industry/consumer-goods-cpg</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-labs-network</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Five Ways Australian Market Leaders Create Winning Customer Experiences]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/five-ways-australian-market-leaders-create-winning-cx</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/five-ways-australian-market-leaders-create-winning-cx</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Leaders from two Australian-based companies shared their thoughts on winning CX strategies during a virtual SAPPHIRE NOW session.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-anz</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-customer-experience</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Named a Leader in 2021 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Digital Commerce]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/gartner-magic-quadrant-for-digital-commerce-sap-a-leader</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/gartner-magic-quadrant-for-digital-commerce-sap-a-leader</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP has been named a Leader in the Gartner Magic Quadrant for Digital Commerce for the seventh time. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a4c969871301bddfedbdb094fe5b6142c0715599.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a4c969871301bddfedbdb094fe5b6142c0715599.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1a4c969871301bddfedbdb094fe5b6142c0715599.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Named a Leader in 2021 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Digital Commerce" src="./media_1a4c969871301bddfedbdb094fe5b6142c0715599.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-named-a-leader-in-2021-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-digital-commerce">SAP Named a Leader in 2021 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Digital Commerce</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="digital-commerce-deliver-a-rich-personalized-omnichannel-e-commerce-experience-and-gain-agility-to-meet-ever-changing-customer-needs">Digital Commerce: Deliver a rich, personalized omnichannel e-commerce experience and gain agility to meet ever-changing customer needs</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm/e-commerce-platforms.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced it has been named a Leader in the 2021 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Digital Commerce* for the seventh time. In its latest 2021 report, Gartner assessed solutions from 17 vendors including <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm/e-commerce-platforms.html">commerce solutions from SAP</a>.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Brands globally, including appliance manufacturer De’Longhi, nutritional products distributor Kyani and retailer Abrakadabra, have recently selected SAP solutions to help deliver a rich, personalized omnichannel e-commerce experience that is reliable and scales to meet the demands of their customers.</p>
  <p>“We believe this latest positioning as a Leader by Gartner is why brands across industries and geographies are turning to SAP to broaden their commerce reach without compromising flexibility,” said Nuno Pedro, global head, Commerce Solutions, SAP. “Digital commerce solutions from SAP enable success across different industries, marketplaces and business models by providing customers enjoyable, individually relevant, in-the-moment experiences.”</p>
  <p><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm/e-commerce-platforms.html">Digital commerce solutions from SAP</a>, which include <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/commerce-cloud.html">SAP Commerce Cloud</a> and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm/e-commerce-platforms.html#upscale-commerce">SAP Upscale Commerce</a>, help brands convert more customers by turning engagements into personal, shoppable moments. Additional companies that recently chose digital commerce solutions from SAP in the first half of 2021 include the following:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Hangcha Group</strong> is one of the largest forklift manufacturers in China and among the top 10 in the world. Hangcha Group chose SAP Commerce Cloud to simplify its front-end sales order intake process and integrate with its back-end digital core system, supporting the group’s business transformation and boosting sales revenue.</li>
    <li><strong><a href="/2021/06/sapphire-now-sap-upscale-commerce-midmarket-brands">JOY</a></strong>, a Swedish fashion retailer, no longer has any physical stores and is instead focusing on e-commerce and personalized fashion advice. Its founders see JOY as a startup building next-generation e-commerce based on AI and slow fashion — a more sustainable alternative with clothes lasting several seasons. JOY is also the first company in the world that has selected the combination of the cloud-based solution SAP Upscale Commerce and the SAP Emarsys Customer Engagement platform.</li>
    <li><strong>Perfumes y Esencias Fraiche</strong>, a Mexican company specializing in fragrances and essences that serves more than 20 million people through different sales channels, chose SAP Commerce Cloud and SAP Marketing Cloud. With these solutions, the company can strengthen its online presence to meet new consumer needs, using a solid digital strategy that enables personalized fragrance sales for its customers and through thousands of distributors.</li>
    <li><strong><a href="/2021/05/leading-european-organizations-deichmann-chemie-sap-cx">WAGO Kontakttechnik GmbH &#x26; Co</a></strong>. KG is a leading German manufacturer of electrical connections and components, and a specialist in spring clamps for automation. It recently implemented SAP Commerce Cloud solutions as part of its cloud transformation. With SAP Commerce Cloud integrated with SAP Marketing Cloud and the SAP ERP application, it plans to provide a great e-commerce experience for its business-to-business (B2B) customers.</li>
    <li><strong><a href="/2021/05/leading-european-organizations-deichmann-chemie-sap-cx">Wacker Chemie</a></strong> is a leading German player in highly developed specialty products for several industrial sectors. It recently implemented SAP Commerce Cloud as its new B2B e-commerce system to increase sales and improve customer satisfaction.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>Digital commerce solutions from SAP are part of the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm.html">SAP Customer Experience</a> portfolio, which goes beyond traditional CRM solutions by bringing together customer data, experiential and operational data, and machine learning.</p>
  <p>To learn more, download a <a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/cx/gartner-magic-quadrant-e-commerce/index.html?campaigncode=CRM-HY21-CIP-AGTMQDC&#x26;source=onlinedisplay-glo--commerce-led-experiences">complimentary copy of the report</a>, including Gartner’s in-depth analysis of the digital commerce landscape.</p>
  <p>SAP was also recognized for the third consecutive year as a Leader in the <a href="/2021/08/sap-leader-2021-gartner-magic-quadrant-sales-force-automation">2021 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Sales Force Automation</a>.** Additionally, Emarsys, now part of SAP, was recently named a Leader for the third time in the <a href="/2021/07/emarsys-personalization-engines-magic-quadrant">2021 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Personalization Engines</a>.***</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="http://news.sap.com/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP on Twitter at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Media Contact:</strong> Samantha Finnegan, +1 (415) 377-0475, <a href="mailto:samantha.finnegan@sap.com">samantha.finnegan@sap.com</a>, ET<br><a href="mailto:SAP%20Press%20Room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>*Gartner, “Magic Quadrant for Digital Commerce,” Jason Daigler, Yanna Dharmasthira, Sandy Shen, Penny Gillespie, Mike Lowndes, Aditya Vasudevan, August 31, 2021.<br>**Gartner, “Magic Quadrant for Sales Force Automation,” Adnan Zijadic, Ilona Hansen, Melissa Hilbert, Steve Rietberg, August 4, 2021.<br>***Gartner, “Magic Quadrant for Personalization Engines,” Jason McNellis, Claire Tassin, Jennifer Polk, July 19, 2021.<br><em>Gartner does not endorse any vendor, product or service depicted in its research publications, and does not advise technology users to select only those vendors with the highest ratings or other designation. Gartner research publications consist of the opinions of Gartner’s research organization and should not be construed as statements of fact. Gartner disclaims all warranties, expressed or implied, with respect to this research, including any warranties of merchantability or fitness for a particular purpose.</em><br><em>Gartner and Magic Quadrant are registered trademarks of Gartner, Inc. and/or its affiliates in the U.S. and internationally and is used herein with permission. All rights reserved.</em></p>
  <p>Any statements contained in this document that are not historical facts are forward-looking statements as defined in the U.S. Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995. Words such as “anticipate,” “believe,” “estimate,” “expect,” “forecast,” “intend,” “may,” “plan,” “project,” “predict,” “should” and “will” and similar expressions as they relate to SAP are intended to identify such forward-looking statements. SAP undertakes no obligation to publicly update or revise any forward-looking statements. All forward-looking statements are subject to various risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results to differ materially from expectations. The factors that could affect SAP’s future financial results are discussed more fully in SAP’s filings with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (“SEC”), including SAP’s most recent Annual Report on Form 20-F filed with the SEC. Readers are cautioned not to place undue reliance on these forward-looking statements, which speak only as of their dates.<br>© 2021 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-commerce</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/magic-quadrant</category>
            <category>product/sap-commerce-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-customer-experience</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Recognized as a Leader in 2021 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Sales Force Automation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/sap-leader-2021-gartner-magic-quadrant-sales-force-automation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/sap-leader-2021-gartner-magic-quadrant-sales-force-automation</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Aug 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[For the third consecutive year, SAP has been recognized as a Leader in the Gartner Magic Quadrant for Sales Force Automation. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_192b9acfd6c0206875099c76186dff8d21cec0319.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_192b9acfd6c0206875099c76186dff8d21cec0319.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_192b9acfd6c0206875099c76186dff8d21cec0319.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Recognized as a Leader in 2021 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Sales Force Automation" src="./media_192b9acfd6c0206875099c76186dff8d21cec0319.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-recognized-as-a-leader-in-2021-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-sales-force-automation">SAP Recognized as a Leader in 2021 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Sales Force Automation</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="deliver-exceptional-sales-experiences-with-sap-sales-cloud">Deliver exceptional sales experiences with SAP Sales Cloud</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/sales-cloud.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced it is again recognized as a Leader in the 2021 Gartner Magic Quadrant™ for Sales Force Automation.* This is the third consecutive year that SAP has been recognized as a Leader based on its “ability to execute” and “completeness of vision.” In its latest report, Gartner assessed SAP for the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/sales-cloud.html">SAP Sales Cloud</a> solution.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“Businesses that understand their customers can ultimately improve how they engage with them and build relationships that last,” said Sameer Patel, chief marketing and solution officer for SAP Customer Experience. “SAP Sales Cloud empowers organizations to deliver customer-centric processes that maximize sales by addressing customers’ needs at each stage of their purchase journey. With the integrated SAP Customer Experience portfolio of cloud solutions, businesses can manage the complete customer experience to improve outcomes based on empathy and trust.”</p>
  <p>The SAP Sales Cloud solution is part of the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm.html">SAP Customer Experience</a> portfolio, which goes beyond traditional CRM solutions by bringing together customer data, experiential and operational data, and machine learning. SAP Customer Experience offers organizations a complete platform to address all customer interactions using a common data model and functionality from commerce, marketing, sales and service to address their business needs.</p>
  <p>To learn more, download a <a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/cx/salesforce-automation-gartner-report/index.html?campaigncode=CRM-HY21-SIP-AGMQSFA&#x26;source=onlinedisplay-glo--sales-evolution">complimentary copy</a> of the report, including Gartner’s in-depth analysis of the sales force automation landscape.</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="http://news.sap.com/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP on Twitter at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><strong>Media Contact:</strong> Susan Miller, +1 (610) 661-9225, <a href="mailto:susan.miller@sap.com">susan.miller@sap.com</a>, ET<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>*Gartner, Magic Quadrant for Sales Force Automation, Adnan Zijadic, Ilona Hansen, Melissa Hilbert, Steve Rietberg, 4 August 2021.<br>Gartner does not endorse any vendor, product or service depicted in its research publications, and does not advise technology users to select only those vendors with the highest ratings or other designation. Gartner research publications consist of the opinions of Gartner’s research organization and should not be construed as statements of fact. Gartner disclaims all warranties, expressed or implied, with respect to this research, including any warranties of merchantability or fitness for a particular purpose. Gartner and Magic Quadrant are registered trademarks of Gartner, Inc. and/or its affiliates in the U.S. and internationally and is used herein with permission. All rights reserved.</p>
  <p>Any statements contained in this document that are not historical facts are forward-looking statements as defined in the U.S. Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995. Words such as “anticipate,” “believe,” “estimate,” “expect,” “forecast,” “intend,” “may,” “plan,” “project,” “predict,” “should” and “will” and similar expressions as they relate to SAP are intended to identify such forward-looking statements. SAP undertakes no obligation to publicly update or revise any forward-looking statements. All forward-looking statements are subject to various risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results to differ materially from expectations. The factors that could affect SAP’s future financial results are discussed more fully in SAP’s filings with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (“SEC”), including SAP’s most recent Annual Report on Form 20-F filed with the SEC. Readers are cautioned not to place undue reliance on these forward-looking statements, which speak only as of their dates.<br>© 2021 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-customer-experience</category>
            <category>product/sap-sales-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Upscale Commerce Offers Midmarket Brands No-Code, Maintenance-Free Path to Direct-to-Consumer Engagement]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/06/sapphire-now-sap-upscale-commerce-midmarket-brands</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/06/sapphire-now-sap-upscale-commerce-midmarket-brands</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[No-code, headless commerce platform SAP Upscale Commerce gets midmarket brands up and running fast. Read the news from SAPPHIRE NOW.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_102af7b26add9fec57f77504e28732f45a2ac74e4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_102af7b26add9fec57f77504e28732f45a2ac74e4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_102af7b26add9fec57f77504e28732f45a2ac74e4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Upscale Commerce Offers Midmarket Brands No-Code, Maintenance-Free Path to Direct-to-Consumer Engagement" src="./media_102af7b26add9fec57f77504e28732f45a2ac74e4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-upscale-commerce-offers-midmarket-brands-no-code-maintenance-free-path-to-direct-to-consumer-engagement">SAP Upscale Commerce Offers Midmarket Brands No-Code, Maintenance-Free Path to Direct-to-Consumer Engagement</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>When the <a href="/covid-19">pandemic</a> hit and physical retail outlets had to close or limit their operations, midmarket brands had to pivot quickly to sell directly to consumers (D2C) and learn how to interact with customers digitally – only to realize that a simple webstore was not enough to compete in the digital world.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>This spiked a need for a new kind of commerce solution, one that equips midmarket companies with all the necessary tools to sell fast and easy, apply changes quickly, and offer intelligent merchandising capabilities that were previously only accessible to large enterprises.</p>
  <p><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/upscale-commerce.html">SAP Upscale Commerce</a> enables this by offering an intelligent selling engine that delivers engaging storefronts while optimizing for sales and profit, with the ability to more rapidly create mobile-first shopping experiences to meet the changing expectations of their customers. Businesses can take full control of the customer journey, drive world-class omnichannel customer experiences, and create a competitive edge by choosing to start with easily configurable building blocks or create completely custom commerce experiences.</p>
  <p>The solution enables brands to:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Sell anywhere — make the store the destination:</strong> SAP Upscale Commerce delivers rich mobile-first, cross-channel, in-store experience for shoppers and makes it easy for shoppers to intuitively shop by swiping, pinching, and tapping their devices.</li>
    <li><strong>Sell intelligently — big or small, sell smart:</strong> With built-in artificial intelligence (AI), brands can create a unique storefront experience for each shopper at scale and deliver intelligent, relevant experiences that optimize business profits. Intelligent capabilities also help to convert one-time purchases into subscriptions.</li>
    <li><strong>Speed and agility — start fast and go far:</strong> Brands can start small and scale as they grow using no code tools out of the box to create new and fresh shopping experiences in days and using low- and no-code tools to easily extend and build the perfect fit solution.</li>
    <li><strong>Keep the promise — deliver on the brand promise:</strong> Brands can sell and ship from everywhere with an agile order orchestration and fulfill orders from the closest stores.</li>
  </ul>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-more-news-and-coverage-from-sapphire-now">Read more news and coverage from SAPPHIRE NOW</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/topics/sapphire-now">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="transitioning-customer-engagement-from-in-store-to-online">Transitioning Customer Engagement from In Store to Online</h2>
  <p>One organization that experienced these changes firsthand is Swedish fashion retailer <a href="https://www.joyshop.se/">JOY</a>. JOY, which for many years has delighted Swedish women with quality clothes, has re-emerged in a completely new form. JOY no longer has any physical stores and is instead focusing on e-commerce and personalized fashion advice. The founders see JOY as a startup building next-generation e-commerce based on AI and slow fashion – a more sustainable alternative with clothes lasting several seasons. JOY is also the first company in the world that has selected the combination of the cloud-based solutions SAP Upscale Commerce and the Emarsys platform for customer engagement functionality.</p>
  <p>“We are definitely in a paradigm shift within e-commerce and digital channels. The retail industry has so far been able to make a living from using large product catalogs, but they do not provide the best customer experience. Instead, customers want inspiration, advice, and, in our case, also ready-made combinations of clothes that suit their own style – and lasting several seasons,” said Anna Ullman Sersé, CEO and co-founder of JOY. “SAP Upscale Commerce fit our needs perfectly. The solution is very flexible, allowing us to make changes quickly and to provide more content than just a traditional product catalog. This frees up more time for us to truly focus on engaging with the customers online, much like we did when we would meet in stores.”</p>
  <h2 id="powering-social-selling-with-top-social-media-platforms">Powering Social Selling with Top Social Media Platforms</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-upscale-commerce-start-fast-and-grow-intelligently-with-an-ai-powered-selling-engine">SAP Upscale Commerce: Start fast and grow intelligently with an AI-powered selling engine</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/upscale-commerce.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Another option for brands pivoting to direct customer engagement is selling through social media channels, more commonly known as “social selling.” With careful and considered targeting of the right products at the right time, it is possible for midmarket brands to drive down the cost of customer acquisition as products find customers directly through algorithmic targeting. However, this means that having the right type of information about products and the right content in posts is critical – as is for that information to be up to date.</p>
  <p>To deliver on this opportunity, SAP Upscale Commerce integrates into social media platforms, enabling organizations to easily start taking advantage of social commerce. The solution makes it easy to connect an online store to a Facebook business account, continuously sync the product catalog, create a Facebook Shop, and use that to drive new sales opportunities to consumers. The result is a consistent shopping experience on social media, with the front-end and back-end business processes fully integrated.</p>
  <h2 id="hackathon-spurs-new-ideas-to-solve-customer-pain-points">Hackathon Spurs New Ideas to Solve Customer Pain Points</h2>
  <p>To meet individual customer challenges, the SAP Customer Experience team in Canada recently hosted a hackathon, in which teams of product experts and solution integration partners battled to create brand new online shopping experiences based on specific, real-world client requirements for fashion, automotive, and retail – all within SAP Upscale Commerce.</p>
  <p>Judging criteria was based on overall creativity, use of available product extensions, ease of shopping experience, time-to-market, and how well the solution drives customers toward long-term loyalty and advocacy for the brand. After a day and a half of competition, the event culminated in a final virtual pitch presentation, with <a href="https://www.ecenta.com/en/company/">ECENTA</a> taking home the award for Most Creative, and <a href="https://www.liveareacx.com/">LiveArea</a> awarded for Best Use of Technology.</p>
  <p>“As a judge, I was truly impressed with the quality and quantity of results after only a day and a half of hacking, showcasing incredible innovation, creativity, and accomplishment by small teams in a small amount of time,” said Frédéric Bouthillier, CEO of <a href="http://www.grtouchette.com/en/home.html">Groupe Touchette</a>. “The teams’ rapid development of new, innovative experiences proves the time to value of SAP Upscale Commerce and headless commerce solutions.”</p>
  <p>The events of the past year have changed the way people shop and the shift to online purchasing is here to stay. Now midmarket brands don’t have to settle with a simple direct-to-consumer webstore. With SAP Upscale Commerce, businesses have the ability to put the customer at the heart of everything they do, connecting front- and back-office data, simplifying and automating complex sales processes, and delivering insights in real time that enable seamless, personalized experiences that grow revenue.</p>
  <p>The SAP Upscale Commerce solution, <a href="https://store.sap.com/en/?campaigncode=CRM-YD21-SOC-0STORPZ&#x26;source=ppc-SAPSTOREPS-GL-202121&#x26;gclid=Cj0KCQjwwLKFBhDPARIsAPzPi-LIG56BYZkTP40_VO10vLETrMtaeoEorbGOdSnJC-bU5MS27bwkfggaAuygEALw_wcB">available on SAP Store</a>, is the next-generation intelligent selling engine that can help midmarket brands to achieve fast growth, create differentiated experiences, and leverage intelligence to optimize sales and profits.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Bob Stutz is president of SAP Customer Experience.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="register-to-join-sapphire-now-in-2021">Register to join SAPPHIRE NOW in 2021</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://reg.sapevents.sap.com/flow/sap/sapphirenow2021/portal/page/home">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/sme</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/commerce</category>
            <category>industry/consumer-goods-cpg</category>
            <category>news-tag/e-commerce</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-customer-experience</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>