<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/rpa/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Delivering Enterprise Automation Across Industries]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/delivering-enterprise-automation-across-industries</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/delivering-enterprise-automation-across-industries</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Enterprise automation from SAP uses best-in-class technology to help connect and automate complex, end-to-end business processes.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/automation</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/rpa</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[BPaaS: Something You Can Rely On]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/06/bpaas-something-you-can-rely-on</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/06/bpaas-something-you-can-rely-on</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[When opting to use BPaaS, companies can redirect saved time from operational process optimization toward innovation.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/bpaas</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/machine-learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/rpa</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-concur</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unleashing Automation for a Resilient Aerospace & Defense Sector]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/unleashing-automation-resilient-aerospace-defense-sector</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/unleashing-automation-resilient-aerospace-defense-sector</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The aerospace and defense industry needs ways to overcome labor shortage-driven production challenges. Automation solutions and SAP can help]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/aerospace-defense</category>
            <category>news-tag/automation</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-twin</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-4-0</category>
            <category>news-tag/rpa</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-signavio</category>
            <category>product/sap-warehouse-robotics</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Recognized as Visionary in 2022 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Robotic Process Automation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/sap-visionary-gartner-robotic-process-automation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/sap-visionary-gartner-robotic-process-automation</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Gartner has ranked SAP as a Visionary in the 2022 Magic Quadrant for Robotic Process Automation (RPA) for its SAP Process Automation solution.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/automation</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/low-code-no-code</category>
            <category>news-tag/rpa</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Now Provides a Unified Low-Code/No-Code Offering]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/sap-now-provides-unified-low-code-no-code-offering</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/sap-now-provides-unified-low-code-no-code-offering</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP BTP allows customers to achieve business agility, specifically with the help of the new unified low-code/no-code offering. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_13f25959e37ea308f738565d586dacbd74230cff3.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_13f25959e37ea308f738565d586dacbd74230cff3.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_13f25959e37ea308f738565d586dacbd74230cff3.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Now Provides a Unified Low-Code/No-Code Offering" src="./media_13f25959e37ea308f738565d586dacbd74230cff3.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-now-provides-a-unified-low-codeno-code-offering">SAP Now Provides a Unified Low-Code/No-Code Offering</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP) allows our customers to achieve business agility, specifically with the help of our new unified low-code/no-code offering. With our low-code and no-code capabilities, we enable everyone to deliver innovation faster and confidently across all lines of business and industries.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP provides:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>An integrated suite of end-to-end business applications</strong> to run your business across all industries and lines of business</li>
    <li><strong>A comprehensive business-centric platform</strong>, with a unified programming model and unified design system, bringing IT and business together to modernize processes and enable rapid innovation – now</li>
  </ul>
  <p>The low-code/no-code offering services in SAP BTP empower IT and citizen developers alike to quickly build enterprise-ready apps, automations, workflows, and chatbots no matter their skill level or coding expertise. Our customers can build enterprise apps fast with SAP’s unified development experience and an ever-growing array of pre-built business content for any line of business, all natively integrated with your SAP applications.</p>
  <p>Examples include <a href="https://store.irpa.cfapps.eu10.hana.ondemand.com/#/explore/order=last-updated%2Cdesc">more than 260 pre-built robotic processing automation (RPA) bots</a> to automate tasks in any line of business – be it finance, sourcing and procurement, manufacturing, sales, and services – and almost <a href="https://api.sap.com/content-type/Workflow/workflowmanagement/packages">40 live process content packages</a> for the SAP Workflow Management service.</p>
  <p>Another example is SAP SuccessFactors Work Zone, which offers a prepackaged experience specifically to address the needs of HR organizations based on SAP Work Zone, with additional functionality such as workflow and mobile services. It has been <a href="/2021/09/hr-executive-top-product-sap-successfactors-work-zone">recognized recently as a Top HR Product</a> by <a href="https://hrexecutive.com/">Human Resource Executive</a> and the <a href="https://www.hrtechnologyconference.com/">HR Technology Conference</a>. Additionally, SAP Business Application Studio comes with pre-built components, wizards, and sample apps.</p>
  <p>SAP unifies the developer experience with low-code and no-code enhancements on SAP BTP to help:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Maximize speed and agility</strong> and <strong>reduce total cost of ownership (TCO)</strong> through accelerated delivery</li>
    <li><strong>Bridge the gap</strong> and <strong>increase adoption</strong> through co-development between business and IT</li>
    <li><strong>Enhance return on investment (ROI)</strong> by leveraging existing investments through seamless integrations</li>
    <li><strong>Accelerate time to value</strong> by implementing best practices with pre-built content packages</li>
  </ul>
  <p>Our low-code/no-code offering covers three areas:</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ba9fc49787f0db173238260324e73caf06eb2b55.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ba9fc49787f0db173238260324e73caf06eb2b55.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1ba9fc49787f0db173238260324e73caf06eb2b55.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Diagram explaining the new low-code/no-code offering" src="./media_1ba9fc49787f0db173238260324e73caf06eb2b55.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1696" height="762">
    </picture>For <strong>process automation</strong>, we offer SAP Workflow Management and SAP Intelligent RPA, enabling citizen developers to easily build workflows and to automate tasks. On top of that, SAP Process Automation can bring no-code process automation to the next level. SAP Process Automation is currently available for co-innovation partners, with general availability planned for the first quarter of 2022.
  </p>
  <p>For <strong>low-code/no-code application composition</strong>, we launched SAP AppGyver and new functionalities in SAP Business Application Studio to enable the entire developer continuum to accelerate application development. SAP AppGyver allows citizen developers to build highly sophisticated standalone applications or extensions without writing a single line of code. With SAP Business Application Studio, we also deliver a simplified application development journey to the professional developer with a low-code perspective.</p>
  <p>In the area of <strong>digital experience</strong>, we are offering SAP Work Zone, SAP Launchpad, and SAP Mobile Start to help drive employee productivity and make newly built apps available to everyone in the company.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-btp-accelerate-business-outcomes-with-integration-data-to-value-and-extensibility">SAP BTP: Accelerate business outcomes with integration, data to value, and extensibility</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="what-else-is-new-at-sap-teched">What Else Is New at SAP TechEd?</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-acquires-no-code-development-pioneer-appgyver">SAP Acquires No-Code Development Pioneer AppGyver</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/02/sap-acquire-appgyver">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Let’s go into some specifics for each of the areas in our new unified low-code/no-code offering:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>SAP Business Application Studio has seen a dramatic improvement in development productivity through the low-code/no-code experience now available.</li>
    <li>We’ve also fully integrated the acquisition in the no-code space. SAP AppGyver is now part of CPEA, available to all our customers as well as planned through the free tier model in the first quarter of 2022.</li>
    <li>We’ve made significant improvements in our SAPUI5 technology performance, which can be of immediate benefit to SAP S/4HANA and any other SAP product built on top of the technology within SAP BTP.</li>
    <li>Launching SAP Process Automation brings an elevated user experience for citizen automation in a no-code development environment. To make citizen developers fully productive, the new solution provides end-to-end automation capabilities leveraging advanced workflow management and embedded RPA functionality in a simple drag-and-drop user interface.</li>
    <li>Last but not least, we’ve delivered artificial intelligence (AI) into our workflow engine, so that the AI system monitors the context with which you approve or not on a given workflow, building up the relevant models of your approval process flow. Your workflow becomes more and more intelligent over time, out of the box.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>I invite you to attend SAP TechEd sessions to learn more about our low-code/no-code offering and how SAP BTP is now accessible to anyone. You’ll find a selection of personally recommended sessions below. Let’s explore together how SAP BTP can help you rapidly integrate, automate, and extend business processes for security and performance at scale across your organization.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Recommended Sessions</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><em>Michael Weingartner is president of SAP Business Technology Platform Core at SAP.</em></p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-more-news-and-coverage-from-sap-teched">Read more news and coverage from SAP TechEd</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/topics/sap-teched">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-teched</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/rpa</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-intelligent-rpa</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-work-zone</category>
            <category>product/sap-workflow-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Next Phase for Robotic Process Automation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/next-phase-advanced-rpa-robotic-process-automation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/next-phase-advanced-rpa-robotic-process-automation</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With advanced RPA, SAP enables customers to derive even more value and free up employees to undertake more interesting activities.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1dd2c32b428934735b8ac109b65f46aab0501d990.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1dd2c32b428934735b8ac109b65f46aab0501d990.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1dd2c32b428934735b8ac109b65f46aab0501d990.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="The Next Phase for Robotic Process Automation" src="./media_1dd2c32b428934735b8ac109b65f46aab0501d990.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="the-next-phase-for-robotic-process-automation">The Next Phase for Robotic Process Automation</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="easily-build-intelligent-bots-with-a-low-code-design-studio-for-hyperautomation">Easily build intelligent bots with a low-code design studio for hyperautomation</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/robotic-process-automation.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>When it comes to responding to an urgent need by quickly developing an automation solution to minimize laborious, time-consuming, and error-prone manual work, robotic process automation (<a href="/topics/rpa">RPA</a>) delivers great value.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>But this is just a first step. Taken to the next level, intelligent RPA, also called “hyperautomation,” offers even more valuable benefits by combining traditional RPA with artificial intelligence (AI) and low-code/no-code development.</p>
  <p>As an example, repetitive tasks and routine activities in finance, purchasing, and customer service were preventing Villeroy &#x26; Boch, one of Europe’s oldest ceramic manufacturers, from improving operational efficiency and delivering great customer service. The German premium tableware and bathroom products company implemented SAP Intelligent RPA for routine activities, helping streamline workflows and free up staff to focus on strategic activities.</p>
  <p>Like other SAP customers benefiting from hyperautomation, Villeroy &#x26; Boch started with automating simple, frequently occurring tasks, such as responding to standard e-mail inquiries with attended RPA bots. Previously known as robotic desktop automation, attended RPA is a software assistant for the human user and interacts with a desktop application while respecting applicable business logic.</p>
  <p>Operating internationally in 125 countries demands smooth workflows and operational efficiency across several business functions, but the ceramics group always had a bigger vision. The company wanted to create a fully automated invoice error-handling process by combining SAP Intelligent RPA and SAP AI Business Services to handle unstructured data and documents.</p>
  <p>Now advanced RPA bots autonomously trigger tasks and automate more complex work such as processing attachments from e-mails according to their type and predefined confidence thresholds. So far, the 10 digital assistants Villeroy &#x26; Boch has deployed are handling 66,000 documents a year.</p>
  <p>“Although we’re just at the beginning of our journey with SAP Intelligent RPA, we are already realizing its potential to help us work more efficiently, serve customers better, and gain competitive advantage,” said Daniel Neuhaeuser, head of ERP Core Solutions at Villeroy &#x26; Boch.</p>
  <p>The advantages of going beyond traditional RPA and tapping the potential of hyperautomation are becoming more widely acknowledged. Industry analysts have forecast that the worldwide hyperautomation-enabling software market will reach nearly US$600 billion by 2022.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="try-sap-intelligent-rpa-today">Try SAP Intelligent RPA today</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/td/sap-intelligent-robotic-process-automation-free-trial.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Hyperautomation services such as SAP Intelligent RPA enable companies to quickly and easily create bots to emulate human users and automate tedious, repetitive, mundane tasks. For example, today’s office workers spend a lot of time moving between different applications and must often reenter or copy and paste data, such as a customer’s name and address details, from one application to another.</p>
  <p>Earlier this year, SAP Intelligent RPA was cited as a Strong Performer in <a href="https://reprints2.forrester.com/#/assets/2/702/RES161538/report">The Forrester Wave™: Robotic Process Automation, Q1 2021</a>. According to the report, “SAP’s RPA solution is a strong alternative for SAP customers, particularly for enterprises concerned with bots disrupting core SAP systems and those usually needing the central SAP development team to design, develop, and maintain RPA for clear accountability, or for companies seeking a feature-rich RPA tool that comes with a broad ecosystem of partners.”</p>
  <p>Typically, customers report that SAP Intelligent RPA deployments free up between 15 and 30% of employees’ time, which means they can focus on tasks that deliver greater value to the organization and improve the customer experience.</p>
  <p>Specific benefits of using SAP Intelligent RPA include being able to use tools such as <a href="https://insights.sap.com/tackling-software-developer-shortage-citizen-developers-lcnc/">low-code or no-code platforms</a>, built-in integration and content for business process management, and fast, cost-effective deployment. By opening current tools to everyone in the enterprise, SAP Intelligent RPA extends its reach beyond software developers. Business users who have no coding skills but have functional expertise and technical acumen can become citizen developers and build their own automations.</p>
  <p>To support this mission and help automate tasks in business processes, SAP Intelligent RPA offers a new bot-building and execution experience and a cloud-based design studio. This allows users to create and deploy software bots as digital assistants that automate repetitive tasks through a low-code approach.</p>
  <p>This low-code tooling speeds up implementation time and offers a short time to value. More than 200 prebuilt bots are now available within SAP Intelligent RPA to help automate tasks, improve productivity, and make work more interesting for employees.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/automation</category>
            <category>news-tag/low-code-no-code</category>
            <category>news-tag/rpa</category>
            <category>product/sap-intelligent-rpa</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Independent Research Firm Evaluates RPA Solutions: “SAP’s RPA Solution Is a Strong Alternative for SAP Customers…”]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/03/forrester-rpa-solution-sap-strong-performer</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/03/forrester-rpa-solution-sap-strong-performer</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In a Forrester Wave, SAP's RPA solution was cited as a “Strong Performer.” Learn more about the benefits of SAP Intelligent RPA.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18fb71dccf06b3a70fedce35b961551ca23f61866.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18fb71dccf06b3a70fedce35b961551ca23f61866.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_18fb71dccf06b3a70fedce35b961551ca23f61866.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Independent Research Firm Evaluates RPA Solutions: “SAP’s RPA Solution Is a Strong Alternative for SAP Customers…”" src="./media_18fb71dccf06b3a70fedce35b961551ca23f61866.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="independent-research-firm-evaluates-rpa-solutions-saps-rpa-solution-is-a-strong-alternative-for-sap-customers">Independent Research Firm Evaluates RPA Solutions: “SAP’s RPA Solution Is a Strong Alternative for SAP Customers…”</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Forrester invited SAP to participate in The Forrester Wave™, Robotic Process Automation, Q1 2021. In this evaluation, SAP was cited as a “Strong Performer.” This is the result of a three-year effort to create the best robotic process automation (RPA) solution for SAP customers.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="easily-build-intelligent-bots-with-a-low-code-design-studio-for-hyperautomation">Easily build intelligent bots with a low-code design studio for hyperautomation</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/robotic-process-automation.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="2020--how-sap-became-an-rpa-vendor">2018-2020 — How SAP Became an RPA Vendor</h2>
  <p>Let me tell you how SAP started in the RPA market: Three years ago, after having been part of SAP’s machine learning initiative, I decided to focus on creating further value for SAP customers by automating business processes. For this, we put together a strategy and a business case and built a development team. We merged SAP technology with proven RPA technology from Contextor, <a href="/2018/11/sap-acquires-contextor-robotic-process-automation">acquired in 2018</a>.</p>
  <p>May 8, 2019, was a great day for us, with the launch of SAP Intelligent RPA at SAPPHIRE NOW; our booth and our sessions were fully packed and we received a lot of positive feedback from SAP customers and partners.</p>
  <p>We rapidly closed our first customer deal with <a href="/2021/02/process-automation-villeroy-boch-bots-decide">Villeroy and Boch</a>, and the solution spread further. It received a lot of interest from more customers and partners that experienced our <strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/td/sap-intelligent-robotic-process-automation-free-trial.html">free trial</a></strong> to experience the outcomes of our solution in their own IT landscape.</p>
  <p>Via many interactions with our ecosystem and analysts, sharing our road map, and getting new ideas, we constantly improved SAP Intelligent RPA. We enabled more than 50 partners worldwide, which helped us grow our customer base in any industry and any region of the world. End of 2020 we reached a major milestone with 1 million automations over the year:</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d2390bfa1f9980e4dafdc57d89cb8f6bfc19564e.gif?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d2390bfa1f9980e4dafdc57d89cb8f6bfc19564e.gif?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/gif" srcset="./media_1d2390bfa1f9980e4dafdc57d89cb8f6bfc19564e.gif?width=2000&#x26;format=gif&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Intelligent RPA: 1 million automations" src="./media_1d2390bfa1f9980e4dafdc57d89cb8f6bfc19564e.gif?width=750&#x26;format=gif&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1280" height="720">
    </picture>According to a survey from another analyst firm in the fourth quarter of 2020, SAP is already in the Top 3 Automation Product Suppliers across the Global 2000 companies. <a href="https://www.forbes.com/global2000/">Global 2000</a> is an annual ranking of the top 2,000 public companies in the world created by Forbes magazine. Published since 2003, it is based on a mix of four metrics: sales, profit, assets, and market value. These very large companies are the core of SAP customers, many of them having deployed SAP ERP and other SAP software for decades.
  </p>
  <p>This survey shows that we have succeeded in providing these customers with an SAP solution that fits their needs. Three months ago at <a href="https://blogs.sap.com/2020/12/14/sap-intelligent-rpa-2.0-sap-teched-2020-is-a-wrap/">SAP Teched</a>, we unveiled SAP Intelligent RPA 2.0, a major release of our product geared toward democratization of automation. It offers bot-building capabilities following a low-code or no-code approach, enabling non-technical business process experts to create customizable automations with clicks, not code. In addition, <a href="https://store.irpa.cfapps.eu10.hana.ondemand.com/">more than 170 prebuilt bot templates</a> are available to automate and drive efficiencies in 12 lines of business for any industry, with about 60 prebuilt bots only for <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/s4hana-erp.html">SAP S/4HANA</a>.</p>
  <p>This new release of SAP Intelligent RPA provides high flexibility while helping ensure IT governance. It received great feedback from the customers: “Great job, we saw and experienced many steps that have become much easier during the robot creation process,” said Balbir Singh Dhillon, Associate Director Intelligent Solutions at Zuellig Pharma. “Just the email capabilities alone save a lot of time and places that functionality in the hands of the citizen user and no longer dependent on experienced developers. The look and feel and the user experience were really great, and I can only see the product getting richer with additional features.”</p>
  <h2 id="sap-named-a-strong-performer-in-the-forrester-wave-robotic-process-automation-q1-2021">2021 — SAP Named a “Strong Performer” in The Forrester Wave™: Robotic Process Automation, Q1 2021</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="register-for-a-free-trial-of-sap-intelligent-rpa-now">Register for a free trial of SAP Intelligent RPA now</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/td/sap-intelligent-robotic-process-automation-free-trial.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>At the end of last year, Forrester invited SAP to participate in its evaluation, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/robotic-process-automation.html?campaigncode=CRM-PM21-SIP-INTTECHFOR&#x26;rc=https%3A%2F%2Freprints2.forrester.com%2F%23%2Fassets%2F2%2F702%2FRES161538%2Freport">The Forrester Wave™, Robotic Process Automation, Q1 2021</a>. The report is now published, and in this evaluation, SAP was cited as a Strong Performer.</p>
  <p>According to the Forrester report, “SAP’s RPA solution is a strong alternative for SAP customers, particularly for enterprises concerned with bots disrupting core SAP systems and those usually needing the central SAP development team to design, develop, and maintain RPA for clear accountability, or for companies seeking a feature-rich RPA tool that comes with a broad ecosystem of partners.”</p>
  <p>We could not agree more. Creating an RPA solution for SAP customers, our aim was to bring an automation tool that fits in their IT landscape and fulfills all of their governance requirements. Because their enterprise resource planning (ERP) is a key component of their daily operations, it is finely tuned by the IT department to run smoothly. For sure, our customers do not want any disruption in the way their ERP runs and need that any software robot interacting with the ERP to be fast and efficient, but without any risk of generating extra system load.</p>
  <p>The prebuilt bot templates available in our SAP Intelligent RPA store are directly created and maintained by major SAP product teams, such as SAP S/4HANA already and soon SAP SuccessFactors and SAP Ariba. This approach offers a strong cohesion among existing SAP systems in place, increasing the bots’ performance. Our prebuilt bots are constantly updated and upgraded to support our customers’ latest ERP, HR, or <a href="https://www.ariba.com/solutions/solutions-overview/procurement">procurement software</a> releases.</p>
  <p>We aim to provide the best RPA solution for SAP customers and this will go far beyond robotic process automation. The <strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-process-intelligence.html">business process intelligence</a></strong> portfolio is a strategic initiative from SAP to deliver process excellence by analyzing, improving, and monitoring processes. Together with SAP Workflow Management, SAP Intelligent RPA turns process insights into actions to help drive digital transformation. It allows non-technical users to create automation scenarios without code, and to deliver outcomes quickly with predefined content.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1fd3a2d29639e1c57bcef58406e1172da2787c444.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1fd3a2d29639e1c57bcef58406e1172da2787c444.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1fd3a2d29639e1c57bcef58406e1172da2787c444.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Graphic: components business process intelligence" src="./media_1fd3a2d29639e1c57bcef58406e1172da2787c444.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1597" height="725">
    </picture>Let us accelerate your business transformation journey — I would be very happy to welcome you as our customer or partner, to do this automation journey together.
  </p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Sebastian Schroetel is vice president and head of SAP Intelligent RPA.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="buy-sap-intelligent-rpa-on-the-sap-store-today">Buy SAP Intelligent RPA on the SAP Store today!</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sapstore.com/solutions/42831/SAP-Intelligent-Robotic-Process-Automation">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/business-process-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/rpa</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-intelligent-rpa</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>