<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/digitalization/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Business Network Digitalizes Procurement for VAT E-Invoicing Mandates]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/sap-business-network-digitalizes-procurement-e-invoicing</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/sap-business-network-digitalizes-procurement-e-invoicing</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With VAT e-invoicing mandates on the rise, buyers and suppliers can join SAP Business Network for trusted, simplified procurement automation.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/financial-management</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/accounting</category>
            <category>news-tag/digitalization</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Clear Path to Digital Supply Chain Excellence with SAP Preferred Success]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/digital-supply-chain-excellence-with-sap-preferred-success</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/digital-supply-chain-excellence-with-sap-preferred-success</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Preferred Success can be a guiding light for businesses keen on transforming to digital supply chain operations.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-supply-chain</category>
            <category>news-tag/digitalization</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-preferred-success</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[RISE with SAP Accelerates Biotech Innovation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/rise-with-sap-accelerates-innovation-stemcell</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/rise-with-sap-accelerates-innovation-stemcell</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[STEMCELL Technologies is digitally transforming to speed up advanced healthcare discoveries, bringing hope to patients and their families.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/digitalization</category>
            <category>industry/healthcare</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>industry/life-sciences</category>
            <category>news-tag/research-development</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Category Management Is About to Take Center Stage]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/category-management-is-about-to-take-center-stage</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/category-management-is-about-to-take-center-stage</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Category Management can help teams automate category management, classify entries consistently, and analyze valuable data. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/digitalization</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>topic/spend-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP and GIZ Cooperate on Digital Solutions for Green Hydrogen Certificates]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/sap-and-giz-digital-solutions-green-hydrogen-certificates</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/sap-and-giz-digital-solutions-green-hydrogen-certificates</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[To support green hydrogen certification in Brazil and Germany, SAP and GIZ have formed a public-private partnership. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/decarbonization</category>
            <category>news-tag/digitalization</category>
            <category>news-tag/renewable-energy</category>
            <category>product/sap-green-token</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sustainable Salmon Farming and the Future of Digital Procurement]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/evonik-industries-digital-procurement</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/evonik-industries-digital-procurement</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Digitalization frees up procurement to stay on top of fast-changing market conditions, including finding suppliers in unexpected disruptions.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>industry/chemicals</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/digitalization</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP and Partners Create Mobile Solutions to Tackle Supply Chain Challenges]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/sap-mobile-day-supply-chain-challenges</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/sap-mobile-day-supply-chain-challenges</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[At Mobile Day, SAP customers and partners shared how mobile apps help modern enterprises tackle supply chain challenges. Read the learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digitalization</category>
            <category>news-tag/mobile</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pharmaceutical Manufacturers Fight Fake Drugs with Intelligent Supply Chains]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/pharmaceutical-manufacturers-drug-supply-chains</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/pharmaceutical-manufacturers-drug-supply-chains</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Investing in intelligent supply chain solutions can enable resilience and prevent counterfeit drugs in the life sciences industry. Learn how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digitalization</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>industry/life-sciences</category>
            <category>product/sap-information-collaboration-hub-for-life-sciences</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-store</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Upward Momentum Builds with Digitalization in the Chemicals Industry]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/upward-momentum-digitalization-chemicals-industry</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/upward-momentum-digitalization-chemicals-industry</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With the right approach to digitalization and the help of SAP Advisory Services, the chemicals industry can innovate across the value chain.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f2348930338cde065afdb2512296e4046afc65b8.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f2348930338cde065afdb2512296e4046afc65b8.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1f2348930338cde065afdb2512296e4046afc65b8.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Upward Momentum Builds with Digitalization in the Chemicals Industry" src="./media_1f2348930338cde065afdb2512296e4046afc65b8.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="upward-momentum-builds-with-digitalization-in-the-chemicals-industry">Upward Momentum Builds with Digitalization in the Chemicals Industry</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Chemical companies are on a nonstop roller coaster of market shocks and digital transformation. Sandwiched between feedstock and energy companies and downstream processing industries, they’re predestined to play a vital role in fulfilling business-to-business (B2B) and consumer expectations for sustainable, reliable, innovative, and trusted products and services.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>But rising to the challenge of today’s marketplace – especially increasing raw material and energy prices, margin pressure, supply chain complexity, and regulatory requirements – requires much more than Industry 4.0 initiatives focused on efficiency and price reduction. From operational performance to customer experience, companies must integrate data from across the enterprise into a single source to form sound decisions that make sustainability profitable and profitability sustainable.</p>
  <p>Such a transformation is undoubtedly technology intensive, but the key enablers are also unassailably human. Understanding this reality, many chemical companies rely on the <a href="https://www.sap.com/services-support/service-offerings/business-transformation.html">SAP Advisory Services</a> portfolio, provided by the Business Transformation Services group at SAP, to help transform their operations and gain a competitive edge amid fast global changes.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="transform-your-business-and-unlock-digital-innovation-with-help-from-sap-advisory-services">Transform your business and unlock digital innovation with help from SAP Advisory Services</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/services-support/service-offerings/business-transformation.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="turning-challenges-into-great-opportunities">Turning Challenges into Great Opportunities</h2>
  <p>Competitively addressing turbulence depends on the ability to view transformation through the lens of six fundamental challenges:</p>
  <p><strong>R&#x26;D Pressure across the Product Portfolio</strong> The imperative to resist margin shrinkage, mitigate risks, increase ROI, and boost growth calls for innovative products and services that offer business value and foster close partnerships with customers. By pushing forward the adoption of advanced technologies to drive global R&#x26;D, supplier, and customer collaborations and joint ventures, businesses can prevent commoditization.</p>
  <p><strong>The Need for Vertical Integration</strong> Evolving production facilities with a balance of high efficiency, global scale, flexibility, and intelligent responsiveness allows supply chains to weigh the synergistic benefits of integrated manufacturing plants or industrial parks against the flexibility of smaller plants. As a result, businesses can leverage new opportunities with disruptive business models, such as making raw materials instead of buying them and producing semi-finished or even finished goods.</p>
  <p><strong>Global Supply Chain Complexity</strong> Global supply chains must be secure enough to mitigate volatile market conditions, such as global health emergencies, rising prices for raw materials and energy, and other factors that impact economic conditions. Companies can gain this advantage by establishing commercial and logistical transparency to support optimization and global planning of demand, sales, and operations.</p>
  <p><strong>Hidden Advantages of Business Networks</strong> Business cannot stay competitive in a complex ecosystem alone. They must also scale and optimize their supply chain globally with business networks, such as the <a href="/2021/03/catena-x-automotive-alliance-picks-up-speed">Catena-X Automotive Network</a>. Doing so empowers suppliers, contract and toll manufacturers, joint ventures, and customers to collaborate openly and create new prospects for co-innovating better products and services, improving value chain efficiency, and fueling long-term growth.</p>
  <p><strong>Compliance and Sustainability Urgency</strong> A primary objective for any chemical business is ensuring compliance with industry regulations. Yet, B2B customers also favor suppliers that help meet their own environmental, social, and governance (ESG) mandates. Sustainable businesses and innovations provide balance between these two expectations, creating a highly sought-after competitive edge by gearing products and services towards a circular economy.</p>
  <p><strong>Business Agility</strong> The industry’s dynamic and fast-changing environment of mergers, acquisitions, and divestitures is creating tremendous complexity and pressure for permanent change and adaptation. Chemical companies need to balance industry-wide globalization and centralization while increasing business agility.</p>
  <p>Chemical companies with a digital strategy encompassing all these topics can address industry challenges and seize on market trends in a disruptive manner. Through <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2016/03/d2238cd0-627c-0010-82c7-eda71af511fa.html">digital innovation</a>, businesses can gain new opportunities and capabilities never previously considered possible – including increased speed and efficiency, process automation, and data transparency.</p>
  <h2 id="seizing-the-moment-with-advisory-expertise">Seizing the Moment with Advisory Expertise</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="at-sap-your-success-is-our-goal">At SAP, your success is our goal</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/support.html#services-support-offerings">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>From the perspective of SAP Advisory Services, digitalization is not just another IT term but also a critical business priority. The more intelligent and sustainable a company becomes, the more agile, flexible, and integrated its value chain becomes.</p>
  <p>Advisory experts from SAP can enable chemical companies to turn their fundamental challenges into opportunities with a well-structured, business-driven design. This approach elaborates on the steps of the digital transformation journey – leading to a road map for future architecture design. Each phase of the road map follows an ideal sequence of digital innovation, technology adoption, and industry best practices and leverages the highest value for the company in the short term.</p>
  <p>SAP Advisory Services help organizations evaluate and act on the sentiments of their customers, partners, and employees and improve their environmental impact. Chemical companies can then be well positioned to keep their workforce engaged, increase organizational agility, and deliver the products and services customers need and trust. Furthermore, they can control their varied sources and categories of spending with outstanding finance and operational efficiency and real-time enterprise insight.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_13184d5b5d29ebbc4d371c407a9c86acc71402ad2.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_13184d5b5d29ebbc4d371c407a9c86acc71402ad2.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_13184d5b5d29ebbc4d371c407a9c86acc71402ad2.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_13184d5b5d29ebbc4d371c407a9c86acc71402ad2.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="300" height="283">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p><em>Intelligent enterprise framework</em></p>
  <p>Essentially, chemical companies that work with SAP advisory experts can realize their potential as <a href="https://www.sap.com/intelligent-enterprise.html">intelligent enterprises</a>. They can make confident decisions and drive continuous innovation to adapt, innovate, and overcome challenges while making responsible choices that help reduce waste and emissions and drive long-term growth.</p>
  <p>This business model is accomplished with intelligent technologies, including business networks, a business technology platform, cloud-based infrastructures, and solutions for business process management, experience management, industry cloud, and sustainability management. Additionally, artificial intelligence (AI), blockchain, data platforms, the Internet of Things (IoT), machine learning, predictive analytics, and virtual as well as augmented realities (VR/AR) are embedded in the intelligent technologies to drive end-to-end business processes and decision-making across enterprise domains.</p>
  <h2 id="bringing-to-life-an-intelligent-and-sustainable-network">Bringing to Life an Intelligent and Sustainable Network</h2>
  <p>The pressures on the chemicals industry may be relentless, with shocks coming in from all directions. However, this doesn’t mean businesses cannot find great opportunities in this volatile environment. With the right approach to digitalization, they can transform, innovate, and collaborate across the value chain to build upward momentum and better serve customers as an intelligent and sustainable network.</p>
  <p>Learn more about the <a href="https://blogs.sap.com/2022/09/29/business-and-digital-trends-in-the-chemical-industry/">market trends and business priorities shaping various lines of businesses in the chemical industry</a> and how SAP can help guide the innovation needed to overcome them. Read the series <a href="https://blogs.sap.com/tag/business-digital-trends-in-the-chemical-industry/">“Business and Digital Trends in the Chemical Industry</a>” on SAP Community.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Ornulf Rexin is chief business consultant of Chemicals and Life Sciences for Business Transformation Services at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/chemicals</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/digitalization</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-advisory-services</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[California’s Low-Cost Insulin Is Symptom of Lifesaving Innovations to Come]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/life-sciences-innovations-to-come</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/life-sciences-innovations-to-come</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Life sciences leaders are connecting data and people to find for more cost-effective disease prevention innovations and lifesaving cures.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digitalization</category>
            <category>industry/healthcare</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>industry/life-sciences</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[U.S. Sugar: Ninety Years of Sustainable, Innovative Agriculture]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/09/u-s-sugar-sustainable-innovative-agriculture</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/09/u-s-sugar-sustainable-innovative-agriculture</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Connecting people, technology, and the environment enables U.S. Sugar to keep innovating for a sustainable future. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/agribusiness</category>
            <category>news-tag/digitalization</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-extreme-series</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Royal Greenland and Local Fishing Communities Embark on Digital Journey]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/royal-greenland-local-fishing-communities-digital-journey</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/royal-greenland-local-fishing-communities-digital-journey</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Royal Greenland built three apps on SAP BTP to help streamline procurement processes for fishermen and support its sustainability goals.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/digitalization</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-apphaus-network</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Procurement in the Spotlight: Exploring How Digitalization Drives Real-Time Transformation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/procurement-in-the-spotlight-economist-impact-report</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/procurement-in-the-spotlight-economist-impact-report</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[As part of a wide-ranging study sponsored by SAP, an Economist Impact report looked at the ongoing transformation of procurement. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digitalization</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hannover Messe Showcases Digitalization at Every Level]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/06/hannover-messe-showcases-digitalization</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/06/hannover-messe-showcases-digitalization</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[At Hannover Messe, SAP showed how Industry 4.0 processes pave the way toward becoming customer-centric, robust, sustainable enterprises.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digitalization</category>
            <category>news-tag/hannover-messe</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-4-0</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Why the Reinvention of the Oil and Gas Industry Begins with Intelligent Enterprise Content Management]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/reinvention-of-oil-and-gas-enterprise-content-management</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/reinvention-of-oil-and-gas-enterprise-content-management</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[More than 65% of oil and gas companies are increasing their investment in enterprise software solutions and cloud migrations. Find out why.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digitalization</category>
            <category>news-tag/esg</category>
            <category>news-tag/greenhouse-gas-emissions</category>
            <category>industry/oil-gas-energy</category>
            <category>news-tag/opentext</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Wholesale Distributors Can Stand Out in a Direct-to-Consumer World]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/04/wholesale-distributors-stand-out-direct-to-consumer-world</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/04/wholesale-distributors-stand-out-direct-to-consumer-world</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With the help of SAP ECM solutions by OpenText, wholesale distributors can close the gap in their e-commerce strategies. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digitalization</category>
            <category>news-tag/opentext</category>
            <category>industry/wholesale-distribution</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Why Retail Has to Adapt with Digitalization]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/04/why-retail-has-to-adapt-digitalization</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/04/why-retail-has-to-adapt-digitalization</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Retailers must leverage customer and operational content with enterprise content management technology that is complete and personalized.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digitalization</category>
            <category>news-tag/opentext</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Information Sharing Can Ease the Consumer Goods Supply Strain]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/03/information-sharing-ease-consumer-goods-supply-strain</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/03/information-sharing-ease-consumer-goods-supply-strain</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Standardized information sharing is a critical first step toward strengthening much-needed resiliency, efficiency, and control. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16acfad5b667087aba74dcf54df81132861712462.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16acfad5b667087aba74dcf54df81132861712462.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_16acfad5b667087aba74dcf54df81132861712462.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Information Sharing Can Ease the Consumer Goods Supply Strain" src="./media_16acfad5b667087aba74dcf54df81132861712462.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="information-sharing-can-ease-the-consumer-goods-supply-strain">Information Sharing Can Ease the Consumer Goods Supply Strain</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Consumer products companies are dealing with an entirely new set of challenges that are driving up costs and increasing supply chain fragility – making them more susceptible to losing consumers. Could it be that quick-fix digitalization efforts during the <a href="/topics/covid-19">pandemic</a> are exacerbating these challenges?</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Every business involved in the consumer products value chain – including raw material suppliers, ingredient producers, manufacturers, logistics providers, retailers, and wholesale distributors – has made great strides in digitalizing its internal operations. Yet, a lack of data exchange across the entire network could intensify delays and inefficiencies as resources or products move from one part of the supply chain to the other.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="how-can-enterprise-content-management-drive-differentiation-in-consumer-products-operations">How can enterprise content management drive differentiation in consumer products operations?</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/09/a01dc772-f87d-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="moving-supplies-with-better-transparency-and-insight">Moving Supplies with Better Transparency and Insight</h2>
  <p>According to <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/09/a01dc772-f87d-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">IDC</a>, consumer products companies are beginning to get the message: 39% of surveyed industry players expect to increase spending on integrated enterprise content management (ECM) applications in 2021. Moreover, nearly half of them expect this digital investment to be a key contributor to operational performance (43%) and employee productivity (44%) – two factors that can significantly ease today’s consumer goods supply strain.</p>
  <p>During the pandemic, most consumer products companies adopted point solutions while maintaining a preexisting infrastructure of isolated legacy systems and spreadsheets for critical functions. However, this setup – which, at the time, was a response to changing consumer behaviors and employee needs – is missing the connectedness, intelligence, and transparency necessary to align operational capacity with surging demand.</p>
  <p>Many businesses now realize that standardized information sharing is a critical first step toward strengthening much-needed resiliency, efficiency, and control. It allows internal and external supply chain participants to exchange consumer expectations insight, communicate actionable next steps, and scale operations as one ecosystem.</p>
  <p>With cloud-based SAP enterprise content management solutions by OpenText, the entire supply chain can connect all this information so stakeholders can access curated content anytime, anywhere, and across the business. Plus, the inclusion of embedded artificial intelligence (AI) and machine learning enables the technology to automatically capture, organize, and analyze massive amounts of data to support higher productivity.</p>
  <p>Along with supply chain operations, SAP ECM solutions by OpenText can improve adjacent departments – such as accounts payable, accounts receivable, inventory, and trade promotion management – that directly impact overall customer satisfaction. These back-office functions can use real-time supply chain information, coupled with insights into emerging customer demand and financial constraints, to reduce the pressure of supply challenges. For example, they can shape product allocation to minimize waste and optimize existing production capacity by adjusting consumer segmentation, evolving product portfolios, and innovating business models – all while offering a consistent brand experience.</p>
  <h2 id="satisfying-consumers-better-despite-shortages">Satisfying Consumers Better Despite Shortages</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="discover-sap-ecm-solutions-by-opentext-to-help-transform-your-business-into-an-intelligent-enterprise">Discover SAP ECM solutions by OpenText to help transform your business into an intelligent enterprise</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/oth/enterprise-content-management/index.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>While conditions on the supply side may not ease until ports add capacity and companies can keep up with growing demand, it’s never too soon to unify the business network with smooth information sharing and workflows. Otherwise, brands risk ignoring revenue growth opportunities while wrestling with supply chain disruptions.</p>
  <p>SAP ECM solutions by OpenText can help relieve consumer products companies from making that trade-off. Now, their employees and stakeholders can make highly informed, data-driven decisions that help satisfy consumer demand – even as the stakes increase during peak buying seasons.</p>
  <p>Find out how personalized communications and a complete understanding of your sellers and consumers can lead to unique and differentiating brand value. Read the info sheet, “<a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/11/c2adb0fe-027e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Drive Differentiation with Intelligent Enterprise Content Management</a>.”</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/consumer-goods-cpg</category>
            <category>news-tag/covid-19</category>
            <category>news-tag/digitalization</category>
            <category>news-tag/opentext</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Enterprise Adoption: Localization Services Power Global Sustainable Business]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/02/localization-services-power-global-sustainable-business</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/02/localization-services-power-global-sustainable-business</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In this exclusive Q&A, SAP’s Eva Zauke talks about the powerful localization revolution happening behind every digital-first business.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/financial-management</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digitalization</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
            <category>product/sap-billing-and-revenue-innovation-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-enterprise-adoption</category>
            <category>product/sap-responsible-design-and-production</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enterprise Content Management: A Pivotal Step to End-to-End Digitalization]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/02/enterprise-content-management-ecm-digitalization</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/02/enterprise-content-management-ecm-digitalization</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[According to an IDC whitepaper, SAP ECM solutions by OpenText can help businesses go paperless, resulting in greater efficiency. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_184c064ceef0464e02871782164bc5c9529c8989b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_184c064ceef0464e02871782164bc5c9529c8989b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_184c064ceef0464e02871782164bc5c9529c8989b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Enterprise Content Management: A Pivotal Step to End-to-End Digitalization" src="./media_184c064ceef0464e02871782164bc5c9529c8989b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="enterprise-content-management-a-pivotal-step-to-end-to-end-digitalization">Enterprise Content Management: A Pivotal Step to End-to-End Digitalization</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Work patterns may have changed over the years, but surprisingly most workplaces have yet to make any meaningful progress toward becoming paperless. Is this resistance to content digitalization and integration holding businesses back from becoming resilient and sustainable enough to stay competitive?</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>While the concept of the paperless workplace is nothing new, the opportunity to achieve this vision is quickly approaching as businesses advance their transformation strategies. Over the past year, companies have invested in software-as-a-service (SaaS) and cloud-enabled systems, new methodologies such as process automation, and network-wide collaboration to keep employees productive, update suppliers, and deliver on customer expectations.</p>
  <p>Now, some organizations are looking to go even further in their business transformation journey by digitalizing and integrating content with a comprehensive enterprise platform.</p>
  <p>According to an IDC whitepaper sponsored by SAP and OpenText, “<a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2022/01/629d79f0-127e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">The Business Value of SAP Enterprise Content Management Solutions by OpenText in the Digital-First World</a>,” implementing solutions ‒ such as <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/enterprise-content-management.html">SAP enterprise content management (ECM) solutions by OpenText</a> ‒ can quickly yield a 288% three-year ROI. And at the center of this effective transformation is fast and efficient document migration, intake, processing, and auditing with fewer errors and higher productivity.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="discover-enterprise-content-management-solutions-to-help-your-business-become-an-intelligent-enterprise">Discover enterprise content management solutions to help your business become an intelligent enterprise</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/oth/enterprise-content-management/index.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="capturing-us7-million-in-revenue-growth">Capturing US$7 Million in Revenue Growth</h2>
  <p>The benefits of content digitalization, integration, and automation with <a href="/2020/05/study-ecm-and-mdg-solution-extensions-opentext-utopia">enterprise content management can be combined to increase revenue</a> by more than $7 million per year. By increasing efficiency, reducing errors, and accelerating processes, organizations surveyed by IDC reported an average gain of 4,794 productive hours each ‒ a 21% increase in gross user productivity.</p>
  <p>This improvement allowed respondents to avoid the hiring of 2.6 full-time employees to accomplish equivalent workloads, resulting in approximately $178,000 in enhanced user productivity value per organization. Additionally, enhanced interdepartmental document sharing and the automation of manual processes boosted profitability even further by driving $3.82 million in savings per one million documents.</p>
  <h2 id="migrating-documents-with-more-efficiency">Migrating Documents with More Efficiency</h2>
  <p>Migrating millions of documents that have been created, managed, and stored on paper to digital is a daunting task during any change initiative, especially when moving to a modern enterprise resource planning (ERP) system, such as <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/s4hana-erp.html">SAP S/4HANA</a>. However, document-related migration is not just a one-time effort; it’s a project that can happen as regularly as organizations continue to evolve throughout their digital transformation.</p>
  <p>Interviewed organizations that use solutions for enterprise content management cited considerable migration efficiencies and cost reductions. For example, some respondents required 24% fewer full-time employees to complete migration projects, from 128.6 to 97.3 on average. The duration of the migration was also shortened from 12.2 months to only seven months, a 43% improvement. As a result of these efficiencies gain, the cost of document-related migration became 24% more affordable.</p>
  <p>As one manufacturing executive noted, “Doing data migration is easier if you minimize the number of applications. SAP ECM solutions by OpenText helped us put building blocks in place. Our knowledge has increased, and the learning curve is less steep. We know more about what is required country to country.”</p>
  <h2 id="decreasing-invoice-errors">Decreasing Invoice Errors</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-a-snapshot-of-the-idc-whitepaper">Get a snapshot of the IDC whitepaper</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/10/3ede3947-027e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>When the volume of paper invoices increases, manual processes become too time-consuming and risk-prone to maintain. For one of the survey participants, the lack of history tracking, trend analysis, and currency distinction led to €300,000 lost on paying invoices because the organization missed out on receiving discounts upwards of two percent. And in some cases, IDC reported that many respondents also paid interest and penalties on late payments that they could have avoided.</p>
  <p>After automating invoicing tasks with enterprise content management, organizations realized a 35% drop in delayed payments and paid 36% less on penalties and interest. The system immediately validates and approves incoming invoices, improving overall invoice performance and decreasing errors by 43% on average.</p>
  <p>A participating executive from an industrial chemicals company remarked on the tremendous value of digitalizing invoice management: “From the moment the organization moved toward less touching, it saw a 70% improvement over paper.”</p>
  <h2 id="boosting-organizational-efficiency">Boosting Organizational Efficiency</h2>
  <p>As digital transformation becomes synonymous with business growth, executives must consistently consider new capabilities and enhancements to improve their operations, employees’ lives, desired outcomes, and customer experiences. In fact, this mindset is bringing forth a new focus on business efficiency and resiliency.</p>
  <p>From invoice intake and processing, accounts payable, and auditing teams to areas outside of finance, solutions for enterprise content management can have an impressive impact on organizational efficiency, ranging from 24% to 41%. This outcome is largely due to allowing multiple users to obtain documents with greater ease. Organizations can work independently of an office location and still have secure access to content from a single centralized environment.</p>
  <p>In return, users who work from remote locations can work more effectively, which is a tremendous benefit for businesses with most of their workforce still working from home and in the field. Companies can support employees from more geographic regions and across all process streams and operational areas ‒ all without shuttling physical documents back and forth in e-mail.</p>
  <p>In addition, since their content is archived and stored in a centralized process and database, organizations can stay compliant with regulatory and business requirements with minimal or no effort. A surveyed healthcare executive noted this advantage’s value: “We can see content now, whereas the older way we had to search. We can now look at transactional records, so compliance is handled on the schedule.”</p>
  <h2 id="gaining-the-full-potential-of-content-management">Gaining the Full Potential of Content Management</h2>
  <p>The deeper companies transform into digital-first enterprises, the closer they get to operate at a level of efficiency, intelligence, and speed that rivals their competitors. And the first place to gain that edge is best found in digitalization through enterprise content management that removes the complexity of siloed information, spreadsheets, data extractions, and manipulations.</p>
  <p>Explore the calculated cost savings and business benefits of SAP enterprise content management solutions by OpenText, which support enterprise content management. Read the IDC whitepaper, “<a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2022/01/629d79f0-127e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">The Business Value of SAP Enterprise Content Management Solutions by OpenText in the Digital-First World</a>,” commissioned by SAP and Open Text.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digitalization</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
            <category>news-tag/opentext</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Vital Truths About Business Digitalization from High Performers in ANZ]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/vital-truths-business-digitalization-high-performers-anz</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/vital-truths-business-digitalization-high-performers-anz</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Leaders from high-performing ANZ organizations shared their digitalization experiences during a virtual SAPPHIRE NOW session. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14e9478cb963a97ba71af61b2a3ab178007a392e6.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14e9478cb963a97ba71af61b2a3ab178007a392e6.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_14e9478cb963a97ba71af61b2a3ab178007a392e6.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Vital Truths About Business Digitalization from High Performers in ANZ" src="./media_14e9478cb963a97ba71af61b2a3ab178007a392e6.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="vital-truths-about-business-digitalization-from-high-performers-in-anz">Vital Truths About Business Digitalization from High Performers in ANZ</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Having experienced the equivalent of 10 years of digital change in the past 18 months or so, organizations are addressing the realities of transformation as <a href="https://insights.sap.com/digitization-vs-digitalization/">digitalization</a> becomes the business norm.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Leaders from two high-performing organizations in ANZ recently shared their experiences with digitalization during a <a href="https://reg.sapevents.sap.com/flow/sap/sapphirenow2021/portal/page/sessions/session/1624909796224001c5ES">SAPPHIRE NOW session</a> hosted by Des Fisher, innovation principal at SAP ANZ. Here is a sampling of the far-ranging thoughts on the sustainable business realities behind innovating on cloud-based digital platforms.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="watch-replays-from-sapphire-now">Watch replays from SAPPHIRE NOW</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://reg.sapevents.sap.com/flow/sap/sapphirenow2021/portal/page/sessions/session/1624909796224001c5ES">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="digitalization-is-a-mindset-and-tech-transformation">Digitalization Is a Mindset and Tech Transformation</h2>
  <p>For Australian-based <a href="/australia/2021/06/30/stockland-settles-in-on-its-new-sap-core">Stockland</a>, digitalization involved transforming people’s mindsets along with systems company-wide. As one of the largest diversified real estate groups in Australia, the company owns, develops, and manages a large portfolio of retail town centers, workplace and logistics assets, residential communities, and retirement living villages. It’s replaced over 100 disparate, legacy software systems with SAP software, including <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/s4hana-erp.html">SAP S/4HANA</a> and <a href="https://www.ariba.com/">SAP Ariba solutions</a>, as well as embedded artificial intelligence (AI) and robotics.</p>
  <p>“We now have a single source of the truth,” said Tiernan O’Rourke, CFO at Stockland. “I’m absolutely convinced that in time we’ll look back and say that was one of the best things we did in the 70-year history of the company…Our digitization journey shows that unless you’re on the journey you’re going to struggle in business, not only in Australia, but globally.”</p>
  <p>Stockland began by defining digitalization in the company’s own terms. The digital platform was designed to strike a balance between achieving three objectives: organizational risk, governance, and business growth.</p>
  <p>“We first looked at what digitization meant to us and came at it by putting the company on the core SAP platform,” said O’Rourke. “We’re a tactile industry of property, bricks, and mortar. Getting people’s minds away from physical to digital was…one of the biggest obstacles to overcome.”</p>
  <h2 id="digital-backbone-drives-innovation">Digital Backbone Drives Innovation</h2>
  <p>Oil and gas provider OMV New Zealand recently won an <a href="/australia/2021/04/20/services-australia-agl-and-omv-new-zealand-win-sap-global-innovation-awards">SAP Innovation Award</a> for its groundbreaking digitalization that included digital twins and augmented reality (AR) in onshore and offshore inspections. Replacing paper-heavy processes with digitalized and integrated workflows based on the latest mobile solutions and wearable technologies will help OMV improve decision-making, performance, and efficiencies in inspections and maintenance. Its integrated workflow management relies on SAP S/4HANA, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/supply-chain-management/asset-management-eam.html">SAP Intelligent Asset Management</a>, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/asset-manager.html">SAP Asset Manager</a>, and HoloLens 2.</p>
  <p>“The use of automation and AI-driven technologies for creating intelligent digital twins is a key enabler for global scalability and accelerates creating the digital backbone of the company during digital transformation. Enhancing this technology with an augmented reality experience including mark-up annotations provides a solid basis for data insights, data-driven decision-making, and performance optimization,” said Farid Akbari, functional lead for Digital Transformation at OMV New Zealand. “This innovation project will change the way we are working and enable us to position ourselves among digital front-runners within our industry.”</p>
  <h2 id="digital-platforms-are-core-to-supplier-relationships">Digital Platforms Are Core to Supplier Relationships</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="anz-leaders-that-invested-early-in-digital-supply-chains-had-tremendous-results">ANZ Leaders That Invested Early in Digital Supply Chains Had Tremendous Results</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/09/anz-digital-supply-chains-tremendous-results">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Acknowledging that no business does business alone, O’Rourke said that Stockland’s deep supplier relationship management strategy is foundational to customer centricity.</p>
  <p>“If you don’t partner with best-in-breed, like-minded companies to help deliver premium services to customers, you won’t win,” he said. “We have 14% market share in residential business…because we evaluate every step of the customer journey, including supplier choice…You can’t know your suppliers unless you have deep relationships and are collaborating with them at a very granular level…Collaboration is an absolute threshold issue in business today.”</p>
  <h2 id="close-gap-between-dx-and-business-realities">Close Gap Between DX and Business Realities</h2>
  <p>When asked about some of the biggest digital transformation challenges, Akbari discussed the gap between innovation aspirations and reality. He pointed out that while everyone wants simplicity, getting there means answering difficult questions.</p>
  <p>“We asked ourselves if we had the right organization in place to achieve digital maturity,” he recalled. “Other questions were about managing resistance to change and how to actively support the change management process with tools that were changing the way we work…We asked how to build and retain skills over time as innovations like blockchain, the Internet of Things (IoT), and cloud computing continue [to emerge].”</p>
  <p>Akbari also warned organizations not to neglect core details such as infrastructure capabilities, technology integration, and resultant business process changes.</p>
  <p>“Often the business comes up with a good idea, but we’re not ready yet,” he said. “For example, AR had to be integrated into the environment…You also have to consider operational maturity…As a global gas and oil company, we have different maturity levels of all assets and have to map where we are for each asset and how we will achieve that automation level.”</p>
  <h2 id="sustainability-is-much-more-than-climate-change">Sustainability Is Much More Than Climate Change</h2>
  <p>While ESG (environmental, social, and governance) demands tend to emphasize climate change, O’Rourke urged companies to consider all aspects of sustainability, including diversity.</p>
  <p>“Everyone talks about climate change, but that’s just about the environment. To do business successfully…you’re going to have to be very balanced in the E, S, and G of ESG,” he said. “Everyone is focused on net zero carbon, and rightly so. But we can’t do that in isolation…We have to jump on [behavior change] proactively to get suppliers to work with us in a way allows us to operate effectively. On the diversity side, business has been playing lip service for so long and needs to get serious about focusing on this change.”</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Follow me @smgaler.</em><br><em><a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2021/08/24/vital-truths-about-business-digitalization-from-high-performers-in-anz/?sh=187392fa331b">This blog also appeared on SAP BrandVoice on Forbes.</a></em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digitalization</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-anz</category>
            <category>sap-award/sap-innovation-awards</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Companies Continue to Digitalize Spend Management with SAP]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/companies-digitalize-spend-management-with-sap</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/companies-digitalize-spend-management-with-sap</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Ariba and SAP Fieldglass solutions help companies across industries digitalize spend management and external workforce management.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18336490c7900d7c1abeb97d7ba5022908af43cf5.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18336490c7900d7c1abeb97d7ba5022908af43cf5.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_18336490c7900d7c1abeb97d7ba5022908af43cf5.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Companies Continue to Digitalize Spend Management with SAP" src="./media_18336490c7900d7c1abeb97d7ba5022908af43cf5.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="companies-continue-to-digitalize-spend-management-with-sap">Companies Continue to Digitalize Spend Management with SAP</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="achieve-digital-transformation-from-source-to-pay-with-sap-ariba-solutions">Achieve digital transformation from source to pay with SAP Ariba solutions</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.ariba.com/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced that Molson Coors Beverage Co. and the Florida Department of Management Services are among the hundreds of companies across industries and geographies in the second quarter to have chosen <a href="http://www.ariba.com/?campaigncode=CRM-IS20-PRL-OOCWA01">SAP Ariba</a> and <a href="https://www.fieldglass.com/?campaigncode=CRM-IS20-PRL-OOCWF02">SAP Fieldglass</a> solutions to digitalize procurement and external workforce management. Hundreds more renewed licenses and still more went live with the solutions to optimize spend management.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“We have seen significant growth this quarter with companies around the world continuing to prioritize improving their spend management operations,” said John Wookey, president of SAP Intelligent Spend and Business Network. “By modernizing and digitalizing critical business processes across procurement and external workforce management, our customers are gaining visibility and insights that enable them to control costs, reduce risk and drive innovation and growth for their businesses.”</p>
  <p>Highlights from the quarter include:</p>
  <p><strong>Alcon Vision</strong>, the Fort Worth, Texas–based company, is a global leader in eye care, specializing in surgical medical devices and nonsurgical vision care products. Alcon selected SAP Ariba solutions for sourcing and procurement for direct and indirect materials. The company also selected the Qualtrics XM for Suppliers solution to help build stronger and more collaborative relationships with suppliers. With a new and improved intuitive source-to-pay experience, Alcon aims to foster simplicity, speed and user-friendly buying services with increased data transparency and compliance.</p>
  <p>Refrigeration and air conditioning technology manufacturer <strong>BITZER SE</strong> has implemented the SAP Ariba Buying solution with guided buying capability to help streamline and digitalize its procurement operations. With the SAP Ariba solution, BITZER, based in Sindelfingen, Germany, aims to drive a more efficient, paperless, transparent process from sourcing to payment as it expands globally.</p>
  <p>The <strong>Florida Department of Management Services (DMS)</strong> selected SAP Ariba solutions for sourcing, contracts, buying and invoicing, and commerce automation to modernize its statewide procurement system with a cloud-based solution. DMS plans to standardize and automate procurement processes across the State of Florida, increase spend visibility and control, and enhance savings statewide.</p>
  <p>Aligned with its innovation and sustainability strategy, <strong>Grupo Financiero Banorte, S.A.B. de C.V.,</strong> one of the largest financial holdings companies in Mexico, continues its procurement transformation with the renewal of SAP Ariba solutions. By further digitalizing its procurement processes and strengthening its supply lifecycle management automation, Banorte will help improve the experience of more than 21,000 suppliers while enhancing process efficiency and spend compliance.</p>
  <p><strong>Molson Coors</strong> made a strategic investment in SAP Ariba solutions to help modernize its global procurement operations, building on its implementation of the SAP Ariba Contracts solution and adding the SAP Ariba Buying and Invoicing solution with commerce automation capabilities. With the new solutions integrated with its multiple ERP infrastructure, the company, headquartered in Golden, Colorado, and Montreal, Canada, intends to standardize on best practices from source to pay, improve efficiency in supplier relationship management and minimize risk.</p>
  <p><strong>Promigas SA ESP</strong>, a leading Colombian provider of natural gas, has selected SAP Ariba solutions for digital procurement as it continued its transformation journey with SAP. Building on its existing transportation management system based on SAP S/4HANA, Promigas will adopt the cloud-based SAP Ariba solutions to help standardize and automate its procurement processes, increase purchasing efficiencies and reduce costs and risks.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-fieldglass-rework-how-work-gets-done">SAP Fieldglass: Rework how work gets done</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.fieldglass.com/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><strong>Roca Sanitario SA</strong>, a global leader in bathroom equipment, selected SAP Ariba solutions for strategic sourcing, buying, commerce automation and supply chain collaboration. The Spanish company will adopt the digital <a href="https://www.fieldglass.com/solutions/services-procurement">procurement solutions</a> to help improve, standardize and automate spend management processes across the organization. The company expects to increase visibility into spend and supplier performance to optimize costs and operational efficiencies.</p>
  <p>For more information, visit the <a href="/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP on Twitter at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>About SAP</strong></p>
  <p>SAP’s strategy is to help every business run as an intelligent enterprise. As a market leader in enterprise application software, we help companies of all sizes and in all industries run at their best: 77% of the world’s transaction revenue touches an SAP system. Our machine learning, Internet of Things (IoT), and advanced analytics technologies help turn customers’ businesses into intelligent enterprises. SAP helps give people and organizations deep business insight and fosters collaboration that helps them stay ahead of their competition. We simplify technology for companies so they can consume our software the way they want – without disruption. Our end-to-end suite of applications and services enables business and public customers across 25 industries globally to operate profitably, adapt continuously, and make a difference. With a global network of customers, partners, employees, and thought leaders, SAP helps the world run better and improve people’s lives. For more information, visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/">www.sap.com</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Note to editors:</strong><br>To preview and download broadcast-standard stock footage and press photos digitally, please visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/photos">www.sap.com/photos</a>. On this platform, you can find high resolution material for your media channels. To view video stories on diverse topics, visit <a href="http://www.sap-tv.com">www.sap-tv.com</a>. From this site, you can embed videos into your own Web pages, share video via email links, and subscribe to RSS feeds from SAP TV.</p>
  <p><strong>For customers interested in learning more about SAP products:</strong><br>Global Customer Center: +49 180 534-34-24<br>United States Only: 1 (800) 872-1SAP (1-800-872-1727)</p>
  <p><strong>For more information, press only:</strong> Kelly Sheldon Murray, +1 (978) 708-6821, <a href="mailto:kelly.murray@sap.com">kelly.murray@sap.com</a><u>,</u> ET<br>Geraldine Lim, +1 (415) 418-0945, <a href="mailto:geraldine.lim@sap.com">geraldine.lim@sap.com</a>, PT<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>Any statements contained in this document that are not historical facts are forward-looking statements as defined in the U.S. Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995. Words such as “anticipate,” “believe,” “estimate,” “expect,” “forecast,” “intend,” “may,” “plan,” “project,” “predict,” “should” and “will” and similar expressions as they relate to SAP are intended to identify such forward-looking statements. SAP undertakes no obligation to publicly update or revise any forward-looking statements. All forward-looking statements are subject to various risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results to differ materially from expectations. The factors that could affect SAP’s future financial results are discussed more fully in SAP’s filings with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (“SEC”), including SAP’s most recent Annual Report on Form 20-F filed with the SEC. Readers are cautioned not to place undue reliance on these forward-looking statements, which speak only as of their dates.<br>© 2021 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="http://www.sap.com/corporate-en/legal/copyright/index.epx#trademark">http://www.sap.com/corporate-en/legal/copyright/index.epx#trademark</a> for additional trademark information and notices.<br>Please consider our <a href="https://www.sap.com/corporate/en/legal/privacy.html">privacy policy</a>. If you received this press release in your e-mail and you wish to unsubscribe to our mailing list please contact <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a> and write Unsubscribe in the subject line.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-news</category>
            <category>news-tag/digitalization</category>
            <category>news-tag/external-workforce-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-spend</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>product/sap-ariba-buying</category>
            <category>product/sap-ariba-contracts</category>
            <category>topic/spend-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Digitalization Supports Business Continuity]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/digitalization-business-continuity-during-covid-19</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/digitalization-business-continuity-during-covid-19</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[For many SAP customers, digitalization has supported their business continuity during COVID-19. Learn how four companies thrived.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/travel-transportation</category>
            <category>news-tag/covid-19</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/digitalization</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>