<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/topic/data-analytics/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[German National Team Relies on SAP Technology at the European Championship]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/german-national-team-dfb-sap-technology-european-championship</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/german-national-team-dfb-sap-technology-european-championship</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The coaches and analysts of the German Football Association (DFB) use SAP Sports One to analyze opponents and share tactics with players.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>topic/data-analytics</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>product/sap-sports-one</category>
            <category>industry/sports-entertainment</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Partnerships Help Customers Successfully Navigate a Data-Driven World]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/partnerships-help-customers-navigate-data-driven-world</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/partnerships-help-customers-navigate-data-driven-world</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP partners can deploy SAP Datasphere and SAP Analytics Cloud to provide data access, effective planning, and trusted AI across operations.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16fa40a8c4f0c1be7eb9eaf1afe27075d1230ec25.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16fa40a8c4f0c1be7eb9eaf1afe27075d1230ec25.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_16fa40a8c4f0c1be7eb9eaf1afe27075d1230ec25.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Partnerships Help Customers Successfully Navigate a Data-Driven World" src="./media_16fa40a8c4f0c1be7eb9eaf1afe27075d1230ec25.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="partnerships-help-customers-successfully-navigate-a-data-driven-world">Partnerships Help Customers Successfully Navigate a Data-Driven World</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>In the modern business environment, the critical need to effectively harness data is undeniable. Companies that fail to become data-driven risk falling behind in a world where agility and informed decision-making are paramount. In the recent <a href="https://www.sap.com/events/data-unleashed.html">SAP Data Unleashed</a> event we explored strategies to help organizations access data from any source, transform planning and analysis with a business data fabric, and foster trusted artificial intelligence (AI) across their businesses. Central to this transformation are <a href="/topics/ecosystem">SAP partners</a>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>For decades, our partners have leveraged their industry expertise and technological know-how to bring immense value to companies of all sizes. They possess a rare fusion of deep industry insights and technological expertise, which they leverage to guide businesses through the delicate process of modernization while ensuring that the essence of their identity remains intact.</p>
  <p>We recently <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/partners.html#trending">asked several of our strategic SAP partners</a> how they’re helping customers take better advantage of their organization’s data. Our partners have observed a significant shift in the way data is perceived and utilized. It’s no longer just a byproduct of business operations but a core asset that, when effectively distributed and made accessible, can revolutionize customer experiences and enable a more strategic, company-wide approach to decision-making.</p>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11f5934a69f41fbb435d136fc80e11b26ab8eb2f5.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11f5934a69f41fbb435d136fc80e11b26ab8eb2f5.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_11f5934a69f41fbb435d136fc80e11b26ab8eb2f5.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Partners Bring Out Your Best as a Data-Driven Organization" src="./media_11f5934a69f41fbb435d136fc80e11b26ab8eb2f5.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://youtu.be/Cj3BF9-9I30">SAP Partners Bring Out Your Best as a Data-Driven Organization</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>However, the mere availability of data is not a panacea. The crux of the matter is transforming data into actionable insights. This is where our partners excel, mapping out advanced use cases and facilitating the transition to cutting-edge platforms like SAP Datasphere and SAP Analytics Cloud. These solutions can empower organizations to evolve into entities where data is not just present but central to every action and decision.</p>
  <p>The practical implications of data are vast and deeply rooted in the operational successes of our clients. AI, for instance, is a frontier rich with potential, but its success is inextricably linked to the quality and accessibility of data. Recognizing this, SAP partners are investing in building AI capabilities that can not only propel new business functions but also deliver substantial value.</p>
  <p>Another key area of focus for our partners is the concept of a business data fabric, which is critical in developing a flexible enterprise architecture. Such an architecture allows for co-innovation and customization of solutions, ensuring that data is not just an afterthought but a driving force in business operations.</p>
  <p>The journey toward a data- and AI-centric business model is an ongoing one, marked by evolving needs, emerging challenges, and a relentless pursuit of innovation. The ultimate aim is to convert potential into lasting business success.</p>
  <p>The essence of our relationship with our partners is rooted in a shared vision. We are united in our pursuit of discovery, innovation, and improvement as we navigate the future together. Be sure to <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/partners.html#trending">watch the videos</a> with our seven strategic partners and discover how the <a href="https://www.sap.com/partners.html">SAP partner ecosystem</a> can help your company become a data-driven organization.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Karl Fahrbach is chief partner officer at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-partners-are-helping-their-clients-solve-critical-business-challenges">SAP partners are helping their clients solve critical business challenges</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/partners.html#trending">Discover how</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>topic/data-analytics</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-datasphere</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Who Really Runs Your Organization]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/who-really-runs-your-organization</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/who-really-runs-your-organization</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Organizational network analysis provides a data-based view into the informal interactions that make companies work.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1bee56882580d353aa873b9348fc4133202e579b5.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1bee56882580d353aa873b9348fc4133202e579b5.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1bee56882580d353aa873b9348fc4133202e579b5.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Magnifying glass on woman’s headshot among others in a yearbook-style layout." src="./media_1bee56882580d353aa873b9348fc4133202e579b5.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1044">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="who-really-runs-your-organization">Who Really Runs Your Organization</h1>
        <p>Organizational network analysis provides a data-based view into the informal interactions that make companies work.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Large companies with geographically dispersed workforces, an ongoing need for the best talent, and the desire to have an adaptive collaborative organization are finding a decades-old academic instrument – organizational network analysis (ONA) – has fresh relevance. ONA, a technique originated by sociologists, maps the informal networks that play just as crucial a role as formal organizational charts in shaping employee experiences, delivering business benefits, and improving operational efficiencies.</p>
  <p>Analyzing how people work together, the networks they form to get work done, make decisions, and act on them, reveals how organizations really operate. And it’s typically not the command-and-control structures that leaders have drawn up.</p>
  <p>For decades, companies have relied on static organizational charts to clarify roles, improve communication, and streamline decision-making. “Julius Caesar organized his army into commanders and lieutenants – a hierarchy that is basically how employees work today,” says Maya Bodan, leader of the organization strategy and design talent group for Deloitte LLP in San Francisco, California.</p>
  <p>ONA is a tool for creating visual representations of how communications, information, and decisions flow through an organization using data from employee surveys, enterprise systems, and other sources. Unlike an organizational chart’s breakdown structure, ONA provides “an x-ray” into how a company actually works by “mapping patterns of connectivity and collaboration inside the organization,” says Rob Cross, an expert on ONA and SVP of research at the Institute for Corporate Productivity.</p>
  <p>By making strategically important individuals visible, the analysis sheds light on informal relationships and invisible patterns, providing deep insight into how information flows, the identity of key influencers, and the existence of silos that can lead to bottlenecks. This has never been more important – or more possible – than in today’s geographically dispersed employees working together using virtual collaboration tools.</p>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div data-valign="middle">A very small set of people have a disproportionate impact on how work gets done.</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div data-valign="middle">Rob Cross, SVP of research, Institute for Corporate Productivity</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Experts describe how the results of an organizational analysis highlight different types of individual contributors. Cross says ONA can reveal, for example, who in the company is a <strong>central connector</strong>, someone whom other members of the network consult frequently for information and hold the network together; <strong>knowledge brokers</strong>, people who connect different groups or teams within a network, and <strong>peripheral</strong>, those who have limited connections with the rest of the network.</p>
  <p>These characterizations can reveal who the major influencers and actors are in an organization, as well as those who could benefit from more engagement. (As you will learn in this article, there are additional employee archetypes.)</p>
  <p>Consider this hypothetical. Mark serves as a central connector in a large pharmaceutical company. As an entry-level data administrator, Mark is low on the corporate hierarchy, but he is critical in that he connects human resources, sales, and marketing colleagues by serving as a conduit for the exchange of ideas and information. Mia, on the other hand, is an expert coder who is great at developing apps, but she is peripheral – disconnected from others in the employee network who could assist and collaborate with her. On paper, Mia’s programmer title may be higher in the organizational hierarchy. However, she is unable to make the connections she needs to progress and be selected for high-value projects.</p>
  <p>These are the kinds of situations and relationships that exist in organizations of any substantial size. Understanding them in depth can help leaders foster more collaboration, enhance employee engagement, and promote talent development.</p>
  <p>But these benefits rely on good data. Organizations need to allay fears about data privacy, communicate the advantages of ONA to employees, and remain clear-eyed about the technology’s limitations.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_157d0358d0a6015b3e3aae97be8899e42f73f7091.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_157d0358d0a6015b3e3aae97be8899e42f73f7091.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_157d0358d0a6015b3e3aae97be8899e42f73f7091.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Man and woman coworkers having a discussion and looking at post-it notes on a clear whiteboard." src="./media_157d0358d0a6015b3e3aae97be8899e42f73f7091.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="visibility-into-far-flung-workforces">Visibility into far-flung workforces</h2>
  <p>Organizational network analysis emerged in the 1930s as a framework for sociologists to study the social interactions of prison inmates and reform school girls. Then, the work was done through observation and paper diagrams. In recent years, ONA has found a foothold in the corporate world for two reasons: the changing nature of work and the ability to analyze communications and other data.</p>
  <p>Over the past few years, organizations of all kinds have gone to great lengths to set up distributed, geographically dispersed, flexible teams. The workplace changes that occurred during the COVID-19 pandemic only reinforce the idea that employees need to be able to respond quickly to change and have the necessary space to pivot and experiment.</p>
  <p>However, companies’ work to make this shift has led to a new challenge: gaps of knowledge and awareness that prevent leaders from knowing who’s working effectively with whom on a wide range of projects.</p>
  <p>This is where the data comes in. Never before have organizations had access to vast volumes of passive data – information that exists within the company, such as e-mail, chat, calendar, and collaboration-software data. Unlike active data, gathered from time-consuming surveys typically administered by human resources teams, passive data provides a more objective, less biased view of workplace dynamics without requiring direct input from employees.</p>
  <p>ONA applications are also becoming easier to use, notes Bodan of Deloitte. “In the past, you needed a data science degree [to understand ONA],” says Bodan. “But there are many user-friendly platforms now that allow non-technical users like HR professionals to easily interpret the data and drive insights.”</p>
  <p>Together, the rise of remote work, passive data, and easier-to-use ONA tools are encouraging organizations to make ONA a key component of their talent strategy, experts say.</p>
  <h2 id="revealing-the-most-valuable-network-players">Revealing the most valuable (network) players</h2>
  <p>As its name suggests, ONA is about analyzing the networks among people who work together. Its value lies in helping companies identify important connections and potential obstacles to information flow and collaboration. ONA can serve like a tide that washes away the sand to reveal what’s hidden underneath. The results of an analysis can pinpoint different employee archetypes that don’t always show up in organizational charts. For example:</p>
  <h3 id="hidden-value-creators">Hidden-value creators</h3>
  <p>One important node in an organizational network is hidden-value creators – employees who contribute significantly to an organization yet are easily overlooked due to factors, such as geographic location, communication style, or corporate rank.</p>
  <p>“A very small set of people have a disproportionate impact on how work gets done,” says Cross of i4cp. He notes that, based on his work with more than 300 organizations, he has found that, on average, 2% to 3% of employees account for 20% to 35% of an organization’s key collaborative work. The problem, he says, is “if these workers are overlooked, they’re far more likely to leave the organization and take their networks with them.”</p>
  <p>ONA can cast a light on these unsung heroes, giving leaders the opportunity to offer incentives for them to stay and keep valuable networks intact.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="the-only-path-forward-is-together">The only path forward is together</h3>
        <p>Discover how business networks find new avenues for growth and innovation.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="/blogs/ext-business-networks-the-only-path-forward">Read more</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="energizers">Energizers</h3>
  <p>Energizers are positive thinkers who are quick to support coworkers’ ideas and “leave people feeling better after an interaction,” says Peter Gray, an ONA expert and professor of commerce at the University of Virginia’s McIntire School of Commerce in Charlottesville, Virginia.</p>
  <p>Gray’s research highlights the role human behavior can play in building a network. The most effective networks include energizers, says Gray. A single energizer in a network can greatly reduce the risk of attrition among team members while leading high performance.</p>
  <p>Organizational network analysis can help identify these such contributors, Gray says, by asking employees in a survey to identify the people in the company who make them feel good about themselves.</p>
  <h3 id="fast-movers">Fast movers</h3>
  <p>Employees who make a concerted effort to discover coworkers’ needs are also more likely to establish mutually beneficial and meaningful connections with coworkers. For example, while researching employee relationships, Cross discovered that 10% to 15% of employees are “fast movers” who become well-connected in less than a year after hiring (most workers require three to five years to become well-connected.) These fast movers, Cross says, share an interesting trait: When asked to disclose information about themselves, “fast movers are much more likely to pivot in that moment and say, ‘I can, but can you first give me a sense of what your priorities are? What are you excited about? What keeps you up at night?’”</p>
  <p>By investing in coworkers’ needs, Cross says fast movers are not only able to infiltrate powerful networks at rapid speed, but they are also more likely to be tapped for high-value projects.</p>
  <h3 id="weak-nodes">Weak nodes</h3>
  <p>As one might expect, the analysis can also highlight employees who are not well-connected to their networks. These weak nodes represent a situation that can “undercut an organization’s ability to deliver enterprise value,” Cross says. Underutilized and at higher risk of departure, he says these siloed workers can create “breakdowns in connectivity that are likely to hurt a company in terms of revenue potential, innovation, scale, or efficiencies – quantifiable points of impact.”</p>
  <p>In this scenario, knowledge is power. By identifying disconnected employees, organizations can stage team-building exercises and launch cross-functional projects that connect these peripheral players to central connectors and knowledge brokers for a more solid network.</p>
  <p>The good news is organizations are finding ways to bridge the gaps of knowledge created by issues related to scalability, engagement, and context. These best practices are not only helping organizations identify key influencers and isolated figures within a network, but also gaining a better understanding of how people work in today’s modern world and why some succeed – and others don’t.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1357353a61bace47c09b540d83a232c12e79cf37f.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1357353a61bace47c09b540d83a232c12e79cf37f.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1357353a61bace47c09b540d83a232c12e79cf37f.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Man working at a creative office using his computer with blurred coworkers moving in the background." src="./media_1357353a61bace47c09b540d83a232c12e79cf37f.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="2160">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="when-insight-leads-to-new-organizational-structures">When insight leads to new organizational structures</h2>
  <p>Retaining hidden talent and connecting valuable outliers aren’t the only business benefits of using ONA. Organizations can also realize substantial operational gains by visualizing the informal relationships that exist within an organization.</p>
  <p>Deloitte’s Bodan describes one client who had 14 different functions, including legal, finance, and accounts payable, all working within a single business unit. Desperate to break down these functional silos, Bodan says the company turned to ONA. Upon analyzing the company’s passive and active data, “we discovered that the natural communities that existed, based on how people operate on a day-to-day basis, was actually four,” she says. Moreover, although the company’s organizational chart dictated that employees collaborate according to function, networks had formed naturally around customer segments.</p>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div data-valign="middle">The modern workplace “is moving away from functional fiefdoms to a much more collaborative environment.</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div data-valign="middle">Maya Bodan, leader of the organization strategy and design talent group, Deloitte LLP</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In response, Bodan says the company whittled down its 14 functional silos into six key collaborative groups, each one dedicated to a particular customer segment. Creating these more meaningful and connected groups not only provided employees “with much more of an end-to-end view of how they’re working,” says Bodan, but also helped to increase speed to market, improve customer experience, and streamline decision-making.</p>
  <p>That’s a case when the analysis leads to organizational change. However, realizing such a result requires overcoming a set of challenges.</p>
  <h2 id="addressing-challenges-to-implementing-ona">Addressing challenges to implementing ONA</h2>
  <p>To achieve the benefits of ONA, companies will need to address technological, cultural, and organizational challenges to effectively apply it.</p>
  <h3 id="confronting-privacy-concerns">Confronting privacy concerns</h3>
  <p>As with any data-crunching tool, privacy concerns can limit the value organizations derive from ONA. Although employees can opt out of participating in a survey, passive data is generated from e-mail, texting, calendars, and collaboration applications without any employee involvement – or expressed consent.</p>
  <p>“Privacy has to be handled incredibly carefully in terms of how and what you're disclosing and to whom,” says Cross.</p>
  <p>But while establishing privacy practices related to disclosure can help protect employees, most ONA tools are already limited in terms of the data they’re able to gather, according to Gray, the University of Virginia professor.</p>
  <p>For example, Gray says, “Passive network data collection software programs that mine e-mail and meeting data are excellent at stripping out any information that could get a company in trouble.” That’s not to suggest, however, that passive data isn’t worth parsing. Rather, by examining the nature of e-mail exchanges, not the communication itself, organizations can discover patterns of collaboration, including which employees are most likely to respond to messages after work hours, and from whom – telltale signs of important relationships.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="hr-and-the-use-of-ai">HR and the Use of AI</h3>
        <p>Learn how HR can lead the way for AI adoption in your organization.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="/resources/how-hr-can-direct-use-of-ai">Read more</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="managing-scalability-limitations">Managing scalability limitations</h3>
  <p>Another obstacle to effective ONA is the nature of work itself – especially when the organization itself is very large. Multinational corporations have hundreds of thousands of employees, making it impractical to chart every single worker and their respective networks. Many employees simply don’t have the time to respond to lengthy surveys, which can prevent companies from achieving the response rates needed for accuracy. Passive data in isolation can fail to provide the necessary context for truly understanding the ties that bind employees.</p>
  <p>For example, is a particularly intense rally of text messages about a business-critical project or Sunday brunch plans? And what exactly constitutes a positive link between two employees? There are simply no standards for what a good network should look like.</p>
  <p>Leaders need to account for these potential weaknesses – just as they adjust their sights when evaluating outputs from business analytics systems with the knowledge that the results reflect incomplete data.</p>
  <h3 id="securing-employee-acceptance">Securing employee acceptance</h3>
  <p>Even the most clearly marked targets can be missed if employees aren’t on board with ONA. “There is sometimes a concern that ONA will be used in regressive ways – that it will be used to fire people,” says Gray. For this reason, he recommends that managers earn employee trust by assuring them that the insights generated by ONA will be used in ways that will benefit them directly, such as improving performance, pinpointing places to build strong connections, and uncovering hidden factors for success.</p>
  <p>Leaders must also take steps to present the discoveries made by ONA as compelling information rather than intractable truths. Consider, for example, the damage that could be done if a veteran manager learns that his energizer score is a fraction of the department’s latest hire. To avoid conflict and bruised egos, Gray says employees should be offered training on how to become more of an energizer, because “there are actual behaviors they can adopt to change their energizing score. You have to help them see that this is a function of behaviors that are malleable and change over time. No one is doomed.”</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1135fcc02c642fb46d5450b14b8a4a9b76968a37e.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1135fcc02c642fb46d5450b14b8a4a9b76968a37e.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1135fcc02c642fb46d5450b14b8a4a9b76968a37e.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Diverse group of businesspeople around a desk smiling cheerfully during an office meeting." src="./media_1135fcc02c642fb46d5450b14b8a4a9b76968a37e.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="adopting-a-data-first-method-to-organizational-thinking">Adopting a data-first method to organizational thinking</h2>
  <p>Adopting ONA will require leaders to use a data-first method to measure and illustrate the collaboration patterns among employees, says Bodan. Moreover, she adds, an “adaptable mindset” is crucial, because ONA’s analysis of the strength, frequency, and nature of employee interactions may reveal some counterintuitive truths about which employees really wield influence in the organization and which ones are simply coasting on their titles.</p>
  <p>Either way, says Bodan, the modern workplace “is moving away from functional fiefdoms to a much more collaborative environment”– one in which ONA can serve as a valuable tool and the hierarchy of Caeser’s legions really is history.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>topic/data-analytics</category>
            <category>content-type/use-case</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Driving Customers’ Business Outcomes with the Growing Power of Telemetry]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/driving-customers-business-outcomes-telemetry</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/driving-customers-business-outcomes-telemetry</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Telemetry empowers software vendors, like SAP, to help customers understand the full potential presented by new software solutions.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f4949b3d53dbf46c9cb030f708afe34afe3a67e8.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f4949b3d53dbf46c9cb030f708afe34afe3a67e8.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1f4949b3d53dbf46c9cb030f708afe34afe3a67e8.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Driving Customers’ Business Outcomes with the Growing Power of Telemetry" src="./media_1f4949b3d53dbf46c9cb030f708afe34afe3a67e8.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="driving-customers-business-outcomes-with-the-growing-power-of-telemetry">Driving Customers’ Business Outcomes with the Growing Power of Telemetry</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>In today’s business landscape, technology plays a pivotal role in solving customer problems and driving growth. But simply purchasing software doesn’t ensure resolution of the business issue.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Consider this: your business implements new software intended to speed up processes but finds out that your processes are instead stalling. Why? Because your employees never fully adopted the solutions. Now you may ultimately decide to stop using that software. To avoid this scenario, more and more software vendors are turning to an adoption-focused mindset that empowers customers to make the most of their software investments.</p>
  <p>In fact, <a href="https://www.concentrix.com/insights/blog/key-adoption-metrics/">85% of businesses say adoption and utilization data is the most valuable information in determining a software renewal</a>. Yet, only one-third of software vendors on the market have a documented adoption framework to assess how well specific customers are adopting their technology. Enter telemetry, which can help organizations make more informed decisions, optimize business processes, and realize the full potential of emerging technologies.</p>
  <h2 id="telemetry-helps-us-help-you">Telemetry Helps Us Help You</h2>
  <p>Telemetry often refers to the automatic collection of data measurements from physical equipment. Telemetry has had profound impacts on Industry 4.0, as it’s adopted by not only manufacturers but also by any business that uses virtually any kind of equipment. But with the advent of <a href="/topics/ai">artificial intelligence (AI)</a> and its seamless integration into many cloud applications, companies from all industries can consume AI-driven insights and capabilities. These innovations are transforming the way businesses operate, creating new opportunities, and driving efficiencies.</p>
  <p>Increasingly though, telemetry is also helping software vendors gather data on the performance and use of their customers’ deployments of their software. This includes SAP. Just like Industry 4.0 data analytics help your business optimize equipment, telemetry from your SAP software helps us see where you could best use our solutions to meet your unique goals, how it can be optimized, and where further enhancements may be necessary.</p>
  <p>The ever-expanding landscape of intelligent software and next-generation technology has opened many new doors for businesses, but all these opportunities can be overwhelming and even confusing. Telemetry empowers software vendors – including SAP – to help their customers understand the full potential presented by new software solutions.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-business-ai-revolutionary-technology-real-world-results">SAP Business AI: Revolutionary technology, real-world results</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="telemetry-driven-customer-success">Telemetry-Driven Customer Success</h2>
  <p>Telemetry is a game-changer in the realm of customer success. It provides a more accurate, near-real-time look at how software investments are performing. For software vendors, telemetry’s greatest advantages to help our customers include:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Identifying user patterns:</strong> Telemetry can provide a real look at user behavior with our software. By tracking navigation patterns and time spent on specific tasks, we can gain a comprehensive understanding of how your users work every day – and how they should work instead. With this insight, businesses can make data-driven decisions to enhance user experiences and drive greater adoption, which drives greater value.</li>
    <li><strong>Optimizing business processes and performance:</strong> Using telemetry, we can see how your software is performing across environments. It helps us discover process bottlenecks, frequently occurring errors, and system resource usage. With these insights, we’re better prepared to help you find out what processes simply aren’t working and why.</li>
    <li><strong>Analyzing feature use:</strong> Find out what features are most popular among your users – and which ones aren’t. Using this information, we can encourage users to take advantage of the features you’ve implemented or implement new ones that help users work more efficiently.</li>
    <li><strong>Predictive analytics:</strong> Telemetry data can be leveraged to create predictive models, anticipating potential issues or opportunities before they arise. This can help businesses stay one step ahead, ensuring smooth technology adoption and minimizing disruptions.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>Telemetry serves as a source of 360-degree signal interpretation, and it provides you with opportunities for intervention in the moments that matter most. Building off the above benefits, you can use telemetry to take advantage of predictive analytics for feature development, feedback-driven iterations, and customized user training.</p>
  <h2 id="bridge-the-hype-reality-gap">Bridge the “Hype-Reality” Gap</h2>
  <p>Telemetry and data analysis are helping us help our customers solve arguably the greatest threat to solution adoption: the “hype-reality” gap. Often, businesses hype up their latest software investment to users, claiming they’ll save employees time and effort. But when users don’t see results, they get disappointed – and they stop using the new software. Telemetry, by providing insight into how real users have been using your new software, is a critical way to show real-time results and get the entire business on board.</p>
  <p>In addition, telemetry builds on the increasing value of partnership between software vendors and their customers. By harnessing the power of real-time insights right from our customers’ own deployments of our software, we’re better prepared to steer the future of our software toward outcomes that support our customers. As organizations combine telemetry with advances in generative AI, they have a powerful tool at their disposal to drive customer technology adoption and success with data-driven insights.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Claudio Muruzabal is chief business officer at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>topic/data-analytics</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Eastman Energizes HR Reporting to Deliver One-Stop Insights to Leaders]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/eastman-hr-reporting-deliver-insights-to-leaders</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/eastman-hr-reporting-deliver-insights-to-leaders</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Eastman accelerated HR reporting for improved efficiency and insights using story reports in SAP SuccessFactors People Analytics. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>topic/data-analytics</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-preferred-success</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-employee-central</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-people-analytics</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-recruiting</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[What is a data fabric?]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/what-is-data-fabric</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/what-is-data-fabric</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn how data fabric architecture can help you connect and manage all your data in real time, across different systems and applications.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/business-transformation</category>
            <category>topic/data-analytics</category>
            <category>content-type/what-is</category>
            <category>stage/acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Esports: Team Liquid’s Masters of Data]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/esports-team-liquid-masters-of-data</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/esports-team-liquid-masters-of-data</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP solutions help Team Liquid succeed at the Dota 2 and League of Legends World Championships. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15daec53a13fbbf487bab50b2abd4b35529f13efe.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15daec53a13fbbf487bab50b2abd4b35529f13efe.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_15daec53a13fbbf487bab50b2abd4b35529f13efe.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Esports: Team Liquid’s Masters of Data" src="./media_15daec53a13fbbf487bab50b2abd4b35529f13efe.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="esports-team-liquids-masters-of-data">Esports: Team Liquid’s Masters of Data</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>This October and November, gaming fans around the globe can enjoy two of the most prestigious and exciting <a href="/topics/esports">esports</a> tournaments: The League of Legends World Championship – also known as Worlds – in South Korea and The International, the annual Dota 2 World Championship in Seattle, Washington.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>It’s a special thrill for Team Liquid fans, as both teams – the Dota 2 and the League of Legends squad – have qualified for the championships and will compete for the title. We tapped into our connection with Team Liquid and had the exclusive opportunity to talk to two team members, <strong>Haitham “Haitham” Algbory, head analyst of the League of Legends team</strong>, and <strong>Mathis “Jabbz” Friesel, assistant coach and analyst of the Dota team</strong>, about how they prepare the teams for the world championships and what role SAP technology plays for the teams to perform at their top level.</p>
  <h2 id="about-sap-and-team-liquid">About SAP and Team Liquid</h2>
  <p>With SAP being the official innovation partner of Team Liquid, the two companies developed a close partnership of co-innovation focused on Team Liquid’s Dota 2 and League of Legends teams. These two multiplayer online battle arena games are highly complex and data-intensive esports. Together with Team Liquid, SAP is co-developing software to help Team Liquid analyze its performance and apply more precision in areas like match preparation, team and player performance, scouting, and others. Read more <a href="https://www.sap.com/asset/dynamic/2023/07/c4e4d3c9-807e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">here</a>.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_146ad53e5c6d85798326e3514162a214869983c15.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_146ad53e5c6d85798326e3514162a214869983c15.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_146ad53e5c6d85798326e3514162a214869983c15.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_146ad53e5c6d85798326e3514162a214869983c15.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="400" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em><a href="https://twitter.com/tbHaitham">Haitham “Haitham” Algbory</a>, head of Analytics &#x26; Data for Team Liquid’s League of Legends Team</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>A big part of what SAP brings to Team Liquid is <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/hana.html">SAP HANA Cloud</a>, which helps make data analysis for both League of Legends and Dota a lot easier. The database allows the analysts to focus less on gathering data and more on analyzing it. Both Jabbz and Haitham have been working in this field for a long time, and there are things that they can do now that they never could before, thanks to a tool specifically made for esports data analysis.</p>
  <p>“I support both the general manager and the coaching staff with scouting new talent,” Haitham said. “The way I do that is by providing periodic solo queue and scrim reports and end-of-season scouting reports. When it comes to the Academy teams of the East Regions, at the same time, we just track the players that are in the scene in general and we see their improvement based off the metrics that we have set in our tools.”</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1fc0e7e2f4de3f3ba1c19914ddcfb1f5a969cb35f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1fc0e7e2f4de3f3ba1c19914ddcfb1f5a969cb35f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1fc0e7e2f4de3f3ba1c19914ddcfb1f5a969cb35f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_1fc0e7e2f4de3f3ba1c19914ddcfb1f5a969cb35f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="200" height="280">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em><a href="https://twitter.com/jabbz1301">Mathis “Jabbz” Friesel</a>, coach and head analyst for Team Liquid’s Dota 2 Team</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>On the League of Legends side, SAP HANA Cloud is Haitham’s primary tool for scouting. But that’s not what Jabbz uses the data for. For Team Liquid Dota, the data is more match-focused.</p>
  <p>“For us, SAP HANA Cloud has more of a different function,” Jabbz said. “We use it mostly for performance-related things. I think the big advantage we have with the database is that we can actually import any public game that we want. Let’s say things have changed in a recent patch; we can make sure that we’re always up-to-date with how the meta is evolving. We also get to have a replay of every tournament game, so we can pick up all the information we need from any game, especially during live events. This is incredibly helpful. By having this tool available, you can quickly see how teams are adapting, how teams are thinking. I save a lot of time getting that information, whereas before I would have to open up the replays in the game and manually scroll through everything.”</p>
  <p>According to Haitham, being able to use real gameplay clips to corroborate the data – and vice versa – often helps build a stronger case for whatever argument he’s trying to make. Players are more inclined to believe the data once they have a reference point, which then allows them to gain a deeper understanding of the game.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="team-liquid-mining-rich-esports-data-to-help-players-managers-and-teams-compete-and-win">Team Liquid: Mining rich esports data to help players, managers, and teams compete and win</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/asset/dynamic/2023/07/c4e4d3c9-807e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“With SAP, we have a lot of good [visualization] tools,” Haitham said. “We have an entire map tool that will just visualize where the wards are and what the movement is looking like. In addition, we have SAP Analytics Cloud that gives us an opportunity to build charts and graphs for the players. I would use videos or clips that are important to show the opponent’s style, and then I support that with the maps or graphs from the SAP tools.”</p>
  <p>For some, all these details might sound small, even insignificant. However, any coach or analyst will tell you that at the highest level of esports, the difference lies in the details. When pretty much every player is equal in skill, it’s those minor advantages that matter – which makes data analysis an important factor for success. After all, a close win is still a win. Both Haitham and Jabbz point to “the small margins” as the reasons why they love their roles as analysts.</p>
  <p>“Personally, I work on my own goal to help others achieve theirs at the same time,” Haitham said. “Seeing how players are able to use science while playing video games, to beat opponents that they may not be able to without that kind of information…it just makes everything worthwhile.”</p>
  <p>“I agree. I think it’s always very satisfying to give information to the guys that they wouldn’t pick up on,” Jabbz added. “I guess we’re very similar in that regard. I also enjoy helping the guys and that’s what gives me the joy in this job. I don’t necessarily have to see myself in the limelight or at the front of the stage, but I really just like seeing my friends succeed.”</p>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18e500dd487b8be270a967b15b532213f90828dbe.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18e500dd487b8be270a967b15b532213f90828dbe.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_18e500dd487b8be270a967b15b532213f90828dbe.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Team Liquid: Masters of Data" src="./media_18e500dd487b8be270a967b15b532213f90828dbe.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://youtu.be/5BZYCILkR6o">Team Liquid: Masters of Data</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>Isabelle Schuhmacher is director of Global Sponsorships at SAP.<br>Christian Kreidt is storytelling lead for Global Sponsorships at SAP.</p>
        <p>Photos courtesy of Team Liquid.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-sap-news-delivered-right-to-your-inbox">Get the latest SAP news delivered right to your inbox</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/nl/sap-news-center-newsletter/index.html">Sign up</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/data-analytics</category>
            <category>news-tag/database-and-data-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/esports</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-hana-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-sponsorships</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The NHL Uses Technology to Pave the Way for Greener Sports]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/nhl-sustainability-technology-greener-sports</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/nhl-sustainability-technology-greener-sports</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The NHL is a sustainability pioneer in the sports industry. Learn how SAP technology helps to understand and manage its carbon footprint.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-emissions</category>
            <category>topic/data-analytics</category>
            <category>news-tag/nhl</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Data and Analytics Solutions Earn Multiple 2023 Best Of Awards from TrustRadius]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/06/sap-data-and-analytics-solutions-trustradius-awards</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/06/sap-data-and-analytics-solutions-trustradius-awards</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP data and analytics solutions have won multiple Best Of awards from TrustRadius, recognizing our excellence in the industry. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/data-analytics</category>
            <category>news-tag/database-and-data-management</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-datasphere</category>
            <category>product/sap-hana-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/trustradius</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Digital Twins at Work: 8 Examples]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/digital-twins-at-work</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/digital-twins-at-work</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Eight examples of organizations using digital twins to simulate factories, water systems, entire urban areas and more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/business-transformation</category>
            <category>topic/data-analytics</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>content-type/what-is</category>
            <category>stage/acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Harrods’ High-Tech Backend Helps Deliver Unparalleled Experience]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/harrods-high-tech-backend-deliver-unparalleled-experience</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/harrods-high-tech-backend-deliver-unparalleled-experience</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Luxury retailer Harrods invested in an analytics initiative to help better understand how its customers interact with the brand.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>topic/data-analytics</category>
            <category>news-tag/nrf</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
            <category>product/sap-customer-data-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-marketing-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-service-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Using Weather Analytics to Reduce Food Waste]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/planalytics-weather-analytics-reduce-food-waste</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/planalytics-weather-analytics-reduce-food-waste</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Integrating weather as a demand signal, like with Planalytics, enables businesses to use analytics to drive measurable, repeatable benefits.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-footprint</category>
            <category>topic/data-analytics</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The National Hockey League Is Changing the Game with Next-Level Data Insights]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/nhl-changing-the-game-next-level-data-insights</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/nhl-changing-the-game-next-level-data-insights</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The National Hockey League (NHL) is using data to reinvigorate the sports league’s position in the global marketplace. Read to learn how!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>topic/data-analytics</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>industry/sports-entertainment</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Three Key Highlights from the Gartner Data & Analytics Summit 2023]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/three-key-highlights-gartner-data-analytics-summit</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/three-key-highlights-gartner-data-analytics-summit</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[At the Gartner Data & Analytics Summit attendees explored recent data and analytics trends, technologies, and strategies, like SAP Datasphere.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/data-analytics</category>
            <category>news-tag/data-fabric</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-datasphere</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Data and Analytics Solutions Win Multiple TrustRadius Winter 2023 "Best Of" Awards]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/winter-2023-trustradius-awards-sap-data-and-analytics-solutions</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/winter-2023-trustradius-awards-sap-data-and-analytics-solutions</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP data and analytics solutions have been recognized with multiple Winter 2023 TrustRadius Best Of awards. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/data-analytics</category>
            <category>news-tag/database-and-data-management</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-data-intelligence-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-hana-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-master-data-governance</category>
            <category>news-tag/trustradius</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Three Reasons You Need the Right Platform Strategy]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/01/right-platform-strategy-three-reasons</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/01/right-platform-strategy-three-reasons</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[An effective platform strategy supports a more resilient business. Learn three reasons why and how SAP BTP can help.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/data-analytics</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Milliken & Company Transforms HR in the Cloud]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/01/milliken-company-transforms-hr-cloud</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/01/milliken-company-transforms-hr-cloud</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Milliken & Company leveraged cloud HR solutions to create a sustainable workforce. Read to learn more about its transformation.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>topic/data-analytics</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-employee-central</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-recruiting</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Named a Leader in Delivering Translytical Data Platforms in Forrester Wave Evaluation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/translytical-data-platforms-forrester-wave-sap-a-leader</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/translytical-data-platforms-forrester-wave-sap-a-leader</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is a leader in The Forrester Wave: Translytical Data Platforms 2022 for the product vision and planned enhancements criteria.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/data-analytics</category>
            <category>news-tag/database-and-data-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/forrester</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Smart Meters Expand Sustainable Horizon of Smart Cities]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/american-water-smart-meters-sustainable-horizon</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/american-water-smart-meters-sustainable-horizon</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Utilities like American Water crunch intelligent data to meet sustainability objectives and build trusted relationships with customers.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/data-analytics</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>industry/utilities</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Future of Analytics: How to Make Sense of Data and Mitigate Business-Critical Risks]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/future-of-analytics-make-sense-of-data-mitigate-risks</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/future-of-analytics-make-sense-of-data-mitigate-risks</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[At SAP, we want to help our customers navigate the data jungle and move into the future of analytics. Learn more about how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/data-analytics</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-innovation-center-network</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Data and Analytics Solutions Earn Multiple 2022 Top Rated and Best of Awards from TrustRadius]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/sap-data-and-analytics-solutions-2022-trustradius-awards</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/sap-data-and-analytics-solutions-2022-trustradius-awards</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP data and analytics solutions have been recognized by TrustRadius with multiple wins in both the Top Rated and Best of Award categories.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/data-analytics</category>
            <category>news-tag/database-and-data-management</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-data-intelligence</category>
            <category>product/sap-hana-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-master-data-governance</category>
            <category>news-tag/trustradius</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Hosts Its First-Ever Esports Tournament]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/sap-hosts-its-first-ever-esports-tournament</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/sap-hosts-its-first-ever-esports-tournament</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP recently hosted its first esports tournament in Berlin. Learn more about how SAP provides in-game, real-time analytics tools to players.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/data-analytics</category>
            <category>news-tag/esports</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-labs-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-sponsorships</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[For High-Tech Supply Chains, CO2 Emission Tracking Is Sustainable Business Currency]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/high-tech-supply-chains-co2-emission-tracking</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/high-tech-supply-chains-co2-emission-tracking</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[High-tech industry leaders are making sustainability a core commitment, and it is transforming business models to address climate change.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-footprint</category>
            <category>news-tag/circular-economy</category>
            <category>topic/data-analytics</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>industry/high-tech</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/net-zero</category>
            <category>product/sap-product-footprint-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Continuous Intelligence: Definition, Benefits, and Examples]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/continuous-intelligence-definition-benefits-examples</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/continuous-intelligence-definition-benefits-examples</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Continuous Intelligence, or continuously monitoring business data for anomalies, can help brands make smart, real-time business decisions.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>topic/data-analytics</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-innovation-center-network</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Morocco’s Ministry of Health Saved Thousands of Lives Overnight]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/04/morocco-ministry-of-health-saved-thousands-overnight</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/04/morocco-ministry-of-health-saved-thousands-overnight</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[To protect its citizens, Morocco’s Ministry of Health developed a COVID-19 Real-Time Monitoring system with SAP Analytics Cloud. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/covid-19</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>topic/data-analytics</category>
            <category>industry/healthcare</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>sap-award/sap-innovation-awards</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How HR Professionals Can Get Past Data Overload and Analysis Paralysis]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/03/hr-professionals-get-past-data-overload-and-analysis-paralysis</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/03/hr-professionals-get-past-data-overload-and-analysis-paralysis</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The best decisions are made when you look at the right data at the right time and analyze it with the right tools. HR data is no exception.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/data-analytics</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-workforce-analytics</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Solving Diversity Problems: One Dream and A Lot of Data]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/01/solving-diversity-problems-dream-data</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/01/solving-diversity-problems-dream-data</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn how people analytics, like SAP SuccessFactors solutions, can help HR to solve diversity problems through a data-driven HR culture.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1381148cc7bc7bd04a2ac63a702d499a37236c656.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1381148cc7bc7bd04a2ac63a702d499a37236c656.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1381148cc7bc7bd04a2ac63a702d499a37236c656.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Solving Diversity Problems: One Dream and A Lot of Data" src="./media_1381148cc7bc7bd04a2ac63a702d499a37236c656.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="solving-diversity-problems-one-dream-and-a-lot-of-data">Solving Diversity Problems: One Dream and A Lot of Data</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>On the third Monday of January each year, Martin Luther King Jr.’s birthday is honored in the U.S. King was an American Baptist minister and activist in the American civil rights movement. At the age of 35, he was the youngest man to have received the Nobel Peace Prize.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>For many, Martin Luther King Jr.’s name is synonymous with his dream of a United States void of segregation and racism. And while his dream has been recognized globally, there is still much work to do to realize it.</p>
  <p>I recently sat down with <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/nigeldias/">Nigel Dias</a> to discuss how people analytics can support organizations’ diversity, equity, and inclusion (DE&#x26;I) strategy. Dias is the managing director of <a href="https://www.3nstrategy.com/">3n Strategy</a> as well as the chair and founder of the <a href="https://www.hranalyticsthinktank.com/">HR Analytics ThinkTank research</a>. He specializes in supporting businesses to make better HR decisions using people analytics and enabling data-driven HR culture.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="drive-performance-and-results-with-data-driven-insights-across-all-your-hr-processes-in-the-cloud">Drive performance and results with data-driven insights across all your HR processes in the cloud</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm/workforce-planning-hr-analytics.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="q-how-does-people-analytics-help-hr-to-solve-diversity-problems">Q: How does people analytics help <a href="/topics/human-resources">HR</a> to solve diversity problems?</h2>
  <p><strong>A:</strong> What areas of your business have the lowest levels of diversity and inclusion, and how bad is the imbalance? Over the years, which HR decisions have caused and added to that inequality? Do different types of employees get promoted differently? Rewarded differently? Hired and retained faster or slower? If you do not change anything, how much worse will the inequality get? If you want to reduce inequality within five years, what HR strategies are most likely to achieve that goal?</p>
  <p>With or without data, organizations are making decisions to try to become fairer and more equal. The purpose of people analytics is to enable organizations to make better people decisions; in this case, about achieving diversity goals and solving inequality. By using HR data to answer questions, people analytics helps organizations to make better decisions increasing the likelihood of achieving diversity outcomes across the entire employee experience.</p>
  <h2 id="what-types-of-diversity-questions-are-sap-successfactors-customers-answering-using-their-data">What types of diversity questions are SAP SuccessFactors customers answering using their data?</h2>
  <p>In the 2020 Benchmarking study by the HR Analytics ThinkTank, <a href="https://www.hranalyticsthinktank.com/news-and-updates/hr-analytics-thinktank-benchmark-2020-release-r30/">93% of people analytics functions said they were actively working with diversity data</a>, which is no surprise given DE&#x26;I is a priority for most organizations.</p>
  <p>These people analytics functions are empowering their HR leaders to solve diversity problems by supplementing HR expertise with answers gleaned directly from data. From day one, people analytics teams can answer descriptive questions, providing facts about what happened in the past and over time. For example, within a particular job family or location, a specific minority group was three times more likely to be promoted than another. Other functions may go one step further, answering questions that diagnose a problem and use data to answer why an outcome has occurred in the past. For example, they might be able to answer why minority groups are more like to resign in particular locations.</p>
  <p>The more advanced functions, which research shows take two to three years to build, will create even more value. Some will be asked to spend more time answering critical questions, predicting how the gender equity gap will increase if nothing changes. The most advanced will provide answers to questions by prescribing what should be done; for example, what strategies are most likely to achieve 25% ethnic minority representation at board level within six years.</p>
  <h2 id="how-are-sap-successfactors-customers-using-workforce-analytics-and-report-stories-to-tackle-diversity-problems">How are SAP SuccessFactors customers using Workforce Analytics and Report Stories to tackle diversity problems?</h2>
  <p>The SAP SuccessFactors People Analytics solutions has the functionality to support organizations to tackle their diversity issues.</p>
  <p>In order to support strategic decision-making, they use SAP SuccessFactors Workforce Analytics to transform HR data into metrics and dashboards, showing end users the answers to questions about what has happened in the past, displaying insights and trends over time. For example, where is minority representation worsening? In particular grades, job families or geographies is there a difference in the way in which different workers are promoted or hired? Using SAP SuccessFactors Workforce Analytics, HR leaders can create better strategies and track progress over time.</p>
  <p>Using report stories, SAP SuccessFactors software can provide anyone in the entire business with a snapshot view of their business area. Stories will allow end users to check an answer at any given moment; for example, whether their recruitment pipeline contains a diverse selection of candidates or if all the resignations in the last month have been women.</p>
  <h2 id="what-steps-can-sap-successfactors-customers-take-to-prepare-for-diversity-analytics">What steps can SAP SuccessFactors customers take to prepare for diversity analytics?</h2>
  <p>The first thing that organizations should do is confirm the objectives that leaders are trying to achieve and identify the questions they need answered to make better choices. In our 2020 study, 94% of SAP SuccessFactors People Analytics leaders said their function was directly sponsored by an HR executive but only 32% were positive that they knew what their leader’s goals were. HR leaders need to clearly articulate what their diversity goals are and establish what questions they would like answered by the people analytics team.</p>
  <p>The second thing they should do is audit the foundations for data-driven HR success and prepare for the journey. According to the same study, only 42% of SAP SuccessFactors customers had a plan for what data to capture, only 16% were sure they knew how the people analytics team should be structured, and only six percent were confident that decision-makers understood how to use their insights in decision-making. A lot of diversity questions can be answered on day one using standard SAP SuccessFactors data, but a plan will be required to provide more complex answers over time.</p>
  <p>The final tip is to provide answers with evidence to help ensure that decision-makers are empowered to actually use the insight. If given the option, most HR and business professionals will welcome evidence that helps them achieve their goals, but they will only use the evidence if it is easy to access and formatted in a way that makes it easy to use in the context of their job. The organizations most successful with data-driven HR make sure that decision-makers are enabled with the right skills, and their dashboards create the best experience for users to find the answers they are looking for.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>To hear more on this topic, <a href="https://gateway.on24.com/wcc/eh/1892128/lp/3582695/jan-2022-solving-diversity-problems-using-your-successfactors-data">register</a> for the upcoming webinar (or listen to the recording), “<a href="https://gateway.on24.com/wcc/eh/1892128/lp/3582695/jan-2022-solving-diversity-problems-using-your-successfactors-data">Solving Diversity Problems using Your SAP SuccessFactors Data</a>” on January 26, or visit <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm/workforce-planning-hr-analytics.html">the HR Analytics and Workforce Planning area of sap.com</a>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/data-analytics</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-people-analytics</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-workforce-analytics</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Life Sciences Industry Digitalizes for People-Centric Clinical Drug Trials]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/life-sciences-symetric-people-centric-clinical-drug-trials</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/life-sciences-symetric-people-centric-clinical-drug-trials</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SyMetric is on a mission to modernize the life sciences industry with its cloud-based analytics solution that runs on SAP BTP. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_19d2ed00090b302d73eb56a097086aa86088d546f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_19d2ed00090b302d73eb56a097086aa86088d546f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_19d2ed00090b302d73eb56a097086aa86088d546f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Life Sciences Industry Digitalizes for People-Centric Clinical Drug Trials" src="./media_19d2ed00090b302d73eb56a097086aa86088d546f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="life-sciences-industry-digitalizes-for-people-centric-clinical-drug-trials">Life Sciences Industry Digitalizes for People-Centric Clinical Drug Trials</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>After the earliest clinical trials in India for <a href="/covid-19">COVID-19</a> plasma therapy went live using <a href="https://www.symetricsystems.com/">SyMetric’s</a> cloud-based analytics solution, the startup hasn’t looked back. With 10 completed COVID-19 studies behind them, SyMetric is on a mission to modernize the <a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/life-sciences.html">life sciences industry</a>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“We are providing a holistic solution for clinical trials management, what we call ERP for clinical research,” said Uma Janapareddy, founder and managing director at SyMetric. “Having easily accessible data on one unified platform helps researchers develop more effective drugs with stronger study results so they can bring pioneering medicines faster to people.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="build-a-strong-digital-platform-with-sap-business-technology-platform">Build a strong digital platform with SAP Business Technology Platform</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="people-driven-clinical-trials">People-Driven Clinical Trials</h2>
  <p>Physicians, researchers, project managers, investigators, and biostatisticians are using SyMetric Trial Analytics to conduct studies at global pharmaceutical companies and clinical research organizations in a variety of therapeutic areas such as neurology, respiratory illness, oncology, and dermatology.</p>
  <p>Running on <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">SAP Business Technology Platform</a>, the solution captures and analyzes historical and updated clinical trial data in one system. This includes patient information indicating initial eligibility to participate in a clinical trial and progress monitoring through rigorous statistical analyses at trial completion for regulatory submission. The tool captures and analyzes electronic data from anywhere, such as a patient’s activities tracked on a mobile device or artificial intelligence (AI)-based imaging that shows medical progress.</p>
  <p>“If you’re starting a lung cancer study, you can easily find out disease prevalence rates and research histories by geography, experience of the investigators, availability of skilled coordinators or pharmacists, and other factors. Our solution brings this data together for informed planning that leads to more efficient execution,” said Janapareddy. “Once the trial is underway, our easy-to-use solutions help researchers accurately track patient recruitment, study progress, make necessary amendments to the clinical study on the fly, and conduct any other activities.”</p>
  <h2 id="time-saving-clinical-data-analytics">Time-Saving Clinical Data Analytics</h2>
  <p>According to Janapareddy, the solution gives clinicians cost-savings foresight and flexibility. Built-in algorithms automatically monitor data, for example, rejecting potential patients who don’t fit certain parameters based on gender, age, or certain health and lifestyle conditions. Real-time data saves time in data clean up at the project completion stage.</p>
  <p>Customers have reduced clinical trial setup and completion timelines by 20%. Some have saved up to 30% wastage of drug supplies during the trial manufacturing phase. One customer saved thousands of dollars using the solution to calculate the number of patient volunteers, as well as the number of drugs and testing kits required to meet randomization objectives with greater precision.</p>
  <p>“With real-time data and built-in algorithms, companies can quickly adapt protocols in response to continuous patient recruitment,” she said. “Researchers can conduct interim analyses at any time before study completion, adjusting drug dosages, delivery mechanisms, and packaging quantities. The system automatically incorporates protocol adjustments and amendments, sans any downtime and without jeopardizing overall study timelines.”</p>
  <h2 id="working-with-sap-labs-india">Working with SAP Labs India</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="the-amazing-inclusion-story-behind-indias-digital-transformation">The Amazing Inclusion Story Behind India’s Digital Transformation</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/05/code-unnati-inclusion-story-india-digital-transformation">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>While most of SyMetric’s customers are based in the United States and India, Janapareddy has set her sights on Europe, inspired by the strength of SAP’s innovation ecosystem. An alumni of SAP Startup Studio at <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/labs-india.html">SAP Labs India</a>, Janapareddy appreciated the design thinking workshops her team used to develop use cases from their collective experiences. She also valued the co-innovation relationships her startup has forged with other members of the program. These include biopharmaceutical companies, medical device manufacturers, and cosmeceutical and nutraceutical manufacturers.</p>
  <p>“We have a shared passion with SAP for the power of life sciences and integrated enterprise resource planning (ERP) data on a single platform – where every company becomes an <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/intelligent-enterprise.html">intelligent enterprise</a>,” said Janapareddy. “SAP is a global leader in life sciences including pharmaceuticals, manufacturing, and ERP, and its leaders generously share their expertise with us. We also appreciate the significant exposure to SAP customers from this partnership.”</p>
  <p>SyMetric Trial Analytics and the SyMetric Clinical Trial Platform are available on <a href="https://store.sap.com/dcp/en/industries/try-and-buy-life-sciences-apps-and-software">SAP Store</a>.</p>
  <h2 id="connected-clinical-trial-supply-chain">Connected Clinical Trial Supply Chain</h2>
  <p>Before she founded SyMetric, Janapareddy held leadership positions at an international non-profit organization that provided funding, education, and other opportunities for underprivileged women. She developed the concept for SyMetric with input from her family and friends at SAP and in the life sciences industry.</p>
  <p>“I wanted to do something big in life, contributing to the community in a way that would have lasting impact,” she said. “There was no integrated system for clinical trials anywhere in the life science industry, so I founded SyMetric to help manage the entire supply chain for people-centric research.”</p>
  <h2 id="from-data-centric-to-patient-centric-trials">From Data-Centric to Patient-Centric Trials</h2>
  <p>Janapareddy envisioned a fully interconnected data platform for everyone involved in life sciences clinical research and manufacturing.</p>
  <p>“The industry is looking ahead to patient-centricity, where people can control their data using the latest technologies to share information and act on it on secure, compliant cloud-based platforms,” she said. “It began with informed consent and now connected data brings researchers and patients even closer together.”</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Follow me @smgaler</em><br><em><a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2021/06/30/life-sciences-industry-digitalizes-for-people-centric-clinical-drug-trials/?sh=12cc7beb55bc">This blog also appeared on SAP BrandVoice on Forbes</a>.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/covid-19</category>
            <category>topic/data-analytics</category>
            <category>industry/life-sciences</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-labs-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-store</category>
            <category>news-tag/startups</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Five Ways to Make the Most of Your Data]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/five-ways-to-make-the-most-of-your-data</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/five-ways-to-make-the-most-of-your-data</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Data is no longer a byproduct of business; it is at the heart of digital businesses. Read to learn how to derive value from your data.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b289ee5de80da992711d931f6888981d72b5f6dd.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b289ee5de80da992711d931f6888981d72b5f6dd.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1b289ee5de80da992711d931f6888981d72b5f6dd.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Five Ways to Make the Most of Your Data" src="./media_1b289ee5de80da992711d931f6888981d72b5f6dd.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="five-ways-to-make-the-most-of-your-data">Five Ways to Make the Most of Your Data</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>It used to be that companies viewed data as a byproduct of their business. Companies knew it had value but didn’t know how to properly utilize it.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>But as economies have digitized, business leaders now recognize that data is at the heart of digital businesses. It fuels differentiation, strategy, rapid innovation, and other important elements of running a successful business. Moreover, truly data-driven companies tend to generate 8% to 10% more profit and are 23 times more likely to acquire new customers – which fuels significantly higher market valuation – compared to their peers.</p>
  <p>In the meantime, organizations struggle to unite and access real-time data. Companies generate a lot of data, and while they have good intentions to use that data, it’s stuck in siloes. That makes it hard to leverage data to optimize business processes across the organization. According to research firm, <a href="https://go.forrester.com/blogs/hadoop-is-datas-darling-for-a-reason/">Forrester</a>, “Between 60% and 73% of all data within an enterprise goes unused for analytics.”</p>
  <p>Below are some suggestions for customers embarking on an enterprise data strategy that will help bring data of all kinds together, allowing companies to turn data into business value.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="register-for-the-sap-data-and-analytics-virtual-forum">Register for the SAP Data and Analytics Virtual Forum</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://events.sap.com/sap-data--and-analytics-virtual-forum-accelerating-outcomes/en/home">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="leave-your-data-where-it-is">Leave Your Data Where It Is</h2>
  <p>Too often companies try to centralize data via a large, top-down project where data from across the organization must be brought into a central repository. The problem with this approach: by the time you bring together data from across different parts of an organization into one place, it’s outdated.</p>
  <p>People need to shift their mindset to connecting – rather than collecting – data. When you consider your data strategy, prioritize a digital business platform that can automatically pull data from wherever it resides – whether that’s your supply chain or finance teams’ applications or somewhere else. Doing that helps ensure your employees can work with real-time information from across the company.</p>
  <h2 id="make-sure-you-can-handle-all-data-types">Make Sure You Can Handle All Data Types</h2>
  <p>Organizations generate all kinds of data – structured, unstructured, relational, and geospatial, to name a few. Too often organizations approach each type of data differently and separately, which replicates the problem of unconnected data that doesn’t come together in one holistic picture.</p>
  <p>Select a platform with data capabilities that can analyze and knit together these different types into a unified whole. Businesses need a modern platform that treats data as multimodal and multidimensional. By looking at the multiple facets of data, business leaders can make new correlations that help to make better decisions while accurately anticipating future opportunities and threats.</p>
  <h2 id="harness-data-to-drive-automation">Harness Data to Drive Automation</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-business-technology-platform-the-platform-for-the-intelligent-enterprise">SAP Business Technology Platform: The platform for the Intelligent Enterprise</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The real power of data kicks in when you can use it to drive automation and machine-augmented decision-making. There’s no reason to maintain so many manual processes, like invoice reconciliation or handling basic customer complaints in call centers. If you can harness data appropriately, many types of tasks can be automated – freeing employees to do more strategic work.</p>
  <p>Automation also augments employees’ on-the-spot decision-making capabilities. For example, a consumer packaged goods company could use data from cameras and machines to help a quality control manager determine whether to approve a certain batch of products. <a href="https://insights.sap.com/what-is-machine-learning/">Machine learning</a> can process varied pieces of information, such as the Internet of Things (IoT) data or bill-of-material changes, faster than a human, providing an extra level of support on the front lines.</p>
  <p>To advance automation, you need a platform that allows you to embed machine learning and artificial intelligence (AI) into your business applications – and one that can handle varied data sources in real-time.</p>
  <h2 id="democratize-data">Democratize Data</h2>
  <p>While data used to be the preserve of elite analysts and data scientists, now it’s a priority to democratize data. Information needs to be easily accessed not just by executives but by people on the front lines so they can use it to make decisions. Enabling self-service access to data also reduces the time IT departments spend on manual work, like running reports.</p>
  <p>Your platform must make it easy for everyone to access and analyze data, so be sure to evaluate the usability of your data management solutions. Ask questions such as: Is it user-friendly and intuitive? What kind of training is involved to empower people with self-service analytics tools?</p>
  <h2 id="protect-your-data">Protect Your Data</h2>
  <p>Related to access is the importance of security. One of the hallmarks of digital business is the ability to seamlessly connect across your organization but also externally to your customers, partners, and suppliers. But this is fraught with risk – especially in this day and age of ransomware.</p>
  <p>Your data platform must take into account any areas of exposure or vulnerability and build in the right security, access controls, and governance to protect your data – and information shared across your network.</p>
  <p>Finally, remember how you use your data will make the difference between success and failure in the next decade. It’s the foundation of digital transformation and will help launch new digital business models that go beyond automation – and truly redefine how companies operate and differentiate themselves. <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">SAP Business Technology Platform</a> provides a platform with database and data management, analytics, and intelligent technology – like embedded AI – solutions that customers around the world are already using.</p>
  <p>So choose wisely. Because with the right platform, your company will be poised for success now and in the future.</p>
  <p>To learn more about this topic, attend the “SAP Data and Analytics Forum: Accelerating Outcomes,” which will be held virtually from September 14 to October 7. <a href="https://events.sap.com/sap-data--and-analytics-virtual-forum-accelerating-outcomes/en/home">Find more information and register for the event</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Raghu Ramanathan is chief revenue officer for Platform and Technologies at SAP.</em><br><em><a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2021/07/28/five-ways-to-make-the-most-of-your-data/?sh=4d86bd7ddb44">This article also appeared on SAP BrandVoice on Forbes.</a></em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/automation</category>
            <category>topic/data-analytics</category>
            <category>news-tag/database-and-data-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/internet-of-things</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Data-Use Lessons from Smart Cities]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/data-use-lessons-smart-cities</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/data-use-lessons-smart-cities</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Business leaders can learn from municipal leaders on how to use data dashboards to gain new, valuable benefits. Learn more about smart cities.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_123768eb534a77c78a05d46612dadeebd7a4e04d6.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_123768eb534a77c78a05d46612dadeebd7a4e04d6.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_123768eb534a77c78a05d46612dadeebd7a4e04d6.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="blur people and traffic on a street at night" src="./media_123768eb534a77c78a05d46612dadeebd7a4e04d6.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1044">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="data-use-lessons-from-smart-cities">Data-Use Lessons from Smart Cities</h1>
        <p>Collaborating with stakeholders and adopting agile project development are among the approaches the elevate public services.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In the United States during the COVID-19 pandemic, there were <a href="https://www.bostonglobe.com/2021/04/09/metro/they-came-vermont-pandemic-retreat-now-some-are-putting-down-roots/">numerous</a> <a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/this-is-how-life-changes-when-you-move-from-the-city-to-the-country-2019-04-02">reports</a> of urbanites moving to the <a href="https://www.weforum.org/agenda/2021/01/rural-life-cities-countryside-covid-coronavirus-united-states-us-usa-america/">country</a>. The reason was straightforward: Fewer neighbors made social distancing and, by extension, healthy living easier. Many people also learned that they could work from anywhere because their jobs did not require commuting to an office.</p>
  <p>But the truth is that <a href="/research/creating-the-cities-of-the-future">cities</a> were never going away. More than half of the world’s people – about 55% – live in urban centers, and this majority is expected to reach close to <a href="https://news.un.org/en/story/2020/10/1076532">70% by 2050</a>, according to the United Nations. Even during the pandemic, cities demonstrated their vitality by providing critical services at a time when officials raced to address both a healthcare crisis and resource constraints.</p>
  <p>Cities remain economic engines, even as people in many regions have shifted to <a href="/resources/remote-work-new-normal">at-home</a> and then <a href="/resources/tailoring-post-pandemic-work-environment-to-employee-strengths-personality">hybrid work</a> arrangements. Indeed, cities still provide critical infrastructure for business, says Anders Lisdorf, a Copenhagen-based consultant and author of <a href="https://www.amazon.com/Demystifying-Smart-Cities-Perspectives-Technologies-ebook/dp/B082KJ1HJX/ref=sr_1_2?dchild=1&#x26;keywords=anders+lisdorf&#x26;qid=1622571983&#x26;s=books&#x26;sr=1-2">Demystifying Smart Cities: Practical Perspectives on How Cities Can Leverage The Potential of New Technologies</a>.</p>
  <p>“The city is and will continue to be the space where the vast majority of business will be done,” says Lisdorf. “Cities will provide the backdrop for future business. Understanding where smart cities are going impacts the future of most businesses.”</p>
  <p>This article highlights the work of three regional governments – Newcastle upon Tyne, UK; Heidelberg, Germany; and Chattanooga, Tennessee – to illustrate the ways in which government, academic, and business collaborations have used data to serve the needs of their constituencies on a shoestring while managing multiple stakeholders. They are role models for business leaders who are looking to do more with – and get more out of – their data. They offer lessons, including how combining existing and new data sources can derive fresh sources of value, how the use of sensor data can predict demand for services, how harvesting and analyzing location data can isolate safety hazards and mitigate public safety risks – and how data that is properly prepared for sharing and analysis can make for an ever-growing set of valuable applications.</p>
  <h2 id="understanding-quality-of-life-measures-with-real-time-data">Understanding quality-of-life measures with real-time data</h2>
  <p><strong>The project:</strong> Newcastle upon Tyne, a city of 268,000 in the UK, developed an urban data <a href="https://covid.view.urbanobservatory.ac.uk/#intro">dashboard</a> powered by advanced analytics that helps city officials and residents understand metrics that affect residents’ health and safety, including compliance with social distancing measures.</p>
  <p><strong>Major benefits:</strong> The dashboard provides an accurate assessment of the population’s performance on COVID-19 safety measures along with a host of other measures, including vehicle and pedestrian movement, air quality, and wind speed measures in real time.</p>
  <p>During the pandemic, it was crucial for cities to understand how well their citizens were complying with safety guidelines such as social distancing. But other than conventional observation, for example, reviewing CCTV footage, it was difficult to systematically gauge compliance levels. The city of Newcastle upon Tyne completed a pilot project to test if it could do just that, working with Newcastle University to provide <a href="https://urbanobservatory.ac.uk/">an online data portal</a> that shows pedestrian congestion in the city center, among other highlights.</p>
  <p>Using a traffic light indicator system with red, green, and yellow lights, the Newcastle Urban Observatory uses advanced analytics to measure pedestrian density and to determine the pedestrians’ proximity to each other. The system strips out personally identifiable details, anonymously identifying people who maintain safe distances while flagging (in red) instances where social distancing measures are violated. During the height of the pandemic, the project team hypothesized that this insight could help public officials make evidence-based decisions, such as understanding what messages would best promote public health.</p>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div data-valign="middle">We can imagine a city where we manage traffic flows or charges for private vehicles based on things like air quality. You can start to tie those things together.</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div data-valign="middle">Phil James, director of the National Urban Observatory Facility, Newcastle upon Tyne, UK</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Funded by several research grants from Newcastle University and in partnership with the City Council, the Urban Observatory, which is now in production, was established long before COVID-19. Its purpose was to provide city managers with a dashboard that tracked key safety performance measures through analysis of thousands of sensors and other data sources with <a href="https://insights.sap.com/what-is-artificial-intelligence/">artificial intelligence (AI)</a> algorithms. The managers also use the dashboard to monitor movement around the city such as traffic and <a href="https://howbusyistoon.com/">pedestrian flow</a> and congestion, <a href="https://howbusyistoon.com/parking.html">car park occupancy</a>, and bus GPS trackers. It also tracks energy consumption, air quality, and noise levels.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="how-data-supports-safer-public-spaces">How Data Supports Safer Public Spaces</h3>
        <p>The Proximity Monitor helps people safely mingle in a post-pandemic world.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="https://news.sap.com/2021/06/proximity-monitor-real-time-data-post-pandemic-world/">Read the news</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>A key value driver for the dashboard: real-time data. The main goal for the project was to measure the impact of policy decisions (such as the recommendation to maintain social distance) in real time, says Phil James, director of the National Urban Observatory Facility and professor of Urban Data at Newcastle University. Having the data enables fundamentally new types of policies, says James. For example, if the dashboard shows congestion in the city center, the city could elect to assess pollution charges on drivers who come into town. To be clear, Newcastle upon Tyne is not doing this now – and may not ever – but having the data enables what James calls “thought experiments.”</p>
  <p>“We can imagine a city where we manage traffic flows or charges for private vehicles based on things like air quality. You can start to tie those things together,” he says.</p>
  <p><strong>Key takeaway:</strong> The dashboard project sets the table for future public service improvements and improved quality of life.</p>
  <p>Jenny Nelson, digital program manager for the city of Newcastle, believes analytics technology that observes and extrapolates from human behavior will be a pillar of future urban management because the results of <a href="https://insights.sap.com/what-is-analytics/">analytics</a> can drive informed policy discussions.</p>
  <p>“Real-time data gives you the potential to create new and different types of decision-making” and to adjust as needed according to conditions, says Nelson.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_177a134706807ce5d4f92bf431c77509ea7253ebf.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_177a134706807ce5d4f92bf431c77509ea7253ebf.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_177a134706807ce5d4f92bf431c77509ea7253ebf.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Garbage truck" src="./media_177a134706807ce5d4f92bf431c77509ea7253ebf.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2600" height="1733">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="sensor-data-enables-smart-resource-management">Sensor data enables smart resource management</h2>
  <p><strong>The project:</strong> Smart waste management powered by sensor data helped Heidelberg, Germany optimize trash and recycling collection as needs proved variable during the pandemic.</p>
  <p><strong>Major benefits:</strong> Fewer truck runs saves time, labor, and fuel consumption and reduces emissions without affecting service quality.</p>
  <p>With 160,000 residents, Heidelberg, a city in the German state of Baden-Württemberg, is a leader at deploying digital technology to improve life for its citizens while boosting sustainability. The city’s digital spinoff, <a href="https://www.heidelberg.de/1192695.html">Digital-Agentur Heidelberg GmbH</a>, features a number of projects, including more efficient <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2019/11/07/how-governments-use-ai-to-create-better-experiences-for-citizens/?sh=1084056a799c">trash collection driven by sensor data</a>. Trash receptacles outfitted with sensors help city managers track the waste levels in real time through a cloud-based dashboard.</p>
  <p>“Instead of traveling to very isolated parts of the city in the forest every second week, the [truck fleet provider can] make data-based decisions on whether to make the trip. On the other hand, we will get an early notice if containers are overflowing, which leads to a nicer cityscape and fewer citizen complaints,” says Sebastian Warkentin, managing director, Digital-Agentur. Trash collection is therefore a more efficient and eco-friendly option during a time of volatile trash needs, helping the city achieve its sustainability goals.</p>
  <p>The smart waste-management system has significantly reduced the noise level, street congestion, and air quality for residents, says Warkentin. It also helps Heidelberg analyze and forecast future waste management needs. The system uses a host of technologies, including <a href="https://insights.sap.com/what-is-iot-internet-of-things/">Internet of Things (IoT)</a> sensors, low-power wide-area network, cloud storage, and software.</p>
  <p>As cities slowly come back, waste management systems powered by real-time sensor data prevent the inefficiency of doing pickups in areas that have not yet come back to their previous waste levels.</p>
  <p>The smart waste management system has significantly reduced the noise level, street congestion, and air quality for residents. It also helps the city of Heidelberg forecast future waste-management needs.</p>
  <p><strong>Key takeaway:</strong> Agile methodology successfully applied to data projects can lead to new opportunities.</p>
  <p>Most business leaders don’t have to ponder the nuances of trash collection to this degree, but Heidelberg showcases how something that starts as a germ of an idea can grow in unexpected ways.</p>
  <p>Heidelberg did not start this waste collection project with the idea that the city would end up establishing a business. Project managers used an agile methodology to experiment with what worked and what needed improvement, and they kept going. The project resulted from co-innovation development among all the providers – including software, hardware, and garbage trucks – to which every partner brought expertise and technology to be tested.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_114f038a38b095c7990427b85da6042f73d1e4451.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_114f038a38b095c7990427b85da6042f73d1e4451.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_114f038a38b095c7990427b85da6042f73d1e4451.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Lines on a road" src="./media_114f038a38b095c7990427b85da6042f73d1e4451.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2121" height="1414">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="dashboard-pinpoints-road-crash-hotspots-improving-public-safety">Dashboard pinpoints road crash hotspots, improving public safety</h2>
  <p><strong>The project:</strong> To address a rise in road crashes, Tennessee’s Hamilton County built a system using multiple data sources for law enforcement to pinpoint the most crash-prone spots.</p>
  <p><strong>Major benefits:</strong> The resulting dashboard is able to visualize likely hotspots for vehicle collisions, enabling emergency services to position personnel to potentially respond more quickly.</p>
  <p>Just one more sad fact about the pandemic: contrary to reasonable expectations (given that there were fewer cars on many roads), the number of fatal car crashes <a href="https://apnews.com/article/pandemics-health-traffic-coronavirus-pandemic-799e455b73902b1638cc2ac46a172972">increased in the state of Tennessee during the shutdown period</a> when there were fewer vehicles on the road. In fact, the number of people killed on U.S. highways rose nearly 5% in the first nine months of 2020, according to the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. Tennessee fared worse than the national average, with a 6% rise to 1,004 <a href="https://www.timesfreepress.com/news/local/story/2020/nov/07/tennessee-sees-more-traffic-fatalities/535656/">traffic deaths</a> in 2020.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="virtual-safety-simulations">Virtual Safety Simulations</h3>
        <p>Learn how virtual testing is expanding to mitigate more risks in the real world.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="/resources/road-to-virtual-safety-simulations">Learn more</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Hamilton County, which includes Chattanooga, had been working since 2019 to build a sophisticated dashboard using a wealth of geographic information system (GIS) data, state crash data from the Chattanooga Department of Transportation, and other public data sources (including Dark Sky weather information) to visualize where the next crash was likely to take place. Funded by the city of Chattanooga, the project cost in the mid-six figures, and the work was done by the Center for Urban Informatics and Progress (CUIP) at the University of Tennessee-Chattanooga, according to Reid Belew, marketing manager, CUIP.</p>
  <p>One goal was for law enforcement to use the dashboard to mitigate conditions that are ripe for car crashes, hopefully reducing actual crashes in the process, according to Jeremy Roland, a recent graduate of the CUIP. Another important goal was to enable both local law enforcement and emergency services to more efficiently allocate resources. The hypothesis, still being tested with data, is that strategically locating officers has the potential to reduce response times and improve crash victim outcomes. “This affects things like where they position their police cars for a given day, where they set patrol routes for a given day,” says Roland.</p>
  <p>Urban areas provide business leaders with takeaways on how municipal leaders use data. That includes their development of dashboards that start with one goal and – because the data quality is strong – lead to new, valuable benefits.</p>
  <p>The third goal for the project was to give prescriptive insights to local governments about high-incident crash sites, enabling them to make improvements in some cases that would make the locations safer. For example, Roland says analysts took a closer look at one location in northern Chattanooga with a very high concentration of crashes happening throughout the data set time span.</p>
  <p>“It turns out that at that location, there was a utility pole that had been placed a little too close to the main roadway, often causing crashes,” Roland says. Once the officials made the connection, they were able to move the pole. They plan to track activity in the area to determine if the move correlates with fewer collisions.</p>
  <p><strong>Key takeaway:</strong> Pilot projects are critical to test data analytics hypotheses.</p>
  <p>Location data is just one indicator that the project team is analyzing to measure the dashboard’s effect. Most importantly, the Chattanooga team plans to examine whether emergency response times were reduced and by how much. In the meantime, Roland and his colleagues say they have gotten a very positive reaction from the police department. The team is evaluating future uses of the data.</p>
  <p>In spite of the pandemic, the central role that cities play in our lives, and the economic life of the regions in which we live and work, is <a href="https://www.weforum.org/agenda/2020/08/future-of-cities-covid-19/">not likely to change much</a>. Pressed to do more with less and to work with academic and business partners, urban areas provide business leaders with takeaways on how municipal leaders use data. That includes their development of dashboards that start with one goal and – because the data quality is strong – lead to new, valuable benefits.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/business-transformation</category>
            <category>topic/data-analytics</category>
            <category>industry/public-sector</category>
            <category>content-type/trends-predictions</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>