<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/magic-quadrant/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Named a Leader in the Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Warehouse Management Systems for the 11th Consecutive Year]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/sap-a-leader-2024-gartner-magic-quadrant-wms</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/sap-a-leader-2024-gartner-magic-quadrant-wms</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[For the 11th time, SAP is a Leader in the Magic Quadrant for WMS, based on ability to execute and for the completeness of vision. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ac123a0a67e3b19450c432a63245f50c1e68b889.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ac123a0a67e3b19450c432a63245f50c1e68b889.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1ac123a0a67e3b19450c432a63245f50c1e68b889.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Named a Leader in the Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Warehouse Management Systems for the 11th Consecutive Year" src="./media_1ac123a0a67e3b19450c432a63245f50c1e68b889.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-named-a-leader-in-the-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-warehouse-management-systems-for-the-11th-consecutive-year">SAP Named a Leader in the Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Warehouse Management Systems for the 11th Consecutive Year</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>SAP has been named as a Leader in the 2024 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Warehouse Management Systems. For the 11th consecutive year, SAP is positioned in the Leaders quadrant based on Ability to Execute and Completeness of Vision.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>We believe that this recognition confirms our strategy in logistics, which is based on three pillars:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Connecting every process to facilitate synchronized logistics execution, supporting highly efficient and fast-paced fulfillment cycles through seamless integration with logistics applications like SAP Transportation Management, SAP Business Network for Logistics, etc.</li>
    <li>Collaborating within a diverse ecosystem of system integrators, software partners, hyperscalers, hardware partners, and robotics OEMs, with warehouse management being an integral part of cloud ERP.</li>
    <li>Contextualizing every decision leveraging artificial intelligence (AI) and machine learning to optimize operations and to provide business insights</li>
  </ul>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="keep-pace-with-demand-minimize-costs-and-maintain-sustainable-risk-resilient-warehouse-operations">Keep pace with demand, minimize costs, and maintain sustainable, risk-resilient warehouse operations</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/extended-warehouse-management.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/extended-warehouse-management.html">SAP Extended Warehouse Management</a> (SAP EWM) is an integral part of the overall SAP strategy and gives companies the ability to operate modern warehouses that must respond quickly to changing business conditions. The flexibility of SAP EWM helps manage a high volume of goods and run sustainable, risk-resilient operations with digitized warehouse processes in the cloud including direct control of warehouse automation equipment.</p>
  <p>SAP continues to innovate in SAP EWM based on market analysis and even more importantly based on feedback from our global install base and ecosystem. Recent innovations include cross-process integration in the areas of transportation, production, and quality management, addressing industry-specific requirements, extensibility, and usability.</p>
  <p>SAP EWM combined with SAP Transportation Management and SAP Business Network for Logistics provides a platform for companies to collaborate with their logistics partners to gain end-to-end visibility and insights across their logistics operations.</p>
  <p>Our global partner network — made up of systems integrators, business consultants, and technology providers — helps our customers manage their warehouse management transformations, whether they be system replacements, upgrades, greenfield deployments, or part of larger enterprise transformations.</p>
  <p>“Warehouse Management with SAP EWM is an integral part of our cloud ERP offering,” said Till Dengel, global head of Logistics and Manufacturing Product Marketing at SAP. “Customers use SAP EWM to manage their warehouse operations in 66 countries and 24 industries.”</p>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div>SAP Extended Warehouse Management helped Bridgestone reduce errors, with a new level of productivity and safety.</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>Eric Dyason, National Distribution Manager, Bridgestone New Zealand Ltd.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/extended-warehouse-management.html?campaigncode=CRM-YD24-DSC-2695614&#x26;url_id=magic-quadrant-for-warehouse-management-systems&#x26;rc=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.gartner.com%2Freprints%2F%3Fid%3D1-2HGS0BJ4%26ct%3D240502%26st%3Dsb">Get more details on the latest</a><br><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/extended-warehouse-management.html?campaigncode=CRM-YD24-DSC-2695614&#x26;url_id=magic-quadrant-for-warehouse-management-systems&#x26;rc=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.gartner.com%2Freprints%2F%3Fid%3D1-2HGS0BJ4%26ct%3D240502%26st%3Dsb">Gartner Magic Quadrant for WMS here</a>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Ganesh Wadawadigi is chief product marketing owner for Logistics at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>*Gartner, Magic Quadrant for Warehouse Management Systems, Simon Tunstall, Dwight Klappich, Rishabh Narang, Federica Stufano, 2 May 2024</p>
  <p>GARTNER is a registered trademark and service mark of Gartner, Inc. and/or its affiliates in the U.S. and internationally, MAGIC QUADRANT is a registered trademark of Gartner, Inc. and/or its affiliates and are used herein with permission. All rights reserved.<br>Gartner does not endorse any vendor, product or service depicted in its research publications, and does not advise technology users to select only those vendors with the highest ratings or other designation. Gartner research publications consist of the opinions of Gartner’s research organization and should not be construed as statements of fact. Gartner disclaims all warranties, expressed or implied, with respect to this research, including any warranties of merchantability or fitness for a particular purpose.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/magic-quadrant</category>
            <category>product/sap-extended-warehouse-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Signavio Is a Leader in the 2024 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Process Mining Platforms]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/sap-signavio-a-leader-2024-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-process-mining-platforms</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/sap-signavio-a-leader-2024-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-process-mining-platforms</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In the 2024 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Process Mining, SAP Signavio has again been recognized as a Leader. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_138b3ef0b5b24b564b18da25ef3b2cde982bba0f8.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_138b3ef0b5b24b564b18da25ef3b2cde982bba0f8.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_138b3ef0b5b24b564b18da25ef3b2cde982bba0f8.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Signavio Is a Leader in the 2024 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Process Mining Platforms" src="./media_138b3ef0b5b24b564b18da25ef3b2cde982bba0f8.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-signavio-is-a-leader-in-the-2024-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-process-mining-platforms">SAP Signavio Is a Leader in the 2024 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Process Mining Platforms</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>In the 2024 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Process Mining, SAP Signavio has once again been recognized as a Leader in the market based on Completeness of Vision and Ability to Execute.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="complimentary-copy-2024-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-process-mining-platforms">Complimentary copy: 2024 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Process Mining Platforms</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.signavio.com/downloads/analyst-reports/2024-gartner-magic-quadrant-process-mining/">Download yours here</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>This is the second year in a row that SAP Signavio has been positioned as a Leader in the report. We believe that this positioning implies that SAP Signavio is a key driver for SAP’s growth and long-term strategy.</p>
  <p>According to the Gartner Magic Quadrant research methodology, “Leaders execute well against their current vision and are well positioned for tomorrow.”</p>
  <p>Our solutions solve today’s real and diverse customer use cases — operational excellence, compliance, automation, transformation, etc.– and recognizes that we have a compelling vision for a future in which process automation and process AI open up new opportunities for our customers and partners.</p>
  <p>SAP Signavio continues to focus on ensuring the long-term success of all of our customers and partners.</p>
  <h2 id="revenue-nsw">Revenue NSW</h2>
  <p>In the Australian state of New South Wales, the tax collected by Revenue NSW accounts for more than 35% of finances, helping fund essential services, from healthcare to education and policing.</p>
  <p>With a vision to be the world’s most innovative and customer-centric revenue agency, Revenue NSW set out with a very specific objective: it wanted to analyze cases in which clients had overpaid land tax to identify why these overpayments occur and what experience clients received when obtaining refunds. This analysis would not only help reduce overpayment volumes and improve the client experience, but also enable the agency to work more efficiently for its diverse stakeholders.</p>
  <p>“As part of our Aspire 2032 strategy, our vision is to be the world’s most innovative and customer-centric revenue collection agency,” shared Jocelyn Yem, director of Strategy and Innovation at Revenue NSW.”‘Embrace Innovation’ is one of our strategic focus areas, where we can respond to our customers’ needs by embedding a culture of continuous improvement. SAP Signavio Process Intelligence has helped us achieve our first stage in this journey.”</p>
  <p>“SAP Signavio Process Intelligence has painted a clear picture of why clients pay too much land tax and how we can process refunds smoothly, along with a detailed road map to help us put these insights into action,” confirmed Sabrina Bazouni, director of Land Tax at Revenue NSW.</p>
  <h2 id="fujitsu-limited">Fujitsu Limited</h2>
  <p>Recognizing the wide-ranging effect of business process transformation solutions, Fujitsu Limited has embraced SAP Signavio solutions across its operations and portfolio.</p>
  <p>At one of its manufacturing plants in Japan, Fujitsu used the SAP Signavio Process Intelligence solution to gather process execution data directly from the shop floor into the continuous improvement model the company had been using for many years. Integrating process data into the Kaizen discussions delivered never-before-seen insights, which helped the company further optimize its shop-floor processes and transform their Kaizen from traditional to digital, using process mining to generate data-driven insights.</p>
  <p>This firsthand experience of the solutions has also allowed Fujitsu to enrich its customer offerings with new frameworks, insights, and tools that can help customers realign their organizations and make changes at speed.</p>
  <p>Having seen the potential of SAP Signavio solutions, Fujitsu now plans to extend its use both internally and externally. One such planned initiative involves combining the concepts of the digital twin on an organization and the intelligent enterprise, using business process transformation solutions as the mechanism of change.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Download a <a href="https://www.signavio.com/downloads/analyst-reports/2024-gartner-magic-quadrant-process-mining/">complimentary copy of the report here</a>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Dee Houchen is global head of Market Impact for SAP Signavio.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="optimize-and-transform-business-processes-fast-and-at-scale">Optimize and transform business processes fast and at scale</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-process-transformation.html">Learn how</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Gartner, Magic Quadrant for Process Mining Platforms, Marc Kerremans, David Sugden, Nick Duffy, 29 April 2024</p>
  <p>GARTNER is a registered trademark and service mark of Gartner, Inc. and/or its affiliates in the U.S. and internationally, and MAGIC QUADRANT is a registered trademark of Gartner, Inc. and/or its affiliates and are used herein with permission. All rights reserved. Gartner does not endorse any vendor, product or service depicted in its research publications, and does not advise technology users to select only those vendors with the highest ratings or other designation. Gartner research publications consist of the opinions of Gartner’s research organization and should not be construed as statements of fact. Gartner disclaims all warranties, expressed or implied, with respect to this research, including any warranties of merchantability or fitness for a particular purpose.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/business-process-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/magic-quadrant</category>
            <category>news-tag/process-mining</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-signavio</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Named a Leader in the 2024 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Transportation Management Systems]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-named-a-leader-2024-gartner-magic-quadrant-transportation-management-systems</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-named-a-leader-2024-gartner-magic-quadrant-transportation-management-systems</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[For the 10th consecutive year, SAP has been named as a Leader in the 2024 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Transportation Management Systems.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_129328166e826d3a52e6b9854f483cc4a5f36fd9a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_129328166e826d3a52e6b9854f483cc4a5f36fd9a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_129328166e826d3a52e6b9854f483cc4a5f36fd9a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Named a Leader in the 2024 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Transportation Management Systems" src="./media_129328166e826d3a52e6b9854f483cc4a5f36fd9a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-named-a-leader-in-the-2024-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-transportation-management-systems">SAP Named a Leader in the 2024 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Transportation Management Systems</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>For the 10th consecutive year, SAP has been named as a Leader in the 2024 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Transportation Management Systems.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP is positioned in the Leaders Quadrant based on our Ability to Execute and for the Completeness of our Vision.</p>
  <p>We believe that this recognition confirms our strategy in Logistics, which is based on three pillars:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Connecting every process and providing synchronized logistics execution to support highly efficient and fast paced fulfillment cycles</li>
    <li>Collaborating with a single network of carriers, digital forwarders, and visibility providers to spot risks and avoid disruptions and thereby provide best-in-class delivery experience</li>
    <li>Contextualizing every decision, leveraging artificial intelligence (<a href="/topics/artificial-intelligence">AI</a>) and machine learning to optimize operations and to provide business insights</li>
  </ul>
  <p>SAP Transportation Management is an integral part of the overall SAP strategy and gives companies the ability to manage their end-to-end transportation processes from procurement through planning and execution to freight settlement with analytics to support each step.</p>
  <p>We continue to innovate in SAP Transportation Management based on our market analysis and even more importantly based on feedback from our global install base and ecosystem. Recent innovations include advancements in areas like sustainability, planning and optimization, supply chain execution, and generative AI.</p>
  <p>SAP Transportation Management and SAP Business Network for Logistics enable logistics partners to collaborate with each other and provide visibility to all stakeholders throughout the shipment lifecycle and help manage risks as they arise through intelligent insights. We continue to grow SAP Business Network, adding more carriers and additional networks to provide expanded coverage around the world and across all transportation modes.</p>
  <p>As more customers evaluate SAP Transportation Management, we continue to strategically expand our partner network to ensure our customers have access to an ecosystem that supports their operations no matter where they are in the world or how they move their freight. Our global partner network made up of systems integrators, business consultants, and technology providers help our customers manage their transportation transformations, whether they be system replacements, upgrades, greenfield deployments, or part of larger enterprise transformations.</p>
  <p>“Our customers use SAP Transportation Management and SAP Business Network for Logistics to manage transportation operations in more than 20 industries and in every corner of the world,” said Till Dengel, global head of Logistics and Manufacturing Product Marketing at SAP. “Because we look at logistics holistically, clients can confidently confirm their orders, knowing that fulfillment can be executed as promised, since ERP, warehousing, and transportation are always in sync.”</p>
  <p>“Adopting logistics solutions from SAP across our facilities in all our markets allowed us to optimize freight transportation,” said Carlo Noè, Global Process and Applications Manager for Trade, Transport, and Logistics Division at Hitachi Energy Ltd. “We can interact with our stakeholders and carriers in a digital way, helping us manage supply chain risk, enhance agility, and build supply chain resilience.”</p>
  <p>For more details on the latest Gartner Magic Quadrant for TMS <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/transportation-logistics.html?campaigncode=CRM-YD24-DSC-2678872&#x26;url_id=magic-quadrant-for-transportation-management-systems&#x26;rc=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.gartner.com%2Freprints%2F%3Fid%3D1-2H3J1JVF%26ct%3D240327%26st%3Dsb">read the Gartner Reprint here</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Bill King is senior product marketing manager for Logistics at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-transportation-management-reduce-complexity-increase-efficiency-and-improve-agility-for-a-more-sustainable-risk-resilient-supply-chain">SAP Transportation Management: Reduce complexity, increase efficiency, and improve agility for a more sustainable, risk-resilient supply chain</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/transportation-logistics.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>GARTNER is a registered trademark and service mark of Gartner, Inc. and/or its affiliates in the U.S. and internationally, MAGIC QUADRANT is a registered trademark of Gartner, Inc. and/or its affiliates and are used herein with permission. All rights reserved.<br><em>Gartner does not endorse any vendor, product or service depicted in its research publications, and does not advise technology users to select only those vendors with the highest ratings or other designation. Gartner research publications consist of the opinions of Gartner’s research organization and should not be construed as statements of fact. Gartner disclaims all warranties, expressed or implied, with respect to this research, including any warranties of merchantability or fitness for a particular purpose.</em></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/travel-transportation</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/magic-quadrant</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-network-for-logistics</category>
            <category>product/sap-transportation-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Is a Leader in the 2023 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Configure, Price, and Quote Application Suites]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/sap-leader-gartner-magic-quadrant-cpq-application-suites</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/sap-leader-gartner-magic-quadrant-cpq-application-suites</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[For the sixth consecutive year, SAP is a Leader in Gartner's Magic Quadrant for Configure, Price, and Quote (CPQ) Application Suites.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/financial-management</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/magic-quadrant</category>
            <category>news-tag/quote-to-cash</category>
            <category>product/sap-cpq</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Is a Leader in the 2023 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Financial Planning Software]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/sap-leader-2023-gartner-magic-quadrant-financial-planning-software</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/sap-leader-2023-gartner-magic-quadrant-financial-planning-software</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[We are proud to announce that Gartner has recognized SAP as a Leader in its 2023 Magic Quadrant for Financial Planning Software.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_12c0f62a0c1bea8cebafaf88b1a2478cf4d11b899.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_12c0f62a0c1bea8cebafaf88b1a2478cf4d11b899.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_12c0f62a0c1bea8cebafaf88b1a2478cf4d11b899.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Is a Leader in the 2023 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Financial Planning Software" src="./media_12c0f62a0c1bea8cebafaf88b1a2478cf4d11b899.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-is-a-leader-in-the-2023-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-financial-planning-software">SAP Is a Leader in the 2023 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Financial Planning Software</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>We are proud to announce that Gartner has recognized SAP as a Leader in its <a href="https://www.gartner.com/reprints/?id=1-2FU0XES5&#x26;ct=231206&#x26;st=sb">2023 Magic Quadrant for Financial Planning Software</a>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>At SAP, our commitment extends beyond traditional financial planning and analysis (FP&#x26;A), reaching across the entire enterprise of financial professionals. To achieve a comprehensive FP&#x26;A transformation, organizations need effortless access to crucial finance data, regardless of its location. In a landscape where financial information is dispersed across various applications, files, and systems – both on premise and in the cloud – organizations often expend significant resources on extracting, rebuilding, and integrating their financial data to deliver forecasts and simulations.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-analytics-cloud-make-decisions-without-doubt">SAP Analytics Cloud: Make decisions without doubt</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/cloud-analytics.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>By harnessing cutting-edge FP&#x26;A software tools and adopting strategic approaches, organizations can seamlessly explore, connect, integrate, govern, and orchestrate their planning and analysis. SAP’s solutions for financial planning and analysis can provide a reliable foundation for finance information, delivering trustworthy, pertinent, and timely financial insights. This can streamline finance data, helping to maximize business information potential. Simultaneously, it can foster an analytics-driven approach to planning and decision-making. Our primary solution for financial planning and analysis is <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/cloud-analytics/features/planning.html">SAP Analytics Cloud</a>. This solution is part of <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">SAP Business Technology Platform</a> (SAP BTP).</p>
  <p>Gartner evaluated 16 vendors and named SAP a Leader based on our “ability to execute” and “completeness of vision.” We believe this recognition serves as an acknowledgment of SAP’s continued commitment to providing our customers with world-class financial planning software.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1db92051bee73b9bb29a5433d2213c41cc9f52bab.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1db92051bee73b9bb29a5433d2213c41cc9f52bab.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1db92051bee73b9bb29a5433d2213c41cc9f52bab.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_1db92051bee73b9bb29a5433d2213c41cc9f52bab.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="570" height="592">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>This graphic was published by Gartner, Inc. as part of a larger research document and should be evaluated in the context of the entire document. The Gartner document is available upon request from SAP here. Click to enlarge.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="future-proof-your-organization-with-sap-solutions-for-xpa">Future-Proof Your Organization with SAP Solutions for xP&#x26;A</h2>
  <p>Our focus on accelerating planning and analysis (xP&#x26;A) is achieved by integrating with SAP S/4HANA Cloud and other SAP applications. This integration helps enable swift planning cycles, providing live access to actuals and plans. Customers can use our solutions to help extend their planning and analysis across the enterprise to facilitate seamlessly connected financial, workforce, sales, and supply chain plans. By adopting this approach, SAP customers can react quickly to changes and increase decision-making agility and performance no matter what events unfold.</p>
  <p>A pivotal aspect of our approach involves harnessing the power of artificial intelligence (AI) and machine learning for everyday planning. With a single click, our users can activate predictive analytics, allowing for insights with greater ease and speed. The AI capabilities within SAP Analytics Cloud are helping organizations unlock the full potential of their data and derive greater value from analytics and planning. With these capabilities, planners can model a wide range of scenarios and generate more accurate forecasts and plans.</p>
  <p>We are committed to instilling unwavering confidence in plans by meticulously ensuring the trustworthiness of data. Leveraging the powerful combination of <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/datasphere.html">SAP Datasphere</a> and SAP Analytics Cloud, we go beyond traditional boundaries to help harmonize planning data seamlessly across SAP and third-party sources, presenting natively integrated plans that can form a reliable foundation for strategic decision-making.</p>
  <p>This approach has yielded tangible benefits for organizations such as <a href="https://www.sap.com/asset/dynamic/2023/06/34b2b0e8-797e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Watco</a> and <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/customer-stories/roche.html">F. Hoffmann-La Roche AG</a>. These SAP Analytics Cloud customers have experienced firsthand the transformative impact of having their planning data seamlessly integrated, resulting in enhanced precision and efficacy in their planning and analysis endeavors. With our holistic approach, we help pave the way for you to navigate the complex landscape of financial planning with confidence, working to ensure your business decisions are backed by a foundation of accurate and planning-ready data.</p>
  <h2 id="next-steps">Next Steps</h2>
  <p>SAP is dedicated to advancing financial planning and analysis through our suite of financial planning software tools. Our commitment is reflected in the seamless transformation of financial data into actionable insights at scale for our customers. If you’re poised to unlock the full potential of your financial data and elevate your FP&#x26;A capabilities, explore the next steps with the resources provided:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Visit our <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/financial-management/financial-planning-analysis-fpa.html">financial planning and analysis page</a></li>
    <li>Try the free <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/financial-management/financial-planning-analysis-fpa/guided-experience.html">financial planning and analysis guided experience</a></li>
    <li>Read the full, complimentary <a href="https://www.gartner.com/reprints/?id=1-2FU0XES5&#x26;ct=231206&#x26;st=sb">Gartner Magic Quadrant for Financial Planning Software</a> report</li>
  </ul>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Dan Yu is senior vice president of SAP Business Technology Platform.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Gartner, Magic Quadrant for Financial Planning Software, Regina Crowder, Matthew Mowrey, Vaughan Archer, 5 December 2023<br>Gartner does not endorse any vendor, product or service depicted in its research publications and does not advise technology users to select only those vendors with the highest ratings or other designation. Gartner research publications consist of the opinions of Gartner’s Research &#x26; Advisory organization and should not be construed as statements of fact. Gartner disclaims all warranties, expressed or implied, with respect to this research, including any warranties of merchantability or fitness for a particular purpose.<br>GARTNER is a registered trademark and service mark of Gartner, Inc. and/or its affiliates in the U.S. and internationally, Magic Quadrant is a registered trademark of Gartner, Inc. and/or its affiliates and is used herein with permission. All rights reserved.</p>
  <p>Top image courtesy of SAP employee Laurentia-Iulia Pavel.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/financial-management</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/magic-quadrant</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Recognized as a Leader in 2023 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Data Integration Tools]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/sap-a-leader-gartner-magic-quadrant-data-integration-tools</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/sap-a-leader-gartner-magic-quadrant-data-integration-tools</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[For the 16th consecutive time, Gartner has recognized SAP as a Leader in its Magic Quadrant for Data Integration Tools.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18676e13249083c87480612ffdb6501c1181d00cd.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18676e13249083c87480612ffdb6501c1181d00cd.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_18676e13249083c87480612ffdb6501c1181d00cd.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Recognized as a Leader in 2023 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Data Integration Tools" src="./media_18676e13249083c87480612ffdb6501c1181d00cd.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-recognized-as-a-leader-in-2023-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-data-integration-tools">SAP Recognized as a Leader in 2023 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Data Integration Tools</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>We are proud to announce that Gartner has recognized SAP as a Leader in its 2023 <a href="https://www.gartner.com/reprints/?id=1-2FTDYPZU&#x26;ct=231204&#x26;st=sb">Magic Quadrant for Data Integration Tools</a> for the 16th consecutive time.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-an-engaging-hands-on-experience-with-sap-datasphere">Get an engaging, hands-on experience with SAP Datasphere</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/datasphere/guided-experience.html">Start now</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>To achieve true digital transformation, organizations must have seamless access to their mission-critical business data no matter where it resides. Yet with data landscapes distributed among different applications and systems both in the cloud and on premises, organizations spend countless resources extracting, rebuilding, and integrating their data.</p>
  <p>By leveraging the right data integration tools and strategies, organizations can easily discover, connect, integrate, govern, and orchestrate their data assets. Data integration offerings from SAP deliver trusted, relevant, and timely information to enable customers to simplify their data landscape and unleash the power of business data. Our primary solutions include <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/datasphere.html">SAP Datasphere</a>, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/cloud-platform/capabilities/integration.html">SAP Data Intelligence</a> Cloud, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/data-services.html">SAP Data Services</a>, and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/cloud-platform/capabilities/integration.html">SAP Integration Suite</a>. These offerings are part of <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">SAP Business Technology Platform</a> (SAP BTP).</p>
  <p>Gartner evaluated 21 vendors and named SAP a Leader based on our “ability to execute” and “completeness of vision.” We believe this recognition serves as acknowledgment of SAP’s continued commitment to providing our customers with world-class data integration tools.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b4a7dd1fbccb32babb1428357e9df797fb738917.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b4a7dd1fbccb32babb1428357e9df797fb738917.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1b4a7dd1fbccb32babb1428357e9df797fb738917.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_1b4a7dd1fbccb32babb1428357e9df797fb738917.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="926" height="1024">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>This graphic was published by Gartner, Inc. as part of a larger research document and should be evaluated in the context of the entire document. The Gartner document is available upon request from SAP here.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="unleash-the-power-of-business-data">Unleash the Power of Business Data</h2>
  <p>Data integration is necessary for customers to gain intelligent, relevant, and contextual insights for better decision-making. However, without the right data management approach and technology, companies can face an uphill battle in integrating, processing, curating, governing, and augmenting their data.</p>
  <p>SAP takes a business data fabric approach, which goes beyond a traditional data fabric. A business data fabric is a data management architecture that delivers an integrated, semantically rich data layer over underlying data landscapes to provide users with scalable access to their data without duplication.</p>
  <p>It eliminates the need to recreate the business context that was lost from extracting and replicating data. This gives users the ability to accelerate their decision-making with trust and confidence, knowing they always have the complete picture of their data regardless of where it is stored or how it was designed.</p>
  <p>SAP Datasphere — and its open data ecosystem — is the foundation for a business data fabric. It equips any organization to deliver meaningful data to every data consumer — with business context and logic intact. SAP Datasphere helps customers:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Access authoritative data:</strong> Accelerate time-to-value by automatically reusing the semantical definitions and associations from SAP applications</li>
    <li><strong>Enrich all data projects:</strong> Harmonize heterogeneous data into a business semantic model of diverse data landscape</li>
    <li><strong>Simplify the data landscape:</strong> Access all data across hybrid and cloud environments no matter where it resides</li>
  </ul>
  <p>With a unified experience for data integration, data cataloging, semantic modeling, data warehousing, data federation, and data virtualization, SAP Datasphere enables data professionals to easily distribute authoritative business data — with business context and logic preserved — across the data landscape.</p>
  <p>Since the launch of SAP Datasphere, we have seen tremendous growth of customers innovating with this technology. For example, Messer CIO David Johnston describes his experience with the solution this way:“The business data fabric architecture enables us to bring SAP and non-SAP data together in the seamless and self-service way we’ve been envisioning. SAP Datasphere provided us with a solution to build a harmonized layer, or business data fabric, across SAP and non-SAP, cloud or on-premise data sources, making the best use of our existing investments in SAP, Microsoft Azure, Salesforce, and Oracle.”</p>
  <h2 id="next-steps">Next Steps</h2>
  <p>For over 16 years, data integration tools from SAP have enabled our customers to turn disjoined data assets into actionable business insights at scale. Take the next step and begin your business data fabric journey today:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Visit the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/datasphere.html">SAP Datasphere page</a></li>
    <li>Try the free <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/datasphere/guided-experience.html">SAP Datasphere guided experience</a></li>
    <li>Read the <a href="https://www.gartner.com/reprints/?id=1-2FTDYPZU&#x26;ct=231204&#x26;st=sb">2023 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Data Integration Tools report</a></li>
  </ul>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Kaiser Larsen is vice president of Data and Analytics at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Gartner, Magic Quadrant for Data Integration Tools, Ehtisham Zaidi, Robert Thanaraj, Sharat Menon, Thornton Craig, Roxane Edjlali, Michele Launi, 4 December 2023<br>Gartner does not endorse any vendor, product or service depicted in its research publications and does not advise technology users to select only those vendors with the highest ratings or other designation. Gartner research publications consist of the opinions of Gartner’s Research &#x26; Advisory organization and should not be construed as statements of fact. Gartner disclaims all warranties, expressed or implied, with respect to this research, including any warranties of merchantability or fitness for a particular purpose.<br>GARTNER is a registered trademark and service mark of Gartner, Inc. and/or its affiliates in the U.S. and internationally, Magic Quadrant is a registered trademark of Gartner, Inc. and/or its affiliates and is used herein with permission. All rights reserved.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/data-fabric</category>
            <category>news-tag/data-integration</category>
            <category>news-tag/database-and-data-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/magic-quadrant</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-datasphere</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP S/4HANA Cloud Is a Leader in the 2023 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Cloud ERP for Product-Centric Enterprises]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/gartner-magic-quadrant-cloud-erp-product-centric-enterprises-sap-s-4-hana</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/gartner-magic-quadrant-cloud-erp-product-centric-enterprises-sap-s-4-hana</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[As enterprises transition mission-critical ERP processes to the cloud, they look to SAP to help them realize business value.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/magic-quadrant</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP S/4HANA Cloud Is a Leader in the 2023 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Cloud ERP for Service-Centric Enterprises]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/sap-leader-2023-gartner-magic-quadrant-cloud-erp-service-centric</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/sap-leader-2023-gartner-magic-quadrant-cloud-erp-service-centric</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP has been recognized as a leader in the 2023 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Cloud ERP for Service-Centric Enterprises. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/grow-with-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/magic-quadrant</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Named a Leader in 2023 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Digital Commerce]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/sap-named-a-leader-in-2023-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-digital-commerce</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/sap-named-a-leader-in-2023-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-digital-commerce</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[This is the ninth time in a row SAP has been rated a leader by Gartner in the Magic Quadrant for Digital Commerce. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/magic-quadrant</category>
            <category>product/sap-commerce-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-customer-experience</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Named a Leader in the 2023 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Warehouse Management Systems]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/sap-a-leader-2023-gartner-magic-quadrant-wms</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/sap-a-leader-2023-gartner-magic-quadrant-wms</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is again a Leader in the Gartner Magic Quadrant for WMS, based on ability to execute and for the completeness of vision. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/magic-quadrant</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-network-for-logistics</category>
            <category>product/sap-extended-warehouse-management</category>
            <category>product/sap-transportation-management</category>
            <category>product/sap-warehouse-insights</category>
            <category>product/sap-warehouse-robotics</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Named a Leader in the 2023 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Transportation Management Systems]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/2023-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-transportation-management-systems</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/2023-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-transportation-management-systems</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is a Leader in the Gartner Magic Quadrant for Transportation Management Systems based on ability to execute and completeness of vision.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/travel-transportation</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/magic-quadrant</category>
            <category>product/sap-transportation-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Named a Leader in 2023 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Integration Platform as a Service, Worldwide]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/01/2023-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-ipaas-sap-a-leader</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/01/2023-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-ipaas-sap-a-leader</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Gartner has recognized SAP as a Leader in the 2023 Magic Quadrant for iPaaS, Worldwide for the third time in a row. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/enterprise-integration</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/integration</category>
            <category>news-tag/magic-quadrant</category>
            <category>product/sap-integration-suite</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Named a Leader in 2022 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Procure-to-Pay Suites]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/sap-a-leader-procure-to-pay-suites-gartner-magic-quadrant</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/sap-a-leader-procure-to-pay-suites-gartner-magic-quadrant</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[For the seventh consecutive time, SAP has been recognized as a Leader in the Gartner Magic Quadrant for Procure-to-Pay suites. Learn why.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/magic-quadrant</category>
            <category>news-tag/procure-to-pay</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Again a Leader in Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Cloud Database Management Systems]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/sap-a-leader-in-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-cdbms</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/sap-a-leader-in-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-cdbms</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP's position in the CDBMS Magic Quadrant supports its mission to help organizations transform their data strategy and give data purpose.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/magic-quadrant</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Recognized as a Leader in 2022 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Data Quality Solutions]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/gartner-magic-quadrant-for-data-quality-solutions-sap-a-leader</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/gartner-magic-quadrant-for-data-quality-solutions-sap-a-leader</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is once again a Leader in the Gartner Magic Quadrant for Data Quality Solutions, for the 16th consecutive year. Learn why.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17da0610c34e8f257d6b846afd52d20285c5e3f79.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17da0610c34e8f257d6b846afd52d20285c5e3f79.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_17da0610c34e8f257d6b846afd52d20285c5e3f79.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Recognized as a Leader in 2022 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Data Quality Solutions" src="./media_17da0610c34e8f257d6b846afd52d20285c5e3f79.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-recognized-as-a-leader-in-2022-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-data-quality-solutions">SAP Recognized as a Leader in 2022 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Data Quality Solutions</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="data-management-transform-your-business-by-making-information-ready-for-action">Data Management: Transform your business by making information ready for action</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/data-management.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>We are proud to announce that Gartner has recognized SAP as a Leader in its <a href="https://www.gartner.com/reprints/?id=1-2BKS6A63&#x26;ct=221102&#x26;st=sb">2022 Magic Quadrant for Data Quality Solutions</a> for the 16th consecutive year.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Digital transformation has changed the conversation about data; it is a shift from “data is not my problem” to “data is everyone’s opportunity.” Organizations are looking for ways to embrace the opportunity — specifically, by exploiting their data as a strategic enterprise asset.</p>
  <p>By leveraging the right data quality solutions, organization can create the data excellence and discipline needed to drive better business outcomes, going beyond just fixing data to helping solve the data challenge. Data quality solutions from SAP provide data profiling and monitoring, metadata management, data cataloging, data cleansing and enrichment, and information policy management capabilities. They helps improve collaboration among data workers, business users, and IT while equipping them to understand, analyze, and quantify the impact of data — and data quality — on enterprise processes, analytics, and governance initiatives. Solutions include <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/data-intelligence.html">SAP Data Intelligence Cloud</a>, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/data-profiling-steward.html">SAP Information Steward</a>, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/data-services.html">SAP Data Services</a>, and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/data-quality-management.html">SAP Data Quality Management, microservices for location data</a>.</p>
  <p>Gartner evaluated 16 vendors and named SAP a Leader based on its “ability to execute” and “completeness of vision.” We believe this recognition serves as acknowledgment of our continued commitment to providing customers with world-class data quality solutions.</p>
  <p>Data is the lifeline of business today. It is critical to not only manage data quality proactively to eliminate the risk to operations and analytics, but also look for opportunities to create organization-wide data excellence and discipline. The SAP portfolio of data management solutions improves the quality of data across the enterprise, delivering trusted, relevant, and timely information to drive better business outcomes and help customers on their path to becoming intelligent enterprises.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-started-with-sap-btp">Get started with SAP BTP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/trial.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Leading integrated business conglomerate <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/customer-stories/adani.html">Adani</a> set out to build a foundation for centralized data management across its business. The company is using SAP Data Services and SAP Information Steward software for regular data validation and enrichment in order to support a single source of truth based on high-quality data. This outcome gives employees the visibility and insights they need to make in-the-moment decisions confidently and supports better quality data with regular data validation, consistent data definition, and internal quality checks.</p>
  <p>As part of <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">SAP Business Technology Platform</a>, the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/data-management.html">SAP portfolio of data management solutions</a> helps customers to optimize analytics, achieve new insights, and improve business outcomes. Users can proactively govern data across the organization to help ensure trustworthy information for smarter decision-making.</p>
  <p>Data quality solutions from SAP help businesses discover, understand, and manage multifaceted data. Companies can profile, cleanse, enrich, and match customer, product, supplier, material, and other data — driving more accurate, trustworthy, and timely information.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Mike Keilen is global vice president for SAP BTP Integration and Data Management Marketing and Solutions.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/database-and-data-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/magic-quadrant</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Named a 2022 Magic Quadrant™ Transportation Management Systems and Magic Quadrant™ for Warehouse Management Systems Leader by Gartner®]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/gartner-magic-quadrant-tms-wms-sap-a-leader</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/gartner-magic-quadrant-tms-wms-sap-a-leader</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP has been recognized by Gartner as a leader in TMS and WMS, demonstrating its position as leading provider in supply chain and procurement.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/travel-transportation</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/magic-quadrant</category>
            <category>news-tag/warehouse-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Positioned as a Leader in 2022 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Cloud HCM Suites for 1,000+ Employee Enterprises for Seventh Consecutive Year]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/sap-a-leader-magic-quadrant-for-cloud-hcm-suites-employee-enterprises</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/sap-a-leader-magic-quadrant-for-cloud-hcm-suites-employee-enterprises</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is a a Leader in the Magic Quadrant for Cloud HCM Suites for 1,000+ Employee Enterprises for the seventh consecutive year.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_12e84929eba593a9c963c2135bbd9c29c6a2d4176.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_12e84929eba593a9c963c2135bbd9c29c6a2d4176.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_12e84929eba593a9c963c2135bbd9c29c6a2d4176.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Positioned as a Leader in 2022 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Cloud HCM Suites for 1,000+ Employee Enterprises for Seventh Consecutive Year" src="./media_12e84929eba593a9c963c2135bbd9c29c6a2d4176.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-positioned-as-a-leader-in-2022-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-cloud-hcm-suites-for-1000-employee-enterprises-for-seventh-consecutive-year">SAP Positioned as a Leader in 2022 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Cloud HCM Suites for 1,000+ Employee Enterprises for Seventh Consecutive Year</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>For the seventh consecutive year, <a href="http://sap.com/hr">SAP</a> has been named a Leader in the “Gartner Magic Quadrant for Cloud HCM Suites for 1,000+ Employee Enterprises.”</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The world of work has changed dramatically since the report’s inception, elevating the role of people and culture leaders. The need for rich data and actionable insights, employee expectations for greater self-service and mobile functionality, a growing skills gap, and the ability to manage an increasingly dispersed workforce are just a few of the major shifts we have experienced. With all of these changes, one constant has remained clear: the need for people to be at the center of business is more critical than ever.</p>
  <p>This is why more than 9,400 customers worldwide — from mid-market organizations to global enterprises with 100,000+ employees — count on SAP SuccessFactors Human Experience Management (HXM) Suite to elevate their people function and drive transformational change throughout their business. Together with <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/s4hana.html">SAP S/4HANA Cloud</a>, <a href="https://www.fieldglass.com/">SAP Fieldglass</a> solutions, and the broader SAP portfolio, they can connect their people processes across the business to truly put people at the center.</p>
  <p>“For MOD Pizza, providing exceptional employee experiences is key to driving workforce engagement and business success,” said Tara Gambill, senior director of Enterprise Systems for <a href="https://www.sap.com/asset/dynamic/2022/8/ed4692e7-32d5-49e9-9240-a0a2dc2f8909.html">MOD Pizza LLC</a>. “People data is the lifeblood of the system. With intelligent technologies from SAP, we can create integration end to end, and leverage that data to get people connected and productive faster.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="put-people-at-the-heart-of-your-hr-strategy">Put people at the heart of your HR strategy</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="building-a-future-ready-workforce">Building a Future-Ready Workforce</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-more-new-and-coverage-from-successconnect">Read more new and coverage from SuccessConnect</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/topics/successconnect">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As we look at the changing dynamics of what people and organizations need to succeed, it requires a change in thinking. People thrive when they are engaged in their careers and have a sense of belonging; organizations thrive when their people are properly skilled and aligned to the right opportunities.</p>
  <p>Global HR industry influencer Josh Bersin recently <a href="https://joshbersin.com/2022/09/sap-successfactors-launches-its-biggest-release-in-a-decade/">said</a>: “[<a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/opportunity-marketplace.html">SAP SuccessFactors Opportunity Marketplace]</a> is integrated into the [SAP] SuccessFactors stack, making talent marketplace an integrated part of HCM. SAP is going further. While the talent marketplace is often seen as a ‘product’ or set of features, it really is much more. It’s a new, modern way of thinking about pay, jobs, roles, and growth.”</p>
  <p>At <a href="https://events.sap.com/successconnect/en/global-home">SuccessConnect</a>, we introduced new innovations to transform talent development for the future of work, and bring the whole self model to life. Informed by our team of behavioral scientists, these innovations use data and machine learning to continuously understand the capabilities within the workforce as well as each person’s whole self — their skills, aspirations, interests, strengths. This intelligence enables organizations to match people with dynamic teams and ongoing growth opportunities. The result is people-centric organizations that provide individuals with opportunities to grow and learn in alignment with the needs of the business.</p>
  <p>Vicki Furnish, vice president of Global People Solutions Operations and Analytics at <a href="/2022/09/ntt-data-it-takes-entire-team-to-win">NTT DATA Services,</a> said it perfectly when discussing NTT DATA Services’ move to SAP SuccessFactors: “If we put the right foundation in for our team and people, our team members will be successful. If they are successful, we will then be successful in our business.”</p>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div>Read the full report here: <a href="https://www.gartner.com/reprints/?id=1-2BGRQGI7&#x26;ct=221021&#x26;st=sb">Gartner Magic Quadrant for Cloud HCM Suites for 1,000+ Employee Enterprises</a>.</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>Amy Wilson is senior vice president of Products and Design for SAP SuccessFactors.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Gartner does not endorse any vendor, product or service depicted in its research publications and does not advise technology users to select only those vendors with the highest ratings or other designation. Gartner research publications consist of the opinions of Gartner’s research organization and should not be construed as statements of fact. Gartner disclaims all warranties, expressed or implied, with respect to this research, including any warranties of merchantability or fitness for a particular purpose.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/future-of-work</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/magic-quadrant</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Is a Leader in the 2022 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Cloud ERP for Product-Centric Enterprises]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/09/magic-quadrant-cloud-erp-for-product-centric-enterprises-sap-a-leader</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/09/magic-quadrant-cloud-erp-for-product-centric-enterprises-sap-a-leader</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Gartner has named SAP a Leader in the Magic Quadrant for Cloud ERP for Product-Centric Enterprises with S/4HANA Cloud being evaluated.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/magic-quadrant</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Recognized as a Leader in 2022 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Data Integration Tools]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/2022-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-data-integration-tools-sap-a-leader</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/2022-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-data-integration-tools-sap-a-leader</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is a Leader in the 2022 Magic Quadrant for Data Integration Tools for the 15th consecutive year. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/data-fabric</category>
            <category>news-tag/data-integration</category>
            <category>news-tag/database-and-data-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/magic-quadrant</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-data-intelligence</category>
            <category>product/sap-data-intelligence-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Named a Leader in 2022 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Digital Commerce]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/2022-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-digital-commerce-sap-a-leader</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/2022-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-digital-commerce-sap-a-leader</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP been named a leader in the 2022 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Digital Commerce for the eighth time. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/magic-quadrant</category>
            <category>product/sap-commerce-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-customer-experience</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP S/4HANA Cloud Is a Leader in the Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Cloud ERP for Service-Centric Enterprises, 2022]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/gartner-magic-quadrant-for-cloud-erp-for-service-centric-enterprises-sap-s-4hana-cloud</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/gartner-magic-quadrant-for-cloud-erp-for-service-centric-enterprises-sap-s-4hana-cloud</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP has been recognized as a leader in the Gartner Magic Quadrant for Cloud ERP for Service-Centric Enterprises. Learn why.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/magic-quadrant</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Again Named a Leader in 2021 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Cloud Database Management Systems]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/sap-again-a-leader-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-cloud-database-management-systems</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/sap-again-a-leader-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-cloud-database-management-systems</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP has once again been positioned as a Leader in the 2021 Gartner Inc. Magic Quadrant for Cloud Database Management Systems.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14e7ea355f2a41e4186af1b367d4bb3ed49371173.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14e7ea355f2a41e4186af1b367d4bb3ed49371173.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_14e7ea355f2a41e4186af1b367d4bb3ed49371173.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Again Named a Leader in 2021 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Cloud Database Management Systems" src="./media_14e7ea355f2a41e4186af1b367d4bb3ed49371173.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-again-named-a-leader-in-2021-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-cloud-database-management-systems">SAP Again Named a Leader in 2021 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Cloud Database Management Systems</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-hana-high-performance-in-memory-database-that-provides-advanced-analytics-on-multimodel-data">SAP HANA: High-performance in-memory database that provides advanced analytics on multimodel data</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hana/cloud.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced it has once again been positioned as a Leader in the 2021 <a href="http://www.gartner.com/technology/home.jsp">Gartner Inc.</a> “<a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hana.html?campaigncode=CRM-PM21-AIP-SYNPR2AGMQ&#x26;rc=https%3A%2F%2Fdam.sap.com%2Fa%2FR8G15H5">Magic Quadrant™ for Cloud Database Management Systems</a>” report.*</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Gartner evaluated 20 vendors and named SAP a Leader based on “completeness of vision and ability to execute.”</p>
  <p>“SAP’s cloud-first mind-set paves a critical, future-proof path forward for our customers. SAP Business Technology Platform serves as the unified, business-centric, and open platform for our customers to become an intelligent enterprise — helping to integrate and extend applications, streamline workflows and processes, and unlock powerful insights across all data,” said JG Chirapurath, Chief Marketing and Solutions Officer, SAP BTP, SAP. “We believe this latest Gartner report demonstrates how we’ve successfully transitioned our leadership in the data management space to the cloud.”</p>
  <p>Gartner reviewed several SAP products for this Magic Quadrant. The products, which address both operational and analytical DBMS use cases, include the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hana/cloud.html">SAP HANA Cloud</a> database, the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/data-warehouse-cloud.html">SAP Data Warehouse Cloud</a> solution, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/sybase-ase.html">SAP Adaptive Server Enterprise</a>, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/sybase-iq-big-data-management.html">SAP IQ</a> software and the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/sql-anywhere.html">SAP SQL Anywhere</a> suite.</p>
  <p>SAP HANA is the database management foundation of SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP) and is trusted by over 58,000 SAP customers to manage their most business-critical data. With the ability to process transactional and analytical workloads in real time — no matter where the data resides — SAP HANA is uniquely suited to support our customers’ intelligent enterprise journey.</p>
  <p>Access a <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hana.html?campaigncode=CRM-PM21-AIP-SYNPR2AGMQ&#x26;rc=https%3A%2F%2Fdam.sap.com%2Fa%2FR8G15H5">complimentary copy</a> of the 2021 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Cloud Database Management Systems report.</p>
  <p>For more information, visit the executive <a href="https://blogs.sap.com/?p=1450757&#x26;preview=true&#x26;preview_id=1450757">blog</a>.</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="http://news.sap.com/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP on Twitter at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Media Contact:</strong> Scott Malinowski, +1 (617) 538-6297, <a href="mailto:scott.malinowski@sap.com">scott.malinowski@sap.com</a>, ET<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p><em>*Gartner <strong>,</strong> Magic Quadrant for Cloud Database Management Systems, <a href="https://www.gartner.com/analyst/58568">Henry Cook</a>, <a href="https://www.gartner.com/analyst/38961">Merv Adrian</a>, <a href="https://www.gartner.com/analyst/50744">Rick Greenwald</a>, <a href="https://www.gartner.com/analyst/52420">Adam Ronthal</a>, <a href="https://www.gartner.com/analyst/96730">Philip Russom</a>, 14 December 2021.</em><br>Gartner and Magic Quadrant are registered trademarks of Gartner, Inc. and/or its affiliates in the United States and internationally and are used herein with permission. All rights reserved. Gartner does not endorse any vendor, product or service depicted in its research publications, and does not advise technology users to select only those vendors with the highest ratings or other designation. Gartner research publications consist of the opinions of Gartner’s research organization and should not be construed as statements of fact. Gartner disclaims all warranties, expressed or implied, with respect to this research, including any warranties of merchantability or fitness for a particular purpose.</p>
  <p>Any statements contained in this document that are not historical facts are forward-looking statements as defined in the U.S. Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995. Words such as “anticipate,” “believe,” “estimate,” “expect,” “forecast,” “intend,” “may,” “plan,” “project,” “predict,” “should” and “will” and similar expressions as they relate to SAP are intended to identify such forward-looking statements. SAP undertakes no obligation to publicly update or revise any forward-looking statements. All forward-looking statements are subject to various risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results to differ materially from expectations. The factors that could affect SAP’s future financial results are discussed more fully in SAP’s filings with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (“SEC”), including SAP’s most recent Annual Report on Form 20-F filed with the SEC. Readers are cautioned not to place undue reliance on these forward-looking statements, which speak only as of their dates.<br>© 2021 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/magic-quadrant</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Named a Leader in 2021 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Configure, Price and Quote Application Suites]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/sap-a-leader-magic-quadrant-cpq-application-suites</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/sap-a-leader-magic-quadrant-cpq-application-suites</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[For the fourth consecutive year, SAP is again a Leader in the 2021 Gartner Magic Quadrant for CPQ Application Suites. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1003a8ab55898d80871e8dfdb899389a2c8a7fc26.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1003a8ab55898d80871e8dfdb899389a2c8a7fc26.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1003a8ab55898d80871e8dfdb899389a2c8a7fc26.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Named a Leader in 2021 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Configure, Price and Quote Application Suites" src="./media_1003a8ab55898d80871e8dfdb899389a2c8a7fc26.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-named-a-leader-in-2021-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-configure-price-and-quote-application-suites">SAP Named a Leader in 2021 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Configure, Price and Quote Application Suites</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-cpq-deliver-the-perfect-solution-for-your-customers-with-fast-and-accurate-quotes">SAP CPQ: Deliver the perfect solution for your customers with fast and accurate quotes</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/cpq.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced it has been positioned as a Leader in the 2021 <a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/cx/gartner-mq-cpq/index.html">Gartner Magic Quadrant for Configure, Price and Quote Application Suites</a>.<sup>1</sup> This is the fourth consecutive year SAP has been positioned as a Leader in this Gartner Magic Quadrant.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/cpq.html">SAP CPQ</a> solution helps streamline the sales-quote-to-cash process, leading to more signed deals, higher margins and a better experience for both sales and customers.</p>
  <p>“Customers expect a buying process that is quick and simple, no matter how complicated the product or service might be,” said Sameer Patel, chief marketing and solution officer for SAP Customer Experience. “The last mile of the transaction is extremely critical in the buying process and serves as an opportunity for brands to stand out from the competition and deliver on the customers expectation of a great experience. With SAP CPQ, sales teams and partners have the power to quickly build a quote for the right solution, at the right price, every single time.”</p>
  <p>SAP CPQ is part of the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm.html">SAP Customer Experience</a> portfolio, which goes beyond traditional CRM solutions by bringing together customer data, experiential and operational data, and machine learning. SAP Customer Experience offers organizations a complete platform to address all customer interactions using a common data model and functionality from commerce, marketing, sales and service to address their business needs.</p>
  <p>To learn more, <a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/cx/gartner-mq-cpq/index.html">download a complimentary copy</a> of the Gartner Magic Quadrant for CPQ Application Suites.</p>
  <p>Recently, SAP was also named a Leader in the <a href="/2021/09/gartner-magic-quadrant-for-digital-commerce-sap-a-leader">2021 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Digital Commerce<sup>2</sup></a> for the seventh time and as a Leader in the <a href="/2021/08/sap-leader-2021-gartner-magic-quadrant-sales-force-automation">2021 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Sales Force Automation</a><sup>3</sup> for the third consecutive year. Additionally, Emarsys, now part of SAP, was recently named a Leader for the third time in the <a href="/2021/07/emarsys-personalization-engines-magic-quadrant">2021 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Personalization Engines</a>.<sup>4</sup></p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Visit the <a href="http://news.sap.com/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP on Twitter at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Media Contact:</strong> Samantha Finnegan, +1 (415) 377-0475, <a href="mailto:samantha.finnegan@sap.com">samantha.finnegan@sap.com</a>, ET<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>1. Gartner, “Magic Quadrant for Configure, Price and Quote Application Suites,” <a href="https://www.gartner.com/analyst/61052">Mark Lewis</a>, <a href="https://www.gartner.com/analyst/84153">Dayna Ford</a>, October 21, 2021.<br>2. Gartner, “Magic Quadrant for Digital Commerce,” Jason Daigler, Yanna Dharmasthira, Sandy Shen, Penny Gillespie, Mike Lowndes, Aditya Vasudevan, August 31, 2021.<br>3. Gartner, “Magic Quadrant for Sales Force Automation,” Adnan Zijadic, Ilona Hansen, Melissa Hilbert, Steve Rietberg, August 4, 2021.<br>4. Gartner, “Magic Quadrant for Personalization Engines,”<a href="https://www.gartner.com/analyst/88875">Jason McNellis</a>, <a href="https://www.gartner.com/analyst/67591">Claire Tassin</a>, <a href="https://www.gartner.com/analyst/46806">Jennifer Polk</a>, July 19, 2021.</p>
  <p><em>Gartner does not endorse any vendor, product or service depicted in its research publications, and does not advise technology users to select only those vendors with the highest ratings or other designation. Gartner research publications consist of the opinions of Gartner’s research organization and should not be construed as statements of fact. Gartner disclaims all warranties, expressed or implied, with respect to this research, including any warranties of merchantability or fitness for a particular purpose.</em><br><em>Gartner and Magic Quadrant are registered trademarks of Gartner, Inc. and/or its affiliates in the U.S. and internationally and is used herein with permission. All rights reserved.</em></p>
  <p>Any statements contained in this document that are not historical facts are forward-looking statements as defined in the U.S. Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995. Words such as “anticipate,” “believe,” “estimate,” “expect,” “forecast,” “intend,” “may,” “plan,” “project,” “predict,” “should” and “will” and similar expressions as they relate to SAP are intended to identify such forward-looking statements. SAP undertakes no obligation to publicly update or revise any forward-looking statements. All forward-looking statements are subject to various risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results to differ materially from expectations. The factors that could affect SAP’s future financial results are discussed more fully in SAP’s filings with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (“SEC”), including SAP’s most recent Annual Report on Form 20-F filed with the SEC. Readers are cautioned not to place undue reliance on these forward-looking statements, which speak only as of their dates.<br>© 2021 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/magic-quadrant</category>
            <category>product/sap-cpq</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-customer-experience</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Named a Leader in 2021 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Procure-to-Pay Suites for the Sixth Time in a Row]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/sap-a-leader-magic-quadrant-for-p2p-suites</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/sap-a-leader-magic-quadrant-for-p2p-suites</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP has been named a Leader in Gartner Magic Quadrant for P2P Suites for the sixth time in a row. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_13efc87f7478d1b22417fed7bb9c5328dab4ce44b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_13efc87f7478d1b22417fed7bb9c5328dab4ce44b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_13efc87f7478d1b22417fed7bb9c5328dab4ce44b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Named a Leader in 2021 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Procure-to-Pay Suites for the Sixth Time in a Row" src="./media_13efc87f7478d1b22417fed7bb9c5328dab4ce44b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-named-a-leader-in-2021-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-procure-to-pay-suites-for-the-sixth-time-in-a-row">SAP Named a Leader in 2021 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Procure-to-Pay Suites for the Sixth Time in a Row</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="rethink-the-procurement-experience-to-streamline-the-process-and-guide-users-to-the-best-choices-in-the-least-amount-of-time">Rethink the procurement experience to streamline the process and guide users to the best choices in the least amount of time</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/10/sap-a-leader-magic-quadrant-for-p2p-suites">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced that independent analyst firm Gartner Inc. has positioned SAP as a Leader in its <a href="https://www.ariba.com/resources/2021-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-procure-to-pay-suites/?campaigncode=CRM-PR21-XIP-P2PMQPR">2021 “Magic Quadrant for Procure-to-Pay Suites” report</a>.* Gartner evaluated 12 vendors, and following an evaluation of SAP Ariba and SAP Fieldglass solutions named SAP a Leader based on its “Ability to Execute” and “Completeness of Vision.”</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>This is the sixth consecutive time Gartner has named SAP a Leader in the Magic Quadrant for Procure-to-Pay Suites.</p>
  <p>Gartner defines the procure-to-pay (P2P) suite market as “integrated solutions with automated workflows to request, procure, receive and pay for goods and services across an enterprise. These solutions are marketed as suitable for processing, at a basic level, all types of spending including indirect goods, direct goods and services. P2P suites optimize the purchasing process, resulting in improved financial controls, process compliance, cost savings (or cost avoidance) and mitigated risk.”</p>
  <p>“The tumultuous past few years have highlighted just how important procurement is to business health and resilience,” said Etosha Thurman, chief marketing and solutions officer, Intelligent Spend and Business Network, SAP. “Gaining real-time visibility into all aspects of the supply chain — from trading partners’ inventory and capacity to enterprise-wide spend — has proven crucial. With SAP solutions, our customers gain a holistic, unified view of all types of spend. We believe our Leader position in this report underscores our best-in-class solutions and continued innovation — particularly our improved buying experience and unmatched network vision.”</p>
  <p>SAP solutions rely on digital networks to create source to pay process efficiencies that improve procurement performance and drive business value. <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-network.html">SAP Business Network</a> brings together Ariba Network, SAP Logistics Business Network and SAP Asset Intelligence Network to help transform fragmented supply chains into unified, collaborative and intelligent networks. The network provides greater agility, visibility and collaboration between organizations and their trading partners. SAP also continues to invest in deeper integration between its intelligent spend management and enterprise resource planning solutions.</p>
  <p>A complimentary copy of <a href="https://www.ariba.com/resources/2021-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-procure-to-pay-suites/?campaigncode=CRM-PR21-XIP-P2PMQPR">the Gartner report is available here</a>.</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="http://news.sap.com/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP on Twitter at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Media Contacts:</strong> Kelly Sheldon Murray, +1 (978) 708-6821, <a href="mailto:kelly.murray@sap.com">kelly.murray@sap.com</a>, ET<br>Geraldine Lim, +1 (415) 418-0945, <a href="mailto:geraldine.lim@sap.com">geraldine.lim@sap.com</a>, PT<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>*Gartner, “Magic Quadrant for Procure-to-Pay Suites,” Kaitlynn Sommers, William McNeill, Micky Keck, Patrick Connaughton, October 25, 2021.<br>SAP was referred to as Ariba (SAP) in the 2015 report and SAP (Ariba and Fieldglass) in 2016, 2018 and 2019 reports.<br>Gartner does not endorse any vendor, product or service depicted in our research publications, and does not advise technology users to select only those vendors with the highest ratings or other designation. Gartner research publications consist of the opinions of Gartner’s research organization and should not be construed as statements of fact. Gartner disclaims all warranties, expressed or implied, with respect to this research, including any warranties of merchantability or fitness for a particular purpose.<br>Gartner and Magic Quadrant are registered trademarks of Gartner, Inc. and/or its affiliates in the U.S. and internationally and are used herein with permission. All rights reserved.</p>
  <p>Any statements contained in this document that are not historical facts are forward-looking statements as defined in the U.S. Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995. Words such as “anticipate,” “believe,” “estimate,” “expect,” “forecast,” “intend,” “may,” “plan,” “project,” “predict,” “should” and “will” and similar expressions as they relate to SAP are intended to identify such forward-looking statements. SAP undertakes no obligation to publicly update or revise any forward-looking statements. All forward-looking statements are subject to various risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results to differ materially from expectations. The factors that could affect SAP’s future financial results are discussed more fully in SAP’s filings with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (“SEC”), including SAP’s most recent Annual Report on Form 20-F filed with the SEC. Readers are cautioned not to place undue reliance on these forward-looking statements, which speak only as of their dates.<br>© 2021 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/magic-quadrant</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Positioned as a Leader in Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Cloud HCM Suites for 1,000+ Employee Enterprises for Sixth Consecutive Year]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/sap-leader-gartner-magic-quadrant-cloud-hcm-suites</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/sap-leader-gartner-magic-quadrant-cloud-hcm-suites</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Gartner has named SAP a Leader in the Magic Quadrant for Cloud HCM Suites for 1,000+ Employee Enterprises. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1cd2f4aafee563e4b7c257647e339e4992f5f137a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1cd2f4aafee563e4b7c257647e339e4992f5f137a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1cd2f4aafee563e4b7c257647e339e4992f5f137a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Positioned as a Leader in Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Cloud HCM Suites for 1,000+ Employee Enterprises for Sixth Consecutive Year" src="./media_1cd2f4aafee563e4b7c257647e339e4992f5f137a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-positioned-as-a-leader-in-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-cloud-hcm-suites-for-1000-employee-enterprises-for-sixth-consecutive-year">SAP Positioned as a Leader in Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Cloud HCM Suites for 1,000+ Employee Enterprises for Sixth Consecutive Year</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="put-employees-at-the-heart-of-everything-you-do-with-sap-successfactors-software">Put employees at the heart of everything you do with SAP SuccessFactors software</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced that Gartner Inc. has named SAP a Leader in the latest “Magic Quadrant for Cloud HCM Suites for 1,000+ Employee Enterprises” report.* The report recognized SAP for its completeness of vision and ability to execute.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP has been positioned as a Leader in this report since its inception in 2016.</p>
  <p>The <a href="https://www.sap.com/hr">SAP SuccessFactors Human Experience Management (HXM) Suite</a> provides scalable, cloud-based solutions that span <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm/products.html#active_tab=item_1602592257238">core HR and payroll</a>, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm/products.html#active_tab=item_1602592296240">talent management</a>, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm/products.html#active_tab=item_1602592281950">people analytics and workforce planning</a>, and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm/products.html#active_tab=item_1602592051931">employee experience management</a>. Over 12,000 customers in more than 200 countries leverage HXM solutions from SAP to deliver individualized experiences that keep employees engaged, productive and connected. More than 4,800 customers use the SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central solution.</p>
  <p>“SAP continues to lead the human capital management [HCM] market globally while building momentum around our HXM vision,” said Meg Bear, SAP SuccessFactors chief product officer. “We have embedded employee listening throughout our portfolio, invested in our architecture, reimagined the user experience of our solutions and delivered new products including the <a href="/2021/09/hr-executive-top-product-sap-successfactors-work-zone">SAP SuccessFactors Work Zone</a> and <a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/dg/g-experience-opportunity-campaign/index.html">SAP SuccessFactors Opportunity Marketplace</a> solutions. By focusing on how to empower people at work, we can help them shape a career that connects to their purpose while helping our customers build the agility they need to keep pace with continuous change.”</p>
  <p><a href="/2021/10/sap-successfactors-opportunity-marketplace-drives-internal-mobility-and-upskilling-to-help-organizations-future-proof-their-business">SAP SuccessFactors Opportunity Marketplace</a>, announced this month, connects workers with individualized recommendations to promote their growth and development including mentorships, learning activities and short-term assignments. It is backed by a center of capabilities, a machine learning–based framework that creates a holistic view of an individual that adapts over time.</p>
  <p>Additionally, SAP unveiled its vision for technology to identify, track, measure and optimize the outcomes of dynamic teams. A dynamic team is a group of people that works together on a project or initiative and disbands once the team’s goals are achieved.</p>
  <p>For more information, visit the <a href="http://news.sap.com/">SAP News Center</a> and the <a href="http://sap.com/hr">Human Experience Management section of SAP.com</a>.</p>
  <p>Follow SAP on Twitter at <a href="https://twitter.com/successfactors">@SuccessFactors</a> and <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Media Contact:</strong><br>Samantha Yerks, +1 (914) 918-6087, <a href="mailto:samantha.yerks@sap.com">samantha.yerks@sap.com</a>, ET<br><a href="mailto:SAP%20News%20Center%20press%20room">SAP News Center press room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p><em>*Gartner, Magic Quadrant for Cloud HCM Suites for 1,000+ Employee Enterprises, Sam Grinter, Chris Pang, et al., 19 October 2021.</em><br><em>Gartner does not endorse any vendor, product or service depicted in its research publications, and does not advise technology users to select only those vendors with the highest ratings or other designation. Gartner research publications consist of the opinions of Gartner’s research organization and should not be construed as statements of fact. Gartner disclaims all warranties, expressed or implied, with respect to this research, including any warranties of merchantability or fitness for a particular purpose.</em><br><em>GARTNER and MAGIC QUADRANT are registered trademark and service mark of Gartner, Inc. and/or its affiliates in the U.S. and internationally and are used herein with permission. All rights reserved.</em></p>
  <p>Any statements contained in this document that are not historical facts are forward-looking statements as defined in the U.S. Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995. Words such as “anticipate,” “believe,” “estimate,” “expect,” “forecast,” “intend,” “may,” “plan,” “project,” “predict,” “should” and “will” and similar expressions as they relate to SAP are intended to identify such forward-looking statements. SAP undertakes no obligation to publicly update or revise any forward-looking statements. All forward-looking statements are subject to various risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results to differ materially from expectations. The factors that could affect SAP’s future financial results are discussed more fully in SAP’s filings with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (“SEC”), including SAP’s most recent Annual Report on Form 20-F filed with the SEC. Readers are cautioned not to place undue reliance on these forward-looking statements, which speak only as of their dates.<br>© 2021 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/magic-quadrant</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Integration Is the Secret Sauce of Digital Transformation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/integration-digital-transformation-endress-hauser-sap-btp</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/integration-digital-transformation-endress-hauser-sap-btp</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 11 Oct 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Endress+Hauser demonstrates why enterprise integration is so important to digital transformation. Read its SAP BTP story here.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/magic-quadrant</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-integration-suite</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Named a Leader in 2021 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Data Quality Solutions for the 15th Time in a Row]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/sap-a-leader-magic-quadrant-for-data-quality-solutions</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/sap-a-leader-magic-quadrant-for-data-quality-solutions</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[For the 15th consecutive year, Gartner has named SAP a Leader in the Magic Quadrant for Data Quality Solutions report.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1381148cc7bc7bd04a2ac63a702d499a37236c656.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1381148cc7bc7bd04a2ac63a702d499a37236c656.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1381148cc7bc7bd04a2ac63a702d499a37236c656.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Named a Leader in 2021 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Data Quality Solutions for the 15th Time in a Row" src="./media_1381148cc7bc7bd04a2ac63a702d499a37236c656.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-named-a-leader-in-2021-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-data-quality-solutions-for-the-15th-time-in-a-row">SAP Named a Leader in 2021 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Data Quality Solutions for the 15th Time in a Row</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-business-technology-platform-accelerate-business-outcomes-with-integration-data-to-value-and-extensibility">SAP Business Technology Platform: Accelerate business outcomes with integration, data to value, and extensibility</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced that independent analyst firm <a href="http://www.gartner.com/technology/home.jsp">Gartner Inc.</a> has named SAP a Leader in its <a href="https://www.gartner.com/reprints/?id=1-27EPJ5JP&#x26;ct=210910&#x26;st=sb">Magic Quadrant for Data Quality Solutions report</a>.*</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Gartner evaluated 15 vendors and named SAP a Leader based on its “ability to execute” and “completeness of vision.” This is the 15th consecutive year that SAP has been named a Leader in the Magic Quadrant for Data Quality Solutions.</p>
  <p>According to Gartner, “Augmented data quality, driven by metadata and AI, is a key dynamic driving the data quality solutions market. Leading vendors’ augmented capabilities provide greater insights and automation. This research helps data and analytics leaders understand the vendor landscape and make the best choice.”</p>
  <p>“In today’s digital economy, data is the most valuable resource,” said Andreas Wesselmann, SAP senior vice president, SAP HANA &#x26; Analytics, Data Management. “Improved data quality can drive profits, innovation and customer satisfaction, while decreasing risk and resulting in consistent improvements in results. SAP’s portfolio of data management solutions improves the quality of data across the enterprise, delivering trusted, relevant and timely information to drive better business outcomes and help customers on their path to becoming intelligent enterprises.”</p>
  <p><a href="https://www.sapowernetworks.com.au/">SA Power Networks</a>, a leading distributor of electricity in Australia, is using SAP Data Services and SAP Information Steward software to boost the management and delivery of customer data. “With SAP Data Services and SAP Information Steward, we’ve slashed response times to issues,” said Janice Espinosa, project manager, Employee Hub for Customer Data, SA Power Network. “And we’ve seen customer satisfaction levels rise as a result.”</p>
  <p>As part of <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">SAP Business Technology Platform</a>, SAP’s portfolio of data management solutions helps customers manage data to glean meaningful insights for creating efficient business processes. Users can proactively govern data across the organization to help ensure trustworthy information for smarter decision-making. Data quality solutions from SAP help businesses discover, understand and manage multifaceted data. Companies can profile, cleanse, enrich and match customer, product, supplier, material and other data, driving more accurate, trustworthy and timely information.</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="http://news.sap.com/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP on Twitter at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Media Contact:</strong> Julia Fargel, +1 (650) 276-8964, <a href="mailto:julia.fargel@sap.com">julia.fargel@sap.com</a>, PT<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>*Gartner, Magic Quadrant for Data Quality Solutions, <a href="https://www.gartner.com/analyst/62722">Melody Chien</a>, <a href="https://www.gartner.com/analyst/54549">Ankush Jain</a>, 29 September 2021.<br>Gartner does not endorse any vendor, product or service depicted in its research publications, and does not advise technology users to select only those vendors with the highest ratings or other designation. Gartner research publications consist of the opinions of Gartner’s research organization and should not be construed as statements of fact. Gartner disclaims all warranties, expressed or implied, with respect to this research, including any warranties of merchantability or fitness for a particular purpose.<br>GARTNER and Magic Quadrant are registered trademarks and service mark of Gartner, Inc. and/or its affiliates in the U.S. and internationally and are used herein with permission. All rights reserved.</p>
  <p>Any statements contained in this document that are not historical facts are forward-looking statements as defined in the U.S. Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995. Words such as “anticipate,” “believe,” “estimate,” “expect,” “forecast,” “intend,” “may,” “plan,” “project,” “predict,” “should” and “will” and similar expressions as they relate to SAP are intended to identify such forward-looking statements. SAP undertakes no obligation to publicly update or revise any forward-looking statements. All forward-looking statements are subject to various risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results to differ materially from expectations. The factors that could affect SAP’s future financial results are discussed more fully in SAP’s filings with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (“SEC”), including SAP’s most recent Annual Report on Form 20-F filed with the SEC. Readers are cautioned not to place undue reliance on these forward-looking statements, which speak only as of their dates.<br>© 2021 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/magic-quadrant</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-integration-suite</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Positioned as a Leader in the Gartner Magic Quadrant for Enterprise Integration Platform-as-a-Service]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/sap-a-leader-magic-quadrant-for-enterprise-integration-platform-as-a-service</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/sap-a-leader-magic-quadrant-for-enterprise-integration-platform-as-a-service</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Gartner has named SAP a Leader in its Magic Quadrant for Enterprise Integration Platform-as-a-Service report for the second year in a row.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/magic-quadrant</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-integration-suite</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Named a Leader in 2021 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Digital Commerce]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/gartner-magic-quadrant-for-digital-commerce-sap-a-leader</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/gartner-magic-quadrant-for-digital-commerce-sap-a-leader</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP has been named a Leader in the Gartner Magic Quadrant for Digital Commerce for the seventh time. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a4c969871301bddfedbdb094fe5b6142c0715599.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a4c969871301bddfedbdb094fe5b6142c0715599.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1a4c969871301bddfedbdb094fe5b6142c0715599.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Named a Leader in 2021 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Digital Commerce" src="./media_1a4c969871301bddfedbdb094fe5b6142c0715599.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-named-a-leader-in-2021-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-digital-commerce">SAP Named a Leader in 2021 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Digital Commerce</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="digital-commerce-deliver-a-rich-personalized-omnichannel-e-commerce-experience-and-gain-agility-to-meet-ever-changing-customer-needs">Digital Commerce: Deliver a rich, personalized omnichannel e-commerce experience and gain agility to meet ever-changing customer needs</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm/e-commerce-platforms.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced it has been named a Leader in the 2021 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Digital Commerce* for the seventh time. In its latest 2021 report, Gartner assessed solutions from 17 vendors including <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm/e-commerce-platforms.html">commerce solutions from SAP</a>.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Brands globally, including appliance manufacturer De’Longhi, nutritional products distributor Kyani and retailer Abrakadabra, have recently selected SAP solutions to help deliver a rich, personalized omnichannel e-commerce experience that is reliable and scales to meet the demands of their customers.</p>
  <p>“We believe this latest positioning as a Leader by Gartner is why brands across industries and geographies are turning to SAP to broaden their commerce reach without compromising flexibility,” said Nuno Pedro, global head, Commerce Solutions, SAP. “Digital commerce solutions from SAP enable success across different industries, marketplaces and business models by providing customers enjoyable, individually relevant, in-the-moment experiences.”</p>
  <p><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm/e-commerce-platforms.html">Digital commerce solutions from SAP</a>, which include <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/commerce-cloud.html">SAP Commerce Cloud</a> and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm/e-commerce-platforms.html#upscale-commerce">SAP Upscale Commerce</a>, help brands convert more customers by turning engagements into personal, shoppable moments. Additional companies that recently chose digital commerce solutions from SAP in the first half of 2021 include the following:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Hangcha Group</strong> is one of the largest forklift manufacturers in China and among the top 10 in the world. Hangcha Group chose SAP Commerce Cloud to simplify its front-end sales order intake process and integrate with its back-end digital core system, supporting the group’s business transformation and boosting sales revenue.</li>
    <li><strong><a href="/2021/06/sapphire-now-sap-upscale-commerce-midmarket-brands">JOY</a></strong>, a Swedish fashion retailer, no longer has any physical stores and is instead focusing on e-commerce and personalized fashion advice. Its founders see JOY as a startup building next-generation e-commerce based on AI and slow fashion — a more sustainable alternative with clothes lasting several seasons. JOY is also the first company in the world that has selected the combination of the cloud-based solution SAP Upscale Commerce and the SAP Emarsys Customer Engagement platform.</li>
    <li><strong>Perfumes y Esencias Fraiche</strong>, a Mexican company specializing in fragrances and essences that serves more than 20 million people through different sales channels, chose SAP Commerce Cloud and SAP Marketing Cloud. With these solutions, the company can strengthen its online presence to meet new consumer needs, using a solid digital strategy that enables personalized fragrance sales for its customers and through thousands of distributors.</li>
    <li><strong><a href="/2021/05/leading-european-organizations-deichmann-chemie-sap-cx">WAGO Kontakttechnik GmbH &#x26; Co</a></strong>. KG is a leading German manufacturer of electrical connections and components, and a specialist in spring clamps for automation. It recently implemented SAP Commerce Cloud solutions as part of its cloud transformation. With SAP Commerce Cloud integrated with SAP Marketing Cloud and the SAP ERP application, it plans to provide a great e-commerce experience for its business-to-business (B2B) customers.</li>
    <li><strong><a href="/2021/05/leading-european-organizations-deichmann-chemie-sap-cx">Wacker Chemie</a></strong> is a leading German player in highly developed specialty products for several industrial sectors. It recently implemented SAP Commerce Cloud as its new B2B e-commerce system to increase sales and improve customer satisfaction.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>Digital commerce solutions from SAP are part of the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm.html">SAP Customer Experience</a> portfolio, which goes beyond traditional CRM solutions by bringing together customer data, experiential and operational data, and machine learning.</p>
  <p>To learn more, download a <a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/cx/gartner-magic-quadrant-e-commerce/index.html?campaigncode=CRM-HY21-CIP-AGTMQDC&#x26;source=onlinedisplay-glo--commerce-led-experiences">complimentary copy of the report</a>, including Gartner’s in-depth analysis of the digital commerce landscape.</p>
  <p>SAP was also recognized for the third consecutive year as a Leader in the <a href="/2021/08/sap-leader-2021-gartner-magic-quadrant-sales-force-automation">2021 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Sales Force Automation</a>.** Additionally, Emarsys, now part of SAP, was recently named a Leader for the third time in the <a href="/2021/07/emarsys-personalization-engines-magic-quadrant">2021 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Personalization Engines</a>.***</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="http://news.sap.com/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP on Twitter at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Media Contact:</strong> Samantha Finnegan, +1 (415) 377-0475, <a href="mailto:samantha.finnegan@sap.com">samantha.finnegan@sap.com</a>, ET<br><a href="mailto:SAP%20Press%20Room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>*Gartner, “Magic Quadrant for Digital Commerce,” Jason Daigler, Yanna Dharmasthira, Sandy Shen, Penny Gillespie, Mike Lowndes, Aditya Vasudevan, August 31, 2021.<br>**Gartner, “Magic Quadrant for Sales Force Automation,” Adnan Zijadic, Ilona Hansen, Melissa Hilbert, Steve Rietberg, August 4, 2021.<br>***Gartner, “Magic Quadrant for Personalization Engines,” Jason McNellis, Claire Tassin, Jennifer Polk, July 19, 2021.<br><em>Gartner does not endorse any vendor, product or service depicted in its research publications, and does not advise technology users to select only those vendors with the highest ratings or other designation. Gartner research publications consist of the opinions of Gartner’s research organization and should not be construed as statements of fact. Gartner disclaims all warranties, expressed or implied, with respect to this research, including any warranties of merchantability or fitness for a particular purpose.</em><br><em>Gartner and Magic Quadrant are registered trademarks of Gartner, Inc. and/or its affiliates in the U.S. and internationally and is used herein with permission. All rights reserved.</em></p>
  <p>Any statements contained in this document that are not historical facts are forward-looking statements as defined in the U.S. Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995. Words such as “anticipate,” “believe,” “estimate,” “expect,” “forecast,” “intend,” “may,” “plan,” “project,” “predict,” “should” and “will” and similar expressions as they relate to SAP are intended to identify such forward-looking statements. SAP undertakes no obligation to publicly update or revise any forward-looking statements. All forward-looking statements are subject to various risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results to differ materially from expectations. The factors that could affect SAP’s future financial results are discussed more fully in SAP’s filings with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (“SEC”), including SAP’s most recent Annual Report on Form 20-F filed with the SEC. Readers are cautioned not to place undue reliance on these forward-looking statements, which speak only as of their dates.<br>© 2021 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-commerce</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/magic-quadrant</category>
            <category>product/sap-commerce-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-customer-experience</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Named a Leader in 2021 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Data Integration Tools for the 14th Year in a Row]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/sap-a-leader-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-data-integration-tools</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/sap-a-leader-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-data-integration-tools</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[For the 14th consecutive year, SAP has been named a Leader in the Magic Quadrant for Data Integration Tools. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_118130ba999d251626784244ba258cc2c6d0cd409.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_118130ba999d251626784244ba258cc2c6d0cd409.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_118130ba999d251626784244ba258cc2c6d0cd409.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Named a Leader in 2021 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Data Integration Tools for the 14th Year in a Row" src="./media_118130ba999d251626784244ba258cc2c6d0cd409.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-named-a-leader-in-2021-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-data-integration-tools-for-the-14th-year-in-a-row">SAP Named a Leader in 2021 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Data Integration Tools for the 14th Year in a Row</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="turn-data-chaos-into-data-value-with-data-intelligence">Turn data chaos into data value with data intelligence</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/data-intelligence.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced that independent analyst firm <a href="http://www.gartner.com/technology/home.jsp">Gartner Inc.</a> has named SAP a Leader in its <a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/dg/gartner-data-integration-tool-mq/index.html">Magic Quadrant™ for Data Integration Tools* report</a>. Gartner evaluated 18 vendors and named SAP a Leader based on “ability to execute” and “completeness of vision.”</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>This is the 14th consecutive year that SAP has been named a Leader in the Magic Quadrant for Data Integration Tools.</p>
  <p>According to Gartner, “The data integration tool market is seeing renewed momentum, driven by requirements for hybrid and multicloud data integration, augmented data management, and data fabric designs. This assessment of 18 vendors will help data and analytics leaders choose a best fit for their data integration needs.”</p>
  <p>“This latest recognition from Gartner acknowledges SAP’s ongoing commitment to improving our customers’ data integration across the enterprise,” said Andreas Wesselmann, senior vice president, SAP HANA Database &#x26; Analytics, Common Data Services at SAP. “As part of the information management layer of SAP Business Technology Platform, SAP’s data integration offerings deliver trusted, relevant and timely information to drive better business outcomes for our customers.”</p>
  <p><a href="https://corporate.evonik.com/en">Evonik Industries AG</a>, headquartered in Germany and one of the largest specialty chemicals companies in the world, is using the SAP Data Intelligence solution. “We have witnessed efficiency improvements for data management as well as higher data quality,” said Frank Schmalle, head of Enterprise Data Management, Global IT, Evonik Industries AG. “Using SAP Data Intelligence, we will continue our journey to streamline the handling of complex materials data across our business.”</p>
  <p>SAP’s data integration offerings include <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/data-intelligence.html">SAP Data Intelligence</a>, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/data-services.html">SAP Data Services</a>, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/landscape-replication-server.html">SAP Landscape Transformation Replication Server</a> and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/cloud-platform/capabilities/integration.html">SAP Integration Suite</a>, along with integration capabilities of <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hana.html">SAP HANA</a>. These offerings are part of <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">SAP Business Technology Platform</a> and focus on delivering comprehensive integration by providing users with intelligent and contextual insights through integration across the IT landscape.</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="http://news.sap.com/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP on Twitter at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Media Contact:</strong> Julia Fargel, +1 (650) 276-8964, <a href="mailto:julia.fargel@sap.com">julia.fargel@sap.com</a>, PT<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p><em>*Gartner, Magic Quadrant for Data Quality Solutions, published on August 25, 2021.</em><br><em>Gartner does not endorse any vendor, product or service depicted in its research publications, and does not advise technology users to select only those vendors with the highest ratings or other designation. Gartner research publications consist of the opinions of Gartner’s research organization and should not be construed as statements of fact. Gartner disclaims all warranties, expressed or implied, with respect to this research, including any warranties of merchantability or fitness for a particular purpose.</em><br><em>GARTNER and Magic Quadrant are registered trademarks and service mark of Gartner, Inc. and/or its affiliates in the U.S. and internationally and are used herein with permission. All rights reserved.</em></p>
  <p>Any statements contained in this document that are not historical facts are forward-looking statements as defined in the U.S. Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995. Words such as “anticipate,” “believe,” “estimate,” “expect,” “forecast,” “intend,” “may,” “plan,” “project,” “predict,” “should” and “will” and similar expressions as they relate to SAP are intended to identify such forward-looking statements. SAP undertakes no obligation to publicly update or revise any forward-looking statements. All forward-looking statements are subject to various risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results to differ materially from expectations. The factors that could affect SAP’s future financial results are discussed more fully in SAP’s filings with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (“SEC”), including SAP’s most recent Annual Report on Form 20-F filed with the SEC. Readers are cautioned not to place undue reliance on these forward-looking statements, which speak only as of their dates.<br>© 2021 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/magic-quadrant</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-data-intelligence</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>