<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/employee-engagement/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Meeting Workout: A Game to Improve the Meeting Experience]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/meeting-workout-game-to-improve-meeting-experience</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/meeting-workout-game-to-improve-meeting-experience</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[To address the challenge of unproductive meetings, SAP's Future of Work team and SAP AppHaus created the Meeting Workout board game.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-engagement</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/future-of-work</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-apphaus</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Game-Changing Role of Incentive Compensation Automation in the Retail Industry]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/incentive-compensation-automation-in-retail</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/incentive-compensation-automation-in-retail</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With SAP SuccessFactors Incentive Management, retailers can incorporate key performance indicators into their incentive structure.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10fff8c20499512be48a61b55b1b6ecdb00d8656a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10fff8c20499512be48a61b55b1b6ecdb00d8656a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_10fff8c20499512be48a61b55b1b6ecdb00d8656a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="The Game-Changing Role of Incentive Compensation Automation in the Retail Industry" src="./media_10fff8c20499512be48a61b55b1b6ecdb00d8656a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="the-game-changing-role-of-incentive-compensation-automation-in-the-retail-industry">The Game-Changing Role of Incentive Compensation Automation in the Retail Industry</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>In the dynamic world of retail, staying ahead means adapting to evolving customer expectations and embracing innovative solutions. The era of omnichannel retailing has ushered in demand for seamless, personalized shopping experiences, compelling businesses to think outside the box to support seamless experiences and minimize friction by providing the right product at the right time in the right place. Moreover, recognizing the intricate dance between employee satisfaction and customer experience, businesses are weaving a narrative where a better employee experience becomes the cornerstone for elevating customer delight.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>At the recent <a href="/topics/nrf">NRF event</a>, the world’s largest retail conference, the mantra of “adjust and adapt” echoed through the halls. AI and digital acceleration took the center stage, making innovation the heart of the conversation. Retailers also highlighted a crucial focus on a motivated workforce, emphasizing how an empowered workforce is critical to delivering exceptional customer experiences.</p>
  <p>In a landscape challenged by high turnover rates, retailers showcased their commitment to navigating complexity through strategic investments in their most valuable asset – their people. One of the pivotal elements that drives employee motivation and engagement in the retail industry is incentive compensation, where associates are often paid on commission.</p>
  <p>During NRF, Daniel Jasper from Neiman Marcus shared insights into how incentive compensation automation transformed the company’s commission payment process. With over 40 stores and a complex commission structure, Neiman Marcus faced challenges in managing incentive compensation. Its previous incentive management system was cumbersome and complex, which led to errors, delays, and frustration among sales associates. Implementing <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/sales-performance-management.html#products">the SAP SuccessFactors Incentive Management solution</a> helped streamline the process, providing real-time monitoring of commission calculations. This allowed Neiman Marcus to identify and resolve issues proactively, resulting in improved accuracy and timeliness of commission payments. “Rather than waiting to hear from associates that something is wrong, we can monitor the calculations in real-time and resolve issues in advance,” said Jasper. This shift has been a game-changer for Neiman Marcus, driving better sales and revenue growth.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="empower-sales-teams-with-the-tools-they-need-to-create-effective-sales-experiences">Empower sales teams with the tools they need to create effective sales experiences</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/sales-performance-management.html">Find out how</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP SuccessFactors Incentive Management is one of the sales performance management solutions in the SAP SuccessFactors portfolio, and it offers a sophisticated platform for tailoring incentive programs to suit the unique needs of retail associates. With powerful analytics, embedded intelligence, and built-in workflows, this solution can revolutionize compensation management. Its intelligent design can not only foster trust but also ignite motivation among store associates. Through a user-friendly mobile app, retail customers can enjoy a comprehensive and easily accessible view of both store and individual performance metrics, promoting transparency and a unified understanding of team dynamics and trends. Personalized recommendations, relevant insights, and interactive monitoring help enhance the user experience, while the mobile app helps ensure that store associates can access their incentives anytime, anywhere, from any device.</p>
  <p>The solution’s agility helps facilitate a swift rollout of new and updated compensation plans, offering the flexibility to manage broadly or tailor plans to individual needs. With a steadfast commitment to accuracy and traceability, associates can trust the fairness of calculations, fostering a positive work environment. The effective dating functionalities help further empower organizations, allowing seamless management of associate promotions and transfers.</p>
  <p>“Retail businesses more than ever need the ability to design and manage incentive plans that align with ever-changing organizational goals, with a focus on store-level personalization and granularity that allow for improved accuracy and timeliness of commission payments,” said Rahul Iyer, general manager of Sales Performance Management at SAP. “With SAP SuccessFactors Incentive Management, retailers can incorporate key performance indicators, such as sales per hour and units per sale, into their incentive structure. The mobile app can provide visibility and transparency into individual and store performance, effectively motivating and ensuring optimal performance from their associates.”</p>
  <p>In essence, SAP SuccessFactors Incentive Management emerges as an indispensable tool, helping to empower retail customers to optimize workforce performance and drive sustained success. Displaying key performance indicators and incentives has proven to be a game changer, helping to drive focus on store and individual performance. The result? Associates are more attentive to customers, guiding them through purchasing decisions and enhancing overall satisfaction.</p>
  <p>In the always-changing retail world, success comes down to three things: using better technology, having happy employees, and keeping customers in focus. The story of Neiman Marcus proves that automating incentives can be a game changer. It shows how a motivated and well-connected team can not just boost how things work but also bring in more sales and money.</p>
  <p>To stay ahead in retail, you need to be ready for change and invest in both tech and your team. This is a clear lesson for retailers planning for the future. Learn more about how <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2023/03/509d257a-677e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">sales performance management can simplify the retail industry</a>. To learn more about how sales performance management solutions can support your organization, visit the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/sales-performance-management.html">sales performance management product page on sap.com</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Kevin Coxwell is vice president of GTM for Sales Performance Management at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-sap-news-on-linkedin">Connect with SAP News on LinkedIn</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news">Follow us</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-engagement</category>
            <category>news-tag/nrf</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
            <category>news-tag/sales-performance-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP SuccessFactors Helps HR Solve Skills Gap with Generative AI]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/sap-successfactors-helps-hr-solve-skills-gap-with-generative-ai</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/sap-successfactors-helps-hr-solve-skills-gap-with-generative-ai</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Sapphire showcased new SAP SuccessFactors innovations that use generative AI to help HR teams recruit, retain, and upskill. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-engagement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>news-tag/total-workforce-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[AKT Global Keeps Remote Workforce Connected and Engaged]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/akt-global-keeps-remote-workforce-connected-engaged</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/akt-global-keeps-remote-workforce-connected-engaged</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP SuccessFactors Work Zone helps AKT Global bring its remote workforce together as one connected, engaged team. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-engagement</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-work-zone</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sustainable Business at Veolia ANZ: A Culture of Employee Engagement]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/veolia-anz-culture-of-employee-engagement</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/veolia-anz-culture-of-employee-engagement</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Aug 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Veolia ANZ builds a culture of employee engagement with SAP solutions as part of its sustainable business mission. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d9756ca8715dfa6172ff87e4a03e6f2be81050f0.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d9756ca8715dfa6172ff87e4a03e6f2be81050f0.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1d9756ca8715dfa6172ff87e4a03e6f2be81050f0.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Sustainable Business at Veolia ANZ: A Culture of Employee Engagement" src="./media_1d9756ca8715dfa6172ff87e4a03e6f2be81050f0.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sustainable-business-at-veolia-anz-a-culture-of-employee-engagement">Sustainable Business at Veolia ANZ: A Culture of Employee Engagement</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Sustainable business is one post-pandemic trend that’s here to stay, especially among global market leaders like <a href="https://www.veolia.com/anz/">Veolia ANZ</a>, a longtime champion of ecological transformation.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>With approximately 4,600 employees in Australia and 182,000 worldwide, Veolia ANZ has extended its sustainable business commitment to both customers and workers. The company’s COVID-19 crisis response team in Australia and New Zealand began using <a href="https://www.qualtrics.com/">Experience Management solutions from SAP and Qualtrics</a> this past year to stay connected with workers and address their challenges.</p>
  <p>“It’s critical that we constantly communicate with employees to understand their challenges and act quickly to address their needs,” said Alexandre Moreau, chief people and safety officer at Veolia ANZ. “We needed a quick and easy solution to keep people connected, whether it was managers and their teams or customers. Qualtrics helped us make sure that our people were okay and receiving the support they needed.”</p>
  <p>Sustainability is in Veolia’s DNA. The company’s business portfolio includes providing environmental solutions across water, waste management, and energy. With operations and treatment facilities nationwide, it serves customers of all sizes – from local cafes and food chains to industrial facilities. One of its business units helps municipal water customers provide safe drinking water for their communities and industrial clients to more sustainably manage water in their operations, while its energy division helps companies build energy resilience and become carbon neutral.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="put-employees-at-the-heart-of-everything-you-do-with-sap-successfactors">Put employees at the heart of everything you do with SAP SuccessFactors</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="listening-translates-employee-feedback-into-engagement">Listening Translates Employee Feedback Into Engagement</h2>
  <p>As a designated essential service during the <a href="/covid-19">pandemic</a>, Veolia ANZ provided the same level of support for customers despite significant challenges, including social distancing, schedule disruptions, and lockdowns. During the height of the crisis, it needed even more flexibility to respond to highly changeable situations. For example, workloads increased in the health sector because of pandemic-related activities. Meanwhile, some employees were working remotely, while others had to be in the field. The company used XM solutions from SAP and Qualtrics to stay in touch with employees.</p>
  <p>Kate Moonen, head of Marketing and Digital Experience at Veolia ANZ, was part of the company’s pandemic response team. Speaking during <a href="https://open.spotify.com/episode/1Xe6n7mvEGJCwKz4A7kOgl">The Best Run Podcast by SAP ANZ</a>, she discussed how short, but targeted surveys helped the company stay in touch with its diverse workforce that includes truck drivers, machine operators, engineers, lawyers, and sustainability experts in urban and remote locations.</p>
  <p>“We really wanted to understand that our people, particularly essential workers, were feeling supported,” she said. “Did they have enough PPE equipment to do their jobs safely? What were their concerns about their mental health and well-being? Based on that feedback, it helped our team formulate what we were going to communicate and what actions we needed to take to continue to support our people.”</p>
  <p>Initially, the team was surprised at the high employee engagement levels with the surveys. Over time, the company rolled out new activities based on the feedback. These included regularly scheduled, anywhere, any device communications with senior leadership through live webinars and question-and-answer sessions. In response to employee requests, executives also sent short video messages that employees could watch on their mobile phones, with personalized stories from company leaders about their lives outside of work and how they adapted to the changed working environment.</p>
  <p>“People felt they wanted to take the opportunity to be heard,” said Moonen. “We would often share regular communications with them about what came out of the latest pulse and what we were going to do about it. If you’re asking people for their time, it’s critical to demonstrate what you’re doing with that feedback to meet their needs.”</p>
  <h2 id="continuous-dialogue-through-employee-surveys">Continuous Dialogue Through Employee Surveys</h2>
  <p>Just like any aspect of sustainable business, employee engagement is not a one-and-done effort.</p>
  <p>“We’re seeing strong employee engagement every time we roll out a new survey,” said Moreau. “Instead of waiting a year to connect with employees, Qualtrics has given us a more agile response tool with a quick pulse check that our people appreciate and we can rely on for updated feedback to make better decisions. We want to know how people are feeling in a fast-changing business environment.”</p>
  <h2 id="go-digital-for-fast-action">Go Digital for Fast Action</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="the-future-of-business-has-feelings">The future of business has feelings</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/experience-management-xm.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Moreau said companies should be explicit about what employees have shared and how they’re taking action. Even if there isn’t an immediate answer, people appreciate the transparency.</p>
  <p>Moonen also advised employers not to overthink the survey process.</p>
  <p>“Sustainable business is all about agility,” she said. “Collecting the feedback and acting quickly is far more valuable than spending months iterating questions. Digital technology gives us the ability to constantly evolve and adapt as customer expectations, market conditions, and employee experiences shift.”</p>
  <h2 id="future-of-work-is-in-employee-experience">Future of Work Is in Employee Experience</h2>
  <p>In the wake of the pandemic, many employees yearn for a greater sense of belonging. They want more help with their individual career goals and to have pride in their workplace. Getting the employee experience right is part of every organization’s transformational journey to sustainable business.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Follow me @smgaler.</em><br><em><a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2021/07/08/sustainable-business-at-veolia-anz-we-make-sure-our-people-are-okay/?sh=5a8244291c0f">This blog also appeared on SAP BrandVoice on Forbes.</a></em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-engagement</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/experience-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/qualtrics</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-anz</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>