<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/sap-social-sabbatical/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP CSR Launches Third Edition of eBook, Celebrating a Year of Global Impact]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/sap-csr-launches-ebook-third-edition</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/sap-csr-launches-ebook-third-edition</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Corporate Social Responsibility (SAP CSR) launched the third edition of its annual eBook, "Helping the World Run Better – Together."]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-social-sabbatical</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Social Sabbatical: Resiliency and Impact in Action]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/sap-social-sabbatical-resiliency-and-impact-in-action</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/sap-social-sabbatical-resiliency-and-impact-in-action</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Pro bono consulting programs like SAP Social Sabbatical build immense impact for employees, social sector partners, and SAP overall.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/purpose</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-social-sabbatical</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Act Now, Together, Through Pro Bono Consulting]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/together-act-now-pro-bono-consulting</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/together-act-now-pro-bono-consulting</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Together Act Now was the theme for the 2022 UN International Volunteer Day. Learn how SAP employees participate.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/life-at-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-social-sabbatical</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
            <category>news-tag/un-sdgs</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fostering Diversity and Inclusion Through Immersive Pro Bono Consulting]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/immersive-pro-bono-consulting-fostering-diversity-inclusion</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/immersive-pro-bono-consulting-fostering-diversity-inclusion</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Pro bono consulting programs like the SAP Social Sabbatical foster diversity and cultivate an inclusive mindset for participants. Learn how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17c7e0cc1436024ff2536a47add3bf4d172041915.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17c7e0cc1436024ff2536a47add3bf4d172041915.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_17c7e0cc1436024ff2536a47add3bf4d172041915.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Fostering Diversity and Inclusion Through Immersive Pro Bono Consulting" src="./media_17c7e0cc1436024ff2536a47add3bf4d172041915.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="fostering-diversity-and-inclusion-through-immersive-pro-bono-consulting">Fostering Diversity and Inclusion Through Immersive Pro Bono Consulting</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Global Diversity Awareness Month is a time to reflect and honor diversity in all its facets – nationality, race, sex, gender, country of origin, and language, just to name a few.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>This is celebrated each year in October; however, at SAP, diversity is something we honor throughout the year. Within our 110,000+ strong company, we have employees from all over the world, with many of our teams working from multiple locations together to reinvent how the world runs as a network of intelligent, sustainable enterprises. Through global teamwork, employees are exposed to different cultures, diverse ways of thinking, and building skills that grow empathy and resiliency. Not only is diversity and inclusion good for employees, but it is also good for business.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-how-sap-is-powering-equitable-access">Learn how SAP is powering equitable access</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/our-values/csr.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="diversity-in-action-through-pro-bono-consulting">Diversity in Action through Pro Bono Consulting</h2>
  <p>As a global organization with employees representing more than 150 nationalities, we are constantly seeking various ways to incorporate diversity and inclusion proactively, both within our workplace and in the markets we serve.</p>
  <p>One of the ways SAP has prioritized a diversity mindset for employees over the past decade is through <a href="https://www.sap.com/socialsabbatical">SAP Social Sabbatical</a>. In this program, SAP employees from around the world can share their skills, knowledge, and professional expertise with innovative non-profit organizations and social enterprises in emerging markets to help them solve their business challenges. The program has been run in over 52 countries with participants representing 64 different nationalities. This highlights our commitment to bring together different perspectives, amplifying the power of diversity of thought and experience, which creates positive impact for both the organizations and participating SAP employees.</p>
  <p>Meera Shenoy, founder of SAP Social Sabbatical host client <a href="https://www.youth4jobs.org/">Youth4Jobs</a>, shared how her organization benefited from the team’s diversity of professional experience: “The volunteers came from three different countries, and each had a different specialty. They quickly adopted our passion for inclusion and became part of the larger Youth4Jobs family, understanding our challenges and transformational work. They also gave us a peek into the amazing SAP processes in several areas. For example, the team shared the SAP neurodiversity training with us, and we got to learn the techniques that a corporation like SAP uses for neurodiversity inclusion in the workplace.”</p>
  <p>When diversity is incorporated through pro bono consulting programs like SAP Social Sabbatical, organizations are able to tap into the varied perspectives and approaches that each individual employee brings to the <a href="https://www2.deloitte.com/us/en/insights/focus/human-capital-trends/2014/hc-trends-2014-diversity-to-inclusion.html">workplace</a>. Research shows that diversified teams can lead to an increase in innovation, improve problem-solving, and boost decision-making. This can heighten performance by <a href="https://diversity-inclusion-speakers.com/news/tips-and-tricks/benefits-diversity-inclusion-workplace-statistics/#:~:text=%E2%80%9CRacially%20diverse%20teams%20report%20a,key%20factor%20in%20any%20workplace.">at least 35%</a>, which not only accelerates innovation within SAP but also helps the host client organization anticipate and fulfill the needs of diverse customers.</p>
  <h2 id="the-employee-advantage">The Employee Advantage</h2>
  <p>For employee participants, we know that the pro bono consulting benefits include skill development, networking opportunities, gaining new perspectives, and cultural immersion, among others. For example, a participant from India stated, “It gives you a whole new perspective that we don’t get in our day-to-day work.”</p>
  <p>From a recent <a href="https://www.sap.com/dmc/exp/2017_03_46558/enUS/impact/">long-term impact study</a> that we conducted in partnership with impact measurement social enterprise <a href="https://60decibels.com/">60 Decibels</a>, 88% of SAP employees who have participated in SAP Social Sabbatical reported that the program benefited them personally. Additionally, 86% of employees said their ability collaborate with global and diverse colleagues improved by their participation.</p>
  <p>“It allowed me to dive into a new world for weeks. You gain experience you have never had before. It brings you to a new level culture-wise, and you meet many talented people from SAP across the world,” said one participant from Germany.</p>
  <p>Another employee commented, “In my personal life, I am more aware of differences in people and better at understanding peoples’ challenges. These differences go beyond age, gender, geography and race but also diversity of thought, upbringing, values and perspectives. Understanding these differences is key to solving problems and empowering others.”</p>
  <h2 id="focusing-on-sustainable-long-term-impact">Focusing on Sustainable Long-Term Impact</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="explore-what-sap-is-doing-to-accelerate-social-businesses">Explore what SAP is doing to accelerate social businesses</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/our-values/csr.html#accelerate">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In addition to the diversity benefits for participants and social sector partners, the long-term impacts have gone beyond the SAP Social Sabbatical program. These principles of diversity as a building block of the program have supported the evolution of new initiatives that address social challenges and build equity, while leveraging pro bono consulting as a tool. In learning from our success over the past 10 years, we developed the Pro Bono for Economic Equity program in North America, which was launched in 2021 in partnership with <a href="https://www.pyxeraglobal.org/">PYXERA Global</a>, as part of SAP’s overall response to the social justice movement with an aim to foster economic equity for Black-owned business and social enterprises.</p>
  <p>The program allows SAP employees to leverage their professional skills and expertise as pro bono volunteer consultants for under-resourced businesses and social enterprises and help them address systemic and business challenges. Within the first year, the program expanded internationally to the UK, Brazil, and South Africa. Based on the success of the program, we have extended the cohorts to have a focus on Indigenous-owned businesses in Canada. <a href="/2022/05/pro-bono-for-economic-equity-impact">Learn more about the program here</a>.</p>
  <h2 id="cultivating-an-inclusive-mindset">Cultivating an Inclusive Mindset</h2>
  <p>At SAP, diversity and inclusion are not simply goals to strive for; they are strategic components of our corporate culture that fuel innovation and help us turn our purpose to action.</p>
  <p>We recognize that continuously bolstering the diversity, equity, and inclusion mindset is crucial when it comes to shaping the next generation of leaders in our company. Not only will this support employee engagement today, but it means that they will build a more inclusive environment when it comes to how they work in teams, how they hire, and how they engage colleagues who are different from them, now and into the future.</p>
  <p>For more information about SAP Social Sabbatical, visit <a href="https://www.sap.com/socialsabbatical">sap.com/socialsabbatical</a> and to learn about how SAP is empowering Black- and Indigenous-owned businesses and social enterprises, read <a href="/topics/pro-bono-for-economic-equity">more stories about the Pro Bono Economic Equity program here</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Hemang Desai is global program director for SAP Corporate Social Responsibility.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/life-at-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-social-sabbatical</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Organizations Measure the Real Impact of Social Enterprise Programs]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/measure-real-impact-of-social-enterprise-programs</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/measure-real-impact-of-social-enterprise-programs</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Social enterprise programs that educate and train disadvantaged people to address challenges are a force for positive change. Learn how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/circular-economy</category>
            <category>news-tag/climate-change</category>
            <category>news-tag/csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>news-tag/entrepreneurship</category>
            <category>news-tag/esg</category>
            <category>news-tag/pyxera-global</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-social-sabbatical</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The "S" in ESG: A Business Imperative]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/esg-business-imperative</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/esg-business-imperative</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The "S" in a company's ESG (environmental, social, and governance) investment strategy is now a business imperative. Learn why.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-social-sabbatical</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Top Five Benefits of Social Sabbaticals]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/top-five-benefits-of-sap-social-sabbatical</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/top-five-benefits-of-sap-social-sabbatical</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Through the SAP Social Sabbatical program, employees experience many benefits, personally and professionally, and gain lifelong skills.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/purpose</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-social-sabbatical</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Businesses Can Accelerate the Work of Social Entrepreneurs to Change the World]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/sap-social-sabbatical-social-sector-partners-change-the-world</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/sap-social-sabbatical-social-sector-partners-change-the-world</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Through SAP Social Sabbatical , global social sector partners experience long-term benefits directly and in the communities they serve.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/purpose</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-social-sabbatical</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Take: You Don’t Have to Quit Your Job to Do Good]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/06/the-take-sheryl-sandberg-meta-departure-dont-quit-your-job-to-do-good</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/06/the-take-sheryl-sandberg-meta-departure-dont-quit-your-job-to-do-good</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Meta COO Sheryl Sandberg is leaving her job to focus on her philanthropy and foundation. Get SAP's take on how to do good without quitting.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/perspective</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-social-sabbatical</category>
            <category>news-tag/the-take</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How to Develop Tomorrow’s Purpose-Driven Leaders Today]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/06/developing-purpose-driven-leaders-sap-social-sabbatical</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/06/developing-purpose-driven-leaders-sap-social-sabbatical</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP has been developing purpose-driven leaders through 10 years of the SAP Social Sabbatical. Learn more about the program's impact.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-social-sabbatical</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Women Empowering Women: Catalyzing Globally-Minded Leaders for Long-Term Impact]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/women-empowering-women-leaders-long-term-impact</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/women-empowering-women-leaders-long-term-impact</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP's Gina McNamara shares her SAP Social Sabbatical experience in Kenya and how it spurred her passion and effort around women empowerment.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/business-womens-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/purpose</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-social-sabbatical</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
            <category>news-tag/women-at-sap</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bringing Our Best to the World: Celebrating 10 Years of Societal Impact Through SAP Social Sabbatical]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/01/sap-social-sabbatical-celebrates-10-years</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/01/sap-social-sabbatical-celebrates-10-years</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[For a decade, the award-winning SAP Social Sabbatical program has brought the company's best out to the world to accelerate social business.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11a05509ca8d00f896d2d297fe73cce982f13bc6b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11a05509ca8d00f896d2d297fe73cce982f13bc6b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_11a05509ca8d00f896d2d297fe73cce982f13bc6b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Bringing Our Best to the World: Celebrating 10 Years of Societal Impact Through SAP Social Sabbatical" src="./media_11a05509ca8d00f896d2d297fe73cce982f13bc6b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="bringing-our-best-to-the-world-celebrating-10-years-of-societal-impact-through-sap-social-sabbatical">Bringing Our Best to the World: Celebrating 10 Years of Societal Impact Through SAP Social Sabbatical</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>The world has grappled with access to quality education for decades — a situation further complicated by the momentum of advancing technologies and, as a result, the ever-changing skills needed to succeed in the world.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>And just when we think we have figured out a <a href="https://sdgs.un.org/goals/goal4">framework</a>, a path forward to “solve the solvable” issues like education through the United Nations’ Sustainable Development Goals (UN SDGs), a global pandemic wipes out educational gains made over the last 20 years.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>The Global Business Coalition for Education confirms that before COVID-19,<br>260 million children were out of primary and secondary school — and<br>75 million had their education interrupted by conflicts and emergencies. Because of<br>the pandemic, 1.6 billion children were forced out of the classroom.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Today we are confronted with both the harsh reality of life and an opportunity for a better tomorrow. <a href="/topics/covid-19">COVID-19</a> has willed the world to prioritize and focus efforts on what matters most.</p>
  <p>On January 24, SAP joins organizations across the world in recognition of <a href="https://en.unesco.org/commemorations/educationday">International Day of Education</a>. We reflect upon the important role education plays for a sustainable future and <a href="http://www.sap.com/csr">SAP Corporate Social Responsibility’s</a> efforts to power equitable access to education and workforce readiness initiatives.</p>
  <p>After a decade of bringing our best to the world to accelerate social business, join us in celebrating the impact achieved in this area through the award-winning <a href="http://www.sap.com/socialsabbatical">SAP Social Sabbatical</a> initiative.</p>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15625fe928213f3128e3442a26bbe6bec70703359.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15625fe928213f3128e3442a26bbe6bec70703359.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_15625fe928213f3128e3442a26bbe6bec70703359.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Social Sabbatical - Celebrating 10 years of impact!" src="./media_15625fe928213f3128e3442a26bbe6bec70703359.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://youtu.be/6goZ_9AlkDw">SAP Social Sabbatical – Celebrating 10 years of impact!</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>For the past 50 years, SAP has guided organizations to become intelligent, sustainable enterprises. SAP Social Sabbatical has embraced this approach. By connecting employees and their skills to social sector organizations through pro bono consulting, we expedite world-changing solutions.</p>
  <p>The portfolio of programs, executed in partnership with <a href="https://www.pyxeraglobal.org/">PYXERA Global</a><u>,</u> offers unique triple impact and delivers long-term sustainable benefits to client organizations, SAP participants, and the company. Our celebration honors this community, which includes 1,371 SAP employees who have worked alongside 453 nonprofit and social enterprise clients spanning 52 countries. Collectively, we have positively impacted more than 6 million people worldwide since 2012.</p>
  <p><a href="https://www.youth4jobs.org/">Youth4Jobs</a> is a nonprofit organization based in Hyderabad, India. The organization creates education and employment opportunities for youth with disabilities that in turn delivers sustainable change for their families. In February 2019, Youth4Jobs hosted SAP Social Sabbatical participants, and challenged them to improve the organization’s business development strategy.</p>
  <p>Founder and CEO Meera Shenoy shared, “The three SAP consultants adopted our passion for inclusion quickly and became part of the larger Youth4Jobs family, understanding our challenges and our transformational work. They also gave us a peek into the amazing processes of SAP in every area, be it recruitment, marketing, or customer cycle.” Shenoy believes that beyond the direct outcome of the project, her team was able to embrace these critical skills which continue to serve the organization and accelerate their incredible work.</p>
  <p>Recently, SAP CSR partnered with <a href="https://60decibels.com/">60 Decibels</a>, an end-to-end impact measurement company, to conduct a study on the SAP Social Sabbatical. Eight-six percent of clients affirmed that participation in the program had a positive long-term impact on the beneficiaries they serve. One program director in Romania shared, “The work that we did together allowed us to build a scaled system to train teachers we serve for free and better prepare them for online teaching during the pandemic and afterwards. Significantly more teachers are now enrolled with our courses and activities than before.”</p>
  <h2 id="our-journey-ahead">Our Journey Ahead</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="choose-both-profitability-and-sustainability-with-sap">Choose both profitability and sustainability with SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/purpose-and-sustainability.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The last decade has demonstrated that pro bono consulting delivers truly transformative and lasting change. Throughout 2022, we are thrilled to bring you additional learnings from our decade of impact study with 60 Decibels to showcase the benefits realized by social sector clients, employees who participate, and SAP overall.</p>
  <p>The strategy for SAP Social Sabbatical, initiated in 2012 as part of SAP’s response to the education crisis, is now evolving to also address the company’s pursuits around zero emissions and zero waste, while continuing to focus on zero inequality. We look forward to sharing more inspiration, innovation, and real solutions from our journey — past, present, and, most importantly, our future.</p>
  <p>For more information, please visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/socialsabbatical">sap.com/socialsabbatical</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Jennifer Beason is global program director of Social Entrepreneurship at SAP.</em><br><em>Hemang Desai is global program director of the SAP Social Sabbatical portfolio at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/purpose</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-social-sabbatical</category>
            <category>news-tag/un-sdgs</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[In a Post-Pandemic World, Youth Take Center Stage and Lead]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/possibilists-study-youth-lead-post-pandemic-world</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/possibilists-study-youth-lead-post-pandemic-world</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is proud to support the Possibilists, youth working to solve the issues of the world and striving to maximize their agency and potential.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning-for-life</category>
            <category>news-tag/redefining-youth</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-social-sabbatical</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>