<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/content-type/expert-opinions/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Case for Pay Transparency]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/the-case-for-pay-transparency</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/the-case-for-pay-transparency</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Author and academic Jake Rosenfeld explodes our fondest beliefs about compensation, especially that employees are paid their worth.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10f00a4c6b9f3c2e482a9a639ba5a8ab676d36d6a.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10f00a4c6b9f3c2e482a9a639ba5a8ab676d36d6a.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_10f00a4c6b9f3c2e482a9a639ba5a8ab676d36d6a.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Two business people sitting at a desk in an office talking to each other." src="./media_10f00a4c6b9f3c2e482a9a639ba5a8ab676d36d6a.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1044">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="the-case-for-pay-transparency">The Case for Pay Transparency</h1>
        <p>Author and academic Jake Rosenfeld explodes our fondest beliefs about compensation, especially that employees are paid their worth.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The setting of pay rates – why exactly people make the amount they do – is shrouded in mystery. Ever was it thus. Companies have never wanted to shine a bright light on employees’ paychecks nor delve too deeply into what they should pay.</p>
  <p>Few employees are willing to enter a frank discussion about the digits on their checks, either. It’s one of the most enduring taboos of corporate life.</p>
  <p>Everyone has their reasons. Employers face too many imponderables – it’s hard to figure out what most employees contribute to corporate coffers – and transparency could open all kinds of cans of worms. Many people would rather not know how they are valued compared to their peers, considering how much our jobs and pay rate underpin our identities.</p>
  <p>But the result, says Jake Rosenfeld, author, and sociology professor at Washington University in St. Louis, is an often unequal playing field. Most pay rates are based on history – the pay rate a company has offered in the past, plus employees’ previous earnings – and market rates. Few other factors come into play.</p>
  <p>In his book <a href="https://www.amazon.com/Youre-Paid-What-Worth-Economy-ebook/dp/B08TJ6J2H8/ref=sr_1_1?crid=PF9EWWA3QX50&#x26;dib=eyJ2IjoiMSJ9.K1WecBmDbRyHHZ0vOmYBCDEX47nNY_4iULlY-0rf4gsiw-NWo6-E1_zuly-kbtQLHDZoZNdQ7lHEYq0dhpycP4UdbXk0UbZ5qITucc72cDY310w6CerWhji676HMoGlglAYWmCJwOCdyujtCKBJDU0xueCz40s5ljymEyWTc9ncW1BNCAVRaT7uXMXgxQ0UtS6zoYGgwBn1-FAKwBhJ9zJr2ZlY4VPuc2kSi34uONIA.VvHlHxX6tUUdKfWZgP_czhx5YSsbSg9icjfHbGspKG4&#x26;dib_tag=se&#x26;keywords=you%27re+paid+what+you%27re+worth&#x26;qid=1711487199&#x26;sprefix=you%27re+paid+%2Caps%2C506&#x26;sr=8-1">You’re Paid What You’re Worth: And Other Myths of the Modern Economy</a>, Rosenfeld blows the doors off the vault of stubborn but unfounded beliefs that underlie our notion of employee compensation.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14a9e86e0f052a504889ced35e43c015b1a7342e5.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14a9e86e0f052a504889ced35e43c015b1a7342e5.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_14a9e86e0f052a504889ced35e43c015b1a7342e5.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Image of Jake Rosenfeld" src="./media_14a9e86e0f052a504889ced35e43c015b1a7342e5.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2740" height="1541">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p><em>Jake Rosenfeld, author of You’re Paid What You’re Worth: And Other Myths of the Modern Economy.</em></p>
  <p>We asked Rosenfeld about the most persistent myths associated with employee compensation, why they are so enduring (and harmful), and what it will take for employers to do better.</p>
  <p>Spoiler alert: There is no magic formula.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1db86572a7958b83644355876a24c89bfc828cf38.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1db86572a7958b83644355876a24c89bfc828cf38.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1db86572a7958b83644355876a24c89bfc828cf38.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Man taking a photo of a check with his cell phone." src="./media_1db86572a7958b83644355876a24c89bfc828cf38.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="sap-insights-in-your-book-you-discuss-pay-transparency-in-depth-giving-the-history-of-the-topic-and-why-both-bosses-and-workers-traditionally-have-avoided-it-but-its-documented-that-pay-opacity-leads-to-unfairness-how-come-this-is-such-a-thorny-issue">SAP Insights: In your book, you discuss pay transparency in depth, giving the history of the topic and why both bosses and workers traditionally have avoided it. But it’s documented that pay opacity leads to unfairness. How come this is such a thorny issue?</h2>
  <p><strong>Jake Rosenfeld:</strong> I'm absolutely fascinated by the salary taboo. It’s taken for granted in the academic literature that we have a reluctance to discuss pay. There are exceptions like Norway, where you can look up everyone’s tax returns to see what they made. But elsewhere, there seems to be something fundamental about our unwillingness to disclose our pay.</p>
  <p>That said, it does seem to be changing, especially among younger workers. They're much more willing to share their wages and salaries. This taboo could be crumbling underneath our feet.</p>
  <h2 id="q-is-that-due-to-a-difference-in-orientation-and-temperament-with-younger-people-or-do-you-think-younger-workers-know-talking-about-salaries-will-help-decrease-unfair-wages">Q: Is that due to a difference in orientation and temperament with younger people? Or do you think younger workers know talking about salaries will help decrease unfair wages?</h2>
  <p><strong>Rosenfeld:</strong> People are beginning to understand it's important to share and gather as much information as they can to make sure that they're getting what they think they deserve. I also take seriously the idea that as younger generations grow into their prime earning years, the reluctance to share may come back.</p>
  <p>But I also wouldn't be surprised if the ground is shifting. Many U.S. states are passing laws requiring disclosure of pay ranges for recruitment purposes. The topic has captured media attention, too. Word has gotten out that you should be much less reluctant to talk about pay because you may be getting underpaid and not know it.</p>
  <h2 id="q-as-you-write-employees-have-tended-to-be-reluctant-to-discuss-pay-because-they-dont-want-to-know-whether-their-pay-is-higher-or-lower-versus-their-colleagues-meanwhile-you-argue-that-bosses-dont-want-anyone-to-discuss-pay-to-keep-unfair-pay-structures-under-wraps-saving-the-organization-money-overall-their-interests-though-different-have-aligned-to-keep-pay-rates-secret">Q: As you write, employees have tended to be reluctant to discuss pay because they don’t want to know whether their pay is higher or lower versus their colleagues. Meanwhile, you argue that bosses don’t want anyone to discuss pay to keep unfair pay structures under wraps, saving the organization money overall. Their interests, though different, have aligned to keep pay rates secret.</h2>
  <p><strong>Rosenfeld:</strong> Absolutely. On the worker side, especially as you get into the upper-middle-class professions, our jobs are tied up with our sense of purpose and identity. People also tend to believe that our pay is ultimately tied to how well we're doing at work.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_172966442f9d1bad55e4b77140f60ff6ea8ede5a6.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_172966442f9d1bad55e4b77140f60ff6ea8ede5a6.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_172966442f9d1bad55e4b77140f60ff6ea8ede5a6.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Two serious-looking business people sitting at a table in an office, looking at data on a tablet." src="./media_172966442f9d1bad55e4b77140f60ff6ea8ede5a6.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="q-why-did-you-write-this-book-who-are-you-hoping-to-reach">Q: Why did you write this book? Who are you hoping to reach?</h2>
  <p><strong>Rosenfeld:</strong> Not many academics share my fascination with pay setting. But the more I dug in, the more I read case studies, the more I surveyed U.S. workers, the messier and more interesting it was. It quickly became clear the textbook models bear little resemblance to the real world of pay setting.</p>
  <p>Although I’m hoping to reach my colleagues in academia, business leaders have their own questions. I've talked to employers, and they tell me about feeling insecure when setting pay rates. They say they often feel they really don't know what they are doing when it comes to pay.</p>
  <p>I try to reassure them there's no exact science here. Everyone must deal with the messy, real phenomenon of trying to put a price on human labor. That's always going to be a challenge and will raise all sorts of thorny moral concerns.</p>
  <h2 id="q-at-the-beginning-of-your-book-you-sketch-out-four-dynamics-that-influence-how-and-what-people-are-paid-equity-or-fairness-mimicry-power-and-inertia-would-you-please-take-them-one-by-one-and-tell-us-what-concerns-you-about-them">Q: At the beginning of your book, you sketch out four dynamics that influence how and what people are paid: equity or fairness, mimicry, power, and inertia. Would you please take them one by one and tell us what concerns you about them?</h2>
  <p><strong>Rosenfeld:</strong> Let’s take fairness first. You're dealing with human beings, who often think they are underpaid. We all would like more money. And when you survey workers, very few say they’re overpaid.</p>
  <p>Employers have to be very delicate when approaching pay issues because they affect employee morale. But if they have a compensation structure they can defend openly, and explain why person X is making more than person Y, that generally goes a long way to engendering worker buy-in. Too often employers either don't have anything as organized as that, or they feel that if they share it, their employees won't support it. And that's where real issues can arise.</p>
  <p>Mimicry is paying the market rate, which is an understandable shortcut. But it means only that employers are surveying similar employers, finding out what they're doing, and making tiny adjustments to go a little above or a little below the average. It's easy to justify to workers: “Hey, we can't go that far above what our competitors are paying, because that will put us at a disadvantage.”</p>
  <p>Then there’s power. In the United States, power is held primarily with whoever pays. Workers have some power, but it differs according to their position in the organization, from the cleaning staff to the C-suite. They also come into the organization with different levels of power. That affects their ability to stake their claim for their share of revenue – that is, their wages and salaries. Their success will be based on where they're positioned and whether they have any other sources of power, such as a labor union.</p>
  <p>And the last factor is inertia. You do a job interview, and you're offered a starting wage or salary. It has a lot to do with what that company has been paying for that position for time immemorial. Sometimes it's the exact same rate they’ve paid for years because no one has the time to reevaluate every position every six months to decide what it should really be. There is no clear guidance for making that calculation, so inertia often takes hold. And then pay rates are taken for granted.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="strategies-for-managing-ai-disruption">Strategies for Managing AI Disruption</h3>
        <p>How HR leaders understand the changes AI brings and give employees a fair voice.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="/research/three-hr-strategies-for-managing-ai-disruption">Learn more</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="q-you-write-about-ceo-pay-and-how-disproportionate-it-has-gotten">Q: You write about CEO pay and how disproportionate it has gotten.</h2>
  <p><strong>Rosenfeld:</strong> There's vast literature showing only a very loose correlation between company performance and CEO pay – or none whatsoever.</p>
  <p>The idea that you have to pay at the top of the market to attract great talent presumes that you know what’s great. A lot of the time we don't know that. Meanwhile, CEOs have been able to bid up their collective pay because they are being hired from a kind of international market for floating CEOs, rather than being cultivated from inside the organization.</p>
  <p>When you ask American workers what they think the average ratio of CEO to worker pay is at a particular firm, respondents say something like 20 to one. When you ask what they think it should be, they say something like five or six to one.</p>
  <p>The reality is that overall, a CEO salary is roughly 400 times the average worker’s pay. That said, there doesn’t seem to be a movement to put real pressure on bringing down CEO pay. There are straightforward policies that could accomplish this, but there’s this question of whether the will is there.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f75594d2d1751e7b65c6c75922ed28dbeaed689a.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f75594d2d1751e7b65c6c75922ed28dbeaed689a.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1f75594d2d1751e7b65c6c75922ed28dbeaed689a.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Close-up image of a businessperson in a meeting room signing a contract." src="./media_1f75594d2d1751e7b65c6c75922ed28dbeaed689a.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="q-as-you-describe-it-the-explosion-of-ceo-pay-corresponds-with-the-rise-in-shareholder-capitalism-you-make-a-case-in-the-book-that-running-companies-for-the-benefit-of-shareholders-above-everyone-else-is-a-foe-of-equity-quality-and-safety-in-the-modern-world-including-that-it-induces-companies-to-pay-workers-as-little-as-they-can-get-away-with">Q: As you describe it, the explosion of CEO pay corresponds with the rise in shareholder capitalism. You make a case in the book that running companies for the benefit of shareholders above everyone else is a foe of equity, quality, and safety in the modern world. Including that it induces companies to pay workers as little as they can get away with.</h2>
  <p><strong>Rosenfeld:</strong> There were justifiable reasons the system needed to get shaken up a bit, especially for climbing out of the malaise of the ’70s and ’80s. A lot of corporations were ruled by longtime CEOs. They were pretty unproductive, not innovating in any way, and often getting beaten by international competitors. Shareholders were rightfully upset and wanted to see some returns they weren't getting.</p>
  <p>It's just that this activist shareholder movement has a lot of perverse incentives that are doing a real disservice for the companies. For starters, shareholders often view pay increases for average workers warily since that’s money not being redistributed upward.</p>
  <p>In the last five to ten years, CEOs have been saying they're tired of it, because they are trading higher CEO pay for less control over what they can do at the company. They are beholden to what the shareholders are demanding – who often do everything they can to jack up short-term stock prices.</p>
  <p>There is a widespread belief that CEOs have a fiduciary duty to shareholders, but they don’t, formally. And they are stymied from implementing any investment plan that’s not going to pay off for years, where they invest in new facilities and train up the workforce.</p>
  <h2 id="q-in-your-view-what-will-be-the-likely-effect-of-ai-on-wages-ever-downward-pressure-for-those-that-are-lucky-to-retain-their-jobs">Q: In your view, what will be the likely effect of AI on wages? Ever downward pressure, for those that are lucky to retain their jobs?</h2>
  <p><strong>Rosenfeld:</strong> Technological innovations often get interpreted as the death knell of millions and millions of jobs. That’s yet to happen, right? We’re sitting at a 3.7% unemployment rate.</p>
  <p>There will be reshuffling, for sure. The question is whether the reshuffled workers will be able to land in equal, or even possibly more highly paid positions. The extent to which that happens is often due to policy decisions that can be made to cushion the impact of technological innovations. The United States often takes none of those choices. The job retraining policies here are really skimpy, but other countries do it differently.</p>
  <h2 id="q-what-do-you-want-senior-business-leaders-to-do-about-pay">Q: What do you want senior business leaders to do about pay?</h2>
  <p><strong>Rosenfeld:</strong> It goes back to transparency. There’s more and more evidence that in the American economy today that workers are generally satisfied with their jobs and trust their bosses. Employers should take advantage of that and share their compensation strategy.</p>
  <p>I see in my own industry, academia, how everyone feels like they're underpaid. And universities are so deeply reluctant to give even one sentence about “here's how pay is determined here.” That just engenders ill will and distrust, because we then personalize everything: “Oh, my employer doesn't like me, doesn't see the value in my work.” We can see the same dynamic at work in every industry.</p>
  <p>Another point: we're in this wave of unionization efforts. But we are seeing kind of a ferocious pushback on the part of employers. I get that in an environment where few of your competitors are unionized, you could be terrified that if your company goes union, you're going to be at a competitive disadvantage. That said, the pushback has its own set of <a href="https://jacobin.com/2024/02/starbucks-workers-united-master-contract-bargaining">negative consequences</a>.</p>
  <p>I have a perhaps naïve hope for this country and the corporate class going forward that there's a way to carve out much more cooperative labor-management relationships where unionization efforts won't be fought to the death and won't be seen as the end of the firm. Because we know from the cross-national picture and from our own history that, in many cases, need not be the case. And higher wages for the average worker will be the welcome result.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/expert-opinions</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Farmers Harvest New Insights with Generative AI]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/how-farmers-harvest-new-insights-with-generative-ai</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/how-farmers-harvest-new-insights-with-generative-ai</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Agribusiness players are using generative AI to find more and better data to improve yields and manage natural resources.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_110073b3f26e477cf3ec92294b3cc1fa8cd859357.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_110073b3f26e477cf3ec92294b3cc1fa8cd859357.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_110073b3f26e477cf3ec92294b3cc1fa8cd859357.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Farmer analyzing corn crop using a tablet with AI technology" src="./media_110073b3f26e477cf3ec92294b3cc1fa8cd859357.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1044">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="how-farmers-harvest-new-insights-with-generative-ai">How Farmers Harvest New Insights with Generative AI</h1>
        <p>Agribusiness players are using generative AI to find more and better data to improve yields and manage natural resources.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>By Eric Somitsch and Tam Harbert</p>
  <p>Imagine a farmer in India growing millet on two acres of land. Rain has been scarce this year, and a new type of pest ate much of his crop. He’s concerned that his tried-and-true practices are not as effective as they used to be, and he’s wondering what might increase his odds of a better harvest next season. He pulls out his phone and asks an AI chatbot, which provides him with recommendations.</p>
  <p>This scenario represents a new use of generative AI in agriculture and illustrates a new opportunity to bring innovations to the world’s farmlands.</p>
  <p>Generative AI promises benefits for society at large as well as for the agriculture industry, from smallholder farmers to larger cooperatives to the giant players in commodity crops, seeds, fertilizers, and pesticides. The extent to which the industry has begun experimenting with targeted uses of generative AI offers multiple lessons learned for other business sectors.</p>
</div>
<div>
  <h2 id="more-on-agriculture-at-sap-insights">More on Agriculture at SAP Insights</h2>
  <p>“<a href="/resources/how-ai-transforms-agriculture">How AI Transforms Agriculture</a>”: Next-generation farming processes promise higher yields, greater efficiency, and better sustainability, all of which will improve business performance.</p>
  <p>“<a href="/blogs/the-future-of-feeding-the-world">The Future Feeding of the World</a>”: How intelligent technologies can help the agricultural industry to lift poor farmers and heal the planet.</p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>Style</div>
      <div>Additional Reading</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
<div>
  <p>More than ever, farmers need to make <a href="/blogs/the-future-of-feeding-the-world">more efficient use of natural resources</a> such as soil, seed, and water and lessen the toll that farming takes on the environment through methane generation, pesticide use, and other factors. The food system generates about one-third of greenhouse gas emissions globally, according to <a href="https://www.un.org/en/actnow/food">the United Nations</a>. Consumers are demanding more sustainably grown products, as Harvard Business Review <a href="https://hbr.org/2023/09/research-consumers-sustainability-demands-are-rising">points out</a>. At the same time, agriculture is part of the climate; for example, when farmers grow perennial crops, their soils <a href="https://climate.mit.edu/explainers/soil-based-carbon-sequestration">store more carbon</a>. But agriculture is also vulnerable to extreme weather patterns that are causing more floods, droughts, and wildfires.</p>
  <p>In agriculture, AI is already being used to improve food production and sustainability. For example, Vista GmbH, a subsidiary of BayWa, Germany’s largest digital agriculture company, uses satellite data and AI models to forecast and improve yields in a project with SAP. Such tools can analyze data in ways that help farmers produce more food more sustainably for the earth’s growing population while also helping them adapt to a changing climate. They can also produce reliable data on sustainability for shareholders and government bodies.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="an-ai-copilot">An AI Copilot</h3>
        <p>Introducing Joule, a natural language GenAI copilot.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/ai-assistant.html">Learn more</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Such data is increasingly important. Agriculture’s role in climate change was highlighted in November 2023 at COP28, the United Nations Climate Change Conference, where 159 countries signed the United Arab Emirates (UAE) Declaration on Sustainable Agriculture, Resilient Food Systems, and Climate Action. Through <a href="https://www.cop28.com/en/food-and-agriculture">this declaration</a>, countries committed to improving sustainable farming practices and pledged to include agricultural emissions in their next round of climate targets. In addition, the United States and the UAE committed about $17 billion toward agricultural innovations to address climate change.</p>
  <p>With the added capabilities of generative AI, farmers and their advisors can more quickly and directly access agronomic data and analysis, enabling them to make near-real-time decisions about soil treatments, seed varieties, and market conditions. Using chatbots, farmers can ask natural language questions in their native languages (When should I plant this crop? How much and what kind of fertilizer should I apply?) and get answers that any farmer, regardless of their training or background, can understand.</p>
  <p>For agricultural companies, generative AI can gather and crunch even more granular and timely information and analysis that help them improve their products, customer service, and processes and operations to better meet business goals – including sustainability targets.</p>
  <p>While the promise is there, agricultural companies will need to carefully navigate four key areas as they implement generative AI:</p>
  <ol>
    <li>Data quality and model training</li>
    <li>Risks associated with the application of generative AI, such as false information</li>
    <li>The need to ensure that IT systems and operational processes are set up to use generative AI</li>
    <li>Developing trust in these systems and their results so that farmers use the technology</li>
  </ol>
  <p>This article describes two examples of generative AI in use today and discusses how companies can reap the benefits and reduce the risks in each of these four areas.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e4196c8a2009a17481771df4d40261adadbeadf1.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e4196c8a2009a17481771df4d40261adadbeadf1.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1e4196c8a2009a17481771df4d40261adadbeadf1.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Person of color using digital tablet for analysis of farm" src="./media_1e4196c8a2009a17481771df4d40261adadbeadf1.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="example-1-generative-ai-chatbot-provides-fast-advice-to-smallholder-farmers">Example 1: Generative AI chatbot provides fast advice to smallholder farmers</h2>
  <p>With the increased reliance on data in farming, every major player in agriculture is experimenting with generative AI – and the first application to find traction is a virtual agronomist chatbot. That’s because the ROI is clear: the cost of providing a chatbot is low in comparison to regularly sending human agronomists to remote areas, and the potential benefits are high. Specifically, a chatbot’s ability to access and analyze data on weather patterns, plant genetics, pesticides, soil chemistry, and other areas offers farmers direct, immediate help in improving their agricultural practices.</p>
  <p>In India, agriculture is a major contributor to the gross domestic product, employing nearly half the population directly or indirectly, <a href="https://analyticsindiamag.com/generative-ai-already-finding-multiple-use-cases-agriculture/">notes</a> Analytics India Magazine. Yet these farms are very small; the average size is just 1.08 hectares (about 2.5 acres), <a href="https://www.fortuneindia.com/opinion/how-to-put-indian-agriculture-back-on-growth-path/113125">reports</a> Fortune India. Half lack basic farming equipment, and three-quarters are at risk of crop damage from pests and weather, according to a May 2023 McKinsey <a href="https://www.mckinsey.com/industries/agriculture/our-insights/how-agtech-is-poised-to-transform-india-into-a-farming-powerhouse">report</a>.</p>
  <p>Digital Green, a global nonprofit that builds technology to help farmers in developing nations, began rolling out an AI assistant in 2023 with farmers in India, Kenya, and Ethiopia. The assistant, a chatbot built into Telegram, initially targets agricultural extension agents, who are professionals providing training and information for farmers. Such agents can be few and far between – the ratio is as low as one agent for every 1,000 farmers in some areas – which makes it hard to provide timely, accurate, localized advice, says Jona Repishti, Digital Green’s head of global gender programs.</p>
  <p>“Extension agents play a critical role in helping smallholder farmers get the information they need to be climate-resilient and get better yields at a time when there is soil degradation and new types of pests,” says Repishti. “But this requires them to be experts in plant genetics, soil health, new types of seeds, climatology, and market and government regulations.”</p>
  <p>In some cases, agents may spend a week to research a problem and deliver an answer, which is often too late. “Agriculture is very time-sensitive,” says Repishti. “You need the right information now or pests quickly devastate your crop.”</p>
  <p>Digital Green built the AI assistant to improve communication and advice to farmers, thereby increasing the speed and effectiveness of extension agents – which in turn will increase farmers’ faith in the agents’ advice.</p>
  <p>Digital Green expects to have the chatbot in the hands of 10,000 agents by the end of 2024. In the early phases of the rollout, the agents used it in several ways: to research across volumes of scientific reports and papers, to quickly answer farmers' questions in the field, and to present information to groups at meetings. The agents have also begun sharing the chatbot with farmers to use directly, says Repishti. Eventually, Digital Green expects the chatbot to incorporate local market data so that a farmer could ask a question such as, “What is the most profitable crop to grow, given variables such as the costs for supplies like seeds and pesticides and local selling prices for certain crops or livestock?,” according to Repishti.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1096004fb2c967e673c70d964e8b17503d58c47df.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1096004fb2c967e673c70d964e8b17503d58c47df.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1096004fb2c967e673c70d964e8b17503d58c47df.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Farmer with digital tablet inspecting cows feeding from trough on dairy farm" src="./media_1096004fb2c967e673c70d964e8b17503d58c47df.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1958" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="example-2-milking-more-data-from-cows">Example 2: Milking more data from cows</h2>
  <p>Datamars, a company based in Switzerland, also develops technology to help farmers become more sustainable. Datamars initially sold radio-frequency ID tags to track farm animals, but today it has a strategic focus on both hardware and software to enable smart farming, according to Kevin Coffey, the company’s global head of smart farming.</p>
  <p>In early 2023, Datamars acquired the sensor business of a technology partner, Connecterra, which has built software that provides data to farmers, their advisors, and agricultural companies. Today, the two companies offer a service that uses data from sensor-chipped animals to create insights for farmers as well as the Connecterra software to crunch data and create insights for farm-supporting partners such as advisors and feed companies. The service helps farmers better manage their animals and in turn provides data that helps companies meet sustainability targets.</p>
  <p>Through networked sensors – “like Fitbits for cows,” says Coffey – a farmer can see the individual characteristics and behavior of each animal, including eating, rumination, and even estrus, or fertility status. That helps farmers better manage their animals, and, says Coffey, “Good farming and sustainability are synergistic.”</p>
  <p>For example, dairy farmers want the cows to be “in calf” as much as possible to maximize milk production, so they can improve collection rates by tracking estrus – which means they don’t need to buy more cows to maintain the same level of milk production. Fewer cows also means less methane, a significant contributor to global warming, Coffey explains. Large dairy processors and slaughterhouses need this information to show customers that their milk and beef is produced in a sustainable way, he notes.</p>
  <p>Given how fast generative AI is developing, it may not be long before other agricultural apps are in the field. (See sidebars: Computer Vision in Farming Equipment and Developing New Crop Breeds Faster.)</p>
</div>
<div>
  <h2 id="computer-vision-in-farming-equipment">Computer Vision in Farming Equipment</h2>
  <p>Some equipment, such as tractors and sprayers, already incorporate cameras and use AI to examine images to spot weeds and spray herbicide in just the right places. This reduces herbicide use and costs for farmers. For example, John Deere uses machine vision in its agricultural equipment, Vision Systems Design <a href="https://www.vision-systems.com/non-factory/environment-agriculture/article/14293351/john-deere-uses-machine-vision-and-machine-learning-to-automate-agriculture">reports</a>.</p>
  <p>Traditionally, training such AI requires a lot of images and tedious work, says Vikram S. Adve of the University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign, where he is the Donald B. Gillies professor of computer science and director of the AIFARMS (Artificial Intelligence for Future Agricultural Resilience, Management, and Sustainability) Institute. “This supervised machine learning is very expensive and requires certain expertise,” says Adve.</p>
  <p>By using the foundational image models now available, which have been trained on very large but general data on all sorts of images, companies could fine-tune agricultural vision apps using synthetic images that are quickly generated by generative AI. This dramatically reduces the time and expense required to train AI to spot particular things such as specific indications of disease.</p>
  <p>Datamars is already evaluating such an application through a collaboration with Serket, a company that develops AI-based vision systems for livestock, according to Kevin Coffey, Global Head of Smart Farming at Datamars. AI trained on a foundation model might recognize a cow as distinct from a goat, for example. But generative AI could further train the model to distinguish between different behaviors of those animals and potentially identify the early onset of disease.</p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>Style</div>
      <div>Additional Reading</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
<div>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17af7f0ac0a6480d769585288d93b885ac33844ef.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17af7f0ac0a6480d769585288d93b885ac33844ef.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_17af7f0ac0a6480d769585288d93b885ac33844ef.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Close-up image of wheat field with sunset in the background" src="./media_17af7f0ac0a6480d769585288d93b885ac33844ef.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="key-takeaways-risks-and-rewards">Key takeaways: Risks and rewards</h2>
  <p>Generative AI holds great promise for agriculture, but companies seeding new applications should pay special attention to the following factors.</p>
  <p><em>Data and model training</em></p>
  <p>All agriculture is local – so for generative AI to be useful, it requires specific, localized data. Climate, soils, diseases, growing practices, and many other factors differ significantly from one region to another. “The answers you get to the same question about the same crop and even the same climate conditions could be quite different in central Illinois versus Mexico versus other corn-growing regions of the world,” explains Vikram S. Adve of the University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign, where he is the Donald B. Gillies professor of computer science and director of the AIFARMS (Artificial Intelligence for Future Agricultural Resilience, Management, and Sustainability) Institute. That means generative AI must be trained not only on domain-specific data but on location-specific data.</p>
  <p>That presents a twofold challenge – first, being able to gather and use the data. Some data, such as weather data, is publicly available, but some, such as details on specific types of seeds developed by specific companies, might be proprietary, which raises legal risk. In addition, if companies are collecting and analyzing data from individual farms, they need to adhere to data privacy rules and make sure they have the express permission of farmers.</p>
  <p>Second, such specificity makes model training more complicated. While ChatGPT – which is trained on information from the Internet – might be a start, agricultural chatbots need to be trained on trusted data sets, such as peer-reviewed agricultural research and best practices. But since farming is local, that training also requires specific data on regional variations in weather patterns, typical crops grown in that geography, and even market conditions in specific areas.</p>
  <p>Digital Green’s Repishti says the organization has developed databases for select high-value crops. In Ethiopia and Kenya, the chatbot supports over 40 value chains, including potato and rice, which are among the major crops in those countries. It plans to expand the databases to additional crops and livestock.</p>
  <p>But static databases may not be enough to enable the chatbot to answer highly specific questions in a changing context. So Digital Green is working to enable the chatbot to connect with dynamic databases through retrieval augmented generation (RAG) as well as fine-tuning the language models to keep up with farmers’ changing needs. In this way, the chatbot could access the most recent data on commodity markets and selling prices, for example.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_173100acba53307e783d8c5f7313694a98fb81fde.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_173100acba53307e783d8c5f7313694a98fb81fde.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_173100acba53307e783d8c5f7313694a98fb81fde.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Close-up image of blueberry plant through mobile device" src="./media_173100acba53307e783d8c5f7313694a98fb81fde.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p>With RAG technology, a model has access to the most current information, helping to ensure accuracy and helping it to sync up with hyperlocal data. This means the AI model can retrieve information while answering a specific question. RAG also reduces the chances of the model “hallucinating,” or making up erroneous answers based on data patterns on which it was trained. However, RAG requires specialized expertise and technology; for example, it depends on coding that enables relevant information to be drawn from specific databases.</p>
  <p><em>Legal risks associated with data ownership</em></p>
  <p>Any company developing a generative AI tool for farmers needs to make sure it owns the data it intends to use or at least has permission to use it. A company must also have knowledge of various laws around the world that govern data ownership and data mining. For years, large agricultural equipment vendors have collected data through sensors and cameras on tractors in addition to data from farmers, so they may have legal ownership of certain information, Adve notes.</p>
  <p>However, there are legal opportunities as well. If trained using the right data, chatbots can help farmers comply with local regulations.</p>
  <p>In addition, agriculture companies, technology suppliers, and software vendors should make sure that users understand the possibility of error. While it is improving, generative AI is still prone to hallucinating. One reason that Digital Green rolled out its chatbot only to extension agents is that the agents have the knowledge to spot such errors. “The agents are another layer of security because they are experts that can critically assess the information the chatbot offers,” Repishti says.</p>
  <p>Adve notes that evaluating the accuracy of generative AI tools is difficult and time-consuming. There are good reasons that most of the large language models come from some of the biggest technology companies in the world, which have the vast resources required to reduce the chance of errors. For all the promise that generative AI holds, business leaders need to remember that it isn’t perfect.</p>
  <p><em>IT systems and operation processes</em></p>
  <p>Because farming is local, sophisticated technical tools were developed in isolation and were not widely adopted until recently. That means that much of the data is not standardized and that systems require integration, potentially leading to some heavy lifting for companies that want to gather and analyze agricultural data. For example, different countries use different codes to identify various cattle breeds, says Coffey.</p>
  <p><em>Developing farmers’ trust</em></p>
  <p>Companies need to pay special attention to gaining the trust of farmers. Traditional farming practices have been developed over many generations; often the same family has worked the same land for hundreds of years. So it is understandable that farmers are skeptical of new technologies like data analytics and generative AI. (For more on this issue, see “<a href="/resources/how-ai-transforms-agriculture">How AI Transforms Agriculture</a>.”)</p>
  <p>Clear explanations can help. State what generative AI can do, what it cannot do, and how it works. For example, describe how generative AI provides information expressed in probabilities and can make mistakes (just as people do) and also how it can take in much more data than people can. Reviewing these issues helps users understand the technology’s strengths and weaknesses – and how it benefits them.</p>
  <p>Companies need to pay special attention to gaining the trust of farmers.</p>
  <p>Digital Green focuses on gaining farmers’ trust. “It's notoriously hard to change farmer behavior and practices in the fields,” Repishti says. When farmers ask their extension agent questions, it can take time to get an answer if the agent must research it. With the AI chatbot, agents can immediately respond to farmer queries with relevant, useful, and accurate advice. In addition, Digital Green’s bot can handle multiple languages and respond to spoken questions rather than relying on one language and text. “Meeting farmers on their terms helps build trust between farmers and extension agents,” she notes.</p>
  <p>The trust factor is important even in developed countries such as the United States because the use of digital technology in agriculture is still relatively new. The AI Institute for Climate-Land Interactions, Mitigation, Adaptation, Tradeoffs, and Economy (AI-CLIMATE), based at the University of Minnesota, is researching how AI can help U.S. farmers adopt and profit from more climate-smart practices.</p>
  <p>“An important factor for this institute to be successful is to bring in the farmer,” says Zhenong Jin, assistant professor of digital agriculture at the University of Minnesota. “We are co-creating the solution with them. Farmers play a significant role in this process. It’s not just a scientist telling them what to do.”</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>industry/agribusiness</category>
            <category>content-type/expert-opinions</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[HR Trends 2024: The Year of AI]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/hr-trends-2024-the-year-of-ai</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/hr-trends-2024-the-year-of-ai</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[See new SAP research on the top HR trends of 2024, including artificial intelligence (AI), diversity and inclusion, and declining leadership trust]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10dcf99ea3e5221344e836a541e1f98e778684500.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10dcf99ea3e5221344e836a541e1f98e778684500.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_10dcf99ea3e5221344e836a541e1f98e778684500.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Grid of people images on a screen" src="./media_10dcf99ea3e5221344e836a541e1f98e778684500.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1044">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="hr-trends-2024-the-year-of-ai">HR Trends 2024: The Year of AI</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>By Dr. Katherine Gibbard, PhD</p>
  <p>To no one’s surprise, artificial intelligence will continue to dominate HR in 2024. But new SAP research indicates other HR trends that might be more surprising: that diversity, equity, inclusion, and belonging (DEI&#x26;B) efforts could stall out in some organizations, and that trust in leadership takes a nosedive. Compensation issues may come to a head, too. Organizations will need to deal with the realities associated with technological advancements, major demographic changes, and changing expectations related to the employee experience.</p>
  <p>The <a href="https://community.sap.com/topics/successfactors/growth-insights-research/growth-insights-team">SAP SuccessFactors Growth and Insights Team</a> conducted extensive research to understand the top HR trends facing organizations today. For 2024, we analyzed 100 reputable business press resources to generate a list of 611 potential trends. Through content analysis and the use of AI tools, we consolidated these trends into nine broader <em>meta trends</em> captured in our <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2024/02/883d4dde-ad7e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">annual HR trends report</a>.</p>
  <p>Employee experience (EX) does not exist in our list as a meta trend, though, because it is important to consider EX more broadly. The biggest issues that organizations and HR teams will face in 2024 are tightly woven into the employee experience, so EX will be a top priority for organizations and HR teams as they plan to address these challenges.</p>
  <p>Understanding these trends and the role that technology – including AI tools – can play in addressing them is essential for HR professionals and business leaders to make strategic decisions. These are the top trends that we’ve identified as most important for the coming year.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c457cdc4bca8f0a53b3f7abaeda3e0966f983436.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c457cdc4bca8f0a53b3f7abaeda3e0966f983436.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1c457cdc4bca8f0a53b3f7abaeda3e0966f983436.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="group of colleagues looking at AI data on transparent screen." src="./media_1c457cdc4bca8f0a53b3f7abaeda3e0966f983436.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="2160">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="ai-upends-the-world-of-work-as-we-know-it">1. AI upends the world of work as we know it.</h2>
  <p>AI dominated the 2024 trends discourse: how it will transform the labor market, how it will drive productivity, and how it will need to be managed to prevent negative outcomes. <a href="/research/three-hr-strategies-for-managing-ai-disruption">Generative AI won’t lead to widespread job losses</a>, but people who use it will replace those who don’t. Employees will need to see AI as a tool to help them complete work, not a force to compete with, but that may be a tough sell for some.</p>
  <p>So then the question arises, how do you prepare people managers to manage the performance of employees who use AI? How do managers incorporate AI into their team members’ performance and development goals? And how do managers determine what level of AI usage is appropriate? Guardrails and guidance are crucial.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="hr-and-the-next-evolution-of-ux">HR and the Next Evolution of UX</h3>
        <p>Discover how AI is revolutionizing the user experience for HR.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="https://news.sap.com/2023/09/hr-flow-of-work-ux-evolution/">Learn more</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="skills-become-the-center-of-hr-practices">2. Skills become the center of HR practices.</h2>
  <p>Organizations will be forced to consider <a href="/blogs/progress-report-addressing-hr-tasks-with-ai">what AI skills they need</a>, to identify who (internally or externally) possesses those skills, and to determine how they should best fill identified skill gaps, be it through reskilling/upskilling, redeployment, external sourcing, or leveraging contract workers. Ironically, <em>human</em> skills such as strategic thinking and complex problem solving will become increasingly important.</p>
  <p>A focus on career development and continuous learning will help employees and their employers rise to the AI challenge. Employees’ expectations for personalized career paths have increased considerably, and <a href="/resources/when-microlearning-met-gamification">microlearning</a> will help them improve their skills and adapt to changing business needs. Reskilling and <a href="/resources/how-to-upskill">upskilling</a> initiatives, especially for urgent skills needs like AI, will lead to increased motivation in employees, so it must also see greater prioritization by organizations.</p>
  <h2 id="workers-return-to-the-office">3. Workers return to the office.</h2>
  <p>Organizations will continue to experiment with motivating employees to return to the office in ways that promote productivity, collaboration, and cost savings, but don’t alienate their top talent. With the recent increase in partial and full return-to-office (RTO) policies, 2024 trends data suggests that the pendulum has swung back to hybrid.</p>
  <p>Data suggests that organizations will take one of two motivational approaches to returning to on-site workplaces in 2024 – incentivizing employees to visit the office with commute-worthy experiences or penalizing employees and/or their managers for not complying with RTO mandates. In this period of rethinking and redesigning hybrid and remote work models, trends indicate that organizations in 2024 will <a href="/resources/replacing-water-cooler-moments">reconsider their culture</a>: what it is, what they want it to be, and how to best sustain it.</p>
  <h2 id="deib-momentum-stalls">4. DEI&#x26;B momentum stalls.</h2>
  <p>Organizations that lack executive-level advocacy and dedicated DEI&#x26;B resources are likely to deprioritize or even defund their DEI&#x26;B efforts this year, in part due to some employees’ <a href="/resources/why-dei-backlash-exists">discontentment with these initiatives</a>, but also due to changing legal landscapes.</p>
  <p>However, demographic, legal, and economic shifts make 2024 the year to lean in to DEI&#x26;B, not shy away from it. An aging workforce and limits on immigration are contributing to a global talent and skills shortage, which forces organizations to rethink how they find talent, and to recognize where bias and exclusion exist in their recruiting and selection practices. Another reason DEI&#x26;B will be crucial in 2024 is that the workforce spans more generations than ever before, and the increase in generational diversity requires effective DEI&#x26;B management to ensure employee and business success.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_12223eb2e3187e234e28acd0c09c2a6ec462da6b2.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_12223eb2e3187e234e28acd0c09c2a6ec462da6b2.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_12223eb2e3187e234e28acd0c09c2a6ec462da6b2.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="group of coworkers meditating at the office" src="./media_12223eb2e3187e234e28acd0c09c2a6ec462da6b2.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="mental-health-reaches-a-breaking-point">5. Mental health reaches a breaking point.</h2>
  <p>As rates of employee stress and burnout increase to all-time highs, this year’s trends make it clear that mental health will need to be a specific and dedicated focus of organizations’ well-being efforts in 2024. Being on the receiving end of countless organizational restructurings, leadership transitions, and technology changes over the past several years have left many employees in a state of total change fatigue.</p>
  <p>Meanwhile, another crucial focus of employers’ well-being efforts will be financial well-being. The link between financial wellness and mental health isn’t difficult to draw; finances are continually reported by employees as a top contributor to their stress.</p>
  <h2 id="trust-in-leadership-plummets-to-new-lows">6. Trust in leadership plummets to new lows.</h2>
  <p>The change-induced stress, burnout, and disconnection that workers are experiencing will require organizations to focus on building a trusting, communicative relationship between employees and their leadership, but the current work climate of instability, prompted by a broader business environment of layoffs, the advent of workplace AI, macroeconomic uncertainty, global conflict, and the likelihood of upcoming political upheaval, has created a strong sense of job insecurity for many workers. This puts leaders in a tough position.</p>
  <p>The current dearth of leadership trust may leave employees feeling less valued and less connected to the larger mission of their organization than in previous years. If employees’ search for meaning is not fulfilled, they may consider looking at other job opportunities where those needs can be met.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="five-steps-to-reduce-emotional-labor">Five steps to reduce emotional labor</h3>
        <p>Is your technology helping solve employee burnout issues, or causing it?</p>
        <p><strong><a href="/resources/how-to-fix-emotional-labor">Get solutions here</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="hr-transforms-its-own-skills-and-agility">7. HR transforms its own skills and agility.</h2>
  <p>HR will undergo its own skills transformation in a few key areas. AI is at the top of the list, of course, but public relations skills are a new necessity in 2024. In a world where RTO mandates and layoffs have become major news headlines, and live reactions to being fired have even gone viral on social media, HR must anticipate this level of exposure and be prepared to address it both internally and externally.</p>
  <p>Intelligent technologies have long been a part of HR’s toolbox, but with the <a href="/resources/how-hr-can-direct-use-of-ai">explosion of generative AI capabilities</a> and access in 2023, there are a wealth of opportunities for HR professionals at all levels to improve the quality and efficiency of their work in 2024.</p>
  <h2 id="pay-gets-put-in-the-spotlight">8. Pay gets put in the spotlight.</h2>
  <p>Several factors have converged over the past year to make pay top of mind for both employees and employers, including continued economic uncertainty, organizational restructuring and layoffs, increased costs of living, and elevated inflation and interest rates. The 2024 trends point to several other employee-driven forces elevating the compensation topic, including changing work arrangements and growing expectations for fair pay.</p>
  <p>On the one hand, employees expect organizations to provide compensation and benefits to address their logistic concerns (for example, to deal with transportation costs associated with returning to the office). On the other, experts have considered wage growth in recent years to be unsustainable. The prediction is for a notable decline in total compensation this year as some organizations attempt to rebalance their compensation costs. What shows no signs of slowing down, though, are calls for pay equity and pay transparency.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_19cda3669c0d4474945867b196cfec535bcda3c14.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_19cda3669c0d4474945867b196cfec535bcda3c14.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_19cda3669c0d4474945867b196cfec535bcda3c14.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Young black woman stands clapping with colleagues in a meeting." src="./media_19cda3669c0d4474945867b196cfec535bcda3c14.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1680" height="1120">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="sustainability-becomes-a-strategy">9. Sustainability becomes a strategy.</h2>
  <p>Sustainability will move beyond compliance and be treated as an important element of employer brand and internal strategy execution. HR will be expected to weave eco-friendly practices into HR policies, to provide employees with training to understand the organization’s sustainability goals, and to implement new technologies or practices that will replace less efficient alternatives.</p>
  <p>Organizations will need to tread carefully as they emphasize environmental sustainability as a key strategic priority while simultaneously enforcing RTO mandates that could be perceived as having negative environmental effects. Addressing the topic openly and transparently will serve organizations well.</p>
  <h2 id="more-about-the-top-2024-hr-trends">More about the top 2024 HR trends</h2>
  <p>For a more in-depth reading of this year’s HR trends, read the <em>complete report,</em> <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2024/02/883d4dde-ad7e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">2024 HR Trends: The Year of AI</a> (free registration required). In addition to a complete analysis of each trend and our perspective, we pose questions for HR and business professionals to consider, and we provide resources to help deal with the important issues now. For an overview of the research, watch the <a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2024/03/ba6018b8-ae7e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">2024 HR Trends video</a> from Dr. Katherine Gibbard, Research Scientist, or check out the <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2024/03/eccb5dad-ae7e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">infographic</a>.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>core-topic/responsible-ai</category>
            <category>content-type/expert-opinions</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Synthetic Data Can Avoid Company Risk with AI]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/how-synthetic-data-can-avoid-company-risk-with-ai</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/how-synthetic-data-can-avoid-company-risk-with-ai</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn how companies can avoid data privacy and copyright issues with synthetic data generation.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>core-topic/responsible-ai</category>
            <category>content-type/expert-opinions</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[What Generative AI Can Do for Utilities]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/what-generative-ai-can-do-for-utilities</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/what-generative-ai-can-do-for-utilities</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With practice, utilities see using Generative AI to better manage power lines, predict and prevent outages, and train field workers.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>industry/utilities</category>
            <category>content-type/expert-opinions</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Future of Supply Chain Podcast | SAP Insights]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/future-of-supply-chain-podcast</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/future-of-supply-chain-podcast</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn from SAP’s Richard Howells how resiliency, sustainability and visibility are becoming more important than ever in future supply chains.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/expert-opinions</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Progress Report: Addressing HR Tasks with AI]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/progress-report-addressing-hr-tasks-with-ai</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/progress-report-addressing-hr-tasks-with-ai</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn how HR is using artificial intelligence and machine learning to streamline processes, enhance decision-making, prevent bias, and train employees.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>core-topic/responsible-ai</category>
            <category>content-type/expert-opinions</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Perspectives on Digital Manufacturing | SAP Insights]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/ext-perspective-on-digital-manufacturing</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/ext-perspective-on-digital-manufacturing</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Gain insights on how to create a resilient and agile manufacturing supply chain by leveraging advanced technology.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>topic/business-transformation</category>
            <category>content-type/expert-opinions</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Turning Agricultural Waste into Buildings]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/turning-agricultural-waste-into-buildings</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/turning-agricultural-waste-into-buildings</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Find out how a sustainable construction-material entrepreneur brought her idea to life by engaging local communities.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11ff1654bf1679391f4ffabdc421a48dedfe40db0.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11ff1654bf1679391f4ffabdc421a48dedfe40db0.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_11ff1654bf1679391f4ffabdc421a48dedfe40db0.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Workers bent over in a large agricultural field in southern India." src="./media_11ff1654bf1679391f4ffabdc421a48dedfe40db0.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1044">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="turning-agricultural-waste-into-buildings">Turning Agricultural Waste into Buildings</h1>
        <p>A sustainable construction-material entrepreneur brought her idea to life by engaging local communities.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>By Lauren Gibbons Paul</p>
  <p>Sometimes, just having a question is enough. That’s how Shriti Pandey, founder and CEO of Strawcture Eco, started a sustainable construction-materials company – despite having virtually no work experience.</p>
  <p>Back home for a 2016 fellowship in India after graduate school in New York, Pandey saw local farmers burning “stubble,” the waste that results from the unusable portion – often 50% of the total weight – of agricultural crops. Farmers burn that byproduct because they can’t make any money from it. Pandey’s business started with a question: What if we could turn that stubble into a material for sustainable construction?</p>
  <p>She had no experience in construction – or any kind of industry – only a degree in civil engineering. And she was a young woman entering an industry largely made up of older men. Pandey did have one advantage: She knew how to approach people and get their input and support for new ideas. This skill became very important when her small team had to engage with farmers to buy waste products from their crops. Barreling in from the outside and demanding a community do things differently, especially given language and cultural barriers, is a formula for failure, she says. Engaging in a meaningful, two-way interchange is the only way to do this work.</p>
  <p>This approach led to Strawcture Eco’s first product, a panel for building as sturdy as steel or concrete, but more affordable and sustainable – as well as some unexpected adventures, like managing the construction of a 75-bed rural COVID-19 hospital in just 45 days.</p>
  <p>The film <em>She Run the World</em> is part of SAP’s Roads to Regeneration series, produced in partnership with Hot Docs. SAP Insights spoke to Pandey about how community engagement has informed her business and career.</p>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b5d305a32c7b85791487ed0e662700a9f598ff71.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b5d305a32c7b85791487ed0e662700a9f598ff71.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1b5d305a32c7b85791487ed0e662700a9f598ff71.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="One of eight documentaries created by Hot Docs and produced by SAP. Part of the Roads to Regeneration compilation." src="./media_1b5d305a32c7b85791487ed0e662700a9f598ff71.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="319" height="179">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://d.dam.sap.com/m/aawW7zb/hls.m3u8">Roads to Regeneration - She Run The World</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>en-US</div>
      <div>English</div>
      <div><a href="https://d.dam.sap.com/o/s7Mct1x/SAP922411-en%5C%5C_us-English?rc=19">https://d.dam.sap.com/o/s7Mct1x/SAP922411-en\\_us-English?rc=19</a></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="sap-insights-what-was-your-core-idea-behind-strawcture-eco">SAP Insights: What was your core idea behind Strawcture Eco?</h2>
  <p><strong>Shriti Pandey:</strong> There's so much agricultural surplus residue – the byproduct of crop harvesting – especially in an agrarian country like India. While we're talking so much about climate change and resource waste, it seemed to me there were genuine renewable raw materials available that no one was using. We are literally burning waste, cutting trees, and then making materials in the factory that require so much fossil fuel. So the core question was, can this waste be converted into valuable products that reduce our reliance on fossil-based energy? That’s what I was obsessed about.</p>
  <h2 id="q-did-you-encounter-barriers-when-you-were-trying-to-break-into-the-construction-space-especially-as-a-young-woman">Q: Did you encounter barriers when you were trying to break into the construction space, especially as a young woman?</h2>
  <p>Pandey: I started Strawcture in 2018. I was 26. I had one year of experience working in New York, no prior work experience in India at all. So the idea was quite daunting to me. And I had no buddies to start the project with. It was not just about being young, but also because I was a solo founder.</p>
  <p>Until I started Strawcture, I thought there was no difference in the opportunities men and women get. I grew up as one of a set of triplets in a small town in India. I had the privilege of an upbringing where my parents were very capable of providing an education for my sister, brother, and me. They never told us what to do, which people think happens a lot in smaller towns and villages in India. I had complete freedom, which is why I thought I could even do this without questioning.</p>
  <p>It was only when I started my company that I realized that the world is not free of discrimination. I got exposed to a very male-dominated industry. Very early on after starting Strawcture, there was this government conference around green materials. As I stepped into that room, I vividly remember that it only had men in it, mostly in their 40s or older. And they all just looked at me, clearly thinking, “Who is she?” I felt for a second that I was in the wrong room. So I left. I asked somebody outside, “Is this the right room?” They said yes. So I went back in, and I didn’t know where to sit or who to talk to.</p>
  <p>It took me a while to get used to it. Before you can get other people to accept you, you also have to accept that you belong. So for me, that was the first step of the journey. Once I felt more confident, I started networking. Now, once they see me on stage as a speaker, there's a level of credibility, of substance. So people are more willing to approach me.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1071e3d8dcc85b3d1d0aabc48f450d2cb12891b35.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1071e3d8dcc85b3d1d0aabc48f450d2cb12891b35.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1071e3d8dcc85b3d1d0aabc48f450d2cb12891b35.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="In this school auditorium in Delhi, the walls, ceiling and stage flooring are made from recycled agricultural waste. Photo courtesy of Shriti Pandey." src="./media_1071e3d8dcc85b3d1d0aabc48f450d2cb12891b35.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="2160">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="q-its-only-five-years-later-but-these-days-are-you-seeing-more-participation-in-the-construction-industry-by-young-or-older-women">Q: It’s only five years later, but these days, are you seeing more participation in the construction industry by young or older women?</h2>
  <p><strong>Pandey:</strong> Yes, definitely. I see more women in these spaces as different stakeholders now, even a lot of women investors who are in the climate tech space.</p>
  <h2 id="q-what-happened-to-your-business-and-your-research-during-the-pandemic-shutdowns">Q: What happened to your business and your research during the pandemic shutdowns?</h2>
  <p><strong>Pandey:</strong> The lockdown happened in India in March 2020, and I had traveled from Delhi to my village for my mother's birthday. I ended up being there for a year. Our line of business is very tactile, very physical. If you don't meet people, they won’t understand, no one will buy. So everything came to a halt for three months.</p>
  <p>Then someone from the SELCO Foundation NGO approached us to build some COVID-19 hospitals. At that point, they could take the risk and let a new technology be tested in that scenario. So, we grabbed that opportunity. There were a lot of companies building COVID hospitals. We ended up building ours the fastest. We built a 75-bed, full COVID [treatment] hospital with 12 doctors in 45 days. The community immediately showed up needing medical services, which they previously had gone without.</p>
  <p>We built three more hospitals made from waste after that – our materials went to the walls and the ceilings. We also made all the furniture. The only thing we didn’t make other than medical equipment was the flooring. But we did everything else. And our materials were also used on the external facades of the building.</p>
  <h2 id="q-where-did-the-hospital-designs-and-plans-come-from-and-what-did-the-process-look-like">Q: Where did the hospital designs and plans come from? And what did the process look like?</h2>
  <p><strong>Pandey:</strong> The NGO gave us the plans and the patch of land in Masaurhi Block, Patna. They wanted to build where governmental services like healthcare and infrastructure were not present. So, this was not in the middle of the city, which made it more challenging. Being a civil engineer became helpful. We made all the structural drawings. We did everything – the plumbing, civil, electrical, which was not even our forte.</p>
  <p>Travel was a challenge. The police commissioner would only give our team permission to move outside of the village when the work was done, so we ended up living on-site for 45 days. I actually ended up living in the hospital itself as it was being built. I’ll never forget that.</p>
  <p>Because everything was locked down, we couldn’t bring in contractors or construction workers. I really learned about getting the community involved in these things. We went into the villages and announced, we've been told to make this hospital for your community. Help us find workers. The next day, almost half of the village showed up, like 100 people. Someone said I'm a carpenter, I'm an electrician, I'm a plumber. Everybody in the village ended up working on that project under our direction. This is during the month of June in India, which is like 48 degrees Celsius (118 degrees Fahrenheit).</p>
  <h2 id="q-you-were-under-30-years-old-at-that-time-and-you-built-a-hospital">Q: You were under 30 years old at that time, and you built a hospital!</h2>
  <p><strong>Pandey:</strong> I was 28. If it wasn’t during COVID-19, they wouldn’t have let me do it.</p>
  <h2 id="q-where-are-your-research-and-development-efforts-focused-these-days">Q: Where are your research and development efforts focused these days?</h2>
  <p><strong>Pandey:</strong> We are working a lot with biomimicry, a relatively new field where architects and product designers look to nature before they go into the lab. For example, how a bee would make its honeycomb. Those are some of the most geometrically stable structures. You can learn a lot from them to apply to making houses that are very earthquake-resistant.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_13ee708d2c78caf083b2fccdc9c3cff9914dfab25.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_13ee708d2c78caf083b2fccdc9c3cff9914dfab25.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_13ee708d2c78caf083b2fccdc9c3cff9914dfab25.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="A farmer works in a paddy field near Mysore in southern India. Photo courtesy of Shriti Pandey." src="./media_13ee708d2c78caf083b2fccdc9c3cff9914dfab25.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="2160">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p>That led to us creating these frame systems that are honeycomb in shape. There’s so much inspiration in nature, in terms of physics, science, and biology.</p>
  <p>We also launched a felt product that can be used for sound and thermal insulation. We were doing a project in Rajasthan, which is one of the hottest desert regions in the world, and the community asked, why do you use so much of the traditional glass wool insulation? Why not use animal-residue material like wool? Nothing is more insulating. That led us to look at the value chain of wool that is not sold for textile use and to a number of pastoralists in India who do sheep shearing, and then to us making 100% biodegradable felt.</p>
  <p>If we were not engaged with the community, we wouldn’t know how to even collect it.</p>
  <h2 id="q-in-the-film-you-talked-about-how-in-small-villages-nothing-goes-to-waste-what-did-you-learn-from-them">Q: In the film, you talked about how in small villages nothing goes to waste. What did you learn from them?</h2>
  <p><strong>Pandey:</strong> When I lived in a village for a year with a family that was living in a very low-cost, makeshift house, I witnessed that, whether it is their structures, the way they cook, the way they engage with each other in the community – they will not let anything go to waste. It's the perspective that when you don't have a lot, there's just no room to waste.</p>
  <p>And that made me realize that waste is only a waste if you waste it. It's a choice. We can look at it differently. Everything that's coming out of a factory, every construction site, demolition, and everything in our houses that we don't need any more is a possible resource for some added-value product. It’s a mind shift.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <h4 id="read-more-in-this-series">Read more in this series</h4>
  <div class="collection">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h6 id="editorial">Editorial</h6>
        <p><a href="/blogs/300-days-of-sun">300 Days of Sun: Communities Power Their Own Future</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>
        <h6 id="editorial-1">Editorial</h6>
        <p><a href="/blogs/a-case-for-carbon-accountability">A Case for Carbon Accountability</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>
        <h6 id="editorial-2">Editorial</h6>
        <p><a href="/blogs/restoring-peatlands">Restoring Peatlands, Nature’s Carbon Sponges</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>
        <h6 id="editorial-3">Editorial</h6>
        <p><a href="/blogs/road-to-regeneration-waste-to-life">Road to Regeneration: Waste to Life</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>
        <h6 id="editorial-4">Editorial</h6>
        <p><a href="/blogs/road-to-regeneration-beautiful-poison">Turning Toxic Coal Mine Waste into the Stuff of Art</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div><a href="/videos/roads-to-regeneration-series">Roads to Regeneration collection</a></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>sidebar</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>core-topic/sustainable-business-operations</category>
            <category>content-type/expert-opinions</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Playbook for Machine Learning Projects That Work]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/a-playbook-for-machine-learning-projects-that-work</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/a-playbook-for-machine-learning-projects-that-work</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn the six-step methodology to help organizations avoid the many potential pitfalls in Machine Learning deployment.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>content-type/expert-opinions</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Building Trust in Businesses with ERP Investments]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/ext-building-better-trust-with-cloud-erp</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/ext-building-better-trust-with-cloud-erp</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn from new research by IDC and sponsored by SAP why ERP systems are key to building trust with your customers.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10ff8949132b92e3fef399b9a8efce56edc342e3c.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10ff8949132b92e3fef399b9a8efce56edc342e3c.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_10ff8949132b92e3fef399b9a8efce56edc342e3c.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Two coworkers huddle over a tablet in a busy setting." src="./media_10ff8949132b92e3fef399b9a8efce56edc342e3c.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1044">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="building-better-trust-in-business-with-cloud-erp-investments">Building Better Trust in Business with Cloud ERP Investments</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Increased customer satisfaction and loyalty, employee retention, business resilience, and operational efficiency – at their core, they all rely on trust.</p>
  <p>An organizational focus on trustworthiness signals to customers that the companies they partner with will handle their business with the competence, transparency, fidelity, and integrity they expect.</p>
  <p>Although trust can seem abstract and subject to infinite interpretations, <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2023/09/f2c65dfe-8e7e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">research</a> by IDC shows that companies can build a robust trust strategy by focusing their efforts on stronger security; privacy; compliance; and environmental, social, and governance (ESG). A majority of respondents also expressed a preference for cloud enterprise resource planning (ERP) systems as part of that strategy.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_134f89ccd7d60a0879972b65a93553aeacfd8c108.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_134f89ccd7d60a0879972b65a93553aeacfd8c108.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_134f89ccd7d60a0879972b65a93553aeacfd8c108.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Young woman smiling at a laptop." src="./media_134f89ccd7d60a0879972b65a93553aeacfd8c108.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="research-highlights">Research highlights</h2>
  <p>Over 400 ERP customers were surveyed in Europe, North America, and Asia/Pacific. Respondents were selected if they met all four of the following criteria:</p>
  <p><strong>1.</strong> Respondent uses an ERP</p>
  <p><strong>2.</strong> Respondent has a role in ERP selection</p>
  <p><strong>3.</strong> Respondent is knowledgeable in one or more areas of trust</p>
  <p><strong>4.</strong> Respondent can identify their current ERP provider</p>
  <p>Results of the survey highlighted some key areas:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>The operational and strategic advantages customers seek when they consider or decide to move to a cloud ERP</li>
    <li>The level of trust customers have in on-prem compared to cloud-based ERP systems</li>
    <li>The priorities of ERP customers in the areas of security, privacy, compliance, and ESG</li>
    <li>The greatest weaknesses perceived by ERP customers of their current vendor</li>
  </ul>
  <p>According to the IDC research, trustworthy businesses feature a robust approach to risk management, security, compliance, privacy, and ESG.</p>
  <p>The top reasons for moving to a cloud ERP system include better security, compliance, privacy, and risk posture (45%) and better alignment with company values/ESG initiatives (34%).</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_13887a4939c723b2adbb9f72bb822eefc32a58425.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_13887a4939c723b2adbb9f72bb822eefc32a58425.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_13887a4939c723b2adbb9f72bb822eefc32a58425.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Chart showing that 45% of survey respondents said better security, compliance, privacy, and risk posture were their top reasons for moving to a cloud ERP system." src="./media_13887a4939c723b2adbb9f72bb822eefc32a58425.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1963" height="1120">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p><em>Source: IDC’s SAP Global Future of Trust &#x26; Security Survey, 2023</em></p>
  <p>Furthermore, cloud-based ERP users report much greater trust in their systems when compared to on-prem ERP users, with 31% of cloud-based ERP users reporting 100% trust in their ERP provider, while only 22% of on-prem ERP users report the same.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ebce84ad92ed5647b7f5480a933a4802abbc21ef.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ebce84ad92ed5647b7f5480a933a4802abbc21ef.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1ebce84ad92ed5647b7f5480a933a4802abbc21ef.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Chart shows 31% of cloud-based ERP users report 100% trust in their ERP provider, while only 22% of on-prem ERP users report the same." src="./media_1ebce84ad92ed5647b7f5480a933a4802abbc21ef.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2161" height="1120">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p><em>Source: IDC’s SAP Global Future of Trust &#x26; Security Survey, 2023</em></p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11bcacdf7b1aaa4b761bbaf0d00c315ec1332f6a2.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11bcacdf7b1aaa4b761bbaf0d00c315ec1332f6a2.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_11bcacdf7b1aaa4b761bbaf0d00c315ec1332f6a2.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Businessman looking away at office desk" src="./media_11bcacdf7b1aaa4b761bbaf0d00c315ec1332f6a2.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1811" height="1120">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="insights-from-idc-research-key-findings">Insights from IDC Research: Key Findings</h2>
  <p>Key findings from IDC's recent survey show that investments in cloud ERP systems have proven to enhance overall business ROI.</p>
  <h3 id="investment-in-cloud-erp-systems-yields-improved-business-roi">Investment in cloud ERP systems yields improved business ROI</h3>
  <p>Organizations prioritizing trust-building efforts with customers and staff have experienced increased efficiency, market value, and better retention rates for both customers and employees.</p>
  <p>Over the last 12 months, respondents reported a 20% boost in customer satisfaction and a corresponding 19% rise in employee productivity. Operational efficiency, a primary business focus, also saw a 19% increase among those investing in ERP initiatives, with respondents reporting a 20% increase in innovation as a result.</p>
  <h3 id="security-matters">Security matters</h3>
  <p>Security emerged as a critical concern for businesses transitioning to cloud ERP solutions, driven by the pursuit of improved privacy, security, and compliance postures.</p>
  <p>The IDC research underscores the foundational role of security, privacy, and compliance in building trust. Cloud ERP users exhibited higher trust levels compared to their on-premise counterparts, with 45% of surveyed ERP customers either migrating or planning to migrate to cloud platforms.</p>
  <p>Among security considerations, managing supply chain vulnerabilities took precedence, emphasizing the need for solutions addressing this complex task.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1dfc45d31697f52f727ee2b6f5bd3d815cd3814a5.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1dfc45d31697f52f727ee2b6f5bd3d815cd3814a5.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1dfc45d31697f52f727ee2b6f5bd3d815cd3814a5.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Two smiling coworkers using a digital tablet together while standing on an office building balcony." src="./media_1dfc45d31697f52f727ee2b6f5bd3d815cd3814a5.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1978" height="1120">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p>The dynamic technology landscape further highlights the flexibility and responsiveness provided by cloud ERP platforms, enabling organizations to adapt to evolving customer and regulatory needs.</p>
  <p>Priorities in compliance and privacy management differ across regions. The IDC research reveals that in the Asia/Pacific region, respondents prioritize data loss prevention and information rights management as their top privacy concerns. Conversely, North American and European respondents prioritize monitoring, reporting, and transparency of privacy policies.</p>
  <p>With leaders increasingly focusing on organizational trust as a key business priority, the IDC research highlights the pivotal role of trusted cloud ERP solutions in preserving business value by efficiently managing security, privacy, and compliance.</p>
</div>
<div>
  <h3 id="learn-more-about-this-research">Learn more about this research:</h3>
  <p>1. <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2023/09/58b65dfe-8e7e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">IDC Future of Trust Infographic</a></p>
  <p>2. <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2023/09/f2c65dfe-8e7e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">IDC Future of Trust Infobrief</a></p>
  <p>3. <a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2023/09/506303cd-8e7e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">IDC Future of Trust Video</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>Style</div>
      <div>Additional Reading</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
<div>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div data-valign="middle">
        <p>All survey findings are sourced from IDC in an InfoBrief sponsored by SAP: Trusted ERP Systems: Priority offerings in security, privacy, compliance, and ESG (IDC #US51001623, September 2023).</p>
        <p>Find more information on security, compliance, privacy, and cloud service performance at the <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/trust-center/security.html">SAP Trust Center.</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>content-type/expert-opinions</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[What Will the Supply Chain of the Future Look Like?]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/ext-what-will-the-future-supply-chain-look-like</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/ext-what-will-the-future-supply-chain-look-like</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn from SAP’s Richard Howells how resiliency, sustainability and visibility are becoming more important than ever in future supply chains.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/expert-opinions</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Future of ERP Podcast]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/future-of-erp-podcast</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/future-of-erp-podcast</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP’s Richard Howells and Oyku Ilgar interviews expert from the world of ERP and finance to learn, share ideas and best practices across the business world.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>content-type/expert-opinions</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Metaverse: A New Space for Business]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/ext-the-metaverse-a-new-space-for-business</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/ext-the-metaverse-a-new-space-for-business</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn how the metaverse can play an important role in the digital transformation of businesses and unveil new business opportunities.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/business-transformation</category>
            <category>content-type/expert-opinions</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Self-Sovereign Identity Improves Online Trust]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/ext-how-ssi-improves-online-trust</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/ext-how-ssi-improves-online-trust</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn how SSI is working to redefine online trust and radically improve business efficiency.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/business-transformation</category>
            <category>content-type/expert-opinions</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bridging the Sustainability Capability Gap]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/ext-bridging-the-sustainability-capability-gap</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/ext-bridging-the-sustainability-capability-gap</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn how businesses and government can come together to make more meaningful advances in sustainability.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>core-topic/sustainable-business-operations</category>
            <category>content-type/expert-opinions</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Generative AI for the Renaissance of Business Process Excellence | SAP Insights]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/ext-generative-ai-for-business-process-excellence</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/ext-generative-ai-for-business-process-excellence</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Explore this business-driven approach to identify application areas for generative AI in business processes.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>content-type/expert-opinions</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Keys to Ignite the Generative AI Business Revolution]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/ext-keys-to-ignite-the-generative-business-revolution</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/ext-keys-to-ignite-the-generative-business-revolution</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Explore how generative AI will transform business processes in this new review from experts.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11727be9daa2135b83aedac57754e71680d4d1b78.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11727be9daa2135b83aedac57754e71680d4d1b78.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_11727be9daa2135b83aedac57754e71680d4d1b78.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="two men looking at digital AI screen" src="./media_11727be9daa2135b83aedac57754e71680d4d1b78.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1044">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="keys-to-ignite-the-generative-business-revolution">Keys to Ignite the Generative Business Revolution</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>By Marco Cigaina and Itzhak Shoshan</p>
  <p>Generative artificial intelligence (AI) is no longer a far off, futuristic technology – as it continues to evolve in its capabilities, it has the potential to transform business processes.</p>
  <p>One way to better understand generative AI is to look at it from a functional perspective. Generative AI models have a diverse range of capabilities across many design options and data types including text, code, images, audio, video, and 3D objects. For example:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Natural language models excel in tasks such as content creation, chatbot development, search enhancement, and document analysis and synthesis.</li>
    <li>Programming code-focused models facilitate code generation, application prototyping, and synthetic data generation.</li>
    <li>Image-processing models enable sophisticated image generation and editing, while those trained on audio data deftly convert text to voice and vice versa, as well as generate and edit sounds.</li>
    <li>3D-data- and design-savvy models revolutionize product design and 3D object generation.</li>
    <li>Finally, video-trained models not only generate and edit videos but also, when integrated with sound and text models, can perform tasks such as video translation.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>For leaders to use generative AI’s capabilities to their full potential, they’ll first need to understand the opportunities, challenges, and implications associated with integrating it into their operations.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10d5b4ea0b7a3daf79e0f48bdf630914f879e0a18.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10d5b4ea0b7a3daf79e0f48bdf630914f879e0a18.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_10d5b4ea0b7a3daf79e0f48bdf630914f879e0a18.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Slide view of two men looking at digital screen" src="./media_10d5b4ea0b7a3daf79e0f48bdf630914f879e0a18.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="284" height="160">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="embracing-the-ai-revolution">Embracing the AI Revolution</h2>
  <p>Generative artificial intelligence has undergone a remarkable evolution, constantly progressing in its capabilities and potential applications.</p>
  <p>The great acceleration of AI followed the publication of the 2017 paper “<a href="https://arxiv.org/abs/1706.03762">Attention is all you need</a>” and the subsequent development of transformers — a new deep learning network architecture — which significantly increased the computational efficiency of the training process. This, coupled with the opportunity to train large language models unsupervised, increased the size of the models, allowing for new capabilities. Innovations in fine-tuning models, based on reinforcement learning from human feedback, led to the development of the powerful generative AI models we see today.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1295e866b79d7067eb5cc7981a10c4f97a9bd9cf8.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1295e866b79d7067eb5cc7981a10c4f97a9bd9cf8.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1295e866b79d7067eb5cc7981a10c4f97a9bd9cf8.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="close up image of fingers tuning a dial button" src="./media_1295e866b79d7067eb5cc7981a10c4f97a9bd9cf8.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="284" height="160">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p>Business leaders should recognize that the generative AI applications available today are just the beginning. As research and development in the field continues to advance, we can expect more sophisticated and powerful models that will open new possibilities for automation, personalization, and creativity. To get there, leaders should stay informed about the latest developments in generative AI, remain adaptable, and embrace a mindset of continuous learning.</p>
  <p>"Generative artificial intelligence has undergone a remarkable evolution, constantly progressing in its capabilities and potential applications."</p>
  <h2 id="unlocking-the-value-of-generative-ai">Unlocking the Value of Generative AI</h2>
  <p>Generative AI brings numerous benefits to employees, companies, and the economy.</p>
  <p><a href="https://www.mckinsey.com/capabilities/mckinsey-digital/our-insights/the-economic-potential-of-generative-ai-the-next-productivity-frontier#key-insights">McKinsey</a> predicts an annual addition of $2.6-$4.4 trillion to the economy through generative AI. In addition, <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-06-01/chatgpt-to-fuel-1-3-trillion-ai-market-by-2032-bi-report-says?srnd=technology-vp">Bloomberg</a> forecasts that the generative AI market is set to skyrocket from $67 billion in 2023 to an impressive $1.3 trillion per annum by 2032.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_183103225d3c290c91527fc75f5f8d75f1fc38d8f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_183103225d3c290c91527fc75f5f8d75f1fc38d8f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_183103225d3c290c91527fc75f5f8d75f1fc38d8f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="man in aprorn paining a red shoe" src="./media_183103225d3c290c91527fc75f5f8d75f1fc38d8f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="284" height="160">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p>It has the potential to boost employee creativity and productivity as a valuable assistant, generating insights, suggestions, and solutions that streamline workflows. It provides workers a platform for experimentation and learning. It also frees up valuable time and mental resources, allowing employees to focus on higher-level tasks that require strategic thinking and decision-making.</p>
  <p>At the organizational level, companies can optimize processes and create personalized experiences for customers. Embracing generative AI also positions businesses toward sustainable growth. It can revolutionize industries such as design, entertainment, healthcare, and marketing by automating creative processes, generating personalized experiences, and advancing research and development. For example, in the design field, it can support and complement architects in designing sustainable buildings, fashion designers in crafting unique garments, and artists in producing captivating visual experiences.</p>
  <p>It can also complement existing workflows by collaborating with human experts and harnessing their domain expertise. To effectively integrate it within enterprise systems, businesses must assess their operational needs, pinpointing areas where automation, decision-making enhancements, or creative content generation can add value.</p>
  <h2 id="separating-hype-from-reality-and-debunking-common-misconceptions">Separating Hype from Reality and Debunking Common Misconceptions</h2>
  <p>It is crucial to differentiate between the real opportunities presented by generative artificial intelligence and the hype surrounding it. While the hype often portrays generative AI as a magic solution capable of instantly transforming businesses, a more nuanced understanding reveals its true potential. It is essential to approach generative AI with a balanced and pragmatic perspective, understanding its limitations and ethical implications. Business leaders should conduct thorough assessments of their specific industry and business needs, identify suitable use cases, and ensure that the integration of generative AI aligns with their ethical values as well as regulatory requirements. By doing so, businesses can harness the true potential of generative AI and use it in a responsible and sustainable manner.</p>
  <p>One major misunderstanding about generative AI is that it operates independently, creating content or solutions without human intervention. These models are meticulously trained and supervised by teams of data scientists and domain experts. They operate within the parameters defined during training and continually require monitoring and adjustment to ensure optimal performance. Contrary to the belief that generative AI might replace human jobs, it is designed to augment human capabilities, not supplant them. While generative AI is an extraordinary tool, it is just that – a tool that complements human ingenuity and expertise. Generative AI also does not “understand” or “think” in the way humans do. It identifies patterns and makes predictions based on its training data, without an inherent understanding of the concepts involved.</p>
  <p>"It is crucial to differentiate between the real opportunities presented by generative artificial intelligence and the hype surrounding it."</p>
  <h2 id="addressing-limitations-and-risks">Addressing Limitations and Risks</h2>
  <p>Like any other emerging technology, there are certain challenges that need to be addressed. These limitations range from understanding and intelligence, through personalization and consistency in learning, to factual and ethical accuracy, scalability, and transparency, among others. Let us delve into these clusters to get a better understanding of the challenges that still need to be addressed and how generative AI could further develop.</p>
  <p><em>Model Understanding and Intelligence</em></p>
  <ul>
    <li>Stateless, context-insensitive operations: The model processes each input independently, struggle with tasks requiring long-term context or common-sense reasoning, and are sensitive to input phrasing.</li>
    <li>Lack of true comprehension: The model generates responses based on patterns, without understanding the content, the emotional implications, or being able to differentiate between niche topics.</li>
  </ul>
  <p><em>Learning, Personalization, and Consistency</em></p>
  <ul>
    <li>Learning and personalization limitations: The model does not learn or adapt after its training is complete, treats all inputs independently, and does not differentiate between users.</li>
    <li>Inconsistent output: Despite identical or similar queries, the model may provide varying responses due to its probabilistic nature.</li>
  </ul>
  <p><em>Factual Accuracy and Ethical Challenges</em></p>
  <ul>
    <li>Propagation of misinformation and biases: Based on its training data, the model can spread misinformation or biases, and generate a substantial number of false positives or negatives.</li>
    <li>Ethical and regulatory challenges: Ensuring AI compliance with constantly changing and geographically diverse regulations is demanding, especially in a fast-evolving technology landscape.</li>
  </ul>
  <p><em>Cost, Scalability, and Environmental Impact</em></p>
  <ul>
    <li>Economic and environmental considerations: Large models require significant computational resources, leading to substantial financial costs and environmental impact.</li>
    <li>Scaling and data issues: Increasing data scale presents computational challenges. Also, the risk of generating harmful or inappropriate content increases.</li>
  </ul>
  <p><em>Transparency, Security, and Language-Specific Limitations</em></p>
  <ul>
    <li>Model interpretability and security: The model’s decisions can be challenging to interpret, and the model can be susceptible to adversarial attacks.</li>
    <li>Language and transparency limitations: The model’s performance may vary for different languages, and it can be difficult to understand why it generates a specific output.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>If these challenges can be addressed, we predict that we will see exciting new applications of generative AI for business.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_194d9ca505a3b5db7a258caa050b68cce0be828d3.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_194d9ca505a3b5db7a258caa050b68cce0be828d3.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_194d9ca505a3b5db7a258caa050b68cce0be828d3.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="boy wearing a vest with googles and a lamp shade hat on his head" src="./media_194d9ca505a3b5db7a258caa050b68cce0be828d3.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="284" height="160">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="human-machine-collaboration">Human-Machine Collaboration</h2>
  <p>One effective strategy for mitigating risks is through diverse and representative training data. By carefully curating and reviewing the data used to train generative AI models, businesses can minimize the likelihood of biased or unethical outputs. Ongoing monitoring and auditing of generated content can help identify and rectify any unintended biases or undesirable outputs.</p>
  <p>Collaboration between human experts and generative AI systems is vital to mitigate risks and limitations. Combining the expertise of human professionals with the capabilities of generative AI can result in more robust and reliable outcomes. Human oversight and intervention can help ensure that the outputs align with ethical standards, business goals, and regulatory requirements.</p>
  <p>Regular training and education for employees on ethical considerations and the responsible use of generative AI is also essential. This helps build awareness and understanding of the risks and limitations, enabling individuals to make informed decisions when utilizing generative AI tools.</p>
  <p>"Collaboration between human experts and generative AI systems is vital to mitigate risks."</p>
  <p>Generative artificial intelligence raises important ethical considerations. A key aspect is the comparison between AI-generated outputs and human intelligence. While generative AI can produce impressive results, questions arise regarding the nature of intelligence and creativity exhibited by these systems. Are they truly intelligent or creative, or are they simply mimicking patterns from existing data?</p>
  <p>Human judgment, empathy, and ethical decision-making play critical roles in guiding the use of generative AI and ensuring responsible and beneficial outcomes. Synergies between human and artificial intelligence can be harnessed to achieve that.</p>
  <p>Considering the ethical implications of generative AI is vital to ensure transparency, fairness, and accountability. It is necessary to address issues of bias, privacy, data ownership, and the potential societal impact of AI-generated content. By actively engaging in discussions surrounding the ethical and philosophical dimensions of generative AI, businesses can make informed decisions, foster responsible AI development, and uphold ethical standards in their operations.</p>
  <h2 id="harnessing-the-power-of-generative-ai">Harnessing the Power of Generative AI</h2>
  <p>Looking ahead, we see different trajectories for the evolution of AI systems. Some are intended to remove the limitations of the current models (e.g., enabling continuous learning), while others aim to add new capabilities:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>making models multi-modals, i.e., using multiple types of data in input and output (e.g., <a href="https://ai.googleblog.com/2023/03/palm-e-embodied-multimodal-language.html">Google PALM-e</a>, which can flexibly control general-purpose robots)</li>
    <li>developing increasingly sophisticated rational agents that can invoke algorithms from marketplaces of AI capabilities (e.g., <a href="https://huggingface.co/">HuggingFace</a>, which builds, trains, and deploys state-of-the-art models powered by the reference open source in machine learning)</li>
    <li>exploring how to solve humanity’s biggest challenges in areas like energy, life sciences, and climate change (e.g., DeepMind <a href="https://www.deepmind.com/research/highlighted-research/alphafold">AlphaFold</a>, which can predict 3D models of protein structures).</li>
  </ul>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_120acf8f431a26c743042231bdf861ff031c3b7fb.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_120acf8f431a26c743042231bdf861ff031c3b7fb.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_120acf8f431a26c743042231bdf861ff031c3b7fb.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="two mini robots facing each other" src="./media_120acf8f431a26c743042231bdf861ff031c3b7fb.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="284" height="160">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p>Generative AI is highly relevant today, but it represents only the beginning. By automating tasks, creating new job roles, fostering innovation, and driving growth, generative AI has significant potential to reshape the economy. Generative AI does not endanger jobs, but instead, it presents a golden chance to amplify your value within your organization. Resisting generative AI is risky: those who embrace this technology will be able to take over the roles of those who oppose it.</p>
  <p>To fully capitalize on its potential, it is crucial to address risks such as bias and ethical considerations. Clear regulations, ethical guidelines, and collaborative efforts are essential for responsible adoption.</p>
  <p>"Generative AI is a transformative technology that enhances creativity, productivity, and competitiveness for individuals and businesses."</p>
  <p>Generative AI could be the catalyst that renews industries and drives economic progress. By embracing generative AI responsibly, we can forge a future where humans and AI coexist and thrive within an ever-evolving economy.</p>
  <h2 id="snapshots">Snapshots:</h2>
  <ul>
    <li><a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2023/10/62bcbae3-917e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Interview</a> | Generative AI Interview with Nicole Büttner, Founder &#x26; CEO of Merantix Momentum</li>
    <li><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jN8JZzd-Xe4&#x26;t=2s">Envision Beyond in 60 Seconds</a> - Keys to Ignite the Generative Business Revolution</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="the-interviews-that-never-happened">The Interviews That Never Happened</h2>
  <p>What if we could use AI to predict famous thinkers have to say about its impact? Browse the interviews below to hear their potential thoughts.</p>
  <ul>
    <li><a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2023/10/581a0874-927e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Episode 1 - Alan Turing</a></li>
    <li><a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2023/10/66ad1a75-927e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Episode 2 - Marie Curie</a></li>
    <li><a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2023/10/b27dc977-927e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Episode 3 - Charles Darwin</a></li>
    <li><a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2023/10/eaffdb78-927e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Episode 4 - Leonardo da Vinci</a></li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="about-the-intelligent-enterprise-institute">About the Intelligent Enterprise Institute</h2>
  <p>The Intelligent Enterprise Institute helps business leaders understand the transformative potential of different forms of intelligence to inspire and accelerate change in their organizations and lives. By generating new insights and bringing together unheard voices and unique perspectives from global thinkers, the Intelligent Enterprise Institute aims to foster different qualities in enterprises and their stakeholders alike and move them into action.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="ready-for-more">Ready for more?</h3>
        <p>Learn how to identify where AI can make the biggest impact in your business.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="/blogs/ext-leveraging-ai-to-drive-performance">Read next story</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <h4 id="read-more-in-this-series">Read more in this series</h4>
  <div class="collection">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h6 id="editorial">Editorial</h6>
        <p><a href="/blogs/ext-envision-beyond-by-the-intelligent-enterprise-institute">Envision Beyond Curated Collection</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>
        <h6 id="editorial-1">Editorial</h6>
        <p><a href="/blogs/ext-accelerating-the-transition-to-clean-energy">Accelerating the Transition to Clean Energy</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>
        <h6 id="editorial-2">Editorial</h6>
        <p><a href="/blogs/ext-business-networks-the-only-path-forward">Business Networks: The Only Path Forward is Together</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>
        <h6 id="editorial-3">Editorial</h6>
        <p><a href="/blogs/ext-the-metaverse-a-new-space-for-business">The Metaverse: A New Space for Business</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>
        <h6 id="editorial-4">Editorial</h6>
        <p><a href="/blogs/ext-trust-in-an-age-of-mistrust">Trust in an Age of Mistrust</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>
        <h6 id="editorial-5">Editorial</h6>
        <p><a href="/blogs/ext-keys-to-ignite-the-generative-business-revolution">Keys to Ignite the Generative Business Revolution</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>
        <h6 id="editorial-6">Editorial</h6>
        <p><a href="/blogs/ext-generative-ai-for-business-process-excellence">Generative AI for the Renaissance of Business Process Excellence</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>sidebar</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>content-type/expert-opinions</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Accelerating the Transition to Clean Energy]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/ext-accelerating-the-transition-to-clean-energy</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/ext-accelerating-the-transition-to-clean-energy</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn what’s driving the transition to renewable energy across the globe and the necessary policy measures and tools used to get to net zero.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_136878ce38bf5d9b8daae1e4695b7b4adfa14c4cd.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_136878ce38bf5d9b8daae1e4695b7b4adfa14c4cd.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_136878ce38bf5d9b8daae1e4695b7b4adfa14c4cd.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="A row of wind turbines against a dark sky." src="./media_136878ce38bf5d9b8daae1e4695b7b4adfa14c4cd.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1044">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="accelerating-the-transition-to-clean-energy">Accelerating the Transition to Clean Energy</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>We are in the midst of a global energy crisis. But in our frantic efforts to fix the situation in the short term with fossil fuels, we can’t lose track of the long-term solution: a full energy transition in line with the United Nations sustainable development goals (Goal 7: <a href="https://unric.org/en/sdg-7/">Affordable and Clean Energy</a>).</p>
  <p>In fact, the current energy crisis might help accelerate the drastic changes needed to make the transition to clean energy. In this article, we’ll examine <strong>necessary policy measures</strong>, the available <strong>pathways to fully renewable energy systems</strong>, a <strong>possible road map to net zero</strong>, and the <strong>progress the global community has made so far</strong>.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14b20ac958df4ef29545f5c5468e7da0f4f7f5115.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14b20ac958df4ef29545f5c5468e7da0f4f7f5115.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_14b20ac958df4ef29545f5c5468e7da0f4f7f5115.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Image card for Envision Beyond chapter" src="./media_14b20ac958df4ef29545f5c5468e7da0f4f7f5115.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="2160">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="necessary-policy-measures">Necessary policy measures</h2>
  <p>The International Energy Agency (<a href="https://www.iea.org/about">IEA</a>) argues in its <em><a href="https://iea.blob.core.windows.net/assets/c282400e-00b0-4edf-9a8e-6f2ca6536ec8/WorldEnergyOutlook2022.pdf">World Energy Outlook 2022</a></em> that “faster clean energy transitions would have helped to moderate the impact of the crisis, and they represent the best way out of it.”</p>
  <p>This is an important point for framing any discussion about potential economic barriers to wide-scale implementation of renewable energies.</p>
  <p>The IEA report underscores that the current energy crisis promises to be a <strong>turning point for the transition to renewables</strong> based on <strong>stated policies</strong> and <strong>increased investment</strong> into clean energy by governments worldwide. Apart from the clear advantages for the environment and energy security, the economic case for the energy transition is getting stronger. According to the IEA, higher shares of renewable energy correlate with lower energy electricity prices.</p>
  <p>IEA’s Stated Policies Scenario (STEPS) predicts government investments in renewables will grow to more than $2 trillion by 2030, approximately 50% higher than today, according to the report. This scenario also foresees a peak or plateau for global fossil fuel demand within the next few years, which would be a singular turning point.</p>
  <p>The current energy crisis might help accelerate the drastic changes needed to make the transition to clean energy.</p>
  <h2 id="pathways-to-fully-renewable-energy-systems">Pathways to fully renewable energy systems</h2>
  <p>A combination of solar, wind, and limited nuclear power will be the primary drivers of the renewable energy transition.</p>
  <p>However, solar and wind energy fluctuate and are not universally available. Energy storage technologies like power-to-X (P2X) are a central component of fully renewable energy systems. P2X enables the production of various fuels, like green hydrogen, which can be transported to locations where renewable energy sources aren’t readily available. With this option for long-term storage and flexibility, strengthening the networking of electricity, heat, and mobility sectors is also possible.</p>
  <h2 id="the-p2x-principle">The P2X Principle</h2>
  <p>Power based on renewable energy (<strong>P</strong>) is converted into (<strong>2</strong>) another energy carrier (<strong>X</strong>) for long-term storage, such as power-to-gas (P2G).</p>
  <p>An <a href="https://hydrogencouncil.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/09/Hydrogen-Insights-2022-2.pdf">analysis</a> by McKinsey and Company and the Hydrogen Council notes that the race for green hydrogen has begun, even though production still needs to grow and supply chains have yet to be established. The report counts 680 large-scale project proposals worth a combined $240 billion, 10% of which have received a final investment decision.</p>
  <h2 id="a-road-map-to-net-zero">A road map to net zero</h2>
  <p>There is still a long way to go to reach our net-zero ambitions, as a closer look at the <a href="https://app.electricitymaps.com/map">Electricity Maps app</a> reveals.</p>
  <p>It’s all the more refreshing and inspiring, then, to read a recent <a href="https://ieeexplore.ieee.org/stamp/stamp.jsp?tp=&#x26;arnumber=9837910">study</a> from nearly 20 researchers and scientists around the world who developed a possible road map to net zero emissions by 2050.</p>
  <p>The route they outline goes far beyond the existing energy scenarios of the Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change reports. The interdisciplinary research team takes into consideration opportunities and challenges connected to grid congestion, energy storage, sector coupling, electrification of transport and industry by using P2X, and approaches to removing carbon dioxide from the atmosphere. Their conclusion is that a global 100% renewable energy system by 2050 is technically feasible <strong><em>and</em></strong> economically possible.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_188766238ed28aceda92d17ce991656f2f0b3a586.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_188766238ed28aceda92d17ce991656f2f0b3a586.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_188766238ed28aceda92d17ce991656f2f0b3a586.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Row of wind turbines bathed in sunlight." src="./media_188766238ed28aceda92d17ce991656f2f0b3a586.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="2160">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="progress-on-the-energy-transition">Progress on the energy transition</h2>
  <p>How far have we come on this journey?</p>
  <p>Renewable energies accounted for more than 80% of all new electricity capacity added in 2020, according to <a href="https://iea.blob.core.windows.net/assets/8b276fc2-c1ae-4a54-9681-eea1eb143d7f/TrackingSDG7TheEnergyProgressReport2022.pdf">Tracking SDG7: The Energy Progress Report 2022</a>. The report also states that IEA and International Renewable Energy Agency (IRENA) scenarios show that solar photovoltaic (PV) and wind will contribute the most growth in electricity production by 2030.</p>
  <p>To show the opportunities of the transition pathway for renewables, let’s look at the European energy market. According to a <a href="https://ember-climate.org/app/uploads/2022/10/E3G-EMBER-Briefing-More-renewables-less-inflation.pdf">status quo report</a> of energy think tanks E3G and Ember, wind and solar power accounted for 24% of the European Union’s energy mix from March through September 2022. Their contribution mitigated the effects of energy supply issues caused by unavailability of nuclear capacity and reduction in hydroelectricity generation during a period of drought. The year-on-year increase of 39 TWh, or 13%, comes at a time when the EU is <a href="https://www.consilium.europa.eu/en/press/press-releases/2022/10/04/repowereu-council-agrees-its-position/">stepping up its measures</a> to implement <a href="https://www.europarl.europa.eu/legislative-train/theme-industry-research-and-energy-itre/file-repower-eu-plan-legislative-proposals">the REPower EU proposal</a> to reduce its dependency on Russian gas.</p>
  <p>Aled Jones, director of the Global Sustainability Institute at Anglia Ruskin University, confirms that the tipping point for the shift to solar and wind as dominant technologies has already been reached in Europe. While the energy transition will cause job losses for roughly 3 million people, more than 12 million new jobs will be created as a result of this change <a href="https://www.weforum.org/agenda/2022/10/green-transition-decarbonization-myths-debunked/">by 2030</a>. This is an immense opportunity.</p>
  <h2 id="innovation-drivers">Innovation drivers</h2>
  <p>Business leaders should focus on the following three innovation areas to significantly accelerate the energy transition.</p>
  <h3 id="business-networks">1. Business networks</h3>
  <p>By leveraging business networks, key players and organizations can make full use of existing infrastructure and the latest technology innovations to accelerate their energy transition efforts.</p>
  <p><strong>Use case: CEO Alliance</strong></p>
  <p>Green hydrogen can play a significant role in creating a carbon-neutral future for energy-intensive industries such as building materials, chemicals, glass, nonferrous metals, paper, and steel. Leveraging business networks and organizations can help create an industrial-scale green hydrogen value chain. One example for cross-industry collaboration in this matter is the <a href="https://www.ceo-alliance.eu/about-the-alliance/">CEO Alliance</a>, an action tank of 14 top European companies. This industry business network aims to build up renewable energy production in Southern Europe to supply green hydrogen and ammonia to industrial hubs in Central and Northern Europe.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11df0c7360cc46dd7dc658153f285ebd57c0285ff.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11df0c7360cc46dd7dc658153f285ebd57c0285ff.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_11df0c7360cc46dd7dc658153f285ebd57c0285ff.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Close-up of blue molecules." src="./media_11df0c7360cc46dd7dc658153f285ebd57c0285ff.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="2160">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h3 id="decentralized-energy-systems">2. Decentralized energy systems</h3>
  <p>Future energy systems will be increasingly decentralized. Today's consumers are future producers, <a href="/resources/distributed-energy-resources-der-and-the-rise-of-the-prosumer">so-called prosumers</a>, who own rooftop solar panels, battery storage, and electric vehicle chargers. The goal is to make the interaction between energy supplier, grid, and prosumer seamless.</p>
  <p><strong>Use case: Integrating prosumers into the grid</strong></p>
  <p>Solar energy is an essential part of the energy transition. Integrating prosumers into the grid will make it possible to sell surplus solar energy to any local consumer, helping to decrease regional dependence on imported energy carriers. To do this, all stakeholders require digital systems and technologies that help collect data from sensors, analyze consumption profiles, and predict, simulate, and balance energy grids. Utility providers profit by integrating prosumers into the grid, because they can offer their smart metering hardware to new customers. An example for a community-centric software approach is <a href="https://www.exnaton.com/">Exnaton</a>’s energy community solution, which enables utility companies to track all relevant energy data and easily bill these energy exchanges.</p>
  <h3 id="digitalization">3. Digitalization</h3>
  <p>Digitalization is central to creating future intelligent and resilient energy systems. The energy transition will go hand in hand with digital transformation. In the future, energy service providers and information and communications technology companies will offer a range of services that go well beyond generating, transmitting, and distributing energy. We’ll see new business models, like energy as a service. IRENA identifies these additional services offerings in its <a href="https://www.irena.org/-/media/Files/IRENA/Agency/Publication/2020/Jul/IRENA_Energy-as-a-Service_2020.pdf">2020 innovation landscape brief</a> as energy advice, energy assets, and energy management.</p>
  <p><strong>Use case: Large real estate and infrastructure owners</strong></p>
  <p>Energy management affects more than utility providers, including large real estate and infrastructure like hotels, retail stores, and warehouses; airports; and train stations. Digitalization can help those stakeholders address challenges with energy efficiency and financial resilience. To better assess financial risks in real time, real estate and infrastructure owners must be able to forecast energy demand and simulate results from fluctuating energy prices. Future digital products and services will support these stakeholders’ net-zero goals by tracking energy assets and their overall energy mix. In addition, they can manage their green purchase agreements and calculate greenhouse gas emissions.</p>
  <p>From the tenant’s point of view, automated billing based on real consumption can provide an incentive to reduce energy use.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1be4eb268c135ce2c007666c3faefdf0e3f4343a9.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1be4eb268c135ce2c007666c3faefdf0e3f4343a9.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1be4eb268c135ce2c007666c3faefdf0e3f4343a9.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Row of blue solar panels in a line facing the sun." src="./media_1be4eb268c135ce2c007666c3faefdf0e3f4343a9.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="2160">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p>These are just some approaches to clean energy. There are many that will help us get to net zero. All will require political interventions by international organizations, technological innovation, regional initiatives, action from public and private companies, and a full commitment from each one of us.</p>
  <p>Business leaders must pursue innovative solutions to accelerate the transition to net zero. The need to use business networks and understand how decentralized energy systems and digitalization might be vital for resilient and sustainable intelligent enterprises.</p>
  <p>Regardless of which routes we might take, they will only be viable if we pursue them together – and if we act now. Especially when faced with current energy crises, there is no time to waste in our collective efforts to speed up the transition to renewable energy systems.</p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><strong>Snapshots</strong></p>
  <ul>
    <li>The Green Hydrogen <a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2023/10/f8639744-947e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Panel</a> features Klaus Schimmer, chief innovation architect of sustainability for SAP, in conversation with leaders from Fortescue Future Industries, E.ON, BMW, and BCG on making the transition to green hydrogen.</li>
    <li>Grace Galdos Arenas, global lead for the sustainability lab for SAP <a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2023/09/3e242cd4-917e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">interview</a>s Carsten Borchers, VP of global green gas projects for E.ON, about how business networks can help accelerate the transition to green energy.</li>
    <li>This episode of <em><a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2023/10/5854edd7-917e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Envision Beyond in 60 Seconds</a></em>, “Leading the Way for Clean Energy,” shares new insights on how to best use business networks to solidify sustainability efforts.</li>
  </ul>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div data-valign="middle">style</div>
      <div data-valign="middle">additional reading</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <h4 id="read-more-in-this-series">Read more in this series</h4>
  <div class="collection">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h6 id="editorial">Editorial</h6>
        <p><a href="/blogs/ext-envision-beyond-by-the-intelligent-enterprise-institute">Envision Beyond Curated Collection</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>
        <h6 id="editorial-1">Editorial</h6>
        <p><a href="/blogs/ext-accelerating-the-transition-to-clean-energy">Accelerating the Transition to Clean Energy</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>
        <h6 id="editorial-2">Editorial</h6>
        <p><a href="/blogs/ext-business-networks-the-only-path-forward">Business Networks: The Only Path Forward is Together</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>
        <h6 id="editorial-3">Editorial</h6>
        <p><a href="/blogs/ext-the-metaverse-a-new-space-for-business">The Metaverse: A New Space for Business</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>
        <h6 id="editorial-4">Editorial</h6>
        <p><a href="/blogs/ext-trust-in-an-age-of-mistrust">Trust in an Age of Mistrust</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>
        <h6 id="editorial-5">Editorial</h6>
        <p><a href="/blogs/ext-keys-to-ignite-the-generative-business-revolution">Keys to Ignite the Generative Business Revolution</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>
        <h6 id="editorial-6">Editorial</h6>
        <p><a href="/blogs/ext-generative-ai-for-business-process-excellence">Generative AI for the Renaissance of Business Process Excellence</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>sidebar</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>core-topic/sustainable-business-operations</category>
            <category>content-type/expert-opinions</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[GenAI: Spurring a New Era of Construction Tech]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/gen-ai-spurring-a-new-era-of-construction-tech</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/gen-ai-spurring-a-new-era-of-construction-tech</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[GenAI could solve a range of construction’s longstanding challenges. But most firms have catching up to do, technology-wise]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>content-type/expert-opinions</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Leveraging AI to Drive Performance]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/ext-leveraging-ai-to-drive-performance</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/ext-leveraging-ai-to-drive-performance</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn how modern business solutions bring the power of artificial intelligence to midsize companies – easily and affordably.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>content-type/expert-opinions</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How AI-Powered Cybersecurity Combats Growing AI Threats]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/ext-how-ai-powered-cybersecurity-combats-ai-threats</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/ext-how-ai-powered-cybersecurity-combats-ai-threats</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[October is Cybersecurity Month: SAP and Splunk unite against AI threats. Stay informed, invest in threat detection, and train your team in strong cybersecurity.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10b3da3d839d62035729bdc44b9f17dc79bcf4213.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10b3da3d839d62035729bdc44b9f17dc79bcf4213.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_10b3da3d839d62035729bdc44b9f17dc79bcf4213.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Man working on laptop in server room" src="./media_10b3da3d839d62035729bdc44b9f17dc79bcf4213.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1044">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="how-ai-powered-cybersecurity-combats-growing-ai-threats">How AI-Powered Cybersecurity Combats Growing AI Threats</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="by-gabriele-fiata-head-of-cybersecurity-market-strategy-sap">By Gabriele Fiata, Head of Cybersecurity Market Strategy SAP</h2>
  <p>The threats related to AI are expanding as systems gain autonomy and sophistication at an alarming rate. From January to February 2023 alone, <a href="https://darktrace.com/blog/tackling-the-soft-underbelly-of-cyber-security-email-compromise">Darktrace researchers</a> observed a 135% increase in “novel social engineering attacks,” corresponding to “the widespread adoption of ChatGPT.”</p>
  <p>Malicious actors can now use AI to launch targeted cyberattacks and exploit vulnerabilities at speeds, scales, and levels of precision previously unattainable by human hackers AI can also be used to craft highly convincing phishing e-mails, create malware that adapts to security measures, and even automate the extraction of valuable data from compromised systems. Traditional cybersecurity measures – such as signature-based antivirus software, firewalls, and rule-based intrusion detection systems – struggle to keep pace with these types of AI-driven attacks, highlighting the need for more adaptive and advanced cybersecurity strategies.</p>
  <p>It’s the perfect time to discuss how leaders can fortify their strategies to mitigate these risks.</p>
  <h2 id="the-best-defense-against-ai-is--ai">The best defense against AI is … AI</h2>
  <p>Ironically, AI itself can be a potent tool in defending against AI threats. Machine learning algorithms can analyze vast data sets to identify anomalies and detect potential security breaches in real time. AI-driven threat detection systems can recognize patterns of behavior that human analysts might miss. This proactive approach to cybersecurity can significantly reduce response times and limit the damage caused by AI-driven attacks.</p>
  <p>To tackle evolving AI threats, SAP is working together with Splunk – creator of prominent technology for data analysis and security – to address the unique challenges posed by AI in the realm of cybersecurity. The following are key initiatives behind their collaboration.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10e47f193bfd72a5b0ecf5263b25b88f2a3275942.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10e47f193bfd72a5b0ecf5263b25b88f2a3275942.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_10e47f193bfd72a5b0ecf5263b25b88f2a3275942.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="A lock sitting on top of a circuitboard." src="./media_10e47f193bfd72a5b0ecf5263b25b88f2a3275942.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="keys-to-the-cybersecurity-strategy-refresh">Keys to the cybersecurity strategy refresh</h2>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>AI-specific threat detection:</strong> AI-powered threat detection systems are being designed to detect AI-driven attacks. These systems identify anomalies such as an unexpected surge in data requests outside of business hours or a sudden influx of simultaneous user login attempts. These specific indicators serve as early alerts, signaling potential cyber threats or unauthorized access and helping organizations fortify their security posture.</li>
    <li><strong>Real-time monitoring:</strong> In the age of AI, real-time monitoring is crucial. SAP and Splunk's collaborative efforts focus on providing businesses with tools to continuously monitor their AI systems. This allows for immediate responses to security threats as they arise, reducing the potential for damage.</li>
    <li><strong>Strong security community:</strong> Engaging with industry experts and cybersecurity professionals facilitates better information exchange, best practices, and threat intelligence sharing. Technical workshops and thought leadership conferences can also foster collective defense strategies. Events like these help security professionals and businesses stay resilient in the face of evolving AI-related security risks, encouraging a proactive and collaborative response within the community.</li>
  </ul>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="curious-about-cybersecurity">Curious about cybersecurity?</h3>
        <p>Join Elena Kvochko for the latest in cybersecurity trends and building trust.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="https://podcast.opensap.info/the-trust-corner/">Listen now</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="what-leaders-can-do-to-tackle-ai-threats">What leaders can do to tackle AI threats</h2>
  <p><strong>Stay informed:</strong> Keep up to date with the latest developments in AI security threats and solutions. Attend industry webinars, such as the <a href="https://webinars.sap.com/sap-user-groups-k4u/en/security">SAP User Groups on Security</a>, and conferences such as SAPinsider and.conf24, to gain insights from experts.</p>
  <p><strong>Regular security audits:</strong> Conduct regular security audits of your AI infrastructure to identify vulnerabilities and weaknesses. Collaborate with AI security experts to ensure comprehensive protection.</p>
  <p><strong>Invest in AI-specific security:</strong> Recognize that AI demands specialized security measures. Explore products, such as those provided by SAP and Splunk, that are capable of early detection. These products can identify abnormal user and system behaviors and safeguard your business data against AI-driven attacks.</p>
  <p><strong>Train your team:</strong> Invest in AI security training for your cybersecurity professionals, and equip them with the knowledge and skills needed to defend against AI-specific threats. Key focus areas include:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Ensuring security is an integral part of the AI development process, from inception to deployment</li>
    <li>Simulating potential AI attacks to identify vulnerabilities and reinforce defensive measures</li>
    <li>Conducting drills to enhance the team's ability to respond effectively to AI-specific incidents, establishing strong processes for detection, response, and recovery strategies</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="stronger-ai-security-hinges-on-collaboration">Stronger AI security hinges on collaboration</h2>
  <p>The collaboration between industry leaders like SAP and Splunk is indicative of the growing recognition of the need for collective action in the face of AI threats. By pooling resources, knowledge, and expertise, organizations can develop more effective AI-specific security products. This collaborative approach is essential for staying ahead of cyber adversaries who continually update their tactics.</p>
  <p>As AI continues to shape our world, companies must have strong cybersecurity strategies to ensure that AI is used safely.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="tackle-ai-threats">Tackle AI Threats</h3>
        <p>Proactively identify attacks and reduce the risk of downtime.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="https://store.sap.com/dcp/en/product/display-2001015322_live_v1/splunk%C2%AE-security-for-sap%C2%AE-solutions">Reduce cyber risks</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>core-topic/responsible-ai</category>
            <category>content-type/expert-opinions</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Do Projects Go Wrong? Let Us Count the Ways]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/how-do-projects-go-wrong</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/how-do-projects-go-wrong</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Author Dan Gardner explains why projects fail, how often projects go wrong, and how to set teams up for success.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/expert-opinions</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Perspectives on Supply Chain Planning | SAP Insights]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/ext-perspective-on-supply-chain-planning</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/ext-perspective-on-supply-chain-planning</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Explore this collection of key insights on how supply chain planning can improve operational efficiency and navigate the complexities of today’s supply chain landscape.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/expert-opinions</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Trust in an Age of Mistrust]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/ext-trust-in-an-age-of-mistrust</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/ext-trust-in-an-age-of-mistrust</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn how businesses can build trust with customers, stakeholders, and the general public for stronger innovation.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/business-transformation</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/expert-opinions</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Business Networks: The Only Path Forward Is Together]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/ext-business-networks-the-only-path-forward</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/ext-business-networks-the-only-path-forward</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Business networks aren’t a new concept, but they are evolving thanks to technological advances. Learn how your business can benefit.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/business-transformation</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>content-type/expert-opinions</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Going to the Office Every Day Is Over]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/going-to-the-office-every-day-is-over</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/going-to-the-office-every-day-is-over</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The days of going to the office every day are over. Learn how to create a hybrid work model that works for your employees and your business.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/expert-opinions</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Port of Entry: Lessons from a Smooth Operator]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/ext-port-of-entry-smooth-operator</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/ext-port-of-entry-smooth-operator</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn how YILPORT Holding is working to become one of the top 10 global port operators by 2030.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_185b9cc883afac73444e30d313c83637dafd4aa2b.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_185b9cc883afac73444e30d313c83637dafd4aa2b.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_185b9cc883afac73444e30d313c83637dafd4aa2b.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Huge container port area containing millions of goods." src="./media_185b9cc883afac73444e30d313c83637dafd4aa2b.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1044">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="port-of-entry-how-a-smooth-operator-moves-millions-of-goods-every-day">Port of Entry: How a Smooth Operator Moves Millions of Goods Every Day</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Images of huge container ships gliding in and out of ports have come to symbolize the modern supply chain. Managing these ports – the gateways of international trade – is a highly complex business. The most important part of the ocean shipping industry, seaports expedite the movement of millions of goods each day. They provide facilities for docking, loading, unloading, and storing cargo, and many are undergoing a massive transformation as the industry recovers from pandemic-related disruptions.</p>
  <h2 id="all-inclusive-logistics-hubs">All-inclusive logistics hubs</h2>
  <p>One company that excels at this intricate task is <a href="https://www.yilport.com/en/">YILPORT Holding</a>, which owns and operates 24 marine ports and terminals and 7 dry terminals around the globe. These terminals offer multipurpose services, supported by inland container terminals, depots, warehouses, and logistics centers.</p>
  <p>The company was established in 1980s by Robert Yüksel Yildirim, Chairman and CEO of YILPORT Holding. Originally known as Mr. Chrome, Yildirim was the market maker of the chrome industry before becoming the Lord of the Ports. As a game-changing mechanical engineer, his vision for YILPORT Holding’s growth strategy in port operations has been followed closely by the industry.</p>
  <p>“Our mission is to rank among the top 10 international operators by 2030 and be the game-changer in port and terminal operations. In a world where everything is so interdependent, our sector is a key player in world trade,” said Murat Akbudak, CFO for YILPORT Holding, at the recent SAP Seaports Innovation Summit held in Istanbul, Turkey. The company’s C-level team was on hand to highlight the advantages and benefits of doing business with YILPORT.</p>
  <p>Erhan Çiloglu, CMO of YILPORT Holding, outlined the company’s <a href="https://yilport.com/en/services/detail/SERVICES/44/32/0">one-stop shop service model</a>. Available at all locations, it includes resources and facilities to handle container, bulk, and liquid cargo and provides damage-free stevedoring for automotive roll-on/roll-off services, logistics services such as freight forwarding, pilotage and tug services at all terminals, and much more.</p>
  <p>“Our customers can take advantage of combined services to minimize costs and maximize the velocity of cargo flow,” said Çiloglu. “We are an end-to-end service provider, with simple supply chain solutions to facilitate operations for our customers. We are very excited about new terminal opportunities in our pipeline that will be implementing our business philosophy to streamline operations.”</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c5854691c4fc251848300526818221cb0de0a8a5.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c5854691c4fc251848300526818221cb0de0a8a5.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1c5854691c4fc251848300526818221cb0de0a8a5.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Aerial, front view of a massive cargo ship on the water." src="./media_1c5854691c4fc251848300526818221cb0de0a8a5.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1958" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="high-end-integrated-technologies">High-end, integrated technologies</h2>
  <p>YILPORT is the fastest-growing international terminal operator in the world, and its equipment can handle the world’s largest container vessels. It manages 17 million TEUs (Twenty-Foot Equivalent Units or 20-foot containers) in 12 different countries. In 2022, it broke its <a href="https://www.yildirimgroup.com/yilport-holding-breaks-all-time-container-handling-record-in-first-half-of-2022">all-time container handling record</a> by growing 9%, a feat which is projected to be repeated this year.</p>
  <p>Operations of this magnitude function smoothly with the help of technology. The company’s linear processes have been built and improved with automation, easy communication tools based on EDI to exchange documents electronically, common platforms, and Web-based solutions and systems.</p>
  <p>“Our operations are managed centrally and embrace automation and the data-centric nature of the new industrial revolution,” said Dericioglu, Business Systems Director of YILDIRIM Group. “Industry 4.0 principles are applied to all systems, remote monitoring through IoT, and our cloud infrastructure. Our assets are already digitalized for the smart ports in the future.”</p>
  <p>To accelerate its journey to the intelligent enterprise and streamline its order-to-cash processes, YILPORT ran a pilot project at Gemport, one of its locations in Turkey, with the help of Acuiti Labs.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_19c0a342a167c07bf45a4f2bb92de23d62d2e8233.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_19c0a342a167c07bf45a4f2bb92de23d62d2e8233.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_19c0a342a167c07bf45a4f2bb92de23d62d2e8233.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Two workers looking at a tablet in front of shipping containers" src="./media_19c0a342a167c07bf45a4f2bb92de23d62d2e8233.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="long-lasting-results">Long-lasting results</h2>
  <p>The pilot implementation had three goals. The first was to automate invoice generation and empower customers through a new, self-service portal. The second was to ensure data consistency across systems for accurate invoicing, reducing disputes and revenue leakage, and the final goal was to provide a holistic 360-degree view of the customer’s financial data.</p>
  <p>At the close of the project, YILPORT boasted a fully operational end-to-end container line of business and a solution scalable enough to be rolled out to other ports in the region.</p>
  <p>YILPORT is well on its way to achieve its vision to become one of the top 10 global port operators by 2030. But technology is just one part of the story. The company is investing in low-carbon and energy-efficient practices to meet regulatory compliance and standards and to reduce waste in the operational environment. It is developing new business models together with customers and partners to provide an even wider range of port service offerings, and it maintains a strong focus on safety and training to reduce work-related injuries.</p>
  <p>Last but not least, YILPORT Holding takes a holistic approach to integrate sustainability within all aspects of its business. This approach is seen as essential to developing a robust business for the people, customers, environment and communities within the operating companies.</p>
  <p>All these actions combined are what give this company its transformative power and pioneering character.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="ready-for-more">Ready for more?</h3>
        <p>Read on for best practices for building resilient, sustainable supply chains.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/resources.html">Learn more</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/business-transformation</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>content-type/expert-opinions</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Startups Can Maximize Their Partnership with Corporates]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/ext-how-startups-maximize-partnerships-with-corporates</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/ext-how-startups-maximize-partnerships-with-corporates</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Find out what corporates should look for in a partner and how startups can increase the chances of a successful collaboration.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/business-transformation</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>content-type/expert-opinions</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[300 Days of Sun: Communities Power Their Own Future]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/300-days-of-sun</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/300-days-of-sun</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Lebanon faces daunting economic and energy problems. A new documentary explores how citizens are looking to the sun for solutions.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>core-topic/sustainable-business-operations</category>
            <category>industry/oil-gas-energy</category>
            <category>industry/utilities</category>
            <category>content-type/expert-opinions</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>