<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/product/sap-integration-suite/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How SAP BTP Becomes the Trusted Platform for Business AI]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/sap-btp-strategy-paper-trusted-platform-business-ai</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/sap-btp-strategy-paper-trusted-platform-business-ai</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP BTP will further evolve to become the trusted business AI platform for SAP-centric landscapes. Learn more in the SAP BTP strategy paper.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-build</category>
            <category>product/sap-integration-suite</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP BTP Wins Multiple TrustRadius 2024 Top Rated Awards]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/sap-btp-wins-trustradius-2024-top-rated-awards</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/sap-btp-wins-trustradius-2024-top-rated-awards</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP BTP has received TrustRadius 2024 Top Rated awards, including SAP Build, SAP Integration Suite, and SAP Master Data Governance.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14e8d52807c7569f208a7c3238193ad8862cdb0a4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14e8d52807c7569f208a7c3238193ad8862cdb0a4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_14e8d52807c7569f208a7c3238193ad8862cdb0a4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP BTP Wins Multiple TrustRadius 2024 Top Rated Awards" src="./media_14e8d52807c7569f208a7c3238193ad8862cdb0a4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-btp-wins-multiple-trustradius-2024-top-rated-awards">SAP BTP Wins Multiple TrustRadius 2024 Top Rated Awards</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>SAP’s commitment to customers is steadfast in making SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP) the best platform to extend and personalize SAP applications, integrate and connect landscapes, maximize the value of data, and drive business innovation through artificial intelligence (AI).</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="discover-which-version-of-sap-btp-meets-your-needs">Discover which version of SAP BTP meets your needs</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/pricing.html">Try it today</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>To that end, I am thrilled to announce that <a href="https://www.trustradius.com/">TrustRadius</a>, a leading independent peer research and review platform, has once again recognized SAP BTP, along with multiple solutions that run on our platform, as winners of the 2024 Top Rated awards.</p>
  <p>As a reflection of direct customer feedback, the TrustRadius Top Rated awards offer an authentic measure of a product’s quality and customer satisfaction and highlight those products that have demonstrated excellence in fulfilling clients’ needs and expectations.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <picture>
          <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1bff4785e82312c107ed744772e802bfd657c73b9.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
          <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1bff4785e82312c107ed744772e802bfd657c73b9.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
          <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1bff4785e82312c107ed744772e802bfd657c73b9.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
          <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_1bff4785e82312c107ed744772e802bfd657c73b9.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="530" height="610">
        </picture>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="best-of-awards">Best of Awards</h2>
  <p>SAP customers’ willingness to share their hands-on experience and opinions of SAP BTP is testament to our platform’s services, robustness, and ongoing innovation.</p>
  <p>We are honored that the following solutions have been recognized with Top Rated awards:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform.html">SAP Business Technology Platform</a> on <a href="https://www.trustradius.com/products/sap-business-technology-platform/reviews">TrustRadius</a>: Platform-as-a-Service (PaaS) and Application Infrastructure</li>
    <li><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/application-development.html">SAP Build</a> on <a href="https://www.trustradius.com/products/sap-build/reviews">TrustRadius</a>: Low-Code Development and Robotic Process Automation (RPA)</li>
    <li><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/integration-suite.html">SAP Integration Suite</a> on <a href="https://www.trustradius.com/products/sap-integration-suite/reviews">TrustRadius</a>: Integration Platform-as-a-Service (iPaaS), and API Management</li>
    <li><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/master-data-governance.html">SAP Master Data Governance</a> on <a href="https://www.trustradius.com/products/sap-master-data-governance/reviews">TrustRadius</a>: Master Data Management (MDM) and Data Governance</li>
  </ul>
  <p>“SAP Business Technology Platform’s comprehensive suite of solutions has been recognized with a TrustRadius Top Rated award,” said Allyson Havener, senior vice president of Marketing and Community at TrustRadius. “SAP is committed to delivering innovative technologies that empower businesses to drive digital transformation, and achieve their goals. We congratulate SAP on this achievement, showcasing their continued leadership and excellence in providing cutting-edge enterprise solutions.”</p>
  <h2 id="our-focus-on-customer-success">Our Focus on Customer Success</h2>
  <p>At SAP, customer success and satisfaction are the ultimate measures of our own success. We strive to deliver industry-leading solutions, functionality, and user experience that exceeds customer expectations and unlocks business potential. This is especially important as customers accelerate their digital innovation across business operations while maintaining the agility to adapt to fluctuating market demands. SAP BTP provides this for our customers.</p>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div>SAP Business Technology Platform is the right tool to manage sites, applications, users, and everything you can imagine in the cloud and non-cloud world, from my point of view BTP is very well focused and has everything that a tool has to have.</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div><em><a href="https://www.trustradius.com/reviews/sap-business-technology-platform-2023-11-08-14-00-23">Read the full review by Warner Bros. Discovery on TrustRadius</a></em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>To read what other customers said about SAP BTP, please take a look at <a href="https://www.trustradius.com/products/sap-business-technology-platform/reviews">our TrustRadius review page</a>. We welcome you to <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/pricing.html">try out SAP BTP for yourself too</a>.</p>
  <p>On behalf of the entire SAP BTP team, we sincerely thank TrustRadius for acknowledging SAP BTP in its 2024 Top Rated awards and our dedicated SAP BTP customers for their unwavering support.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>JG Chirapurath is chief marketing and solutions officer for SAP Business Technology Platform.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-build</category>
            <category>product/sap-integration-suite</category>
            <category>product/sap-master-data-governance</category>
            <category>news-tag/trustradius</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Named Leader in the 2024 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for iPaaS for Fourth Consecutive Time]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/sap-named-leader-2024-gartner-magic-quadrant-ipaas</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/sap-named-leader-2024-gartner-magic-quadrant-ipaas</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP was named a Leader in the 2024 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Integration Platform as a Service (iPaaS) for the fourth consecutive time.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11e0cc32a99eaafa84b0f392021aac0d9ea3ac792.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11e0cc32a99eaafa84b0f392021aac0d9ea3ac792.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_11e0cc32a99eaafa84b0f392021aac0d9ea3ac792.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Named Leader in the 2024 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for iPaaS for Fourth Consecutive Time" src="./media_11e0cc32a99eaafa84b0f392021aac0d9ea3ac792.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-named-leader-in-the-2024-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-ipaas-for-fourth-consecutive-time">SAP Named Leader in the 2024 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for iPaaS for Fourth Consecutive Time</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>We are proud to announce SAP has been recognized as a Leader in the 2024 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Integration Platform as a Service (iPaaS) with SAP Integration Suite for the fourth consecutive time.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>We believe this prestigious recognition is a testament to our current capabilities, ongoing innovation, and commitment to providing world-class integration solutions for customers.</p>
  <h2 id="unparalleled-recognition-in-ipaas">Unparalleled Recognition in iPaaS</h2>
  <p>The Gartner Magic Quadrant provides an overview of the technology vendors in the iPaaS market and positions them according to their Ability to Execute and Completeness of Vision. According to Gartner, “Leaders have a deep understanding of the iPaaS market. They have a record of strong execution and an ability to influence the market’s direction. Leaders have a clear product road map to solidify the product’s position and to help buyers protect their investments. In <a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/dg/integration-platform-as-a-service-leader/index.html">the latest report</a>, SAP is positioned as a Leader again.”</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="unleash-the-power-of-connectivity-and-innovation-with-sap-integration-suite">Unleash the power of connectivity and innovation with SAP Integration Suite</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/integration-suite.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The ability for an organization to connect and automate its business applications faster and in new ways is critical in today’s digital world. SAP customers are seeking a robust integration solution to support their innovation and modernization initiatives. We believe this recognition serves as validation of our commitment to delivering industry-leading solutions that can empower businesses to seamlessly connect their applications, data, and processes.</p>
  <h2 id="a-winning-combination-of-technology-and-expertise">A Winning Combination of Technology and Expertise</h2>
  <p>SAP’s vision for SAP Integration Suite is to connect and automate business processes. As the key integration technology of <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform.html">SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP)</a>, SAP Integration Suite can empower customers to achieve seamless, scalable business processes without disruption. Its user-friendly interface, extensive library of proven prebuilt content for SAP and non-SAP applications, and robust security features help make it easy for customers to jump-start their integrations.</p>
  <p>Organizations across the globe have embraced SAP Integration Suite to help support automation of business processes, streamline operations, and strengthen their collaboration with partners and customers. Take <a href="https://www.sap.com/asset/dynamic/2024/01/6a507734-a27e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Pitney Bowes</a> for example. It wanted a solution to support its transformation from selling stand-alone products to offering holistic solutions that orchestrate physical delivery, installation, and support while minimizing the need for customization and providing growth for the company.</p>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div>Using SAP Integration Suite, part of SAP BTP, to integrate SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition with SAP Sales Cloud and third-party providers, we’re simplifying and standardizing business processes, increasing agility, and supporting our growth ambitions in select countries.</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>Stuart Beadle, Senior Director, Global Order Management, Supply Chain Applications and SAP Service, Pitney Bowes Inc.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Customer experience is one of the criteria evaluated by Gartner in the report for the ability to execute. According to the report, “Relationships, products, and services/programs that enable clients to be successful with the products are evaluated. Specifically, this includes the ways customers receive technical support or account support. This can also include ancillary tools, customer support programs (and the quality thereof), availability of user groups, service-level agreements, and so on.”</p>
  <p>See <a href="https://www.gartner.com/reviews/market/integration-platform-as-a-service-worldwide/vendor/sap/product/sap-integration-suite">Gartner Peer Insights</a> to read the reviews.</p>
  <h2 id="learn-more">Learn More</h2>
  <p><a href="/topics/sap-integration-suite">SAP Integration Suite</a> can accelerate innovation, speed connectivity, and connect everyone to automated processes. We remain steadfast in providing powerful and reliable integration solutions. To learn more:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/dg/integration-platform-as-a-service-leader/index.html">Read the full report</a></li>
    <li>Explore exclusive iPaaS content on <a href="https://gateway.on24.com/wcc/eh/3869277/integration-space">SAP’s integration space</a></li>
    <li><a href="https://discovery-center.cloud.sap/serviceCatalog/integration-suite?region=all&#x26;category=all">Get started for free</a> with SAP Integration Suite</li>
    <li>Learn more about <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/integration-suite.html">SAP Integration Suite</a></li>
  </ul>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>JG Chirapurath is chief marketing and solutions officer for SAP BTP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-sap-news-delivered-to-your-inbox-once-a-week">Get the latest SAP news delivered to your inbox once a week</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/nl/sap-news-center-newsletter/index.html">Sign up today</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Gartner, Magic Quadrant for Integration Platform as a Service 19 February 2024, Keith Guttridge Et Al.<br>Gartner does not endorse any vendor, product or service depicted in its research publications and does not advise technology users to select only those vendors with the highest ratings or other designation. Gartner research publications consist of the opinions of Gartner’s research organization and should not be construed as statements of fact. Gartner disclaims all warranties, expressed or implied, with respect to this research, including any warranties of merchantability or fitness for a particular purpose.<br>GARTNER is a registered trademark and service mark of Gartner and Magic Quadrant is a registered trademark of Gartner, Inc. and/or its affiliates in the U.S. and internationally and are used herein with permission. All rights reserved.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-integration-suite</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Kemira Leaps Forward with SAP and cbs Corporate Business Solutions]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/kemira-leaps-forward-with-sap-and-cbs</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/kemira-leaps-forward-with-sap-and-cbs</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Industrial enterprise Kemira launched its digital business process platform based on SAP with help from cbs Corporate Business Solutions.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/chemicals</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-datasphere</category>
            <category>product/sap-integration-suite</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Innovating with SAP Business Technology Platform]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/innovating-with-sap-btp</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/innovating-with-sap-btp</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[At SAP Sapphire, we introduced new SAP BTP capabilities in application development, automation, integration, data and analytics, and AI.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-build</category>
            <category>product/sap-datasphere</category>
            <category>product/sap-integration-suite</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-signavio</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Integration Is Key to Business Success]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/integration-key-business-success</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/integration-key-business-success</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Choosing the right enterprise-grade integration solution is critical to creating a path to accelerated connectivity and innovation.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/integration</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-integration-suite</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Named a Leader in 2023 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Integration Platform as a Service, Worldwide]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/01/2023-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-ipaas-sap-a-leader</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/01/2023-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-ipaas-sap-a-leader</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Gartner has recognized SAP as a Leader in the 2023 Magic Quadrant for iPaaS, Worldwide for the third time in a row. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/enterprise-integration</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/integration</category>
            <category>news-tag/magic-quadrant</category>
            <category>product/sap-integration-suite</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Receives TrustRadius Awards in Multiple Data Management and Integration Categories]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/06/sap-receives-trustradius-awards-data-management-and-integration</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/06/sap-receives-trustradius-awards-data-management-and-integration</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[TrustRadius has recognized SAP solutions for data management and integration with Top-Rated awards. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/database-and-data-management</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-data-intelligence</category>
            <category>product/sap-integration-suite</category>
            <category>product/sap-master-data-governance</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Partner delaware: SAP BTP Is for Today and the Future]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/06/sap-partner-delaware-sap-btp-for-today-and-future</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/06/sap-partner-delaware-sap-btp-for-today-and-future</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP partner delaware reveals how SAP BTP helps its customers become intelligent enterprises and helps it to win the war on talent. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-integration-suite</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How This Belgian Utility Delivers Clean Water across the Country]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/04/how-farys-delivers-clean-water-across-belgium</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/04/how-farys-delivers-clean-water-across-belgium</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Farys succeeds by adopting cutting-edge technology to drive socially responsible operations. Read to learn how its use of SAP BTP helps.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-integration-suite</category>
            <category>industry/utilities</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Lloyd’s Register Sets Sails to New Markets, Guided by Its Technology Platform Strategy]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/03/lloyds-register-sets-sails-technology-platform-strategy</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/03/lloyds-register-sets-sails-technology-platform-strategy</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Read why Lloyd's Register chose SAP Business Technology Platform to help develop AllAssets, its asset performance management solution.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>industry/oil-gas-energy</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-integration-suite</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How One Tech Company Enhances Port Operations]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/01/how-tech-mahindra-enhances-port-operations</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/01/how-tech-mahindra-enhances-port-operations</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Tech Mahindra used SAP BTP to develop its Port Logistics solution, a unified platform for secure, faster clearance processes in ports.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_182d398af4a2bb68db62043dac2a2a6276377336a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_182d398af4a2bb68db62043dac2a2a6276377336a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_182d398af4a2bb68db62043dac2a2a6276377336a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="How One Tech Company Enhances Port Operations" src="./media_182d398af4a2bb68db62043dac2a2a6276377336a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="how-one-tech-company-enhances-port-operations">How One Tech Company Enhances Port Operations</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><a href="/covid-19">COVID-19</a>: a topic that we have all become intimately familiar with over the last two years. And although scientists have made great strides in developing effective vaccines since the beginning of the pandemic, they certainly cannot account for the ways in which COVID-19 has impacted nearly every sector of the economy.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In particular, COVID-19 continues to have far-reaching consequences on global supply chains. This perhaps would come as no surprise in early 2020, when many were scrambling in grocery stores for toilet paper, cleaning products, and other necessities in preparation for quarantine lockdowns.</p>
  <p>However, more than a year has passed since this frantic phase and global supply chains are still trying to recover from the whiplash. In turn, major ports across the U.S. – from Los Angeles and Long Beach in California to Savannah, Georgia – are facing unprecedented backlogs. Whether it be buying gifts or purchasing a new car, the shipping crisis is sure to impact many of us.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-tech-mahindras-sap-innovation-awards-pitch-deck">Read Tech Mahindra's SAP Innovation Awards pitch deck</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/idea-place/sap-innovation-awards/submission-details-2021.html?idea_id=2387">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="port-logistics-operations">Port Logistics Operations</h2>
  <p>Focusing on the <strong>ports and maritime industry</strong>, the most significantly affected sectors have been chemical tankers, cruise ships, and passenger ships. The ship traffic from Europe to China and the U.S. has declined compared to the same periods in 2019.</p>
  <p>To cope with the disruption, changes are expected to happen in operational, financial, and economic areas – as well as sanitary protocols and processes and adjustments to working practices and organizational aspects.</p>
  <p>So where do businesses like Tech Mahindra come in?</p>
  <p>Based in Pune, India, <strong>Tech Mahindra</strong> is a multinational technology company with over 125,000 employees. Working with SAP Co-Innovation Lab, Tech Mahindra developed a cloud-based solution for handling port logistics operations. Its Port Logistics solution, built on <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/integration-suite.html">SAP Integration Suite</a>, provides a unified and collaborative platform for secure and faster clearance processes in ports.</p>
  <h2 id="sailing-past-the-paperwork">Sailing Past the Paperwork</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-btp-the-platform-for-the-intelligent-enterprise">SAP BTP: The platform for the Intelligent Enterprise</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Leveraging the Port Logistics solution reduces the amount of paperwork and in less time. This translates into more funds, and who doesn’t want to save a little extra money? The solution enhances port operations using automation that:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Provides a single window for the port authorities receiving the products to have secure communication and exchange information with the ship personnel for handling the cargo and logistics clearance</li>
    <li>Tracks transactions and approvals</li>
    <li>Analyzes deviation reports for transparency</li>
  </ul>
  <p>The solution offers real-time analysis for quick decisions, smooth information flow, and automated document verification. The new process saves time in checking in and cross-verifying for each clearance process requirement. This means no more manual paperwork, customers receive their goods faster, and revenue is realized sooner.</p>
  <p>In real-world application, the process <strong>reduces the cost</strong> of data transfer and documentation management by 90% and <strong>increases revenue</strong> by 20%.</p>
  <h2 id="looking-to-the-future">Looking to the Future</h2>
  <p>Automation is more than convenience – it’s necessary. It saves time and money in unexpected ways, such as facilitating supply chains for food. As we learn to stay afloat amidst a global pandemic, improving operational efficiency for ports remains a priority. Tech Mahindra has been planning for the next generation of smart ports to prepare for the expected upsurge in shipping volume.</p>
  <p>To learn more about Tech Mahindra and its Port Logistics solution, check out its SAP Innovation Awards 2021 <a href="https://www.sap.com/idea-place/sap-innovation-awards/submission-details-2021.html?idea_id=2387">pitch deck</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Rajshree Chauhan and Casey Tobias are SAP Global Marketing contributors.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/covid-19</category>
            <category>sap-award/sap-innovation-awards</category>
            <category>product/sap-integration-suite</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Turning the Cloud Into a High-Powered Innovation Engine]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/turning-the-cloud-into-a-high-powered-innovation-engine</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/turning-the-cloud-into-a-high-powered-innovation-engine</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With a unified, business-centric technology platform, companies of all industries can turn the cloud into a high-powered innovation engine.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_168974d465266f6b6227e97c9b9606df18440f4ef.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_168974d465266f6b6227e97c9b9606df18440f4ef.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_168974d465266f6b6227e97c9b9606df18440f4ef.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Turning the Cloud Into a High-Powered Innovation Engine" src="./media_168974d465266f6b6227e97c9b9606df18440f4ef.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="turning-the-cloud-into-a-high-powered-innovation-engine">Turning the Cloud Into a High-Powered Innovation Engine</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>For most companies, cloud adoption represents an early milestone in their path to becoming an intelligent enterprise. Now, looking back on the last two years, we can see that it also laid the foundation for accelerated digital transformation, where years of process changes had to be squeezed into a matter of months. But instead of pure innovation, the driver behind all this change was surviving pandemic-induced disruption in market conditions, supply chains, employee work arrangements, and more.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>According to <a href="https://www.gartner.com/en/newsroom/press-releases/2021-08-02-gartner-says-four-trends-are-shaping-the-future-of-public-cloud">Gartner</a>, public cloud spending is expected to continue to grow – consuming nearly half of all enterprise IT budgets by 2026, up from less than 17% this year. However, cloud investments will now focus more on strengthening operations, building differentiation, and improving sustainability with intelligent technologies such as machine learning, artificial intelligence (AI), and process automation.</p>
  <p>Increased investments in the cloud will undoubtedly encompass a desire to innovate across the enterprise without being locked into a single cloud provider or set of cloud offerings. To keep options open, organizations may want to adopt a technology platform that provides open cloud services and enables them and their partners to innovate with greater control over their data, solutions, workflows, and user experiences.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-btp-accelerate-business-outcomes-with-integration-data-to-value-and-extensibility">SAP BTP: Accelerate business outcomes with integration, data to value, and extensibility</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="opening-up-new-possibilities-with-cloud-services">Opening Up New Possibilities with Cloud Services</h2>
  <p>Savvy decision-makers who seek to differentiate and grow their organizations must find ways to accelerate the creation and modification of business models, experiences, processes, and applications. To make that happen, they need access to the latest database and data management, analytics, integration, and extension capabilities.</p>
  <p>A unified technology platform – such as <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">SAP Business Technology Platform</a> (SAP BTP) – works to answer that need by delivering accelerated business outcomes with integration, data and analytics, and extensibility within the context of business domains to empower business centricity. It can enable organizations to solve unique business process challenges and create more meaningful outcomes.</p>
  <p><a href="/topics/business-technology-platform">SAP BTP</a> also offers prebuilt integrations and analytics with workflows for line-of-business and industry processes to help accelerate the realization of these benefits by reducing development and innovation cycles.</p>
  <h2 id="transforming-digitally-through-connected-systems-and-prebuilt-content">Transforming Digitally Through Connected Systems and Prebuilt Content</h2>
  <p>For many organizations, adopting an open business technology platform is the key to accelerating their digital transformation journey. This journey is only possible by connecting data-driven enterprise processes, extending core business solutions, and allowing a consistent experience across different processes and workflow customizations.</p>
  <p>Take, for example, the lead-to-cash process. With a unified technology platform, businesses and their partners can design an application that creates sales contracts capable of referencing agreed pricing terms and recommending relevant promotions, incentives, and rebates. This connected, process-aware application enables sales teams to benefit from workflows that are joined across marketing, finance, supply chain, and operations.</p>
  <p>Other key components of speeding the digital transformation journey are prebuilt integrations and packaged content. For example, prepackaged contracting capabilities, configurable proposal creation rules and templates, guided self-service sales contract wizards, and adaptable approval workflows can enable lead-to-cash business stakeholders to accelerate design, development, and implementation cycles.</p>
  <h2 id="integrating-extending-and-keeping-the-core-clean">Integrating, Extending, and Keeping the Core Clean</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="build-extend-integrate-and-market-solutions-with-sap">Build, extend, integrate, and market solutions with SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/partner/become/partneredge-build.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The first step in this cloud-based innovation process is leveraging integration services to bridge disconnected systems, making the lead-to-cash process flexible and agile. For example, SAP customers and partners use <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/integration-suite.html">SAP Integration Suite</a>, which offers a choice of more than 1,800 prebuilt integrations, 2,100 APIs, and 160 third-party connectors to smoothly integrate on-premise and cloud-based applications and processes.</p>
  <p>By complementing these integration services with application extensions available through <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/extension-suite.html">SAP Extension Suite</a>, customers and partners can simplify application development and extend line-of-business solution capabilities. Additionally, they can quickly adapt and innovate across a heterogeneous mix of private cloud, public cloud, hyperscaler, and on-premise landscapes.</p>
  <p>These extension services enable partners to transition away from classic extensions that directly customize primary business solutions, enabling them to keep the digital core clean through side-by-side innovations that decouple their intellectual property. As a result, customers can achieve a better long-term outcome with applications that benefit from consistent upgrades to core solutions. Plus, by combining integration and extension services with prebuilt business content and native APIs, organizations can build and connect applications and data with less technical complexity – accelerating the time to results.</p>
  <h2 id="transforming-with-a-balance-of-control-and-flexibility">Transforming with a Balance of Control and Flexibility</h2>
  <p>When laying the groundwork for more stable operations and more predictive growth, nothing beats having real-time, accurate data from connected systems to make decisions confidently. And with a truly unified, business-centric technology platform, companies of all sizes and industries can turn their cloud into a high-powered innovation engine, producing better outcomes and experiences for their employees and customers.</p>
  <p>As a next step, explore <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">SAP Business Technology Platform</a> or, if you’re interested in software partnership opportunities with SAP, learn more at <a href="https://www.sap.com/partner/become/partneredge-build.html">SAP PartnerEdge – Build</a>. If you’re already a partner, check out these exciting initiatives: <a href="https://events.sap.com/hack2build/en/home">Hack2Build</a> and <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/innovation/coil.html">SAP Co-Innovation Lab</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Tom Le is global vice president of Partner Solution Advisory at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-integration-suite</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-partneredge</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-partneredge-build</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Everyone Can Be a Developer: SAP Introduces Tools for Citizen and Professional Developers, Embedded AI, and a Free Learning Experience]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/sap-teched-news-citizen-professional-developer-tools-embedded-ai-free-learning-experience</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/sap-teched-news-citizen-professional-developer-tools-embedded-ai-free-learning-experience</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Get the SAP TechEd news for 2021, which includes tools for citizen and professional developers, embedded AI, and a free learning experience.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-teched</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-appgyver</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fiori</category>
            <category>product/sap-hana-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-integration-suite</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Integration Is the Secret Sauce of Digital Transformation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/integration-digital-transformation-endress-hauser-sap-btp</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/integration-digital-transformation-endress-hauser-sap-btp</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 11 Oct 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Endress+Hauser demonstrates why enterprise integration is so important to digital transformation. Read its SAP BTP story here.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/magic-quadrant</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-integration-suite</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Named a Leader in 2021 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Data Quality Solutions for the 15th Time in a Row]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/sap-a-leader-magic-quadrant-for-data-quality-solutions</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/sap-a-leader-magic-quadrant-for-data-quality-solutions</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[For the 15th consecutive year, Gartner has named SAP a Leader in the Magic Quadrant for Data Quality Solutions report.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1381148cc7bc7bd04a2ac63a702d499a37236c656.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1381148cc7bc7bd04a2ac63a702d499a37236c656.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1381148cc7bc7bd04a2ac63a702d499a37236c656.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Named a Leader in 2021 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Data Quality Solutions for the 15th Time in a Row" src="./media_1381148cc7bc7bd04a2ac63a702d499a37236c656.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-named-a-leader-in-2021-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-data-quality-solutions-for-the-15th-time-in-a-row">SAP Named a Leader in 2021 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Data Quality Solutions for the 15th Time in a Row</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-business-technology-platform-accelerate-business-outcomes-with-integration-data-to-value-and-extensibility">SAP Business Technology Platform: Accelerate business outcomes with integration, data to value, and extensibility</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced that independent analyst firm <a href="http://www.gartner.com/technology/home.jsp">Gartner Inc.</a> has named SAP a Leader in its <a href="https://www.gartner.com/reprints/?id=1-27EPJ5JP&#x26;ct=210910&#x26;st=sb">Magic Quadrant for Data Quality Solutions report</a>.*</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Gartner evaluated 15 vendors and named SAP a Leader based on its “ability to execute” and “completeness of vision.” This is the 15th consecutive year that SAP has been named a Leader in the Magic Quadrant for Data Quality Solutions.</p>
  <p>According to Gartner, “Augmented data quality, driven by metadata and AI, is a key dynamic driving the data quality solutions market. Leading vendors’ augmented capabilities provide greater insights and automation. This research helps data and analytics leaders understand the vendor landscape and make the best choice.”</p>
  <p>“In today’s digital economy, data is the most valuable resource,” said Andreas Wesselmann, SAP senior vice president, SAP HANA &#x26; Analytics, Data Management. “Improved data quality can drive profits, innovation and customer satisfaction, while decreasing risk and resulting in consistent improvements in results. SAP’s portfolio of data management solutions improves the quality of data across the enterprise, delivering trusted, relevant and timely information to drive better business outcomes and help customers on their path to becoming intelligent enterprises.”</p>
  <p><a href="https://www.sapowernetworks.com.au/">SA Power Networks</a>, a leading distributor of electricity in Australia, is using SAP Data Services and SAP Information Steward software to boost the management and delivery of customer data. “With SAP Data Services and SAP Information Steward, we’ve slashed response times to issues,” said Janice Espinosa, project manager, Employee Hub for Customer Data, SA Power Network. “And we’ve seen customer satisfaction levels rise as a result.”</p>
  <p>As part of <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">SAP Business Technology Platform</a>, SAP’s portfolio of data management solutions helps customers manage data to glean meaningful insights for creating efficient business processes. Users can proactively govern data across the organization to help ensure trustworthy information for smarter decision-making. Data quality solutions from SAP help businesses discover, understand and manage multifaceted data. Companies can profile, cleanse, enrich and match customer, product, supplier, material and other data, driving more accurate, trustworthy and timely information.</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="http://news.sap.com/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP on Twitter at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Media Contact:</strong> Julia Fargel, +1 (650) 276-8964, <a href="mailto:julia.fargel@sap.com">julia.fargel@sap.com</a>, PT<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>*Gartner, Magic Quadrant for Data Quality Solutions, <a href="https://www.gartner.com/analyst/62722">Melody Chien</a>, <a href="https://www.gartner.com/analyst/54549">Ankush Jain</a>, 29 September 2021.<br>Gartner does not endorse any vendor, product or service depicted in its research publications, and does not advise technology users to select only those vendors with the highest ratings or other designation. Gartner research publications consist of the opinions of Gartner’s research organization and should not be construed as statements of fact. Gartner disclaims all warranties, expressed or implied, with respect to this research, including any warranties of merchantability or fitness for a particular purpose.<br>GARTNER and Magic Quadrant are registered trademarks and service mark of Gartner, Inc. and/or its affiliates in the U.S. and internationally and are used herein with permission. All rights reserved.</p>
  <p>Any statements contained in this document that are not historical facts are forward-looking statements as defined in the U.S. Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995. Words such as “anticipate,” “believe,” “estimate,” “expect,” “forecast,” “intend,” “may,” “plan,” “project,” “predict,” “should” and “will” and similar expressions as they relate to SAP are intended to identify such forward-looking statements. SAP undertakes no obligation to publicly update or revise any forward-looking statements. All forward-looking statements are subject to various risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results to differ materially from expectations. The factors that could affect SAP’s future financial results are discussed more fully in SAP’s filings with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (“SEC”), including SAP’s most recent Annual Report on Form 20-F filed with the SEC. Readers are cautioned not to place undue reliance on these forward-looking statements, which speak only as of their dates.<br>© 2021 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/magic-quadrant</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-integration-suite</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Positioned as a Leader in the Gartner Magic Quadrant for Enterprise Integration Platform-as-a-Service]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/sap-a-leader-magic-quadrant-for-enterprise-integration-platform-as-a-service</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/sap-a-leader-magic-quadrant-for-enterprise-integration-platform-as-a-service</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Gartner has named SAP a Leader in its Magic Quadrant for Enterprise Integration Platform-as-a-Service report for the second year in a row.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/magic-quadrant</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-integration-suite</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Extending the Boundaries of Today's Technologies]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/extending-boundaries-today-technologies-hr-and-finance</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/extending-boundaries-today-technologies-hr-and-finance</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Find out how customers and partners are using SAP BTP to build intelligent solutions that solve complex HR and finance challenges.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1833aa92c0e527a1546cc43db653314a6a5bde258.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1833aa92c0e527a1546cc43db653314a6a5bde258.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1833aa92c0e527a1546cc43db653314a6a5bde258.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Extending the Boundaries of Today’s Technologies" src="./media_1833aa92c0e527a1546cc43db653314a6a5bde258.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="extending-the-boundaries-of-todays-technologies">Extending the Boundaries of Today’s Technologies</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Companies that are building modern, data-driven applications to deliver the future of human experience management (HXM) and finance are well positioned to outpace the competition, even in the face of today’s unprecedented challenges.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Leveling up business efficiency and performance are two critical strategies for staying competitive in today’s increased market volatility and disruption. For most businesses, this means delivering modern, data-driven processes that go beyond merely adding custom functions or tweaking screens within existing business applications. In fact, for many organizations, delivering on this goal requires radically innovating solutions – adding new capabilities and workflows that address evolving needs and bring a new vision.</p>
  <p>Meanwhile, SAP partners can benefit from this growing desire for future-proofing businesses, with intelligent and workflow-aware applications opening new revenue streams driven by cloud adoption. By counteracting declining income from on-premise implementation and operations, savvy partners can recover and grow profits with larger engagements and the conversion of the latest applications into packaged solutions, driving repeatable business across multiple customers.</p>
  <p>At SAP, we see a growing number of companies realizing this potential, bringing to life incredibly inventive business cases. With a portfolio of application development services, such as <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/extension-suite.html">SAP Extension Suite</a> and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/integration-suite.html">SAP Integration Suite</a>, which power <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">SAP Business Technology Platform</a> (SAP BTP), customers and partners can access the tools to support new levels of innovation. They can leverage the platform and its services to integrate SAP and third-party processes, manage data, and deliver modern, intelligent, data-driven capabilities that enable them to digitally transform.</p>
  <p>Let me share some of my personal favorites across various lines of business – such as HR, finance, commerce, and operations – where people are experiencing more streamlined, intelligent, and human-centered work.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-business-technology-platform-accelerate-business-outcomes-with-integration-data-to-value-and-extensibility">SAP Business Technology Platform: Accelerate business outcomes with integration, data to value, and extensibility</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="customizing-cloud-based-hr-integration-for-tax-credit">Customizing Cloud-Based HR Integration for Tax Credit</h2>
  <p>A great example of how our customers and partners extend HR capabilities in the cloud relates to the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/recruiting-software.html">SAP SuccessFactors Recruiting</a> and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/employee-central-hris.html">SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central</a> solutions, which are part of <a href="https://www.sap.com/programs/experience-wins.html">SAP SuccessFactors HXM Suite</a>. The suite provides powerful cloud-based solutions for core HR and payroll, talent management, employee experience management, and people analytics.</p>
  <p>By directly integrating SAP SuccessFactors solutions with APIs and intelligent services, HR organizations can assess, validate, and process new hires while determining whether their business qualifies for a Work Opportunity Tax Credit (WOTC). WOTCs allow U.S. companies to receive federal tax credits every year they hire employees who systematically experience significant barriers against employment.</p>
  <p>Although the recruiting and core HR solutions do not include the means to track and validate individual new hires, they contain the framework to build those capabilities. SAP partners can leverage integration workflows available in SAP BTP and use them to connect the two SAP SuccessFactors solutions to the digital job application. Our customers can then schedule assessments with frequent intervals, read applicants’ qualifications, and prompt candidates to complete a WOTC assessment, and the results from that evaluation are updated in the related SAP SuccessFactors solution.</p>
  <p>This scenario exemplifies how partners can leverage SAP BTP to introduce capabilities – which may not be a standard function in the existing software – into current business processes. Many of our customers and partners have taken advantage of this opportunity to streamline related workflows, connect relevant business entities, and deliver an experience-first approach to HR.</p>
  <h2 id="closing-the-gap-in-dispute-and-grievance-resolution">Closing the Gap in Dispute and Grievance Resolution</h2>
  <p>An under-served area in most HR technologies is the employee dispute and grievance resolution process. For example, one of our partners helped a customer develop an application that settles and handles grievance cases with greater transparency.</p>
  <p>By tightly coupling <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm.html">SAP SuccessFactors solutions</a> and SAP BTP, the partner solution emulates the core solution experience. When launched from an SAP SuccessFactors solution, the look and feel of the partner application is consistent for the user. The interface is developed with <a href="https://sapui5.hana.ondemand.com/">SAPUI5</a> and the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/fiori.html">SAP Fiori</a> design system, while the integration is enabled by the SAP Platform Identity Provider service for SAP BTP and the Identity Authentication service.</p>
  <p>Through this co-innovation effort, our customers can address various grievance types that represent unique workflows, approval processes, and business scenarios – operated smoothly with the <a href="https://discovery-center.cloud.sap/serviceCatalog/workflow-management">SAP Workflow Management</a> service. As a result, our customers can improve auditability and accelerate the entire resolution process. They can trace a grievance throughout its lifecycle from the complaint to resolution, standardize information gathering, and conduct an organizational-level review of complaints and their progress in real time.</p>
  <h2 id="optimizing-the-use-of-talent-anytime-and-anywhere">Optimizing the Use of Talent, Anytime and Anywhere</h2>
  <p>By extending the core HR capabilities of SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central, our partners also develop applications that help improve resource management and utilization. In return, our customers can assign the right talent to the right projects with a real-time schedule, built by reading a project-related business system, such as SAP S/4HANA.</p>
  <p>In this case, SAP BTP smoothly integrates employee leave data, skill set information, and details on organizational needs. Plus, different approval processes are made available through SAP Workflow Management.</p>
  <p>Extending core HR capabilities in this manner allows details, including assignment duration and employee proficiency, to be considered when assigning employees to projects and roles – helping to ensure every person can contribute to their fullest potential. Similar implementations of this use case can also help customers develop workflow applications related to security clearance, visa applications, and work permit processes, to name a few.</p>
  <h2 id="maximizing-the-product-life-cycle-with-a-new-business-model">Maximizing the Product Life Cycle with a New Business Model</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="hxm-deliver-exceptional-employee-experiences-for-the-employee-life-cycle">HXM: Deliver exceptional employee experiences for the employee life cycle</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/programs/experience-wins.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Speaking of improved resource contribution and utilization, the fashion industry is discovering a better way to recapture US$460 billion in value lost to discarded clothing each year. In this use case, retailers embrace an online rental business model that adds new revenue streams, making the business more competitive, and reduces their carbon footprint, resulting in improved consumer trust and loyalty.</p>
  <p>Under a similar product lifecycle use case, one of our customers integrated its back-office system with an e-commerce portal by using intelligent technologies such as robotic process automation (RPA). Using <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/s4hana-erp.html">SAP S/4HANA Cloud</a> and SAP BTP, the retailer integrated and automated its rental order fulfillment and return processes.</p>
  <h2 id="detecting-anomalies-in-business-operations-to-prevent-fraud">Detecting Anomalies in Business Operations to Prevent Fraud</h2>
  <p>Historically, procure-to-pay processes are fraught with excess payments, operational risks, rising costs, incomplete audit verification, arduous recovery efforts, and noncompliant purchasing behaviors. But SAP BTP enables our partners and customers to overcome these challenges with tip-based alerting, rules-based detection, and pattern-based prediction.</p>
  <p>Organizations focused on tackling these issues integrate their offerings with the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/data-intelligence.html">SAP Data Intelligence</a> solution, SAP Fiori user experience, runtime application self-protection for SAP BTP, and SAP BTP, Cloud Foundry environment. They can then decipher data-driven patterns to identify new anomalies and fraud types and customize red-flag thresholds based on criticality and risk tolerance. Furthermore, finance decision-makers can learn from user feedback by using the intelligent data capture and processing solution to continuously improve fraud detection practices.</p>
  <p>Outcomes from this procure-to-pay approach include 70% savings in compliance effort, 95% straight-through processing, 100% audit coverage, and more on-time payments.</p>
  <h2 id="using-powerful-technology-today-evolving-for-tomorrow">Using Powerful Technology Today, Evolving for Tomorrow</h2>
  <p>Most applications come with their own stack of tools, methodologies, and workbenches that enable companies to make fundamental changes to the user experience. But with SAP BTP, SAP partners and our customers can come together to build more intelligent, workflow-aware solutions that solve more complex customer process challenges.</p>
  <p>By building intelligent solutions with the unified, business-centric, and open platform, our partners can access the technology foundation, tools, and development practices necessary to extend the boundaries of digitalization and cloud architecture. As a result, they can increase their average engagement sizes, convert their IP into repeatable, packaged software offerings, and generate new revenue streams under new business models. And more importantly, these technology and business experts can help customers of all industries and sizes become more agile, future-proof their processes, and realize their full potential as intelligent enterprises.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>To learn more about how SAP partners are helping businesses succeed with a unified technology platform, <a href="/author/jagdishsahasrabudhe">explore Jagdish’s other articles</a>. Those interested in software partnership opportunities with SAP can check out <a href="https://www.sap.com/partner/become/partneredge-build.html">SAP PartnerEdge Build</a>, and existing partners can learn more about the initiatives <a href="https://events.sap.com/hack2build/en/home">Hack2Build</a>, <a href="https://saphanajourney.com/sap-analytics-cloud/sac-business-content/">SAP Analytics Cloud Business Content Wave</a>, and <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/innovation/coil.html">SAP Co-Innovation Lab</a>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><em>Jagdish Sahasrabudhe is CTO of the Global Partner Organization at SAP.</em></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-integration-suite</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-partneredge-build</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[AGL Employees Go Digital with New iOS App and SAP BTP]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/agl-ios-app-sap-btp</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/agl-ios-app-sap-btp</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A new app for AGL employees is based on SAP BTP and offers a single digital experience to access the right tool at the right time.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f9cea16c408670ab68c426efa9336619a2f98ccc.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f9cea16c408670ab68c426efa9336619a2f98ccc.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1f9cea16c408670ab68c426efa9336619a2f98ccc.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="AGL Employees Go Digital with New iOS App and SAP BTP" src="./media_1f9cea16c408670ab68c426efa9336619a2f98ccc.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="agl-employees-go-digital-with-new-ios-app-and-sap-btp">AGL Employees Go Digital with New iOS App and SAP BTP</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>As a leading integrated essential service provider, AGL has a proud 184-year history of innovation along with a passionate belief in human and technological progress. The company delivers 3.95 million gas, electricity, and telecommunications services to residential, small, and large businesses, as well as wholesale customers across Australia.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>AGL also operates Australia’s largest electricity generation portfolio, responsible for about 20% of the total electricity capacity of the country.</p>
  <p>AGL recently partnered with SAP AppHaus Network member Bourne Digital to create the AGL One iOS app. Based on SAP Integration Suite and SAP Extension Suite, the app brings together AGL’s employee network in a single digital experience so they can access the right tool at the right time — every time, from anywhere. Powered by SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP), the solution recently won a SAP Innovation Award in the Transformation Champion category.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="explore-the-sap-apphaus-network">Explore the SAP AppHaus Network</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://experience.sap.com/designservices/network">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="growing-company-needs-enhanced-digital-infrastructure">Growing Company Needs Enhanced Digital Infrastructure</h2>
  <p>In June of 2019, AGL launched PT3 (People, Process and Performance Transformation), its initiative to unite all AGL sites across corporate and group operations into one technical platform. The initiative also aimed at delivering greater mobility and enabling AGL staff to work flexibly with mobile applications on their phones or tablets.</p>
  <p>After first launch, however, user feedback showed the need to improve the solution and explore ways to better enable employees digitally.</p>
  <p>AGL decided to examine employees’ user experience (UX) to help ensure a better adoption of the new platform. Clear focus of the new solution would be consolidation and ease of use. After a complete redesign of the mobile interface, AGL wanted to extend the strong relationship already in place with customers to the people who worked for the company.</p>
  <h2 id="bringing-in-sap-apphaus-network-member-bourne-digital">Bringing in SAP AppHaus Network Member Bourne Digital</h2>
  <p>AGL consulted with the same firm that helped design its customer experience, Bourne Digital. As an SAP AppHaus Network member, Bourne Digital is part of the worldwide community of like-minded SAP-partners that work with customers in a creative environment to make innovation real, following SAP’s human-centered approach to innovation.</p>
  <p>As a first step toward the new solution for employees, AGL tasked an internal service design team with replicating the service design process for employees’ mobile app. With the help of its employee experience center, the joint AGL and Bourne Digital project team conducted lifecycle mapping and extensive interviews with staff to discover the following key issues with the existing mobile interface:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Too many tools in the environment made it hard for the employees to identify the correct tool for each situation.</li>
    <li>The usability of the previous solution was not simple and prevented proficiency.</li>
    <li>The solution missed data consolidation of several sources.</li>
    <li>Employee engagement was low due to dissatisfaction with the efficiency of the tools.</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="agl-one-ios-app-simplifies-employees-lives">AGL One: iOS App Simplifies Employees’ Lives</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="review-agls-sap-innovation-award-winning-pitch">Review AGL's SAP Innovation Award-winning pitch</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/bin/sapdxc/inm/attachment.11319/pitch-deck.pdf">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Employees wanted a straightforward, consolidated, easy-to-use mobile experience. AGL and Bourne Digital worked with Apple to create an iOS app called <strong>AGL One</strong>. The feedback collected in the interviews was used to create a completely redesigned mobile employee interface. Based on SAP Integration Suite and SAP Extension Suite, the app now brings together AGL’s employee network in a single digital experience.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14695ba332da86f0ed1e2ce2affdc732d865aa30c.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14695ba332da86f0ed1e2ce2affdc732d865aa30c.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_14695ba332da86f0ed1e2ce2affdc732d865aa30c.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="AGL app explainer" src="./media_14695ba332da86f0ed1e2ce2affdc732d865aa30c.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1050" height="513">
    </picture>“AGL was focused on creating a highly engaging mobile experience for employees to improve productivity and engagement,” said Selim Ahmed, CEO of Bourne Digital. “Together, AGL, Apple, SAP, and Bourne Digital created an integrated and scalable solution that extended their investment in SAP S/4HANA with the agility of SAP Integration Suite and SAP Extension Suite. It has been a wonderful innovation story that puts employees at the center of the organization. The Bourne Digital SAP AppHaus facility supported employee experience design thinking sessions.”
  </p>
  <h2 id="one-stop-shop-for-all-actions">One-Stop Shop for All Actions</h2>
  <p>The project team held a number of design thinking sessions at Bourne Digital’s AppHaus facility in Melbourne to re-imagine the employee experience.</p>
  <p>Building on its existing investment in SAP S4/HANA with SAP BTP, the AGL One app combines a landscape of more than 300 IT applications into one single interface with only one main login to use. Even when employees want to switch back and forth between apps, they do not have to re-login and remember different passwords every time. Once signed in, the UX itself is accessible to the average employee, so they do not have to know specific tool names or apps to use them.</p>
  <p>Built-in capabilities within AGL One prioritize tasks that are easy to do on the go, such as administrative tasks and approvals. This helps reduce cycle time on tasks that are often put off and need to be followed up on, making employees’ workdays more productive and efficient. Key features of the app include:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Quick access to action all purchase order approvals in SAP S/4HANA</li>
    <li>Assessments of workplace safety and reports available on the go, with the option to use a phone’s camera to add a photo and record safety observations or hazards in SAP S/4HANA</li>
    <li>Personalization of the homepage for quick access to tools the employee uses most often</li>
    <li>Desk booking with desk locator, particularly following COVID-19 restrictions</li>
    <li>Holiday and leave request entry and management</li>
    <li>New colleague appreciation tool called “Energise”</li>
    <li>AGL news service with talking points, friends and family discounts, and easy access to AGL job boards to be active ambassadors outside the company</li>
    <li>Live news feed along with integration to “The Source,” AGL’s news and intranet</li>
    <li>Seamless third-party collaborations between SAP back end and Apple user interface</li>
  </ul>
  <p>By building an app expressly for its employees, AGL has successfully placed their user experience on the same priority level as its customers’. AGL One supports a positive, streamlined experience for employees, whether at the office or in the field. After rolling out the app, the company has seen a motivation and engagement boost at work among employees. The app was released in October 2020 and the number of downloads speaks for itself: 1,600 out of 3,700 employees have downloaded the app so far, an adoption rate of nearly 50%.</p>
  <p>“When we first started this project, we looked at it the same way we’d look at anything we were doing for our customers,” explained Joy Marrocco, IT Transformation Manager at AGL. “We already had a great relationship there, why not apply that same approach to our employees? We wanted to drive digital adoption of employee tools, and this app is one of the ways that we are working to make access to these tools much quicker and easier for our people.”</p>
  <h2 id="award-winning-solution-built-with-sap-btp">Award-Winning Solution Built with SAP BTP</h2>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_197d0f2d37f648a9fe6fcb28b20007fd5bc4ce8e6.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_197d0f2d37f648a9fe6fcb28b20007fd5bc4ce8e6.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_197d0f2d37f648a9fe6fcb28b20007fd5bc4ce8e6.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Screenshots: AGL iOS app" src="./media_197d0f2d37f648a9fe6fcb28b20007fd5bc4ce8e6.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1050" height="430">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p>The innovation power of this application and the entire project was also recognized by the jury of the 2021 SAP Innovation Awards, with the AGL One app for employees winning in the Transformation Champion category.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Svenja Mueller is the communications associate for SAP AppHaus.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-apphaus</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>sap-award/sap-innovation-awards</category>
            <category>product/sap-integration-suite</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Integrated Order Management Cockpit on SAP BTP at Border States]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/05/border-states-industries-integrated-order-management-cockpit-sap-btp</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/05/border-states-industries-integrated-order-management-cockpit-sap-btp</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[At Border States, an integrated order management cockpit on SAP BTP provides visibility into sales and purchase orders in real time.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_13760278b7b7182c07df081bbf1d8cc472b06fb53.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_13760278b7b7182c07df081bbf1d8cc472b06fb53.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_13760278b7b7182c07df081bbf1d8cc472b06fb53.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Integrated Order Management Cockpit on SAP BTP at Border States" src="./media_13760278b7b7182c07df081bbf1d8cc472b06fb53.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="integrated-order-management-cockpit-on-sap-btp-at-border-states">Integrated Order Management Cockpit on SAP BTP at Border States</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>As <a href="/covid-19">COVID-19</a> impacted supply chains, Border States Industries Inc., the seventh largest <a href="https://www.borderstates.com/">electrical distributor in the U.S.</a>, needed to optimize and streamline its purchase and sales order management to manage delayed and escalated orders specifically. It was critical to consolidate disjointed systems and tools, increase cross-team visibility, and reduce the duplication of work in order to provide its innovative supply chain products and services to the construction, industrial, and utility markets.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The integrated order management cockpit on SAP Business Technology Platform provides end-to-end and real-time visibility into sales and purchase orders and can enable colleagues from procurement, customer service, and application engineering to collaborate in order to handle material delays, escalations, and other issues. This way, the business can experience improved customer experience (like on-time delivery), an optimized and streamlined order management with clear line of sight for all stakeholders, a reduction of duplicate work, the facilitation of hand-offs and material escalations, and increased visibility and accountability.</p>
  <p>Tony Serati, vice president of Procurement at Border States, said, “The solution will improve collaboration and speed of information within our company, resulting in an improved experience and service for our customers.”</p>
  <p>Border States is 100% employee-owned and has more than 2,300 employee owners and 98 branch locations in 22 states. Employee ownership drives Border States’ commitment to deliver total satisfaction. Border States was founded in 1952, when two entrepreneurs wanted to serve the electric utility industry. After nearly 70 years in business, the company’s mission and values haven’t changed; Border States remains a trusted advisor and problem solver, providing value to tens of thousands of customers in the construction, industrial, and utility markets. The company does this by delivering quality products, material management solutions, and industry expertise.</p>
  <p>The integrated order management cockpit provides a centralized space for all stakeholders to have visibility into order statuses, collaborate, and resolve escalations in a timely manner.</p>
  <p>“I am very excited about the collaboration piece. It is an immediate way of communication and will make the life of a buyer much easier,” said Christa Lavey, purchasing supervisor at Border States.</p>
  <p>The flag feature allows CSR teams to request specific actions from the procurement teams. They are also able to post comments on order status updates.</p>
  <p>With an escalation toggle, the subject matter experts can help resolve escalated orders proactively. The stakeholders can provide material level updates, too.
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e021ee5453216e1f5574b02dff2de811fa7568bc.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e021ee5453216e1f5574b02dff2de811fa7568bc.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1e021ee5453216e1f5574b02dff2de811fa7568bc.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Screenshot: escalation toggle" src="./media_1e021ee5453216e1f5574b02dff2de811fa7568bc.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1440" height="806">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p>“This tool allows us to escalate and collaborate on orders to find alternatives and work with customers and suppliers to prevent impacts,” said Lex Silbernagel, vice president of Alliances at Border States. “It will enable us to better manage and communicate as challenges arise.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-business-technology-platform-accelerate-business-outcomes-with-integration-data-to-value-and-extensibility">SAP Business Technology Platform: Accelerate business outcomes with integration, data to value, and extensibility</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="technological-foundation">Technological Foundation</h2>
  <p>The integrated order management cockpit is built on SAP Business Technology Platform, leveraging SAP Integration Suite, SAP Extension Suite, SAP HANA Cloud, and the SAP Fiori design system. It provides colleagues from procurement, customer service, and application engineering with a central place to manage escalated purchase and sales orders. With this solution, teams can have real-time, cross-team visibility, rather than working in multiple disjointed systems and unsynchronized tools. This allows for improved communication and direct feedback between stakeholders, working to improve process efficiency and eliminate the duplication of work. In addition, new team members can be onboarded quickly and raise and manage issues as they occur.</p>
  <p>The semantic data models on SAP HANA Cloud make the solution SAP ERP data agnostic, allowing for seamless integration with SAP ERP now and SAP S/4HANA in the future. SAP Integration Suite helps integrate the solution directly with data from backend solutions. SAP Fiori provides a simplified user experience, enabling users to manage escalations quicker and more effectively.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h2 id="key-results">Key Results</h2>
        <table>
          <thead>
            <tr>
              <th colspan="2">Promo</th>
            </tr>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td>
                <h3 id="explore-border-states-2021-sap-innovation-awards-pitch-deck">Explore Border States 2021 SAP Innovation Awards pitch deck</h3>
              </td>
              <td><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/idea-place/sap-innovation-awards/submission-details-2021.html?idea_id=2453">Learn more</a></strong></td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
        <ul>
          <li>Approximately 16,000 hours saved annually for customer service representatives and buyer roles</li>
          <li>About 2% productivity gained for CSR and buyer roles</li>
          <li>About 1% improvement on material availability resulting in improved on-time delivery, improved customer experience and increased revenues</li>
        </ul>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fiori</category>
            <category>product/sap-hana-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-integration-suite</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Integration Suite Recognized as a 2021 Gartner Peer Insights Customers’ Choice for Enterprise Integration Platform as a Service]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/sap-integration-suite-gartner-peer-insights-enterprise-integration-platform-as-a-service</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/sap-integration-suite-gartner-peer-insights-enterprise-integration-platform-as-a-service</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Integration Suite is a Customers’ Choice in the 2021 Gartner Peer Insights for Enterprise Integration Platform as a Service]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1964df759a05df323800cea1bed52a6fd8fdfcfa0.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1964df759a05df323800cea1bed52a6fd8fdfcfa0.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1964df759a05df323800cea1bed52a6fd8fdfcfa0.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Integration Suite Recognized as a 2021 Gartner Peer Insights Customers’ Choice for Enterprise Integration Platform as a Service" src="./media_1964df759a05df323800cea1bed52a6fd8fdfcfa0.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-integration-suite-recognized-as-a-2021-gartner-peer-insights-customers-choice-for-enterprise-integration-platform-as-a-service">SAP Integration Suite Recognized as a 2021 Gartner Peer Insights Customers’ Choice for Enterprise Integration Platform as a Service</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-integration-suite-connect-applications-processes-and-people-with-speed-and-ease">SAP Integration Suite: Connect applications, processes, and people with speed and ease</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/integration-suite.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/integration-suite.html">SAP Integration Suite</a>, a key solution powering <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">SAP Business Technology Platform</a>, was named a Customers’ Choice in the 2021 “<a href="https://www.gartner.com/doc/reprints?id=1-25QQIZBR&#x26;ct=210405&#x26;st=sb">Gartner Peer Insights ‘Voice of the Customer’: Enterprise Integration Platform as a Service</a>.”</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP is one of only two vendors to be named a Customers’ Choice in this category and received a 4.6 out of 5 overall rating. Ninety-three percent of the customers indicated that they would recommend SAP Integration Suite as their preferred enterprise integration platform as a service.</p>
  <p>Gartner Peer Insights Customers’ Choice Distinction is a free peer review and ratings platform designed for enterprise software and services decision-makers.</p>
  <p>“We believe this recognition is a further validation that SAP Integration Suite is a proven solution to support our customers with their growing integration needs across all landscapes,” said Juergen Mueller, chief technology officer and member of the SAP Executive Board. “Companies are using SAP Integration Suite to stay agile and competitive as they transform their businesses into an intelligent enterprise. We are continuously listening to customer feedback to make sure we deliver a valuable experience.”</p>
  <p>Customer reviews go through a strict validation and moderation process in an effort to ensure they are authentic. Some of the reviews include:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><em>“<a href="https://www.gartner.com/reviews/market/enterprise-integration-platform-as-a-service/vendor/sap/product/sap-integration-suite/review/view/3465326">Best Cloud Platform For Multiple SAP Solutions:</a></em> <em>Best cloud platform for our organization. Fast and reliable cloud platform for business applications. Better integration capabilities and allows to integrate multiple SAP solutions.”</em> — Assistant professor in the education industry</li>
    <li>“<a href="https://www.gartner.com/reviews/market/enterprise-integration-platform-as-a-service/vendor/sap/product/sap-integration-suite/review/view/1341493"><em>Reliability, Trust, Content And Performance Are A Basis For A Stable Integration Platform</em>:</a> <em>Very good collaboration between SAP and our company when it comes to discussions or needs that we want to address. Openness and trust is an important factor, as well as the reliability of people and the products themselves in terms of availability, stability and performance. The huge advantage SAP gives us, is the predefined integration content which we find on the API Business Hub. These pre-configured integration scenarios save us time and money. Also to be mentioned is the strong user community.”</em> — Director, business application platforms, in the manufacturing industry</li>
    <li>“<em><a href="https://www.gartner.com/reviews/market/enterprise-integration-platform-as-a-service/vendor/sap/product/sap-integration-suite/review/view/1357917">Very Robust Platform</a>: Integration layer tied with the SAP SCP platform bring easier integrations thru external services and platforms. In general they are easy to use and have very good performance and stability. Also it´s and SAP Roadmap for integration of SAP Products and Services.”</em> — Enterprise architect in the energy and utilities industry</li>
    <li><em><strong>“</strong><a href="https://www.gartner.com/reviews/market/enterprise-integration-platform-as-a-service/vendor/sap/product/sap-integration-suite/review/view/1356873">Lower TCO</a>: SAP Cloud Platform integration provides seamless integration with SAP and NON-SAP products and financial benefits. The financial benefits are related to a lower Totall Cost of Ownership (TCO).”</em> — Integration specialist in the services industry</li>
  </ul>
  <p>Vendors placed in the upper-right quadrant of the “Voice of the Customer” quadrants are recognized with the Gartner Peer Insights Customers’ Choice distinction. A maximum of seven vendors can qualify. To qualify, vendors must have a product that is listed in this market on Gartner Peer Insights, have their overall rating (out of five stars) above or equal to the mean rating for that market, and receive 50 or more eligible published customer reviews during the one-year submission period. In addition, customer reviews must be representative of a broad mix of enterprise clients from different industries, company sizes and deployment regions. More <a href="https://blogs.gartner.com/reviews-pages/peer-insights-customers-choice-distinctions-methodology/gartner-peer-insights-customers-choice-methodology-1-5/">details about the Customers’ Choice distinction are available here</a>.</p>
  <p>To learn more, <a href="https://www.gartner.com/doc/reprints?id=1-25QQIZBR&#x26;ct=210405&#x26;st=sb">access the 2021 report here</a>.</p>
  <p>Additionally, SAP Integration Suite has been named as <a href="/2020/09/sap-a-leader-gartner-magic-quadrant-enterprise-integration-paas">a Leader in 2020 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Enterprise Integration Platform as a Service</a>.</p>
  <p>Designed to support a multitude of integration scenarios — hybrid, on-premise and cloud as well as with 160 third-party applications — SAP Integration Suite is also the underpinning technology supporting the integration strategy across SAP’s entire application portfolio, including SAP S/4HANA and other line-of-business applications from SAP. Learn more in <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2020/02/520ea921-847d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff.html">SAP’s integration road map to the cloud</a>.</p>
  <p>SAP Integration Suite is available for online trial and purchase on <a href="https://www.sapstore.com/solutions/55519/SAP-Integration-Suite?url_id=ctabutton-UnifiedSearchResult">SAP Store</a>.</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="http://news.sap.com/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP on Twitter at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Media Contact:</strong> Julia Fargel +1 (650) 276-8964, <a href="mailto:julia.fargel@sap.com">julia.fargel@sap.com</a>, PT<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p><strong>Disclaimers</strong><br><strong><em>Gartner, Gartner Peer Insights ‘Voice of the Customer’: Voice of the Customer: Enterprise Integrations Platform as a Service.”, 1 April 2021.</em></strong> <em>Rating and scoring as on 31 January, 2021.</em></p>
  <p><em>Gartner Peer Insights Customers’ Choice constitute the subjective opinions of individual end-user reviews, ratings, and data applied against a documented methodology; they neither represent the views of, nor constitute an endorsement by, Gartner or its affiliates.</em></p>
  <p><em>Gartner does not endorse any vendor, product or service depicted in its research publications, and does not advise technology users to select only those vendors with the highest ratings or other designation. Gartner research publications consist of the opinions of Gartner’s research organization and should not be construed as statements of fact. Gartner disclaims all warranties, express or implied, with respect to this research, including any warranties of merchantability or fitness for a particular purpose.</em></p>
  <p><em>Gartner does not endorse any vendor, product or service depicted in its research publications and does not advise technology users to select only those vendors with the highest ratings or other designation. Gartner research publications consist of the opinions of Gartner’s Research &#x26; Advisory organization and should not be construed as statements of fact. Gartner disclaims all warranties, expressed or implied, with respect to this research, including any warranties of merchantability or fitness for a particular purpose.</em></p>
  <p>Any statements contained in this document that are not historical facts are forward-looking statements as defined in the U.S. Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995. Words such as “anticipate,” “believe,” “estimate,” “expect,” “forecast,” “intend,” “may,” “plan,” “project,” “predict,” “should” and “will” and similar expressions as they relate to SAP are intended to identify such forward-looking statements. SAP undertakes no obligation to publicly update or revise any forward-looking statements. All forward-looking statements are subject to various risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results to differ materially from expectations. The factors that could affect SAP’s future financial results are discussed more fully in SAP’s filings with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (“SEC”), including SAP’s most recent Annual Report on Form 20-F filed with the SEC. Readers are cautioned not to place undue reliance on these forward-looking statements, which speak only as of their dates.<br>© 2021 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-integration-suite</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>