<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/sap-store/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Helping Customers Innovate with More Than 125 AI-Powered Startup Partner Solutions]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/ai-powered-startup-partner-solutions-sap-io</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/ai-powered-startup-partner-solutions-sap-io</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[More than 125 AI-powered startup partner solutions are fully integrated with SAP and available via SAP Store. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-store</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-io</category>
            <category>news-tag/startups</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Industry Innovation Gives Partners a Runway for Sustained Success]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/industry-cloud-innovation-sap-partners-success</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/industry-cloud-innovation-sap-partners-success</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP's industry cloud offers partners boundless opportunities to cultivate new markets, customers, and revenue sources. Read to learn how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11d9ba4b00dd11ddbd90c3e316d0c28742fc92154.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11d9ba4b00dd11ddbd90c3e316d0c28742fc92154.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_11d9ba4b00dd11ddbd90c3e316d0c28742fc92154.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="How Industry Innovation Gives Partners a Runway for Sustained Success" src="./media_11d9ba4b00dd11ddbd90c3e316d0c28742fc92154.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="how-industry-innovation-gives-partners-a-runway-for-sustained-success">How Industry Innovation Gives Partners a Runway for Sustained Success</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Have you ever wondered at the workings of the modern airport and the ecosystem around it, how so many complex and disparate moving parts come together to deliver a high-quality travel experience to flyers?</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Granted, those experiences aren’t always positive. But when everything is working in sync – travel and transportation infrastructure, aerospace technology, energy, retail, hospitality, and more – to create a whole greater than the sum of its parts, my thoughts can’t help but shift skyward, to another more familiar ecosystem.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="grow-and-find-a-competitive-edge-with-industry-cloud-solutions-from-sap-and-partners">Grow and find a competitive edge with industry cloud solutions from SAP and partners</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/industry-cloud.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Among the many developments I’ve witnessed lately as a result of SAP’s growing focus on industry innovation, SAP’s industry cloud and the partner ecosystem that supports it stand out. They’re proving my long-held belief that a high level of collaboration with partners across companies and industries, similar to what occurs at airports, can open boundless opportunities to cultivate new markets, customers, and revenue sources. SAP’s industry cloud has yielded close to 400 solutions across 25 industry verticals, 80% of which were developed by partners either on their own or in collaboration with SAP. About 1,900 unique customers are using these solutions, and they’re renewing them at a rate above 90%.</p>
  <p>What’s driving the industry innovation momentum? And why should SAP partners consider engaging in the co-innovation effort if they’re not already, or get more involved if they are? Here are five competitive justifications:</p>
  <ol>
    <li><strong>Future readiness:</strong> A business landscape that is perpetually shifting and evolving, often in unexpected ways, demands a business mindset that embraces change and seeks out opportunities to innovate – a mindset of future readiness. A focus on industry innovation fosters future readiness on multiple levels. It gives partners a portfolio of solutions to help their customers prepare for a future where cloud solutions will be instrumental to their digital transformation efforts. One leading global consulting firm predicts that by 2027, enterprises will be using industry cloud platforms to accelerate more than half of their critical business initiatives. What’s more, working within an industry cloud environment like SAP’s can give partners themselves a future-ready model for growing their business.</li>
    <li><strong>Business ecosystems and networks:</strong> By bringing their industry knowledge and intellectual property to a business ecosystem like the one that supports SAP’s industry cloud, partners can become a multiplier for industry innovation, moving solutions through the development pipeline and to customers faster together than they otherwise could working individually. We’re witnessing this multiplier effect within specific industries like consumer products, life sciences, automotive, energy, and industrial manufacturing, where collaboration within industry-focused business ecosystems is fueling a fresh wave of co-innovation.</li>
    <li><strong>Modularity and integration:</strong> One of my team’s responsibilities is to maintain the industry cloud opportunity map, a comprehensive architecture of potential and already developed solutions that comprise the present and future of industry innovation in the cloud. A glance at the opportunity map tells a compelling story about all the white space available to partners to fill out the portfolio. Intellectual property and ideas are the building blocks in this case. The door is wide open for partners to bring use cases that enhance, extend, or add to an existing solution, or that fill gaps in the opportunity map. Using SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP) and SAP Store, they can rapidly develop their ideas and turn them into commercialized solutions that customers can readily integrate.</li>
    <li><strong>Industry convergence:</strong> Just like at the airport, we’re seeing the lines between industries blur and converge as traditional value chains merge. This creates massive opportunities for SAP partners to develop new revenue streams around solutions that they adapt from one industry for use in another, or that can be used by customers across multiple industries. Electric vehicle charging is sparking a convergence among automotive, energy, oil and gas, utility, and retail and consumer products, for example. And that, in turn, is providing fertile territory for SAP partners with use cases and intellectual property in these areas to collaborate and create new solutions that can add value for customers.</li>
    <li><strong>Customer experience:</strong> By focusing on industry innovation, our goal is to give customers exactly what they need to succeed from a digital solutions standpoint. The better SAP, our partners, and all of us collectively as an ecosystem are at delivering the solutions customers need, the more trust we create with them. And that opens even more possibilities for SAP, partners, and customers alike – possibilities that conjure the familiar feeling I get at the airport when I’m waiting to board my next flight.</li>
  </ol>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Sven Denecken is senior vice president and chief marketing and solutions officer for SAP Industries &#x26; CX.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-store</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP's Industry Cloud Drives Innovation in Utilities Through Cloud-Based Apps and Partner Collaborations]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/sap-industry-cloud-drives-innovation-in-utilities</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/sap-industry-cloud-drives-innovation-in-utilities</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP's industry cloud is driving innovation in the utilities sector through cloud-based apps and partner collaborations. Read to learn how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-co-innovation-lab</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-store</category>
            <category>industry/utilities</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP BTP Use Cases: Going Deeper, Broader, and Faster]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/sap-btp-use-cases-deeper-broader-faster</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/sap-btp-use-cases-deeper-broader-faster</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP BTP use cases offer various opportunities to help move to the cloud by consuming technology, such as generative AI, faster.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-apphaus</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-apphaus-network</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-store</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Leveraging SAP’s Industry Cloud, Going from Concept to Commercialization Can Be Fast and Fulfilling]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/cogniac-sap-syntax-industry-cloud</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/cogniac-sap-syntax-industry-cloud</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The industry cloud partnership between Cogniac, Syntax, and SAP illustrates how combining forces can deliver more value to customers.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>product/sap-digital-manufacturing</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-store</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-io</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Better Together: How SAP Expands Its Cloud ERP Portfolio Through Partnering]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/planon-sap-sapphire-expanded-cloud-erp-portfolio</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/planon-sap-sapphire-expanded-cloud-erp-portfolio</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Combining the strengths of Planon and Schneider Electric with the expertise of SAP will connect buildings, people, and processes. Learn how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-store</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP BTP Use Cases Kick-Start Transformation with Pre-Built Business Content]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/sap-btp-use-cases-art-of-the-possible</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/sap-btp-use-cases-art-of-the-possible</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Actionable use cases show customers what can be done with SAP BTP to help solve specific situations in their enterprise. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/esg</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-apphaus</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-apphaus-network</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-store</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Intelligent Data Drives Growth Across Farm-to-Consume Food Value Chain]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/intelligent-data-drives-growth-food-value-chain</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/intelligent-data-drives-growth-food-value-chain</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP’s industry cloud can help help fresh produce companies use data to make better decisions for managing the food value chain.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/agribusiness</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-store</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Partners Drive a Wave of Industry Cloud Innovation in Discrete Manufacturing]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/sap-partners-industry-cloud-innovation-discrete-manufacturing</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/sap-partners-industry-cloud-innovation-discrete-manufacturing</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP and its partners are capitalizing on industry cloud opportunities in the discrete manufacturing industries. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-store</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Consumer Industries Witness Surge of Innovation, Thanks to SAP’s Industry Cloud Partners]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/consumer-industries-innovation-sap-industry-cloud-partners</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/consumer-industries-innovation-sap-industry-cloud-partners</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Industry cloud solutions from SAP and our partners are changing the way consumer industries customers do business.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/consumer-goods-cpg</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-store</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Revolution in Product Discovery with Zoovu Apps on SAP Store]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/revolution-in-product-discovery-zoovu-sap-store</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/revolution-in-product-discovery-zoovu-sap-store</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Zoovu humanizes product discovery, making products easier to find, evaluate, and buy by bringing context to your search. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-commerce</category>
            <category>news-tag/e-commerce</category>
            <category>product/sap-commerce-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-cpq</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-digital-commerce</category>
            <category>product/sap-sales-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-store</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[New Survey Finds Digital Marketplaces Are the Future of Commerce]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/digital-marketplaces-future-commerce-new-survey</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/digital-marketplaces-future-commerce-new-survey</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New survey results show that digital marketplaces are here to stay and resources like SAP Store and SAP.com are key.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-commerce</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-store</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pharmaceutical Manufacturers Fight Fake Drugs with Intelligent Supply Chains]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/pharmaceutical-manufacturers-drug-supply-chains</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/pharmaceutical-manufacturers-drug-supply-chains</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Investing in intelligent supply chain solutions can enable resilience and prevent counterfeit drugs in the life sciences industry. Learn how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digitalization</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>industry/life-sciences</category>
            <category>product/sap-information-collaboration-hub-for-life-sciences</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-store</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Brings Cloud Software Repurchases in Minutes to Customers and Partners]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/sap-for-me-on-sap-store-cloud-software-repurchases</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/sap-for-me-on-sap-store-cloud-software-repurchases</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With SAP for Me on SAP Store, customer and partners have efficiency, simplicity, insights, and transparency into repurchasing and upselling.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/sap-teched</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-for-me</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-store</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Buying and Selling Renewable Energy Enables Communities across Europe to Become More Independent and Sustainable]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/09/exnaton-buying-and-selling-renewable-energy</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/09/exnaton-buying-and-selling-renewable-energy</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Thanks to an innovative solution developed by Exnaton, you can take your surplus solar energy to the market. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_19c8daa63aba95e847020c46340b735287f3308a9.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_19c8daa63aba95e847020c46340b735287f3308a9.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_19c8daa63aba95e847020c46340b735287f3308a9.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Buying and Selling Renewable Energy Enables Communities across Europe to Become More Independent and Sustainable" src="./media_19c8daa63aba95e847020c46340b735287f3308a9.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="buying-and-selling-renewable-energy-enables-communities-across-europe-to-become-more-independent-and-sustainable">Buying and Selling Renewable Energy Enables Communities across Europe to Become More Independent and Sustainable</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Going to market is an age-old activity when it comes to buying and selling goods – from cash crops to cattle, everything under the sun has been traded in some form or another. Now, you can even take your surplus solar energy to the market, thanks to an innovative solution developed by a team of young Swiss entrepreneurs.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“There is no life on earth without the sun, and it’s there for everyone,” said Anselma Wörner, COO and one of the three cofounders of Exnaton, a Swiss company that develops software for communities trading renewable energy in local neighborhoods.</p>
  <p>Wörner was explaining how her company created a smart energy system at the recent <a href="https://tacinsights.eventsair.com/international-sap-conference-for-utilities-2022/conference-brochure">International Conference for Utilities, presented by SAP and TAC Events</a> in Munich, Germany. “We have a new generation of prosumers – people who consume and produce their own energy – who are using new connected technologies and renewable power like solar to exchange energy through the grid.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="become-a-sustainable-intelligent-enterprise-with-sap-solutions">Become a sustainable, intelligent enterprise with SAP solutions</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/sustainability.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="sun-powered">Sun Powered</h2>
  <p>Humans have always depended on the sun for light, heat, and food, and its all-encompassing power has influenced cultures and religions around the world. Although advances in technology have decreased our dependence, the importance of solar energy in our efforts to reduce our carbon footprint is a reminder that we still depend on it for survival. That’s why the cofounders picked the name <a href="https://www.exnaton.com/about-us">Exnaton</a> for their enterprise. Looking for a word that connects “energy” and “exchange,” they hit upon the Egyptian pharaoh Akhenaten (pronounced Echnaton) who raised the status of the sun above that of all other gods and created an early monotheism that briefly became a state religion.</p>
  <p>The goal of Exnaton is to help integrate prosumers into the grid. Currently, the legal framework is very complex, and there is no clear ROI for them. There are no feed-in tariffs or policy mechanisms designed to accelerate investment in renewable energy technologies by offering long-term contracts to renewable energy producers.</p>
  <p>“At the moment, there is no value for the community, and we want to change that,” said Wörner, who is responsible for fundraising, data science, and recruiting at Exnaton. “What most people don’t realize is that renewable energy is not always produced when it’s needed most. So, when it is available, prosumers should be able to sell their energy directly.”</p>
  <p>People who own solar panels could actually sell a lot of energy to other households, if only they had the means. Wörner and her team believe it should be as easy to sell to other consumers as it is to sell any other products on the market. “Prosumers are faced with fragmented solutions, complex regulations, and frustrating user experiences. What they need are simple solutions, trusted local providers, and proactive community and user groups,” she explained.</p>
  <h2 id="community-centric">Community Centric</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="thrive-in-a-time-of-energy-transition-with-utilities-management-systems-that-support-a-sustainable-future">Thrive in a time of energy transition with utilities management systems that support a sustainable future</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/energy-utilities.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Enter Exnaton’s EnergyCommunity software add-on for <a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/energy-utilities.html">SAP for Utilities</a> solutions, which won an <a href="https://www.sap.com/idea-place/sap-innovation-awards/submission-details-2022.html?idea_id=2903">SAP Innovation Award</a> in the Partner Paragon category together with Best Practice Consulting (BPC) and is now available on SAP Store. This user-centric extension enables utility companies to empower prosumers to buy and sell energy within their local communities and also track all relevant data.</p>
  <p>Here’s how it works. Any prosumers in the community can sell their solar energy to any consumers in the grid. The EnergyCommunity tracks their energy data and informs them exactly where the energy is coming from and how much CO2 it is generating. The utility company can easily bill these energy exchanges with their regular SAP billing system thanks to the integration offered by Exnaton in working with the SAP system integrator BPC. At the same time, the utility company can sell additional hardware installations to members of the community, making it an attractive option for all parties.</p>
  <p>“The EnergyCommunity makes it easy to exchange energy within the community. Participating in their local community creates a closer bond between people, and the platform provides a new customer channel for the utility company,” said the technology expert, who has a PhD in Information Systems. “At the end of the day, with Exnaton’s energy sharing software-as-a-service platform, energy suppliers can offer their customers more independence.”</p>
  <p>Exnaton is responding to the challenge faced by prosumers who currently have no possibility to sell their extra energy directly on the market and the one faced by utilities companies as they realize they must offer new models as they transition to renewables with a decentralized approach. A number of utility companies are already running the solution in communities across Germany, Austria, Luxemburg, and Switzerland, and the goal is to expand to other European countries where there is a strong regulatory framework. More importantly, the solution enables energy companies to equip their customers for a <a href="/topics/sustainability">sustainable future</a>.</p>
  <h2 id="future-focused">Future Focused</h2>
  <p>Over 733 million people on the planet still don’t have access to affordable, sustainable energy, which is why providing energy is goal seven on the list of the <a href="https://sdgs.un.org/goals">UN Sustainable Development Goals</a>. For Exnaton, goal seven is its core business, but at the same time, it is equally committed to goal 11, developing sustainable cities and communities; goal 12, enabling responsible production and consumption; and goal 13, taking urgent action to combat climate change and its impact.</p>
  <p>The good news, according to the recent <a href="https://ec.europa.eu/commission/presscorner/detail/en/ip_21_5554">State of the Energy Union</a> report, is that renewables overtook fossil fuels as the number one power source in the European Union for the first time in 2020. Renewables generate 38% of electricity, compared to 37% for fossil fuels. Also, at least two million people in the EU are already involved in more than 7,700 energy communities, and engagement is rising. Energy communities have also contributed up to 7% of nationally installed capacities of renewables, estimated at 6.3 GW.</p>
  <p>For Wörner and the team at Exnaton, producing energy where it is consumed decreases the dependence of the region on imported resources. Energy from the sun is practically limitless, and it more than covers the entire demand of the planet. With advances in technology and solutions like the EnergyCommunity, households and small businesses benefit from electricity powered by the sun, making renewable energy accessible and cost effective. What could be more natural, sensible, or sustainable?</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em><a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2022/08/31/buying-and-selling-their-own-renewable-energy-makes-prosumers--more-independent-and-sustainable/?sh=7aa6082d492f">This article was first published on forbes.com</a>.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/renewable-energy</category>
            <category>sap-award/sap-innovation-awards</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-store</category>
            <category>news-tag/un-sdgs</category>
            <category>industry/utilities</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A DIY Solution for Building Complex Digital Forms on SAP Store]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/09/mirata-diy-solution-complex-digital-forms-sap-store</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/09/mirata-diy-solution-complex-digital-forms-sap-store</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Available on SAP Store, Mirata Digital Forms lets business users build forms to meet their workflow needs while IT to manages data governance.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-store</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Shippeo's Supply Chain Visibility Solution Moving Fast on SAP Store]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/shippeo-supply-chain-visibility-sap-store</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/shippeo-supply-chain-visibility-sap-store</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Shippeo is a European specialist in real-time transportation visibility. Learn how working with SAP helped their journey.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/travel-transportation</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-store</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Coveo Search and Recommendation Quickly Finds Relevance on SAP Store]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/coveo-search-and-recommendation-sap-store</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/coveo-search-and-recommendation-sap-store</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Coveo helps online buyers easily and quickly find what they’re looking for—and what they might be looking for. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-commerce</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-store</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Signavio and LeanIX Bring Process Excellence and Enterprise Architecture Closer Together]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/06/sap-signavio-leanix-process-excellence-enterprise-architecture</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/06/sap-signavio-leanix-process-excellence-enterprise-architecture</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Signavio and LeanIX bring together process excellence and enterprise architecture management, connecting IT and business leaders.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/business-process-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-endorsed-apps</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-signavio</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-store</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Stratesys U-Verify: Intelligent Document Verification on SAP Store]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/06/stratesys-u-verify-intelligent-document-verification</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/06/stratesys-u-verify-intelligent-document-verification</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Available on SAP Store, Stratesys U-Verify for SAP Fieldglass validates compliance with encryption and security. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-digital-commerce</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-store</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Graham Construction Builds Intelligent Enterprise with SAP]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/06/graham-construction-builds-intelligent-enterprise-with-sap</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/06/graham-construction-builds-intelligent-enterprise-with-sap</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Graham Construction is applying ETM.next, an industry cloud solution from SAP and BearingPoint, to centralize equipment inventory management.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-store</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Updates Pricing Structure of SAP Store to Make It Easier for Partners to Build and Commercialize Solutions for SAP Customers]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/sap-updates-pricing-structure-of-sap-store</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/sap-updates-pricing-structure-of-sap-store</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Changes to the pricing structure on SAP Store will make it as easier for partners to make the most of cloud-based software.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-partneredge</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-partneredge-build</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-store</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Will the Great Reshuffle Incentivize Employers to Reckon with AI?]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/will-great-reshuffle-incentivize-employers-to-reckon-with-ai</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/will-great-reshuffle-incentivize-employers-to-reckon-with-ai</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[AI innovations enable HR teams to deliver a new level of experience to transform internal mobility and talent attraction. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/recruiting</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-store</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-opportunity-marketplace</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Forter Trust Platform: On the Right Side of Digital Commerce]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/04/forter-trust-platform-digital-commerce</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/04/forter-trust-platform-digital-commerce</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[To combat fraud, the Forter Trust Platform recognizes shoppers through their data profile and authenticates them quickly and automatically.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1452c9c8db651a795c453d665f6511e78d518a805.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1452c9c8db651a795c453d665f6511e78d518a805.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1452c9c8db651a795c453d665f6511e78d518a805.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Forter Trust Platform: On the Right Side of Digital Commerce" src="./media_1452c9c8db651a795c453d665f6511e78d518a805.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="forter-trust-platform-on-the-right-side-of-digital-commerce">Forter Trust Platform: On the Right Side of Digital Commerce</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>If your organization has a stake in preventing fraud across your digital commerce operations, I’ll venture to say that you want Michael Reitblat and his team at Forter on your side.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As co-founder of the preeminent fraud-detection platform on the market – now available on <a href="https://store.sap.com/dcp/en/product/display-0000042467_live_v1/Forter%20Fraud%20Protection">SAP Store</a> – Reitblat told me that he has long experience in the “bad guy space,” building a successful career around staying ahead of bad actors. That means he’s the good guy for those making an honest living selling products and services online, and for buyers and shoppers making purchases digitally.</p>
  <p>Known as “The Trust Platform” for digital commerce, Forter doesn’t focus on keeping people out, rather on creating a seamless customer experience for trusted shoppers. How is this done? Machine learning and automated decisioning. Built upon a data set of billions of online identities, the Forter platform provides accurate decisions on whether the end shopper is who they say they are instantly. This ability to provide real-time decisions also streamlines merchant operations, eliminating any dependence on manual transaction reviews. That’s the key to understanding the value of this great app.</p>
  <p>The truth is that both online consumers and merchants are victimized by sophisticated, well-organized fraud networks, Reitblat explained, stealing and selling data in a chain of hard-to-detect transactions. To counteract that, merchants can inadvertently block shoppers who most need to purchase online because they fit the “wrong profile” – living in a country known for a high preponderance of fraudsters, for example. Someone might live a long distance from a physical retailer and be unable to buy essential items online, through no fault of their own. “We are here to give those buyers access, and that is a great source of pride,” he remarked. Further, if a consumer faces hurdles to online purchasing because of clumsy verification processes, they’ll just shop somewhere else. It is therefore crucial to eliminate false declines and reduce friction throughout the purchase journey.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-the-forter-trust-platform">Learn more about the Forter Trust Platform</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://store.sap.com/dcp/en/product/display-0000042467_live_v1/Forter%20Trust%20Platform%20for%20Digital%20Commerce">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="foiling-scams-through-a-circle-of-trust">Foiling Scams through a Circle of Trust</h2>
  <p>It’s somewhat ironic that the best way to thwart fraud is to operate in an environment of trust. In fact, trust among competitors is at the heart of Forter Fraud Protection. Criminals will target one type of company – a shoe manufacturer, for example – and, when detected, move on to exploit the next, giving them the advantage. “We reverse that asymmetry,” Reitblat said. “If you attack one of our customers, the others are immunized, thanks to an aggregated global network of data. They would never share their data with each other, but they are happy to do it through us.” Simply put, the Forter solution is built to recognize people through their data profile and authenticate them quickly and automatically.</p>
  <p>I asked Reitblat about credit card protection. When a consumer reports a fraudulent charge, he replied, the onus is on the retailer, who is left with the expense and is subject to fines or suspension by the credit card issuers if there are too many instances. I was also curious about how Forter stays in front of the fraudsters. Let’s just say that Reitblat, who grew up in Israel and was once a member of the intelligence community there, has his people. “Detecting security breaches, theft, the dark economy – it’s the same world,” he said. “We have an active research team staying on top of these constantly evolving threats.”</p>
  <h2 id="strength-in-numbers">Strength in Numbers</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="explore-all-that-sap-store-has-to-offer">Explore all that SAP Store has to offer</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="http://store.sap.com/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Reitblat co-founded Forter after working with a cybersecurity company that went through an acquisition – a crushing blow for him. Fortunately, he had reunited with an old high school friend from Jerusalem who also recognized that online commerce was about to take off. “In 2013, we still had to convince investors of the need for an authentication capability, and that it had to be fully automated or otherwise would require too many people to be scalable.” That resistance changed quickly, and today Forter is larger than many of its major customers, processing more than US$250 billion in transaction value per year and employing 500 professionals around the world. The solution is deployed in more than 30 countries.</p>
  <p>The <a href="http://news.sap.com/tags/covid-19">events of the past two years</a> have resulted in a burst of demand that Reitblat and his partner could not have foreseen. Besides the explosion in online shopping, purchasing behavior and customer demographics across industries changed. New retail features appeared, like curbside pickup, buy online/pick up in store (BOPIS), and contactless check-in and check-out in the hospitality industry. New online buyers included senior citizens, students, and those in advancing geographies who had never transacted online before. Additionally, with the sudden surge of orders to be delivered to alternate addresses – holiday gifts, for example, or people purchasing for family members – e-commerce systems had an extra challenge in verifying legitimacy. That process was less complex for Forter customers because its customers were already authenticated in the system.</p>
  <p>Forter Fraud Protection is tightly integrated with SAP Commerce Cloud. Laura Jorgens, director of Partnerships for Forter, acknowledged SAP partner <a href="https://netconomy.net/">Netconomy</a> for its “incredible support” in building out the integration. “Working with SAP and Netconomy feels like one ecosystem pulling together,” she said. “Hats off to the SAP partnership organization.” With the inclusion of Forter’s solution on SAP Store, she added, “SAP has become one of Forter’s most important partners.”</p>
  <p>Why not see for yourself how <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Tp3RHdk5Yic">Forter Trust Platform</a> works? The solution was just <a href="https://store.sap.com/dcp/en/news-blogs/blogs/celebrating-the-20th-year-of-sap-pinnacle-awards-and-partner-innovations-on-sap-store">named</a> an SAP Pinnacle Award finalist in the New App of the Year on SAP Store category. It’s available for download on <a href="https://store.sap.com/dcp/en/product/display-0000042467_live_v1/Forter%20Fraud%20Protection">SAP Store</a>. Or download the SAP and Forter <a href="https://l.forter.com/hubfs/forter-SAP-brochure.pdf">overview brochure</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Rajiv Nema is senior director of SAP Store Partner Solutions.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/financial-management</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/cybersecurity</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-commerce</category>
            <category>news-tag/e-commerce</category>
            <category>product/sap-commerce-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-digital-commerce</category>
            <category>sap-award/sap-pinnacle-awards</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-store</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sustainable AI Turns Small Data into Huge Results for Manufacturers and Researchers]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/04/sustainable-sparse-modeling-ai-manufacturers-researchers</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/04/sustainable-sparse-modeling-ai-manufacturers-researchers</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Sparse modeling AI is the tech of choice for manufacturers and researchers who demand speed, sustainability, and explainability. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/electric-vehicles</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/research-development</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-store</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-io</category>
            <category>news-tag/startups</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Great Resignation Compels Companies to Make a Great First Impression]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/04/great-resignation-companies-first-impression</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/04/great-resignation-companies-first-impression</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The Great Resignation left thousands of companies with job openings to fill. When competing for top talent, a smoother hiring process helps.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/future-of-work</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>news-tag/recruiting</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-store</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Without More Flexible Hours and Locations, 54% of Workers to Quit]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/02/without-flexibility-54-percent-to-quit</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/02/without-flexibility-54-percent-to-quit</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Global talent marketplaces help business and HR leaders head off tech worker shortages and power massive growth from digitalization.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1de65b4f8c903741801eae2d7b08e181383eefa42.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1de65b4f8c903741801eae2d7b08e181383eefa42.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1de65b4f8c903741801eae2d7b08e181383eefa42.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Without More Flexible Hours and Locations, 54% of Workers to Quit" src="./media_1de65b4f8c903741801eae2d7b08e181383eefa42.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="without-more-flexible-hours-and-locations-54-of-workers-to-quit">Without More Flexible Hours and Locations, 54% of Workers to Quit</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>On the cusp of economic growth fueled by a huge wave of digitalization, organizations in Australia and New Zealand (ANZ) are transforming talent management strategies to find the tech workers they need.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>A recent EY study found that nine out of 10 respondents worldwide, including workers from ANZ, wanted flexibility in their working hours and location. Fifty-four percent of employees were prepared to quit if they weren’t offered some form of flexibility. According to Thomas Barlow, head of SAP Fieldglass Centre of Excellence, Australia and New Zealand, the talent challenge is acute when it comes to tech employees.</p>
  <p>“Technology permeates every part of an organization, requiring people with new skills in areas like data science, artificial intelligence (AI), machine learning, blockchain, robotics, and the Internet of Things (IoT). Organizations need to build a global workforce that meets digitalized business demands,” said Barlow. “Workers with specialized expertise typically operate in a highly flexible, agile way. They’re likelier to be more mobile, in charge of managing their own learning experiences and careers. They also may not be located nearby.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="put-employees-at-the-heart-of-everything-you-do-with-sap-successfactors-software">Put employees at the heart of everything you do with SAP SuccessFactors software</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="complete-talent-pool-data-creates-business-resilience">Complete Talent Pool Data Creates Business Resilience</h2>
  <p>The latest data from the <a href="https://www.abs.gov.au/">Australian Bureau of Statistics</a> revealed how <a href="/covid-19">pandemic</a> lockdowns have accelerated the skills shortage. <a href="https://www.businessinsider.com.au/australia-skills-shortage-wage-growth-2021-6">Business Insider Australia</a> reported one in four Australian businesses were struggling to find suitable staff to fill job vacancies. In a recent COVID-19 Resilience Ranking from <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/graphics/covid-resilience-ranking/">Bloomberg</a>, Australia dropped 21 points compared to over 50 other major economies worldwide. To meet this workforce challenge, leaders are turning to connected data.</p>
  <p>“As companies build more flexible, cross-border workforces, they need full transparency of all employees, including permanent and external workers,” said Barlow. “With complete workforce data, companies are better prepared to identify and deploy the right people with the right skills to support growth forecasts, or pivot quickly in case of unexpected disruptions like the pandemic.”</p>
  <p>AI-based talent pools like <a href="https://store.sap.com/dcp/en/product/display-0000056483_live_v1">WillHire</a> have emerged to help organizations quickly match open positions with pre-qualified candidates from the global external labor pool. Integrated with <a href="https://www.fieldglass.com/">SAP Fieldglass solutions</a> and available on <a href="https://store.sap.com/dcp/en/">SAP Store</a>, WillHire curates emerging talent who have the niche skills that support digital transformation.</p>
  <h2 id="global-people-strategy-is-core-to-business-execution">Global People Strategy Is Core to Business Execution</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="five-workplace-norms-innovative-hxm-leaders-are-replacing-right-now">Five Workplace Norms Innovative HXM Leaders Are Replacing Right Now</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/11/five-workplace-norms-innovative-hxm-leaders-are-replacing">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Historical talent strategies distinguished between permanent full-time employees and external workers who were typically hired to pitch in as a short-term business fix. With the advent of global marketplaces, talent strategies have transformed to flex with changing business demands.</p>
  <p>“Companies need to embrace fluidity, looking at talent from the perspective of business results, as opposed to permanent versus contract workers,” said Marc Havercroft, global chief customer officer at SAP SuccessFactors. “For example, organizations using <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm.html">SAP SuccessFactors solutions</a> and SAP Fieldglass solutions can easily see how many people work for the company irrespective of an end date on their contract. Data reveals where people are, what skills they have, and their work quality over time. Organizations can quickly identify gaps and find the additional specialists with the latest skills anywhere in the world.”</p>
  <p>One SAP customer, an established ANZ-based financial services organization, needed to digitally transform to attract the next generation of customers. Using both SAP SuccessFactors and SAP Fieldglass solutions, leaders sourced external tech experts to build digital services, pairing them with existing employees who shared their business knowledge while gaining new skills.</p>
  <p>At the other end of the spectrum, a native digital banking startup in ANZ relied on both SAP solutions to help guide talent investments in business specialists with go-to-market and customer upselling and engagement capabilities. These experts rounded out the existing team’s tech-centric skills.</p>
  <h2 id="employee-experience-attracts-global-talent-pool">Employee Experience Attracts Global Talent Pool</h2>
  <p>The same EY study found that worldwide, 72% of respondents believed remotely working would likely have a negative impact on their career opportunities. That percentage was higher (82%) among employees in Asia-Pacific. With greater visibility across the entire workforce, companies can create a strong employee experience in a hybrid ‘work-from-anywhere’ world.</p>
  <p>“Full transparency into an organization’s workforce capabilities and recruitment needs allows leaders to adopt a continuous learning culture with benefits to the business and employees,” said Havercroft. “People want to learn, making their work enjoyable and career secure. They want to be valued globally for their skills and knowledge, which is probably the biggest benefit of a global talent marketplace.”</p>
  <p>Business resiliency demands new talent management strategies to match recruitment programs with forecasted growth opportunities, factoring in skills and roles that might not exist yet but are surely on the horizon. For example, SAP’s recent acquisition of <a href="/2021/08/sap-acquires-swooptalent-intellectual-property-to-boost-talent-data-intelligence">SwoopTalent’s IP</a>, an AI-based talent data platform, will allow companies to explore ‘what-if’ scenarios, combining real-world total workforce data to improve ROI on talent investments and other decisions as businesses evolve. Massive growth from digitalization is all well and good. Just make sure you have the business and tech experts on hand to power it.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Follow me @smgaler.</em><br><em>This also appeared on <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2021/10/05/54-percent-of-workers-plan-to-quit-without-more-flexible-hours-and-locations/?sh=1148b4b83bab">SAP BrandVoice on Forbes.</a></em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-anz</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-store</category>
            <category>news-tag/talent-acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Road to Fix the Massive Truck Driver Shortage Is Paved with Data]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/01/road-to-fix-truck-driver-shortage-is-paved-with-data</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/01/road-to-fix-truck-driver-shortage-is-paved-with-data</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Wise Systems offers an AI-based delivery management platform, forging the connection between last-mile delivery and the customer experience.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_143e6fd42f76b12c65e80c5efb16b1e49080d6b24.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_143e6fd42f76b12c65e80c5efb16b1e49080d6b24.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_143e6fd42f76b12c65e80c5efb16b1e49080d6b24.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="The Road to Fix the Massive Truck Driver Shortage Is Paved with Data" src="./media_143e6fd42f76b12c65e80c5efb16b1e49080d6b24.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="the-road-to-fix-the-massive-truck-driver-shortage-is-paved-with-data">The Road to Fix the Massive Truck Driver Shortage Is Paved with Data</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Hidden in the furor about disrupted supply chains is how the experience of the drivers delivering all those goods directly impacts the customer experience. That’s where <a href="https://www.wisesystems.com/">Wise Systems</a> comes in, offering an artificial intelligence (AI)-based delivery management platform that originated at the Media Lab at MIT, when three of the company’s co-founders responded to a professor’s challenge to find the best way to change one billion lives with data.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“The free flow of goods is the lifeblood of communities,” said Allison Parker, vice president of Marketing at Wise Systems. “We decided to apply machine learning to real-time data that captures what’s happening on the ground so organizations can better plan and continuously improve every last-mile route and delivery. Drivers have an intuitive, easier experience managing their schedule directly from their mobile devices, while fleet managers have up-to-the-minute plan tracking for resource allocation and utilization.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-how-sapio-foundries-support-b2b-technology-startups-worldwide">Learn more about how SAP.iO Foundries support B2B technology startups worldwide</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://sap.io/foundries/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="data-intelligence-drives-seamless-delivery-experience">Data Intelligence Drives Seamless Delivery Experience</h2>
  <p>Fast forward to a post-pandemic world facing an 80,000 <a href="https://www.trucking.org/news-insights/ata-chief-economist-pegs-driver-shortage-historic-high">driver shortage</a> in the U.S. alone, and Wise Systems is leaving legacy “dispatch and routing” systems in the dust. Clients in the food and beverage industry, as well as courier companies, rely on Wise Systems to synthesize orders by product volume, location, and time frames into delivery stops for truck fleets and other vehicles. Fleet managers, dispatchers, and drivers can make tweaks, factoring in their knowledge, including customer preferences. The system monitors traffic and weather conditions in real time, alerting dispatchers to potential risks that could jeopardize scheduled deliveries.</p>
  <p>“Automating the routing process for the perfect, seamless experience requires intelligence up front, along with ongoing monitoring as each day unfolds,” said Parker. “Drivers appreciate having full visibility into all the data about every delivery stop, including the number of products they’re expected to deliver. All they need to do is swipe in and out when they arrive and leave. The system can also record proof of delivery. They can also leave notes for themselves or future drivers on our secure app, such as a passcode for a loading dock.”</p>
  <h2 id="machine-learning-perfectly-choreographs-route-plans">Machine Learning Perfectly Choreographs Route Plans</h2>
  <p>Contrary to misconceptions, behind the wheel is not necessarily where drivers spend the bulk of their time. It’s the on-site visits that eat up the greatest number of minutes during the course of a day. The machine learning models in Wise Systems calculate route plans based on historical and real-time data. Meantime, delivery companies can set delivery status notifications as well, allowing clients to receive updates at specified intervals.</p>
  <p>“The system can more accurately predict service times, taking into account the time it takes to complete a stop and factoring in the preferences of the retailer, hotel, medical institution, or other type of client,” said Parker. “The goal is route planning efficiency combined with customer service so people receive their inventory when and where they expect it; this is the number one priority of our clients.”</p>
  <p>From a fleet management perspective, machine learning also helps keep vehicles fully utilized to maximum capacity for both route efficiencies and more sustainable business. One global food and beverage client reduced late deliveries by 80, decreasing fleet mileage by up to 15%. On-time deliveries can contribute to a company’s carbon reduction goals as it reduces redeliveries.</p>
  <h2 id="capturing-performance-metrics-with-data-analytics">Capturing Performance Metrics with Data Analytics</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-s4hana-a-complete-intelligent-erp-system-with-embedded-ai-and-machine-learning">SAP S/4HANA: A complete, intelligent ERP system with embedded AI and machine learning</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/s4hana-erp.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Wise Systems also serves up analytics that managers and drivers find valuable. Fleet managers can immediately see everything from inventory volumes on the road and delivered, to driver times at any point in the workday. They can benchmark that data against the company’s performance metrics that typically vary depending on the type of vehicle and amount of goods. They can make fleet size adjustments to better meet vehicle utilization and sustainable business targets. Some clients have increased their fleet utilization on average by 20 percentage points. Data helps individual drivers see where they stand too, as many are compensated with performance premiums for on-time deliveries.</p>
  <h2 id="sapio-expands-market-opportunities">SAP.iO Expands Market Opportunities</h2>
  <p>When the Wise Systems team participated in the <a href="/covid-19">COVID-19</a> recovery cohort of <a href="https://sap.io/ny-demo-day-2021/">SAP.iO Foundry New York City</a>, they discovered new market opportunities.</p>
  <p>“We learned so much about customer needs from SAP experts,” said Parker. “Integrating information from Wise Systems with <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/s4hana-erp.html">SAP S/4HANA</a> is a great example of how companies are using connected data between ERP systems, such as order and warehouse management, finance, and last-mile logistics operations and back, to become intelligent enterprises.”</p>
  <p>Wise Systems is available on <a href="https://store.sap.com/dcp/en/product/display-0000059776_live_v1">SAP Store</a>.</p>
  <h2 id="modern-experience-can-help-solve-the-driver-shortage">Modern Experience Can Help Solve the Driver Shortage</h2>
  <p>Recruiting and retaining drivers for last-mile delivery is just one segment of the disrupted supply chain, but it’s a big one. Anything organizations can do to improve the quality of their day-to-day experience matters. As companies modernize the systems that power vast supply chains, don’t leave the truck driver’s experience behind.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Follow me @smgaler.</em><br><em><a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2021/12/14/the-road-to-fix-the-massive-truck-driver-shortage-is-paved-with-data/?sh=6790faf338e4">This blog also appeared on SAP BrandVoice on Forbes.</a></em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>industry/travel-transportation</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-store</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-io</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Industry Cloud: Advancing Business Transformation for a Changing World]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/01/industry-cloud-solutions-business-transformation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/01/industry-cloud-solutions-business-transformation</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP makes industry cloud solutions available for organizations to optimize, extend, and transform their core business processes.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1757da8a7acfbe5a5106c2cdd6ac202a6380443f0.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1757da8a7acfbe5a5106c2cdd6ac202a6380443f0.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1757da8a7acfbe5a5106c2cdd6ac202a6380443f0.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Industry Cloud: Advancing Business Transformation for a Changing World" src="./media_1757da8a7acfbe5a5106c2cdd6ac202a6380443f0.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="industry-cloud-advancing-business-transformation-for-a-changing-world">Industry Cloud: Advancing Business Transformation for a Changing World</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Justifiably proud of their digital accomplishments, most companies still suffer from a false sense of digital capabilities. Their increasing attention on evolving customer experiences, product and service innovations, production efficiencies, and competitive advantages leaves little room for driving much needed change in core operations, such as facility management or payroll processing.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>But the world is changing, and keeping one foot on the gas pedal for higher visibility projects while pumping the brakes with the other foot for back-office changes is not enough to keep up. Businesses must rapidly move both aspects of their digital strategies in unison to drive significant progress so that competitors are challenged to keep pace.</p>
  <p>With <a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/industry-cloud.html?source=social-global-news-blog-IEumbrella-2021-industrycloud">industry cloud solutions</a>, organizations can achieve this balance.</p>
  <h2 id="modernizing-industries-to-meet-unique-expectations">Modernizing Industries to Meet Unique Expectations</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="shop-industry-cloud-solutions-on-sap-store">Shop industry cloud solutions on SAP Store</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://store.sap.com/dcp/en/industry-cloud">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP makes industry cloud solutions easier to discover, subscribe to, and use, offering customers access to unified user experiences, familiar design paradigms, and plug-and-play integrations to reinvent themselves and their markets simultaneously. Organizations from every industry can then deploy specialized solutions to optimize, extend, and transform their core business processes by digitalizing and automating operations across their business.</p>
  <p>For example, <strong>utilities</strong> companies are shifting operations to provide more <a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2021/06/2abac107-e87d-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html?source=social-global-news-blog-IEumbrella-2021-industrycloud">sustainable and renewable energy</a> in response to growing demand for decarbonization and decentralization. Industry cloud solutions can be used to combine Big Data-enabled energy data management for millions of end devices on a cloud-based, open platform with smart, industry-specific analytics and integration to support energy-related core processes.</p>
  <p>Meanwhile, <strong>logistics service providers</strong> can collect various types of information from their vehicle fleets with a <a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2021/06/e0f83fc4-f47d-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html?source=social-global-news-blog-IEumbrella-2021-industrycloud">digital vehicle hub</a> enabled by an asset network. By consolidating multiple data sources into a single network-based cloud platform, they can rapidly ramp up new business models, monetize vehicle information across customer channels, and enable collaboration and innovation with third-party participants.</p>
  <p><strong>Consumer products companies</strong> also have access to an intelligent virtual assistant that streamlines the <a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2021/09/e2ec4787-f77d-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html?source=social-global-news-blog-IEumbrella-2021-industrycloud">trade claims management</a> process and eliminates the need for manual matching and auditing. The solution leverages embedded machine learning to automate steps, reduce errors, and help avoid disputes. Organizations can then aggregate and enrich market activity in real time, accelerate balance sheet reconciliation with greater accuracy, lower the cost per claim, and enhance workflow productivity — all while establishing stronger customer relationships.</p>
  <p>With an industry cloud solution, <strong>retailers</strong> can improve their <a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2021/10/1cb575ce-fd7d-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html?source=social-global-news-blog-IEumbrella-2021-industrycloud">intelligent returns management</a> processes through embedded machine learning models and an analytics engine that accelerate and ease profitable decision-making. The solution turns the challenges of product returns into opportunities that improve customer retention and brand connection with a fluid returns experience for consumers, while increasing productivity and lowering processing costs across sales channels.</p>
  <p>Retailers can also benefit from an <a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2021/11/4e536978-087e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html?source=social-global-news-blog-IEumbrella-2021-industrycloud">order management foundation</a> developed to centralize the monitoring, analysis, and management of their omnichannel order processes. By optimizing nodes in their network — such as distribution centers, stores, dark stores, and third-party drop shipping — they can reduce costs, improve agility, and increase brand satisfaction by meeting their customer promises as expected.</p>
  <p>Industry cloud solutions can even enable emerging industries, such as <strong>automotive original equipment manufacturers (</strong> OEMs) installing and operating residential and commercial charging stations for electric vehicles. An <a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2021/11/509d5249-077e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html?source=social-global-news-blog-IEumbrella-2021-industrycloud">e-mobility</a> solution integrates end-to-end billing processes with one platform to lower energy costs and avoid expensive grid-connection expenditure through connections to energy service providers. And for their customers, the cost of improving their carbon footprint and impact on the planet becomes more affordable.</p>
  <h2 id="competing-as-an-ecosystem-forged-by-innovation">Competing as an Ecosystem Forged by Innovation</h2>
  <p>Business transformation begins with an idea – whether fixing a problem or discovering and creating new value. But eventually, companies translate ideas differently to address their industry’s unique market dynamics, customer demands, public expectations, and regulatory pressures.</p>
  <p>For SAP customers, the answer to turning their ideas into meaningful technologies, products, services, business models, or people experiences is an industry cloud solution designed to meet their unique reality. Doing so offers the scale, access, and support they need to adapt to emerging dynamics continuously and rapidly, without sacrificing process efficiency or disrupting their other innovation efforts.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="augment-your-intelligent-enterprise-with-industry-cloud-solutions">Augment your intelligent enterprise with industry cloud solutions</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/industry-cloud.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="visit-the-sap-store-site-to-explore-and-access-the-latest-industry-cloud-solutions-from-sap">Visit the <a href="https://store.sap.com/dcp/en/product/display-0000008655_live_v1?source=social-global-news-blog-IEumbrella-2021-industrycloud">SAP Store</a> site to explore and access the latest industry cloud solutions from SAP.</h3>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Joe Pacor is senior director of Industries Marketing at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/automotive</category>
            <category>industry/consumer-goods-cpg</category>
            <category>news-tag/electric-vehicles</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-store</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bots Meet Humans for Top-Notch Customer Service with CommBox Platform]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/bots-meet-humans-top-notch-customer-service-commbox</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/bots-meet-humans-top-notch-customer-service-commbox</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The CommBox platform, available on SAP Store, succeeds in bridging the gap between automated processes and human contact. Learn more!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>product/sap-sales-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-store</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>