<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/industry/travel-transportation/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Named a Leader in the 2024 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Transportation Management Systems]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-named-a-leader-2024-gartner-magic-quadrant-transportation-management-systems</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-named-a-leader-2024-gartner-magic-quadrant-transportation-management-systems</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[For the 10th consecutive year, SAP has been named as a Leader in the 2024 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Transportation Management Systems.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_129328166e826d3a52e6b9854f483cc4a5f36fd9a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_129328166e826d3a52e6b9854f483cc4a5f36fd9a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_129328166e826d3a52e6b9854f483cc4a5f36fd9a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Named a Leader in the 2024 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Transportation Management Systems" src="./media_129328166e826d3a52e6b9854f483cc4a5f36fd9a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-named-a-leader-in-the-2024-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-transportation-management-systems">SAP Named a Leader in the 2024 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Transportation Management Systems</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>For the 10th consecutive year, SAP has been named as a Leader in the 2024 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Transportation Management Systems.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP is positioned in the Leaders Quadrant based on our Ability to Execute and for the Completeness of our Vision.</p>
  <p>We believe that this recognition confirms our strategy in Logistics, which is based on three pillars:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Connecting every process and providing synchronized logistics execution to support highly efficient and fast paced fulfillment cycles</li>
    <li>Collaborating with a single network of carriers, digital forwarders, and visibility providers to spot risks and avoid disruptions and thereby provide best-in-class delivery experience</li>
    <li>Contextualizing every decision, leveraging artificial intelligence (<a href="/topics/artificial-intelligence">AI</a>) and machine learning to optimize operations and to provide business insights</li>
  </ul>
  <p>SAP Transportation Management is an integral part of the overall SAP strategy and gives companies the ability to manage their end-to-end transportation processes from procurement through planning and execution to freight settlement with analytics to support each step.</p>
  <p>We continue to innovate in SAP Transportation Management based on our market analysis and even more importantly based on feedback from our global install base and ecosystem. Recent innovations include advancements in areas like sustainability, planning and optimization, supply chain execution, and generative AI.</p>
  <p>SAP Transportation Management and SAP Business Network for Logistics enable logistics partners to collaborate with each other and provide visibility to all stakeholders throughout the shipment lifecycle and help manage risks as they arise through intelligent insights. We continue to grow SAP Business Network, adding more carriers and additional networks to provide expanded coverage around the world and across all transportation modes.</p>
  <p>As more customers evaluate SAP Transportation Management, we continue to strategically expand our partner network to ensure our customers have access to an ecosystem that supports their operations no matter where they are in the world or how they move their freight. Our global partner network made up of systems integrators, business consultants, and technology providers help our customers manage their transportation transformations, whether they be system replacements, upgrades, greenfield deployments, or part of larger enterprise transformations.</p>
  <p>“Our customers use SAP Transportation Management and SAP Business Network for Logistics to manage transportation operations in more than 20 industries and in every corner of the world,” said Till Dengel, global head of Logistics and Manufacturing Product Marketing at SAP. “Because we look at logistics holistically, clients can confidently confirm their orders, knowing that fulfillment can be executed as promised, since ERP, warehousing, and transportation are always in sync.”</p>
  <p>“Adopting logistics solutions from SAP across our facilities in all our markets allowed us to optimize freight transportation,” said Carlo Noè, Global Process and Applications Manager for Trade, Transport, and Logistics Division at Hitachi Energy Ltd. “We can interact with our stakeholders and carriers in a digital way, helping us manage supply chain risk, enhance agility, and build supply chain resilience.”</p>
  <p>For more details on the latest Gartner Magic Quadrant for TMS <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/transportation-logistics.html?campaigncode=CRM-YD24-DSC-2678872&#x26;url_id=magic-quadrant-for-transportation-management-systems&#x26;rc=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.gartner.com%2Freprints%2F%3Fid%3D1-2H3J1JVF%26ct%3D240327%26st%3Dsb">read the Gartner Reprint here</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Bill King is senior product marketing manager for Logistics at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-transportation-management-reduce-complexity-increase-efficiency-and-improve-agility-for-a-more-sustainable-risk-resilient-supply-chain">SAP Transportation Management: Reduce complexity, increase efficiency, and improve agility for a more sustainable, risk-resilient supply chain</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/transportation-logistics.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>GARTNER is a registered trademark and service mark of Gartner, Inc. and/or its affiliates in the U.S. and internationally, MAGIC QUADRANT is a registered trademark of Gartner, Inc. and/or its affiliates and are used herein with permission. All rights reserved.<br><em>Gartner does not endorse any vendor, product or service depicted in its research publications, and does not advise technology users to select only those vendors with the highest ratings or other designation. Gartner research publications consist of the opinions of Gartner’s research organization and should not be construed as statements of fact. Gartner disclaims all warranties, expressed or implied, with respect to this research, including any warranties of merchantability or fitness for a particular purpose.</em></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/travel-transportation</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/magic-quadrant</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-network-for-logistics</category>
            <category>product/sap-transportation-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Addressing the Supply Chain Logistics Challenges Arising from the Events in Baltimore]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/addressing-supply-chain-logistics-port-disruptions</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/addressing-supply-chain-logistics-port-disruptions</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Using technology to react to supply chain port disruptions is not new. Read to learn more about how SAP Business Network can help.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/travel-transportation</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>product/sap-transportation-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cloud-Based Visibility Equips Trading Partners to Counter Supply Chain Disruption]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/cloud-based-business-networks-equip-trading-partners</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/cloud-based-business-networks-equip-trading-partners</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Enterprises rely increasingly on cloud-based business networks to extend visibility, facilitate collaboration, and stay ahead of disruption.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17eccb1dbc9662324e6f79b18766a0335800c285f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17eccb1dbc9662324e6f79b18766a0335800c285f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_17eccb1dbc9662324e6f79b18766a0335800c285f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Cloud-Based Visibility Equips Trading Partners to Counter Supply Chain Disruption" src="./media_17eccb1dbc9662324e6f79b18766a0335800c285f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="cloud-based-visibility-equips-trading-partners-to-counter-supply-chain-disruption">Cloud-Based Visibility Equips Trading Partners to Counter Supply Chain Disruption</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>With geopolitical conflict and climate change roiling global shipping corridors from the <a href="https://www.arabnews.com/node/2463151/business-economy">Suez Canal</a> to <a href="https://www.reuters.com/business/panama-canal-does-not-plan-transit-restrictions-least-until-april-2024-02-07">Panama</a> and <a href="https://apnews.com/article/persian-gulf-oman-strait-hormuz-3a906e909be2ce63c87c1b208ed05baa">elsewhere</a>, enterprises rely increasingly on cloud-based business networks and artificial intelligence (AI) applications to extend visibility, facilitate collaboration, and ensure they stay one step ahead of the looming threat of disruption.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Meanwhile, as legislation to bolster transparency in supply chains <a href="https://www.bundesregierung.de/breg-en/service/archive/supply-chain-act-1872076">takes</a> <a href="https://minister.homeaffairs.gov.au/jasonwood/Pages/modern-slavery-act-delivers-transparency-in-supply-chains.aspx">hold</a> <a href="https://oag.ca.gov/SB657">around</a> <a href="https://laws.justice.gc.ca/eng/acts/F-10.6">the</a> <a href="https://www.consilium.europa.eu/en/press/press-releases/2023/12/14/corporate-sustainability-due-diligence-council-and-parliament-strike-deal-to-protect-environment-and-human-rights">world</a>, the digital platforms through which trading partners carry out interconnected operational processes have become indispensable for managing risk, advancing sustainability objectives, and verifying adherence to ethical business practices – even as volatility in international commerce gathers pace.</p>
  <p>After rebounding from several years of logjammed seaports, idled factories, and quarantined workers, many businesses find that though COVID-19 has receded, disruption stubbornly persists. Yet visibility across all aspects of the supply chain – from sourcing raw materials and managing logistics capacity to securing working capital solutions and managing dispersed physical assets – remains paramount in the quest to ensure business continuity, instill operational resilience, and deepen competitive advantage.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-business-network-powers-transparency-resiliency-and-sustainability">SAP Business Network powers transparency, resiliency, and sustainability</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-network.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>To help provide businesses with the 360-degree visibility and collaborative capabilities they require across complex trading relationships, SAP Business Network can connect people, processes, and systems across multiple enterprises to help digitize transactions, harness data-driven insights, and create transparent, resilient, and sustainable supply chains. Through <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-network/solutions.html#active_tab_item_1602592051931">SAP Business Network for Procurement</a>, trading partners can gain process efficiencies, improve supply assurance, and achieve business process and regulatory compliance by increasing operational transparency. With <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-network/solutions.html#active_tab_item_1602592257238">SAP Business Network Supply Chain Collaboration</a>, companies can achieve supply chain visibility by enabling plan-driven automation, optimizing capacity and inventory, and streamlining workflow. Aided by <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-network/solutions.html#active_tab_item_1602592296240">SAP Business Network for Logistics</a>, shippers and carriers can work together in unison, track and trace goods in transit, and achieve transparency throughout the supply chain by optimizing logistics processes, increasing on-time deliveries, and mitigating third-party risk. Relying on <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-network/solutions.html#active_tab_item_1660146110353">SAP Business Network Asset Collaboration</a>, owners, operators, and service providers can strengthen joint processes and the flow of shared information through a single, consistent version of asset master data to help streamline asset maintenance processes and reduce maintenance costs. With the benefit of <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-network/solutions.html#active_tab_item_1660146142567">SAP Business Network for Finance</a>, trading partners can enhance payment security, free up working capital through early-payment discounts, and leverage access to capital bound up in outstanding receivables.</p>
  <p>By linking together the routine business processes of trading partners, cloud-based networks establish the breadth of data necessary to apply predictive and generative AI applications to yield meaningful insights and outcomes. Through large language models and other forms of machine learning, cloud-based applications create new content with characteristics resembling that which precedes it. With every successive effort, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/spend-management/innovations.html#ai">generative AI</a> sharpens its ability to tailor desired content.</p>
  <p>As the world’s largest platform for business-to-business commerce, SAP Business Network can present an ideal setting for generative AI, in that it helps bring together an extremely large volume of trading partners across hundreds of millions of transactions representing US$5.3 trillion in commerce annually. Later this year, generative AI capabilities in SAP Business Network will be able to help detect errors and present automatic summaries when businesses create invoices. AI will also enable the network to help enrich catalog content and discovery posting responses for suppliers.</p>
  <p>SAP Business Network has accumulated significant structured content over many years to help generate broad operational insights for trading partners. When buyers, suppliers, carriers, and financing solution providers share operational data with each other in real time, the mutual value they create can be exponential rather than additive, enabling all participants in commerce to plan ahead with confidence, continuity, and enduring resilience.</p>
  <p>For further information on SAP Business Network and how we are equipping enterprises large and small with the digital tools needed to counter disruption, visit <a href="https://www.sap.com/businessnetwork">sap.com/businessnetwork</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Jörn Keller is executive vice president and chief product officer of SAP Business Network.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="stay-in-touch-and-follow-sap-news-on-linkedin">Stay in touch and follow SAP News on LinkedIn</h3>
        <p><em><a href="">Join us on LinkedIn</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/asset-management</category>
            <category>industry/travel-transportation</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-network-for-logistics</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Generative AI Takes Employee Experience at Delta Air Lines to New Heights]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/generative-ai-employee-experience-delta</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/generative-ai-employee-experience-delta</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With AI and SAP, Delta Air Lines provides a positive, personalized employee experience that motivates people to go above and beyond.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>industry/travel-transportation</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Concur Unveils New Experiences for Concur Travel]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/new-experiences-for-concur-travel</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/new-experiences-for-concur-travel</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn how SAP is modernizing the Concur Travel booking experience to make booking and expensing travel more productive.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/concur-travel</category>
            <category>industry/travel-transportation</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-concur</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Creating an Agile, Resilient, and Sustainable Logistics Network]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/creating-agile-resilient-sustainable-logistics-network</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/creating-agile-resilient-sustainable-logistics-network</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP's Till Dengel shares how industrial manufacturing businesses can drive an agile, resilient, and sustainable logistics network.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/travel-transportation</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-network-for-logistics</category>
            <category>product/sap-warehouse-robotics</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Majority Feel Business Travel Isn’t Offered Equally to All, SAP Concur Survey Finds]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/06/business-travel-sap-concur-survey</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/06/business-travel-sap-concur-survey</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The SAP Concur Global Business Travel Survey explores challenges facing business travelers today. Here are this year's findings.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/travel-transportation</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-concur</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Named a Leader in the 2023 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Transportation Management Systems]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/2023-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-transportation-management-systems</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/2023-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-transportation-management-systems</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is a Leader in the Gartner Magic Quadrant for Transportation Management Systems based on ability to execute and completeness of vision.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/travel-transportation</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/magic-quadrant</category>
            <category>product/sap-transportation-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Labs India: A Pioneer in Transitioning to Electric Vehicles]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/sap-labs-india-pioneer-transitioning-to-electric-vehicles</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/sap-labs-india-pioneer-transitioning-to-electric-vehicles</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Over the past decade, the transportation team at SAP Labs India implemented various initiatives to encourage employees to use EVs.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/automotive</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-emissions</category>
            <category>news-tag/decarbonization</category>
            <category>news-tag/electric-vehicles</category>
            <category>industry/travel-transportation</category>
            <category>product/sap-e-mobility</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhancing Customer Experience with Risk-Resilient Supply Chains at BSH Home Appliances Group]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/risk-resilient-supply-chains-at-bsh</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/risk-resilient-supply-chains-at-bsh</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[BSH Home Appliances Group chose SAP Integrated Business Planning for Supply Chain and SAP S/4HANA to coordinate business planning.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/travel-transportation</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-digital-supply-chain</category>
            <category>product/sap-integrated-business-planning-for-supply-chain</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Deepening Operational Resilience with SAP Business Network for Logistics]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/01/operational-resilience-sap-business-network-for-logistics</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/01/operational-resilience-sap-business-network-for-logistics</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Through SAP Business Network for Logistics, trading partners can plan more accurately, innovate collaboratively, and create value enduringly.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/travel-transportation</category>
            <category>news-tag/catena-x</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Take: Early Signs That Supply Chain Disruptions Are Easing]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/the-take-easing-supply-chain-disruptions-early-signs</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/the-take-easing-supply-chain-disruptions-early-signs</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With the holiday season in full flow, it is great to see some news of easing supply chain disruptions is welcome. Get SAP's take.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/perspective</category>
            <category>industry/travel-transportation</category>
            <category>news-tag/china</category>
            <category>news-tag/the-take</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Named a 2022 Magic Quadrant™ Transportation Management Systems and Magic Quadrant™ for Warehouse Management Systems Leader by Gartner®]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/gartner-magic-quadrant-tms-wms-sap-a-leader</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/gartner-magic-quadrant-tms-wms-sap-a-leader</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP has been recognized by Gartner as a leader in TMS and WMS, demonstrating its position as leading provider in supply chain and procurement.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/travel-transportation</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/magic-quadrant</category>
            <category>news-tag/warehouse-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Take: Mississippi Water Levels Disrupt Grain Shipments]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/the-take-mississippi-river-water-levels-disrupt-grain-shipments</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/the-take-mississippi-river-water-levels-disrupt-grain-shipments</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Water levels in some parts of the Mississippi river are now so low that commercial traffic has been halted. Get SAP's take on the impact.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/perspective</category>
            <category>industry/agribusiness</category>
            <category>industry/travel-transportation</category>
            <category>news-tag/climate-change</category>
            <category>product/sap-transportation-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/the-take</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Shippeo's Supply Chain Visibility Solution Moving Fast on SAP Store]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/shippeo-supply-chain-visibility-sap-store</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/shippeo-supply-chain-visibility-sap-store</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Shippeo is a European specialist in real-time transportation visibility. Learn how working with SAP helped their journey.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/travel-transportation</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-store</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Take: Railroads Sound the Whistle on Labor Shortages]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/the-take-railroad-industry-labor-shortages</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/the-take-railroad-industry-labor-shortages</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The railroad industry is suffering labor shortages equal to those of the air travel industry. Get SAP's take on the challenges.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/perspective</category>
            <category>industry/travel-transportation</category>
            <category>news-tag/the-take</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Take: Clearing Bridge Blockade Eases Supply Chain Woes]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/02/the-take-ambassador-bridge-blockade-supply-chain</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/02/the-take-ambassador-bridge-blockade-supply-chain</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[When a major trade link like the Ambassador Bridge is blocked, it can have a ripple effect across the entire supply chain. Get SAP's take.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1757ca0c89f98bd920670b0e1192f2aa76882c160.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1757ca0c89f98bd920670b0e1192f2aa76882c160.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1757ca0c89f98bd920670b0e1192f2aa76882c160.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="The Take: Clearing Bridge Blockade Eases Supply Chain Woes" src="./media_1757ca0c89f98bd920670b0e1192f2aa76882c160.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="the-take-clearing-bridge-blockade-eases-supply-chain-woes">The Take: Clearing Bridge Blockade Eases Supply Chain Woes</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>What’s News</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>North America’s busiest trade link — the Ambassador Bridge between Canada and the U.S. — reopened on Sunday evening, after Canadian police ended a six-day blockade by protesters objecting to <a href="/topics/covid-19">COVID-19</a> mandates and restrictions.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-customer-centric-products-to-market-faster-and-at-less-cost-with-global-supply-chain-management-software-from-sap">Get customer-centric products to market faster and at less cost with global supply chain management software from SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/supply-chain-management.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="saps-take">SAP’s Take</h2>
  <p>Canadian police cleared the bridge, which had been blocked by truckers and other protesters, after obtaining a court order on Friday. Normally the bridge carries goods worth about $360 million every day between the two countries — roughly a quarter of all Canadian/U.S. daily trade.</p>
  <p>Detroit-based auto makers ,including General Motors, Ford and Toyota, have been particularly hard hit and have announced production cutbacks because many of the components they rely on traverse the bridge.</p>
  <p>The bridge blockade has had an impact on a wide range of industries and added to inflationary pressures in both nations while once again highlighting the fragility of some supply chains.</p>
  <p>“When a major bridge like the Ambassador Bridge is blocked, it can have a ripple effect across the entire supply chain,” says Richard Howells, an SAP expert on <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/supply-chain-management.html">supply chains</a>. “Companies must have the resiliency to minimize and mitigate risks by designing supply chains to withstand disruptions and respond to business opportunities.”</p>
  <p>He adds: “In this case, you need the visibility to identify which shipments and resulting orders are effected, and the agility to sense, predict and respond by re-planning distribution routes, or even identify different modes of transport.”</p>
  <p>Among the factors Howells identifies as crucial for enterprises he says companies must have visibility into:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Which materials and goods are at risk?</li>
    <li>What are my alternate sources of supply for key resources?</li>
    <li>Where is my inventory?</li>
    <li>Which shipments are affected?</li>
    <li>What are the knock-on effects to production scheduled, customer orders and ongoing campaigns?</li>
  </ul>
  <p>In addition he says, they need agility to redirect shipments in transit, identify and switch to alternate suppliers, identify alternate logistics modes and routes, collaborate with trading partners to secure alternate materials, products and logistics capacity, and adjust manufacturing to respond to unavailable materials.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Contact:</strong> Joellen Perry, Head of <a href="/press-room">Global Public Relations</a>, SAP<br>+1 (626) 265-0370, <a href="mailto:joellen.perry@sap.com">joellen.perry@sap.com</a>, PST</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/perspective</category>
            <category>industry/travel-transportation</category>
            <category>news-tag/covid-19</category>
            <category>news-tag/the-take</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Road to Fix the Massive Truck Driver Shortage Is Paved with Data]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/01/road-to-fix-truck-driver-shortage-is-paved-with-data</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/01/road-to-fix-truck-driver-shortage-is-paved-with-data</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Wise Systems offers an AI-based delivery management platform, forging the connection between last-mile delivery and the customer experience.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_143e6fd42f76b12c65e80c5efb16b1e49080d6b24.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_143e6fd42f76b12c65e80c5efb16b1e49080d6b24.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_143e6fd42f76b12c65e80c5efb16b1e49080d6b24.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="The Road to Fix the Massive Truck Driver Shortage Is Paved with Data" src="./media_143e6fd42f76b12c65e80c5efb16b1e49080d6b24.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="the-road-to-fix-the-massive-truck-driver-shortage-is-paved-with-data">The Road to Fix the Massive Truck Driver Shortage Is Paved with Data</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Hidden in the furor about disrupted supply chains is how the experience of the drivers delivering all those goods directly impacts the customer experience. That’s where <a href="https://www.wisesystems.com/">Wise Systems</a> comes in, offering an artificial intelligence (AI)-based delivery management platform that originated at the Media Lab at MIT, when three of the company’s co-founders responded to a professor’s challenge to find the best way to change one billion lives with data.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“The free flow of goods is the lifeblood of communities,” said Allison Parker, vice president of Marketing at Wise Systems. “We decided to apply machine learning to real-time data that captures what’s happening on the ground so organizations can better plan and continuously improve every last-mile route and delivery. Drivers have an intuitive, easier experience managing their schedule directly from their mobile devices, while fleet managers have up-to-the-minute plan tracking for resource allocation and utilization.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-how-sapio-foundries-support-b2b-technology-startups-worldwide">Learn more about how SAP.iO Foundries support B2B technology startups worldwide</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://sap.io/foundries/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="data-intelligence-drives-seamless-delivery-experience">Data Intelligence Drives Seamless Delivery Experience</h2>
  <p>Fast forward to a post-pandemic world facing an 80,000 <a href="https://www.trucking.org/news-insights/ata-chief-economist-pegs-driver-shortage-historic-high">driver shortage</a> in the U.S. alone, and Wise Systems is leaving legacy “dispatch and routing” systems in the dust. Clients in the food and beverage industry, as well as courier companies, rely on Wise Systems to synthesize orders by product volume, location, and time frames into delivery stops for truck fleets and other vehicles. Fleet managers, dispatchers, and drivers can make tweaks, factoring in their knowledge, including customer preferences. The system monitors traffic and weather conditions in real time, alerting dispatchers to potential risks that could jeopardize scheduled deliveries.</p>
  <p>“Automating the routing process for the perfect, seamless experience requires intelligence up front, along with ongoing monitoring as each day unfolds,” said Parker. “Drivers appreciate having full visibility into all the data about every delivery stop, including the number of products they’re expected to deliver. All they need to do is swipe in and out when they arrive and leave. The system can also record proof of delivery. They can also leave notes for themselves or future drivers on our secure app, such as a passcode for a loading dock.”</p>
  <h2 id="machine-learning-perfectly-choreographs-route-plans">Machine Learning Perfectly Choreographs Route Plans</h2>
  <p>Contrary to misconceptions, behind the wheel is not necessarily where drivers spend the bulk of their time. It’s the on-site visits that eat up the greatest number of minutes during the course of a day. The machine learning models in Wise Systems calculate route plans based on historical and real-time data. Meantime, delivery companies can set delivery status notifications as well, allowing clients to receive updates at specified intervals.</p>
  <p>“The system can more accurately predict service times, taking into account the time it takes to complete a stop and factoring in the preferences of the retailer, hotel, medical institution, or other type of client,” said Parker. “The goal is route planning efficiency combined with customer service so people receive their inventory when and where they expect it; this is the number one priority of our clients.”</p>
  <p>From a fleet management perspective, machine learning also helps keep vehicles fully utilized to maximum capacity for both route efficiencies and more sustainable business. One global food and beverage client reduced late deliveries by 80, decreasing fleet mileage by up to 15%. On-time deliveries can contribute to a company’s carbon reduction goals as it reduces redeliveries.</p>
  <h2 id="capturing-performance-metrics-with-data-analytics">Capturing Performance Metrics with Data Analytics</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-s4hana-a-complete-intelligent-erp-system-with-embedded-ai-and-machine-learning">SAP S/4HANA: A complete, intelligent ERP system with embedded AI and machine learning</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/s4hana-erp.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Wise Systems also serves up analytics that managers and drivers find valuable. Fleet managers can immediately see everything from inventory volumes on the road and delivered, to driver times at any point in the workday. They can benchmark that data against the company’s performance metrics that typically vary depending on the type of vehicle and amount of goods. They can make fleet size adjustments to better meet vehicle utilization and sustainable business targets. Some clients have increased their fleet utilization on average by 20 percentage points. Data helps individual drivers see where they stand too, as many are compensated with performance premiums for on-time deliveries.</p>
  <h2 id="sapio-expands-market-opportunities">SAP.iO Expands Market Opportunities</h2>
  <p>When the Wise Systems team participated in the <a href="/covid-19">COVID-19</a> recovery cohort of <a href="https://sap.io/ny-demo-day-2021/">SAP.iO Foundry New York City</a>, they discovered new market opportunities.</p>
  <p>“We learned so much about customer needs from SAP experts,” said Parker. “Integrating information from Wise Systems with <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/s4hana-erp.html">SAP S/4HANA</a> is a great example of how companies are using connected data between ERP systems, such as order and warehouse management, finance, and last-mile logistics operations and back, to become intelligent enterprises.”</p>
  <p>Wise Systems is available on <a href="https://store.sap.com/dcp/en/product/display-0000059776_live_v1">SAP Store</a>.</p>
  <h2 id="modern-experience-can-help-solve-the-driver-shortage">Modern Experience Can Help Solve the Driver Shortage</h2>
  <p>Recruiting and retaining drivers for last-mile delivery is just one segment of the disrupted supply chain, but it’s a big one. Anything organizations can do to improve the quality of their day-to-day experience matters. As companies modernize the systems that power vast supply chains, don’t leave the truck driver’s experience behind.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Follow me @smgaler.</em><br><em><a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2021/12/14/the-road-to-fix-the-massive-truck-driver-shortage-is-paved-with-data/?sh=6790faf338e4">This blog also appeared on SAP BrandVoice on Forbes.</a></em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>industry/travel-transportation</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-store</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-io</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Dutch Car Manufacturer VDL Nedcar Digitalized Yard Operations to Boost Efficiency]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/vdl-nedcar-digitalized-yard-operations-to-boost-efficiency</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/vdl-nedcar-digitalized-yard-operations-to-boost-efficiency</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Read to learn how SAP Yard Logistics helped Dutch car manufacturer VDL Nedcar digitalize yard operations and boost efficiency.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1757ca0c89f98bd920670b0e1192f2aa76882c160.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1757ca0c89f98bd920670b0e1192f2aa76882c160.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1757ca0c89f98bd920670b0e1192f2aa76882c160.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="How Dutch Car Manufacturer VDL Nedcar Digitalized Yard Operations to Boost Efficiency" src="./media_1757ca0c89f98bd920670b0e1192f2aa76882c160.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="how-dutch-car-manufacturer-vdl-nedcar-digitalized-yard-operations-to-boost-efficiency">How Dutch Car Manufacturer VDL Nedcar Digitalized Yard Operations to Boost Efficiency</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>“With a growing number of customers and increasingly complex supply chain processes, VDL needed to replace its legacy system with a modern and flexible IT landscape to support our clear <a href="/topics/industry-4-0">Industry 4.0</a> vision to drive efficiencies and be ready for the future.”</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>These were the words of Pepijn Timmermans, vice president of Digitalization at VDL Nedcar, who I recently had the chance to speak to about how the company modernized and digitalized its yard operations.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="prepare-your-logistics-for-the-future-with-integrated-yard-management">Prepare your logistics for the future with integrated yard management</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/yard-logistics.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="what-is-vdl-nedcar">What Is VDL Nedcar?</h2>
  <p><a href="https://www.vdlnedcar.nl/en">VDL Nedcar</a> is not just the only independent contract manufacturer in the Netherlands but also one of the most advanced vehicle manufacturers in Europe. The 50-year-old company builds high-quality cars for major brands such as BMW, as well as a plug-in hybrid electric vehicle (PHEV) variant of the MINI Countryman. And as a company that banks on strong partnerships and innovation, VDL will also build electric vehicles for their newest customer, the U.S. company Canoo.</p>
  <h2 id="how-to-manage-a-yard-full-of-moving-products">How to Manage a Yard Full of Moving Products</h2>
  <p>VDL Nedcar faced the challenge of managing the movement of vehicles, parts, and materials. “We have 1,000 parts suppliers, 12,000 parts numbers, and seven carriers who bring all these parts by truck to our plant, which results in an inbound of 270 full trucks per day coming in and going out,” Timmermans explained.</p>
  <p>“The automotive industry has a closed loop where packaging material is brought back to the supplier. This means transport can arrive at any moment and within only one hour the driver drops a trailer, picks up another with packaging materials, and leaves the yard,” he added. “We have to manage 350 trailers in our yard. Basically, it’s a warehouse management system for trailers.”</p>
  <p>The process to do this was very manual. When a carrier came in, they picked an empty spot in the yard, filled out papers, and took them to the office where the information was put into the system. This was a very labor-intensive and error-prone process, and, as Timmermans explained, “If we missed only one trailer, the impact could be dramatic and costly.” A missed trailer of a vital part could harm the production processes and even lead to major stoppages of the plant for a full day, which relies on a just-in-time approach.</p>
  <h2 id="the-answer-warehouses-on-wheels">The Answer? Warehouses on Wheels</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-the-document-how-can-automated-inbound-logistics-processes-help-yard-staff-work-more-productively">Read the document "How Can Automated Inbound Logistics Processes Help Yard Staff Work More Productively?"</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/customer-stories.html?search=SAP+yard+logistics&#x26;pdf-asset=ba8be30c-0a7e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b&#x26;page=1#customer-stories-finder">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The answer was to analyze business processes. “We have a very unique inbound logistics supply chain concept. I think we are the only one of the OEMs in Europe who has control of inbound transport fully in our own hands,” Timmermans said. “In our material requirement system, we also integrate the whole of inbound logistics transport planning as part of the <a href="https://insights.sap.com/what-is-mrp/">material requirement planning</a>, which makes us unique and enables us to have very efficient inbound logistics.”</p>
  <p>“We established a ‘warehouse on wheels’ concept, which optimizes our transport efficiency,” he said. “Instead of booking a time slot days ahead with the risk of long waiting times at the gate and manual management of documents in the past, carriers can arrive at our plant 24/7, sign in at the gate, get a parking location assigned for the trailer, and receive a note where to pick up an empty trailer with packaging materials.”</p>
  <h2 id="managing-the-logistics-of-the-yard">Managing the Logistics of the Yard</h2>
  <p>To get full control and transparency of this warehouse on wheels, VDL Nedcar implemented <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/yard-logistics.html">SAP Yard Logistics</a>.</p>
  <p>“Based on <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/yard-logistics.html">SAP Yard Logistics</a> and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/fiori.html">SAP Fiori apps</a>, we developed a solution where our six dock master trucks that drive the trailers from the yard to the loading dock and empty back to the yard can be steered fully automatically,” Timmermans explained. “The trucks are equipped with industrial flat screens and connected to the solution. All movement triggers are visualized for the dock masters and they get automated priorities for which trailer to transport where, including an optimization algorithm to indicate which truck is close to the trailer to be picked up. Getting this process automated and optimized saved one employee per shift.”</p>
  <p>“Previously, we also did a manual weekly inventory of all trailers on the yard for which we needed one man day per week. That has all gone,” he added.</p>
  <p>“SAP Yard Logistics helps us cooperate with our suppliers much better. We have an easier, digitalized, and transparent process at the gate for our carriers, which boosts efficiency, reduces waiting time, and eases administration,” he said.</p>
  <p><strong>Tangible benefits</strong> include:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Increased process transparency</li>
    <li>Reduced administrative effort of one day per week</li>
    <li>Time savings thanks to inventory automation</li>
    <li>Efficiency gains due to automated and digitalized processes on the yard saving one employee per shift</li>
    <li>Reduced waiting time for carriers and enabling them to plan better</li>
    <li>Streamlined and transparent processes at the gate</li>
    <li>Almost no incidents or administrative mistakes</li>
    <li>Standard solution that is integrated with <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/s4hana-erp.html">SAP S/4HANA</a></li>
  </ul>
  <p>“In the future, we plan to connect our yard logistics processes with <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/transportation-logistics.html">SAP Transportation Management</a> to provide a self-service portal for the carriers, automate gate processes with cameras, and leverage <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/extended-warehouse-management.html">SAP Extended Warehouse Management</a> to get full transparency across the entire supply chain,” Timmermans concluded.</p>
  <p>To learn more about how to achieve efficient and sustainable processes with SAP Yard Logistics, <a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/td/sap-yard-logistics-free-trial.html">start your free trial today</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Karin Fent is senior director of Global Customer Success Digital Supply Chain at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/automotive</category>
            <category>industry/travel-transportation</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-4-0</category>
            <category>product/sap-extended-warehouse-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>product/sap-transportation-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Giving Thanks to Those Who Support the Thanksgiving Supply Chain]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/thanksgiving-supply-chain</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/thanksgiving-supply-chain</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[This year, give thanks to all who have supported the Thankgiving supply chain to keep our lives if not normal, at least bearable.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d3d7601b0a14a5e2bb41c01fe56a12df1e516e7d.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d3d7601b0a14a5e2bb41c01fe56a12df1e516e7d.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1d3d7601b0a14a5e2bb41c01fe56a12df1e516e7d.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Giving Thanks to Those Who Support the Thanksgiving Supply Chain" src="./media_1d3d7601b0a14a5e2bb41c01fe56a12df1e516e7d.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="giving-thanks-to-those-who-support-the-thanksgiving-supply-chain">Giving Thanks to Those Who Support the Thanksgiving Supply Chain</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>As we look back on almost two years of a global <a href="/covid-19">pandemic</a>, I think it’s time we take a look around this holiday season and give thanks to all those who have gone above and beyond to make our lives if not normal, at least bearable, by providing the goods, services, and support that we need in our lives.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Of course, we start with the healthcare workers and first responders who must risk their own safety, day in day out, to make sure we are safe; the scientists who have designed, manufactured, and delivered vaccines to fight this terrible COVID-19 pandemic.</p>
  <p>But let’s not forget all the people who work tirelessly to make sure that there is food on our table, clothes on our backs, deliveries at our doorsteps, and supplies in the stores. The essential workers across the global supply chain.</p>
  <p>Supply chains have had some bad press in the past few months, with plant shutdowns, port closures, cargo ship congestion, the inflation blame games, and labor shortages. But we must remember that behind this nebulous thing called the “supply chain” are people who make things tick.</p>
  <p>There are people in the manufacturing facilities who have had to work short staffed, in protective clothing and complying to environmental health and safety protocols. There are people driving through the night, sacrificing time with loved ones, to move goods around the country. There are people, along with the cargo, sitting out at sea waiting for the call to come into dock, and there are people trying to keep the shelves stocked, with limited supply, and handling disgruntled customers who are looking for their favorite brand of cranberries to put on the Thanksgiving table.</p>
  <h2 id="cranberries--from-farm-to-table">Cranberries – From Farm to Table</h2>
  <p>It is estimated that Americans consume about 80 million pounds of cranberries during Thanksgiving. Taking a closer look at that can of cranberry sauce, here’s what it takes to provide this staple of the Thanksgiving meal.</p>
  <p>It starts with a farmer in a cranberry bog, where it can take up to 16 months for the berries to ripen, before they are harvested in September — in New England at least. To harvest, the farmers must flood the cranberry bog to let the berries rise to the surface to be loosened from the vine, collected, and loaded into trucks, then transported by drivers to a manufacturing plant.</p>
  <p>At the <strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/supply-chain-management/manufacturing.html">manufacturing</a></strong> plant, the berries are sorted by size and cleaned. They are then placed in wooden crates, frozen, and stored ready for production.</p>
  <p>The production process starts by “spiking” the frozen berries in order to loosen them up and then fresh berries are added, and the batch is inspected for quality. They are then ground up into a puree, some sweetener is added, and the resulting mixture is pasteurized. The finished batch then goes into the canning process, after which the full cans are steamed and sealed, cooled, labeled, and finally packed into cases that are moved into a warehouse prior to shipping.</p>
  <p>All of these steps require a team of production planners, supervisors, and workers.</p>
  <p>Shipping requires a <strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/supply-chain-management/supply-chain-logistics.html">logistics network</a></strong> of planners, warehouse personnel, and drivers to move, store, and distribute pallets of cranberry sauce all over the country to retail stores where, again, there are teams of people stacking and replenishing the shelves.</p>
  <p>To put it in perspective, for this holiday season, the process from farm to table started about the time the pandemic hit the U.S., and involved hundreds of people, just so we as consumers can have cranberry sauce as a side this Thanksgiving.</p>
  <h2 id="showing-gratitude-this-holiday-season">Showing Gratitude this Holiday Season</h2>
  <p>This Thanksgiving, I for one will be giving thanks for what I do have, and for all the people who made it possible — and not complaining about what is not available.</p>
  <p>Thank you to all those honest, hardworking people behind the scenes, making the best of a tough situation, so that we can all try and enjoy some semblance of normality this holiday season.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-customer-centric-products-to-market-faster-and-at-less-cost-with-global-supply-chain-management-software-from-sap">Get customer-centric products to market faster and at less cost with global supply chain management software from SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/supply-chain-management.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="to-learn-more-about-how-to-manage-teams-of-people-across-a-sustainable-supply-chain-download-this-recent-oxford-economics-study">To learn more about how to manage teams of people across a sustainable supply chain download this recent <a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/dg/sustainable-supply-chain/index.html">Oxford Economics study</a>.</h3>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em><a href="https://www.twitter.com/@howellsrichard">Follow me on Twitter</a>.</em><br><em><a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2021/11/17/lets-give-thanks-to-the-people-supporting-the-thanksgiving-supply-chain/?sh=d7769477d024">This story originally appeared on SAP BrandVoice on Forbes</a>.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/travel-transportation</category>
            <category>news-tag/covid-19</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The New Rules of Competition for Today’s Distributor]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/new-rules-of-competition-for-todays-distributors</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/new-rules-of-competition-for-todays-distributors</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[To stay relevant and competitive in any market condition, wholesale distributors need to rethink their business and operations strategies.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f9da2820936b7055a711bcac1c73b9837db4504d.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f9da2820936b7055a711bcac1c73b9837db4504d.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1f9da2820936b7055a711bcac1c73b9837db4504d.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="The New Rules of Competition for Today’s Distributor" src="./media_1f9da2820936b7055a711bcac1c73b9837db4504d.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="the-new-rules-of-competition-for-todays-distributor">The New Rules of Competition for Today’s Distributor</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>It is common knowledge that every business experienced some form of unpredictable disruption over the last two years. Acting as the first responders in the logistics supply chain, this disruption threatened many wholesale distributors’ ability to provide essential goods to vital businesses, such as healthcare providers and grocery stores. To stay relevant and competitive amidst all market conditions, distribution leaders need to rethink their business and operations strategies.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>During a recent online event, Distribution Strategy Group’s Founder and Senior Partner Ian Heller exposed five major sources of disruption for this vital industry:</p>
  <ol>
    <li><strong>Workforce</strong>: The youngest generations (Generation Y and Generation Z) now make up approximately 70% of the total workforce. These generations are the most technically affluent, which means they expect to be connected on any device, anytime, anywhere, with easy-to-use applications.</li>
    <li><strong>E-Commerce</strong>: E-commerce is no longer just about having a slick website. Today, distributors must have a strong technology foundation to deliver an easy-to-use, personalized, B2C-like purchasing experience for customers.</li>
    <li><strong>Cybersecurity</strong>: The <a href="/covid-19">COVID-19 pandemic</a> has underlined cybersecurity as a prevalent concern as new vulnerabilities arose due to employees working from home. Phishing and ransomware attacks have virtually exploded across every industry in the past few years.</li>
    <li><strong>Cloud</strong>: To stay competitive, many distributors are moving their technology stack to the cloud to lower capital expenditures and enjoy a better margin advantage.</li>
    <li><strong>Marketplaces</strong>: B2B buyers are turning to marketplaces for a one-stop shopping experience. Distributors that can successfully adopt a marketplace model will stand to deepen customer relationships and drive growth.</li>
  </ol>
  <p>Heller shared that as an industry, distributors are still working out solutions to these challenges as they continue to adjust to the ever-evolving market challenges. Digital transformation continues to be an enabler of business models, allowing distributors to go from reactive, reporting on things that are happening, to proactive, anticipating the future and mitigating risks.</p>
  <p>Magnus Meier, vice president and global head of the Wholesale Distribution Business Unit at SAP, went on to share that high-tech distributors have started to market themselves as solution aggregators to underline how committed they are to long-term customer relationships, taking care of the product and customer life cycle. In addition, digital transformation continues to play a significant role during the pandemic, specifically in operations. “Distributors that have a modern ERP system have data on hand, which gives them a significant advantage over their competitors,” says Meier.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="expand-beyond-traditional-industry-boundaries-with-sap-solutions">Expand beyond traditional industry boundaries with SAP solutions</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/wholesale-distribution.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="using-services-as-a-differentiator">Using Services as a Differentiator</h2>
  <p>For distributors to successfully implement everything from business strategy to operations to customer experience, they first need to determine what is most important to their business. Competitive differentiators come in all shapes and sizes for wholesale distributors, be it a great service like replenishment of bins near the production line, dedicated jobs like delivery of materials, on-site safety training, or even simply having the most responsive, proactive salespeople. Aligning business priorities with competitive differentiators allows distributors to position their business model as not just indispensable to customers, but profitable.</p>
  <p>The big players, by and large, are not great at services. Services almost always represent the introduction of variable costs into a business model. Traditionally, distributors have rolled the costs of services into the gross margin of products, but they have not monetized them or charged the cost back to customers. “If distributors put a general manager in charge of services, one must treat it the way that a manufacturer treats new product development. Figure out how to monetize it with a P&#x26;L to build a business that’s much different and adds value for their customers,” says Heller.</p>
  <p>The technology that enables distributors to have the right level of visibility into their business starts with an enterprise resource planning (ERP) system, which is critical to transformation. Having the right processing system enables order-to-cash (O2C) and procure-to-pay (P2P) business processes, which are critical to operations. For many distributors, more than 50% of orders come through as e-mailed PDF or Excel files, creating a manual process for customer sales representatives to then enter the orders into proprietary systems.</p>
  <p>Counterintuitive to what distributors assume, the number of manual orders received is increasing, not decreasing. To enable efficiency and resiliency, distributors must find a way to automate manual and redundant tasks and redirect that energy towards value-added efforts. “Conexiom can help process those orders with the same customer service expectations that a buyer experiences when placing an e-commerce order, a marketplace order, or any other type of digital order,” says Erik Severinghaus, executive vice president of Business Development at Conexiom.</p>
  <h2 id="preempting-issues-within-the-supply-chain">Preempting Issues within the Supply Chain</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="explore-conexiom-on-sap-store">Explore Conexiom on SAP Store</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://store.sap.com/dcp/en/product/display-0000059854_live_v1/Conexiom%20Digital%20Order%20Capture%20for%20SAP%20Solutions">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Whether it’s due to trade agreements, politics, or biological threats like pandemics, these is less predictability in the supply chain. A good example is what happened at the Suez Canal. The only way distributors can anticipate these issues is to have complete transparency and visibility across the supply chain, all the way through to the demand side. They need to leverage technology to gain the transparency to track which boxes are in which containers and on which ships. And if one of those ships goes astray, they need to be able to understand the implications and trigger follow-up processes to minimize disruption.</p>
  <p>“Distributors are operating at greater scale than ever before and it is essential that distributors overcome silos, talk to sellers to overcome those challenges, understand how their customers will be affected, and take mitigating action,” says Meier.</p>
  <h2 id="navigating-the-talent-shortage">Navigating the Talent Shortage</h2>
  <p>Every business is grappling with the talent shortage today. To attract the right talent, distributors need to invest in modern technology to bolster employee experience in the workplace. Distributors need to leverage intelligent technologies to automate routine tasks so employees can focus on more complex customer requirements. They need to provide collaboration tools between different teams to drive ongoing business alignment, openness for change, business agility, and improved collaboration between sales, marketing, and demand-planning teams. The distribution industry as a whole must challenge the way it has traditionally handled work-from-home policies, salaries, long-term incentives, and other benefits to make employees want to stay in this lesser-known B2B industry. “Distributors need to offer a competitive workplace environment, not just against other distributors, but against other industries,” says Severinghaus.</p>
  <p>Meier, Severinghaus, and Heller have a lot of commendable and proven advice on these topics. In this <a href="https://conexiom.com/resources/the-new-rules-of-competition-for-todays-distributor/">on-demand video</a>, these speakers discuss the challenges facing distributors today and provide tangible guidance on how to prepare and respond to market disruptions.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Sam Nohava is global industry marketing lead at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/travel-transportation</category>
            <category>news-tag/e-commerce</category>
            <category>industry/wholesale-distribution</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Ranked No. 1 in Gartner Market Share Analysis Report and Recognized as a Leader in Transportation and Warehouse Management Systems]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/sap-a-leader-supply-chain-management-transportation-warehouse-management</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/sap-a-leader-supply-chain-management-transportation-warehouse-management</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is ranked the No. 1 supply chain management software vendor by market share in revenue worldwide by Gartner. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1de94c869ef89399d5940ea21e2e295e14b890cee.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1de94c869ef89399d5940ea21e2e295e14b890cee.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1de94c869ef89399d5940ea21e2e295e14b890cee.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Ranked No. 1 in Gartner Market Share Analysis Report and Recognized as a Leader in Transportation and Warehouse Management Systems" src="./media_1de94c869ef89399d5940ea21e2e295e14b890cee.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-ranked-no-1-in-gartner-market-share-analysis-report-and-recognized-as-a-leader-in-transportation-and-warehouse-management-systems">SAP Ranked No. 1 in Gartner Market Share Analysis Report and Recognized as a Leader in Transportation and Warehouse Management Systems</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-customer-centric-products-to-market-faster-and-at-less-cost-with-global-supply-chain-management-software-from-sap">Get customer-centric products to market faster and at less cost with global supply chain management software from SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/supply-chain-management.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced that it is ranked the No. 1 supply chain management software vendor by market share in revenue worldwide in the Gartner® “<a href="https://www.gartner.com/document/4003648?ref=solrAll&#x26;refval=295315829">Market Share Analysis: Supply Chain Management Software, Worldwide, 2020</a>” report.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Vendors were analyzed across procurement, supply chain execution and supply chain planning and, for the second year in a row, SAP ranked No. 1 across all three categories.</p>
  <p>In addition, SAP was also recognized as a Leader in both the “<a href="https://www.gartner.com/document/4003090?ref=solrAll&#x26;refval=299962045">2021 Gartner Magic Quadrant™ for Warehouse Management Systems</a>” report and the “<a href="https://www.gartner.com/document/4000019">2021 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Transportation Management Systems</a>” report. These recognitions illustrate SAP’s continued influence on the future of resilient digital supply chains.</p>
  <p>“In our opinion, this trio of recognitions from Gartner reflects our commitment to improving outcomes for our customers,” said Franz Hero, head of SAP Digital Supply Chain Development. “We’ve worked to ensure they are empowered to rapidly respond to changing market conditions, and that invested commitment is being recognized.”</p>
  <p>The SAP Extended Warehouse Management application helps customers manage high-volume warehouse operations and integrate complex supply chain logistics within their warehouse and distribution processes to deliver visibility and control.</p>
  <p>The SAP Transportation Management application supports customers across all major industries, with a focus on consumer products, agriculture, mining, construction, chemical and retail. The application helps customers dramatically reduce transportation complexity by integrating fleet and logistics management throughout their network.</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="http://news.sap.com/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP on Twitter at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Media Contact:</strong> Angela Feher, +1 (347) 882-1689, <a href="mailto:angela.feher@sap.com">angela.feher@sap.com</a>, ET<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p><em>Gartner, “Market Share Analysis: Supply Chain Management Software, Worldwide, 2020,” Balaji Abbabatulla, Satyam ., Neha Gupta, Amarendra , Christian Titze, Micky Keck, 15 July 2021.</em><br><em>Gartner, “Magic Quadrant for Warehouse Management Systems,” Simon Tunstall, Dwight Klappich, 30 June 2021.</em><br><em>Gartner, “Magic Quadrant for Transportation Management Systems,” Bart De Muynck, Brock Johns, Oscar Sanchez Duran, Carly West, 30 March 2021.</em><br><em>Gartner does not endorse any vendor, product or service depicted in its research publications and does not advise technology users to select only those vendors with the highest ratings or other designation. Gartner research publications consist of the opinions of Gartner’s Research &#x26; Advisory organization and should not be construed as statements of fact. Gartner disclaims all warranties, expressed or implied, with respect to this research, including any warranties of merchantability or fitness for a particular purpose. GARTNER and Magic Quadrant are registered trademarks and service marks of Gartner, Inc. and/or its affiliates in the U.S. and internationally and are used herein with permission. All rights reserved.</em></p>
  <p>Any statements contained in this document that are not historical facts are forward-looking statements as defined in the U.S. Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995. Words such as “anticipate,” “believe,” “estimate,” “expect,” “forecast,” “intend,” “may,” “plan,” “project,” “predict,” “should” and “will” and similar expressions as they relate to SAP are intended to identify such forward-looking statements. SAP undertakes no obligation to publicly update or revise any forward-looking statements. All forward-looking statements are subject to various risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results to differ materially from expectations. The factors that could affect SAP’s future financial results are discussed more fully in SAP’s filings with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (“SEC”), including SAP’s most recent Annual Report on Form 20-F filed with the SEC. Readers are cautioned not to place undue reliance on these forward-looking statements, which speak only as of their dates.<br>© 2021 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>industry/travel-transportation</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-supply-chain</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>product/sap-extended-warehouse-management</category>
            <category>product/sap-transportation-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/warehouse-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Startup refundrebel Simplifies Reimbursements in SAP Concur Solutions]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/refundrebel-simplifies-reimbursements-sap-concur</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/refundrebel-simplifies-reimbursements-sap-concur</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The integration between Concur Travel and refundrebel enables companies to avoid cumbersome, manual compensation claim processes. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/travel-transportation</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-concur</category>
            <category>news-tag/startups</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SBB’s Asset Management and Reliability Journey in the Digital Age]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/06/sbb-asset-management-reliability-journey</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/06/sbb-asset-management-reliability-journey</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Read to learn how rail and transportation company SBB digitally transformed maintenance practices to allow for a complete, reliable system.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c858668b4a53062c7974e6380d00cc9cf669ae1c.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c858668b4a53062c7974e6380d00cc9cf669ae1c.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1c858668b4a53062c7974e6380d00cc9cf669ae1c.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SBB’s Asset Management and Reliability Journey in the Digital Age" src="./media_1c858668b4a53062c7974e6380d00cc9cf669ae1c.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sbbs-asset-management-and-reliability-journey-in-the-digital-age">SBB’s Asset Management and Reliability Journey in the Digital Age</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>In a world of ever-increasing mobility, travel and transportation companies can benefit from planning asset management strategically and considering factors such as risk, reliability, and impact. Not doing so will reduce speed and efficiency while increasing cost.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As such, providing safe, reliable, and comfortable rail transportation that’s enhanced for the digital age is at the center of rail and transportation company <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2020/02/ec15beec-847d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff.html">SBB’s vision</a>. Through a relentless focus on this vision, the company is benefitting from a complete digital transformation of maintenance practices. This helps SBB to drive continuous improvement through new and innovative maintenance practices.</p>
  <p>SAP recently hosted an industry forum about <a href="https://event.on24.com/wcc/r/3088186/281D20D6AC683612D363AD7ED0BF743E">asset management and reliability in the new digital age</a> with leading global solution providers and consultants. Featured speakers included:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Urs Gehrig</strong>, senior consultant, Business Development, Lead Integration Management SAP S/4HANA SBB Infrastructure, SBB, Swiss Federal Railways</li>
    <li><strong>Tom Kurtz</strong>, global solution lead, Intelligent Asset Management, SAP</li>
  </ul>
  <p>Here are the key takeaways and experiences regarding SBB’s asset management and reliability practices.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="maximize-asset-performance-with-sap-intelligent-asset-management">Maximize asset performance with SAP Intelligent Asset Management</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/supply-chain-management/asset-management-eam.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="current-challenges-require-dynamic-adaptation">Current Challenges Require Dynamic Adaptation</h2>
  <p>Companies in the travel and transportation industry cannot remain stagnant. Businesses must always pivot and adapt. Embracing digital transformation enables companies to react with speed and flexibility to increasingly complex business challenges.</p>
  <p>By viewing the operational context of fixed and movable assets, companies can have a better idea of where they are succeeding or falling short. In addition to dynamically adapting to modern challenges, companies like SBB need to create strategies for asset management that allow them to operate their assets in the most cost-effective manner possible.</p>
  <h2 id="asset-lifecycle-is-the-heart-of-digital-transformation">Asset Lifecycle Is the Heart of Digital Transformation</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-the-document-using-a-digital-maintenance-platform-to-keep-swiss-trains-running-like-clockwork">Read the document "Using a Digital Maintenance Platform to Keep Swiss Trains Running Like Clockwork"</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2020/02/ec15beec-847d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As the backbone of the Swiss public transport system, SBB AG plays a vital role in keeping the country moving. Every day, the rail company transports 1.25 million passengers on more than 6,000 trains across Switzerland and into neighboring countries. The company had already recognized the changing mobility patterns and customers’ rising expectations for their travel experience. Therefore, SBB invests in modern, high-performance train sets. The company expects that these trains will help deliver quality customer experiences and ensure train services are safe, comfortable, and punctual for all customers.</p>
  <p>By investing in modern fleets, SBB knows that it is vital to gain maximum return on its investment. For the rail company to gain optimal operational use of its new, technologically advanced train sets, SBB also needs to enhance its fleet maintenance processes. To accomplish this, SBB reviews its end-to-end asset management practices for all asset types, including real estate, logistics, rolling stock, and infrastructure.</p>
  <h2 id="reliability-centered-maintenance-is-key">Reliability Centered Maintenance Is Key</h2>
  <p>Asset management requires a multi-faceted strategy to help drive peak asset performance. Reliability-centered maintenance is a cornerstone of such a multi-faceted strategy.</p>
  <p>As a forward-thinking industry leader, SBB is adopting reliability-centered maintenance practices as a core part of its asset management improvement journey.</p>
  <p>SBB is also integrating additional <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/supply-chain-management/asset-management-eam.html">SAP Intelligent Asset Management</a> solutions into its operational processes. With real-time data and analysis, the rail company will be able to gain asset performance insights. These insights can allow it to predict and manage issues before they arise.</p>
  <p>Every business is unique, even if they are in the same industry. Asset management improvement does not follow a “one-size-fits-all” approach. What is important is for companies to make an effective start to optimize asset availability to grow more efficiently.</p>
  <p>Did you miss “SBB’s Asset Management and Reliability Journey in The Digital Age” webinar? <a href="https://event.on24.com/wcc/r/3088186/281D20D6AC683612D363AD7ED0BF743E">Watch the replay</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Johann Schachtner is Travel &#x26; Transportation Industry solution manager at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>industry/travel-transportation</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[EVs Go Mainstream: Plug into the Sustainable Energy of E-Mobility]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/evs-sustainable-energy-e-mobility</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/evs-sustainable-energy-e-mobility</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Despite a push for electric vehicles (EVs), a profitable and sustainable e-mobility business model requires industry overhaul.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ab0a1efd18faa7aa854e3a865ca5a76765e8fdf6.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ab0a1efd18faa7aa854e3a865ca5a76765e8fdf6.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1ab0a1efd18faa7aa854e3a865ca5a76765e8fdf6.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="EVs Go Mainstream: Plug into the Sustainable Energy of E-Mobility" src="./media_1ab0a1efd18faa7aa854e3a865ca5a76765e8fdf6.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="evs-go-mainstream-plug-into-the-sustainable-energy-of-e-mobility">EVs Go Mainstream: Plug into the Sustainable Energy of E-Mobility</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>The push for electric vehicles (EVs) may have shifted into overdrive, but it is going to take a serious overhaul of the entire transportation ecosystem to build a profitable and sustainable e-mobility business model.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Having sufficient charging stations is just the tip of the iceberg. The transportation network is facing a major reboot, forcing automobile original equipment manufacturer (OEMs), utilities, corporations, regulators, and retailers to collaborate for innovation as never before.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="augment-your-intelligent-enterprise-with-industry-cloud-solutions">Augment your intelligent enterprise with industry cloud solutions</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/industry-cloud.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="networks-power-e-mobility-innovation">Networks Power E-Mobility Innovation</h2>
  <p>Compared to gas-powered cars, EVs and the services around them are far more interconnected. This demands a new kind of collaboration across the e-mobility value chain from corporate fleets, regulators, and smart cities to service providers and consumers.</p>
  <p>“The e-mobility network consists of multiple players from different industries and sectors with intertwined supply chains,” said Ulrich Scholl, vice president of E-Mobility at SAP. “To operate with flexibility and cost-efficiency they need to collaborate across stable, cloud-based <a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/industry-cloud.html">industry networks</a> that foster sustainable innovation around standardized processes, including invoicing and billing, as well as overall e-mobility management among partners.”</p>
  <h2 id="evs-spark-new-business-models">EVs Spark New Business Models</h2>
  <p>As sustainability mandates and promises grow, one central question is how to make EV battery recharging as easy and convenient as refilling a gas tank. Utilities are drawn to bi-directional charging that simultaneously recharges EVs while adding the battery’s stored energy back into the electrical power grid. This turns drivers into energy producers and cars into mobile power storage. Retailers are starting to monetize their solar panel energy, offering consumers free car charging while they shop, increasing customer loyalty. Meantime, corporate fleet managers are taking action by increasing EV and charging infrastructure investments that support company sustainability commitments.</p>
  <p>For example, Hanno Klausmeier, managing director of SAP Labs France, received a <a href="https://www.automobile-entreprise.com/CONNECT-fleet-Awards-derniers,9679">Fleet Manager of the Year</a> award for leading the electrification of the company’s fleet of cars for hundreds of employees located across three sites.</p>
  <p>Converting to EVs has been a seven-year journey at SAP, grounded in the company’s global commitment to sustainability, as well as the initial battery limitations of early EVs. After eliminating gas-fueled vehicles as a choice for employees several years ago, over 90% of the cars in the company’s fleet in SAP Labs France are now EVs. Convenient access to charging stations along with new fleet management operations were critical to the successful roll-out.</p>
  <p>“We knew that employees would need more stations to charge their cars so we installed super-fast charging stations conveniently located across our facilities,” Klausmeier said. “We revamped fleet management to make sure we could supervise and optimize charging stations for uninterrupted operations. Connecting the e-mobility ecosystem on one transparent platform is the only way for organizations to keep pace with the rapidly-changing industry.”</p>
  <p>Indeed, SAP Labs France developed new software to remotely manage the status of its charging stations, installing it on-site and at employee’s homes. Now available publicly, the solution helps corporate car fleet operations manage relationships with fleet management service companies, OEMs, and other suppliers that are involved with charging stations. Managers have real-time visibility into e-fleet charging station status and can quickly solve problems remotely for an easier experience.</p>
  <h2 id="market-fragmentation-gives-way-to-network-convergence">Market Fragmentation Gives Way to Network Convergence</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="the-electrification-of-mobility-challenges-and-opportunities-for-travel-and-transportation-operators">The Electrification of Mobility: Challenges and Opportunities for Travel and Transportation Operators</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/04/e-mobility-travel-transportation-operators">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Entirely new competitors are emerging with EVs, including “roaming” providers, which help consumers locate reliable charging stations and pay for the electricity as validated users. This is likely a temporary stop gap because it is unnecessarily complex and more costly for drivers.</p>
  <p>“We need to shorten the e-mobility value chain for cost efficiencies to charge point operators and an improved experience for customers,” said Scholl. “There’s no need to have another layer between energy providers and customers. With an open mobility platform, the whole ecosystem has the ability to build relationships for service convenience and affordable innovation, especially incorporating the use of renewable energy that’s produced locally and stored in EVs.”</p>
  <h2 id="transforming-the-transportation-sector">Transforming the Transportation Sector</h2>
  <p>Just like the iPhone disrupted the cellphone industry, e-mobility redefines the purpose of a vehicle. Already some manufacturers tout EVs as self-powered RVs. Even bigger are the implications for large-scale innovations, such as vehicles that are able to provide uninterrupted power for tools at remote construction sites.</p>
  <p>Similarly, transformations could be in store for energy retailers if OEMs bypass them to become energy providers themselves. On the corporate side, shared EVs could be part of an organization’s mobility budget for employees to spend as they see fit.</p>
  <p>EVs’ star is rising as sustainability nears the top of many consumer, corporate, and government priority lists. Over 80% of automobile manufacturers have committed to <a href="https://www.gartner.com/en/marketing/research/auto-us-2020">electrifying</a> their lineup in the near future, and some plan to go all electric within the decade. Modernizing the transportation industry means rethinking mobility as concept to make sure EVs pay off on the sustainable promise.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Follow me: @smgaler</em><br><em><a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2021/03/16/evs-go-mainstream-how-to-plug-into-the-sustainable-energy-power-of-e-mobility/?sh=2fba8aab2c82">This story originally appeared on SAP BrandVoice on Forbes</a></em>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/automotive</category>
            <category>news-tag/discrete-industries</category>
            <category>news-tag/e-mobility</category>
            <category>news-tag/electric-vehicles</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>industry/travel-transportation</category>
            <category>news-tag/renewable-energy</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-labs-network</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Electrification of Mobility: Challenges and Opportunities for Travel and Transportation Operators]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/e-mobility-travel-transportation-operators</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/e-mobility-travel-transportation-operators</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP recently hosted an industry forum about the e-mobility with leading operators and industry value chain actors. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-footprint</category>
            <category>news-tag/electric-vehicles</category>
            <category>news-tag/mobile</category>
            <category>industry/travel-transportation</category>
            <category>news-tag/service-industries</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Not-So-Obvious Lessons Learned Managing a Global Vaccine Distribution Cold-Chain]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/vaccine-supply-chain-lessons-distribution-cold-chain</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/vaccine-supply-chain-lessons-distribution-cold-chain</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Vaccine supply chain lessons learned this year are setting companies up for future excellence. Discover how quick pivots have imparted wisdom.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/travel-transportation</category>
            <category>news-tag/covid-19</category>
            <category>industry/healthcare</category>
            <category>industry/life-sciences</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Digitalization Supports Business Continuity]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/digitalization-business-continuity-during-covid-19</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/digitalization-business-continuity-during-covid-19</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[For many SAP customers, digitalization has supported their business continuity during COVID-19. Learn how four companies thrived.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/travel-transportation</category>
            <category>news-tag/covid-19</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/digitalization</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>