<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/industry-cloud/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP and Infosys Introduce New Sustainable and Innovative Industry Cloud Solution]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/sap-and-infosys-introduce-sustainable-industry-cloud-solution</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/sap-and-infosys-introduce-sustainable-industry-cloud-solution</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With the SAP-validated partner use case program, Infosys and SAP created a solution to help companies monitor their carbon footprints.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_164f38f864e0733a6806af629b2d24613241a4b15.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_164f38f864e0733a6806af629b2d24613241a4b15.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_164f38f864e0733a6806af629b2d24613241a4b15.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP and Infosys Introduce New Sustainable and Innovative Industry Cloud Solution" src="./media_164f38f864e0733a6806af629b2d24613241a4b15.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-and-infosys-introduce-new-sustainable-and-innovative-industry-cloud-solution">SAP and Infosys Introduce New Sustainable and Innovative Industry Cloud Solution</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>In today’s fast-paced and dynamic business environment, <a href="/topics/sustainability">sustainability</a> is no longer a buzzword; it’s a critical business priority. Investors and customers seek more sustainable business practices from their solution providers and enterprises are keenly focused on integrating sustainability into their operations. This is no easy lift, and it doesn’t happen overnight. Several challenges need to be addressed, including action planning, effective resource allocation, and prioritization.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>For companies to act sustainably, responsibly, and efficiently, they must harness the power of data-driven decisions and advanced technology to reduce their carbon footprint and create sustainable product portfolios. Enter SAP and its broad ecosystem of industry cloud partners with a shared vision to help businesses become strategic, sustainable, intelligent enterprises.</p>
  <h2 id="hack2build-opens-door-for-innovation-and-sustainability">Hack2Build Opens Door for Innovation and Sustainability</h2>
  <p>The <a href="https://events.sap.com/hack2build/en/home">Hack2Build event from SAP</a>, organized by SAP Co-Innovation Lab, is an initiative designed to harness the creativity and speed of prototyping industry cloud solutions by SAP partners in days as opposed to weeks. At a September 2022 Hack2Build event, SAP partner Infosys presented a solution for organizations to identify, track, predict, and refine carbon emissions during sales and operations planning (S&#x26;OP) and make sustainable decisions. The solution, <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2023/08/7affe1f5-847e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Sustainable S&#x26;OP and Carbon Footprint Management</a>, was built using SAP Integrated Business Planning (SAP IBP) for Supply Chain, SAP S/4HANA, SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP), SAP Integration Suite, and SAP Sustainability Footprint Management.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="industry-cloud-solutions-from-sap-and-partners-can-help-you-find-a-competitive-edge">Industry cloud solutions from SAP and partners can help you find a competitive edge</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/industry-cloud.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="framework-for-tracking-emissions-leverages-the-power-of-saps-industry-cloud">Framework for Tracking Emissions Leverages the Power of SAP’s Industry Cloud</h2>
  <p>Infosys’ carbon footprint solution calculates carbon emissions based on greenhouse gas protocols and global warming potential factors across an organization’s procurement, production, and distribution processes. It helps calculate key information, such as estimates of CO2e emissions per order level, thereby helping to make decisions that can ensure a smaller carbon footprint. The solution also provides an innovative framework to help companies identify, track, predict, and refine their carbon emissions numbers throughout the entire supply chain process.</p>
  <h2 id="sap-validated-partner-use-case-program-offers-momentum-to-service-partner-solution">SAP-Validated Partner Use Case Program Offers Momentum to Service Partner Solution</h2>
  <p>Infosys’ solution is part of the SAP-validated partner use case program. The program was established to give SAP service partners the ability to showcase, position, and promote solutions and spotlight their expertise of SAP Business Technology Platform, leveraging the power of SAP’s vast customer base and industry networks.</p>
  <p>The SAP-validated partner use case program offers service partners the ability to:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Get amplified market reach</strong>: Increased visibility enables service partners to target a broader audience, opening doors to new markets and untapped opportunities. Leveraging SAP’s robust platform, partners can position themselves strategically and expand their global reach.</li>
    <li><strong>Collaborate and co-innovate</strong>: Participating in the SAP-validated partner use case program can foster collaboration with SAP experts, industry leaders, and customers.</li>
    <li><strong>Access a dynamic ecosystem</strong>: Partners can benefit from SAP’s ecosystem, where they can collaborate, exchange knowledge, and share best practices with some of the industry’s best leaders.</li>
    <li><strong>Develop customer-centric solutions</strong>: The program helps put the customer at the core of solution development. Service partners can gain valuable customer insights though interactions facilitated by SAP, leading to better-tailored products and services that can precisely address users’ pain points.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>The program presents opportunities for both customers and service partners to flourish. By achieving certification, service partners can earn credibility, expand market reach, and foster collaborative innovation with industry giants. Its streamlined processes help accelerate time-to-market, providing a significant advantage in today’s fast-paced business landscape.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-information-training-tools-and-resources-you-need">Get the information, training, tools, and resources you need</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://partneredge.sap.com/en/welcome.html?pexpRequestedURL=%2Fen%2Flibrary%2Feducation%2Fpsd%2F2023%2Fmar%2Fe_oe_te_w_rnbo_31837.html">Visit the SAP Partner Portal site</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The program unlocks a door to a dynamic ecosystem where partners can learn, grow, and develop customer-centric solutions that can meet industry demands head-on. For partners aiming to thrive in their respective industries, this program is a game changer. Service partners are encouraged to embrace the power of the SAP-validated partner use case program and transform their business.</p>
  <p>“Infosys is delighted to publish the Infosys Sustainable S&#x26;OP and Carbon Footprint Management Solution through the SAP-validated partner use case program,” said Atul Chorbele, AVP at Infosys. “We are confident that customers across industries will benefit from adopting this solution.”</p>
  <p>Holger Brammer, Global Partner Ecosystem vice president at SAP, praised this partner solution and the development process: “It was impressive to see how fast Infosys developed this solution on SAP BTP and integrated it with SAP S/4HANA, SAP IBP, and SAP Sustainability Footprint Management. I’m quite confident that this solution will resonate very well with customers.”</p>
  <p>To learn how to build industry innovation on SAP BTP and the SAP-validated partner use case program or get more information about <a href="mailto:lucca.sperl@sap.com">validated use cases on the SAP PartnerEdge site</a>, contact <a href="mailto:lucca.sperl@sap.com">Lucca Sperl</a>, industry cloud innovation program lead. To learn more about Infosys’ solution, <a href="https://www.infosys.com/campaigns/documents/sop-carbon-footprint-management.pdf">visit here</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>Vidya Gugnani is senior director and industry cloud ecosystem lead for Strategic Partners, North America at SAP.<br>Nitin Majahan is COE lead for SAP Industrial Manufacturing at Infosys.</p>
        <p>Top image courtesy of SAP employee Karsten Hohage</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-emissions</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-footprint</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-integrated-business-planning-for-supply-chain</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Industry Innovation Gives Partners a Runway for Sustained Success]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/industry-cloud-innovation-sap-partners-success</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/industry-cloud-innovation-sap-partners-success</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP's industry cloud offers partners boundless opportunities to cultivate new markets, customers, and revenue sources. Read to learn how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11d9ba4b00dd11ddbd90c3e316d0c28742fc92154.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11d9ba4b00dd11ddbd90c3e316d0c28742fc92154.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_11d9ba4b00dd11ddbd90c3e316d0c28742fc92154.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="How Industry Innovation Gives Partners a Runway for Sustained Success" src="./media_11d9ba4b00dd11ddbd90c3e316d0c28742fc92154.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="how-industry-innovation-gives-partners-a-runway-for-sustained-success">How Industry Innovation Gives Partners a Runway for Sustained Success</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Have you ever wondered at the workings of the modern airport and the ecosystem around it, how so many complex and disparate moving parts come together to deliver a high-quality travel experience to flyers?</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Granted, those experiences aren’t always positive. But when everything is working in sync – travel and transportation infrastructure, aerospace technology, energy, retail, hospitality, and more – to create a whole greater than the sum of its parts, my thoughts can’t help but shift skyward, to another more familiar ecosystem.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="grow-and-find-a-competitive-edge-with-industry-cloud-solutions-from-sap-and-partners">Grow and find a competitive edge with industry cloud solutions from SAP and partners</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/industry-cloud.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Among the many developments I’ve witnessed lately as a result of SAP’s growing focus on industry innovation, SAP’s industry cloud and the partner ecosystem that supports it stand out. They’re proving my long-held belief that a high level of collaboration with partners across companies and industries, similar to what occurs at airports, can open boundless opportunities to cultivate new markets, customers, and revenue sources. SAP’s industry cloud has yielded close to 400 solutions across 25 industry verticals, 80% of which were developed by partners either on their own or in collaboration with SAP. About 1,900 unique customers are using these solutions, and they’re renewing them at a rate above 90%.</p>
  <p>What’s driving the industry innovation momentum? And why should SAP partners consider engaging in the co-innovation effort if they’re not already, or get more involved if they are? Here are five competitive justifications:</p>
  <ol>
    <li><strong>Future readiness:</strong> A business landscape that is perpetually shifting and evolving, often in unexpected ways, demands a business mindset that embraces change and seeks out opportunities to innovate – a mindset of future readiness. A focus on industry innovation fosters future readiness on multiple levels. It gives partners a portfolio of solutions to help their customers prepare for a future where cloud solutions will be instrumental to their digital transformation efforts. One leading global consulting firm predicts that by 2027, enterprises will be using industry cloud platforms to accelerate more than half of their critical business initiatives. What’s more, working within an industry cloud environment like SAP’s can give partners themselves a future-ready model for growing their business.</li>
    <li><strong>Business ecosystems and networks:</strong> By bringing their industry knowledge and intellectual property to a business ecosystem like the one that supports SAP’s industry cloud, partners can become a multiplier for industry innovation, moving solutions through the development pipeline and to customers faster together than they otherwise could working individually. We’re witnessing this multiplier effect within specific industries like consumer products, life sciences, automotive, energy, and industrial manufacturing, where collaboration within industry-focused business ecosystems is fueling a fresh wave of co-innovation.</li>
    <li><strong>Modularity and integration:</strong> One of my team’s responsibilities is to maintain the industry cloud opportunity map, a comprehensive architecture of potential and already developed solutions that comprise the present and future of industry innovation in the cloud. A glance at the opportunity map tells a compelling story about all the white space available to partners to fill out the portfolio. Intellectual property and ideas are the building blocks in this case. The door is wide open for partners to bring use cases that enhance, extend, or add to an existing solution, or that fill gaps in the opportunity map. Using SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP) and SAP Store, they can rapidly develop their ideas and turn them into commercialized solutions that customers can readily integrate.</li>
    <li><strong>Industry convergence:</strong> Just like at the airport, we’re seeing the lines between industries blur and converge as traditional value chains merge. This creates massive opportunities for SAP partners to develop new revenue streams around solutions that they adapt from one industry for use in another, or that can be used by customers across multiple industries. Electric vehicle charging is sparking a convergence among automotive, energy, oil and gas, utility, and retail and consumer products, for example. And that, in turn, is providing fertile territory for SAP partners with use cases and intellectual property in these areas to collaborate and create new solutions that can add value for customers.</li>
    <li><strong>Customer experience:</strong> By focusing on industry innovation, our goal is to give customers exactly what they need to succeed from a digital solutions standpoint. The better SAP, our partners, and all of us collectively as an ecosystem are at delivering the solutions customers need, the more trust we create with them. And that opens even more possibilities for SAP, partners, and customers alike – possibilities that conjure the familiar feeling I get at the airport when I’m waiting to board my next flight.</li>
  </ol>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Sven Denecken is senior vice president and chief marketing and solutions officer for SAP Industries &#x26; CX.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-store</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Recent Partner-Driven Project Wins Highlight Huge Industry Cloud Opportunities]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/partner-gsps-wins-highlight-sap-industry-cloud-opportunities</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/partner-gsps-wins-highlight-sap-industry-cloud-opportunities</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Global strategic partners (GSPs) are driving a surge of activity, collaboration, and investment in SAP's industry cloud. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Industry Cloud Builds on the Past to Invent a Future Where Industries Converge and Boundaries Disappear]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/industry-cloud-future-industries-converge-boundaries-disappear</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/industry-cloud-future-industries-converge-boundaries-disappear</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP's industry cloud is driving business transformation and innovation, empowering enterprises through partner-focused digital solutions.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP's Industry Cloud Drives Innovation in Utilities Through Cloud-Based Apps and Partner Collaborations]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/sap-industry-cloud-drives-innovation-in-utilities</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/sap-industry-cloud-drives-innovation-in-utilities</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP's industry cloud is driving innovation in the utilities sector through cloud-based apps and partner collaborations. Read to learn how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-co-innovation-lab</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-store</category>
            <category>industry/utilities</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Channel Partners Can Write a Profitable New Chapter in the Industry Cloud Story]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/channel-partners-profitable-industry-cloud</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/channel-partners-profitable-industry-cloud</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP channel partners are leveraging industry cloud to help diversify their businesses and monetize their intellectual property. Read how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unlocking Industries’ Full Potential with SAP Business AI]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/unlocking-industries-full-potential-sap-business-ai</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/unlocking-industries-full-potential-sap-business-ai</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[We have embedded SAP Business AI functionality in our industry-specific solutions to help optimize our customers' strategic areas.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[What Is Customer Loyalty?]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/what-is-customer-loyalty</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/what-is-customer-loyalty</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Effectively measuring and learning from customer behavior with loyalty solutions is the key to taking customer loyalty to the next level.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1095042ae655d1c2458fed3b507068ee0b10d7433.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1095042ae655d1c2458fed3b507068ee0b10d7433.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1095042ae655d1c2458fed3b507068ee0b10d7433.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="What Is Customer Loyalty?" src="./media_1095042ae655d1c2458fed3b507068ee0b10d7433.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="what-is-customer-loyalty">What Is Customer Loyalty?</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>What makes you stick with a brand – is it the quality of the product or service? Is it the support you receive when something goes wrong? Is it the availability in the market or the compatibility with other products? Is it the rewards you are offered for being a loyal customer?</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>When I’m in the market for new sport shoes, I stick to the brand that I know is the most comfortable for me. There’s nothing worse than buying a pair of sneakers and going jogging with them for the first time, only to realize in the first few minutes of your run that they don’t fit properly.</p>
  <p>On the other hand, if I’m shopping for groceries, it’s how healthy the product is, then the selection, freshness, and price that matter the most. Time is also a factor – the quicker I can find exactly what I need, the better.</p>
  <p>But what happens if another sport shoe manufacturer sets up a loyalty program, allowing me to collect points and offering discounts? Or, what if a new grocery store opens that allows me to save even more time by eliminating the checkout counter? Would that make me change my buying behavior?</p>
  <p>What I’m talking about is loyalty in the context of <a href="/topics/crm-customer-experience">customer experience</a>. It’s different for every industry. How can you as a supplier or service provider ensure that you are offering the best experience possible to your customers?</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="intelligent-cx-solutions-from-sap-help-connect-customer-data-and-improve-loyalty">Intelligent CX solutions from SAP help connect customer data and improve loyalty</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="loyalty-is-a-very-noisy-space">Loyalty Is a Very Noisy Space</h2>
  <p>Recently, I spoke to Riad Hijal, head of Commerce Solution Management at SAP Customer Experience. “Loyalty is a very noisy space. I think for retailers, for example, to be successful and ultimately drive customer lifetime value through loyalty, they need to cut through that noise,” he said. “We as consumers are faced with dozens of rewards or loyalty accounts – most of them aren’t really driving any kind of real modification in behavior. We don’t buy more just because we have a loyalty account with someone and are collecting points; we are merely using it as a discount mechanism. That’s how to do loyalty wrong.”</p>
  <p>Loyalty requires a reimagination of the loyalty experience and underlying process. To stand out from the crowd, companies need to be leveraging measurement. In addition, what are the themes that we need to focus on to rethink loyalty to truly drive long-term customer value? What does the measurement look like? According to Hijal, historically, efficient and tangible measurement has been lacking in loyalty programs due to the complexity of the topic.</p>
  <h2 id="what-should-loyalty-solutions-really-be-offering">What Should Loyalty Solutions Really Be Offering?</h2>
  <p>By leveraging data and analytics, a loyalty platform helps businesses understand why customers regard certain experiences as more memorable and important than others. This allows businesses to dig deeper into the different elements of behavior-driven customer loyalty.</p>
  <p>And, the truth is, data is siloed within a multitude of systems within your organization. As a company, you need to be able to reconcile all of it, across both transactional and behavioral dimensions so that you can understand which customers are truly profitable and worth your focus. With SAP Customer Data Platform, for example, which is part of RISE with SAP, you can prioritize your customers with intelligent insights delivered by the platform. See more about SAP Customer Data Platform in <a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2023/04/8ad02f10-6e7e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">this video</a>.</p>
  <p>As such, there are key capabilities necessary for modern experiential loyalty platforms. These are rewards and incentive management, personalization, gamification, communication and engagement, feedback and surveys, data-driven insights, and integration and convenience.</p>
  <h2 id="puma-and-mention-me-an-industry-cloud-solution">PUMA and Mention Me: An Industry Cloud Solution</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="watch-how-rise-with-sap-can-help-you-prioritize-your-customers">Watch how RISE with SAP can help you prioritize your customers</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2023/04/8ad02f10-6e7e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As a leading sports brand, PUMA wanted to transform its fan base to a key growth-driver by not only attracting new customers, but also improving brand awareness and loyalty. Mention Me, an industry cloud partner solution, in combination with SAP Emarsys Customer Engagement, helped PUMA launch referral programs in six European countries.</p>
  <p>PUMA has integrated Mention Me with SAP Emarsys Customer Engagement, its customer relationship management (CRM) platform. This helps equip PUMA to serve seamless customer journeys that drive more referrals, such as sending reward reminders and encouraging referrers to introduce more friends. PUMA is also able to feed first-party referral data into the CRM platform in real time – growing its database and giving a whole new level of insight. The combination of these solutions is giving the company remarkable growth, increasing its ROI through referral to six times its investment just nine months after launching the campaigns. <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2023/05/0227ee79-727e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Learn more about this transformation</a>.</p>
  <h2 id="valora-revolutionizing-convenience-store-shopping">Valora: Revolutionizing Convenience Store Shopping</h2>
  <p>Valora wanted to better meet customer needs by combining the convenience of a physical store with the simplicity of a digital business model. This was the beginning of its newest brand of cashier-free convenience store – avec box. To help realize the project, Valora chose SAP Customer Experience solutions, used the rich knowledge available with SAP Services and Support, and worked with Webtiser AG and Pagnos GmbH on a proof of concept. The goal was to start with a single store, using a minimal viable product collaboration approach, then scale the solution further.</p>
  <p>Now, Valora is winning new customers by offering them an even more convenient and flexible shopping experience – without the hassle of waiting in line at the cash register. Plus, with customers registering with the avec app, Valora is able to get new insight into what customers want. Not only does make it possible to give personalized recommendations, but it is also now easier than ever for Valora to reward customer loyalty and keep people coming back for more. <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/04/9c274ed9-dc7d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff.html">Read the full story here</a>.</p>
  <h2 id="measurement-is-key">Measurement Is Key</h2>
  <p>Effectively measuring and then learning from customer behavior with loyalty solutions to improve reward experiences is the key to taking customer loyalty to the next level. “Since loyalty is such a mature space, measurement is key,” said Hijal. “Most loyalty programs are abundant and don’t achieve much, but focusing on measurement is what the next generation of loyalty programs is all about.”</p>
  <p>Speaking of next generation, SAP Customer Experience solutions are also artificial intelligence (AI)- and machine learning-fueled. These types of insights can help you make each customer feel like they are your only customer. They can help you engage and understand consumers on their terms while respecting their privacy preferences during the customer journey, to retain and upsell using machine learning and smart automation.</p>
  <p>So, the next time I’m in the market for sports shoes, maybe the AI-fueled loyalty program will be able to convince me to try something new…and stick with it.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Sven Denecken is senior vice president and chief marketing and solutions officer for SAP Industries and CX.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-customer-data-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-customer-experience</category>
            <category>product/sap-emarsys-customer-engagement</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Creating an Agile, Resilient, and Sustainable Logistics Network]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/creating-agile-resilient-sustainable-logistics-network</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/creating-agile-resilient-sustainable-logistics-network</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP's Till Dengel shares how industrial manufacturing businesses can drive an agile, resilient, and sustainable logistics network.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/travel-transportation</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-network-for-logistics</category>
            <category>product/sap-warehouse-robotics</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Accelerating the Sustainable Energy Transition with SAP's Industry Cloud]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/sustainable-energy-transition-sap-industry-cloud</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/sustainable-energy-transition-sap-industry-cloud</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Oil, gas, and energy businesses can channel the power of SAP's industry cloud to ensure a secure, affordable, and sustainable future.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/net-zero</category>
            <category>industry/oil-gas-energy</category>
            <category>news-tag/renewable-energy</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Leveraging SAP’s Industry Cloud, Going from Concept to Commercialization Can Be Fast and Fulfilling]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/cogniac-sap-syntax-industry-cloud</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/cogniac-sap-syntax-industry-cloud</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The industry cloud partnership between Cogniac, Syntax, and SAP illustrates how combining forces can deliver more value to customers.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>product/sap-digital-manufacturing</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-store</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-io</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Celebrating People’s Differences with Inclusive Fashion]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/06/celebrating-differences-inclusive-fashion</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/06/celebrating-differences-inclusive-fashion</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The fashion industry is just one example of how SAP helps customers stay ahead of market dynamics and industry innovation and convergence.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/fashion</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-experience-center</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Supporting All Farmers with Technology to Sustainably Feed the World]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/06/supporting-farmers-with-technology-sap-intelligent-agriculture</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/06/supporting-farmers-with-technology-sap-intelligent-agriculture</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With SAP Intelligent Agriculture, an industry cloud solution from SAP, agribusiness companies can become more sustainable and efficient.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/agribusiness</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Direct-to-Consumer Imperative for Today’s Consumer Product and Retail Brands]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/the-d2c-imperative-consumer-product-retail-brands</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/the-d2c-imperative-consumer-product-retail-brands</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[When faced with the D2C imperative, SAP is uniquely positioned to help consumer product and retail brands drive profitable results.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/consumer-goods-cpg</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-customer-experience</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Retail Order Management: Everything, Everywhere, All at Once]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/retail-order-management-everything-everywhere-all-at-once</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/retail-order-management-everything-everywhere-all-at-once</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Retail order management solutions can help build enjoyable omnichannel shopping experiences for customers while improving profit margins.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Intelligent Data Drives Growth Across Farm-to-Consume Food Value Chain]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/intelligent-data-drives-growth-food-value-chain</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/intelligent-data-drives-growth-food-value-chain</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP’s industry cloud can help help fresh produce companies use data to make better decisions for managing the food value chain.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/agribusiness</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-store</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Partners Drive a Wave of Industry Cloud Innovation in Discrete Manufacturing]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/sap-partners-industry-cloud-innovation-discrete-manufacturing</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/sap-partners-industry-cloud-innovation-discrete-manufacturing</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP and its partners are capitalizing on industry cloud opportunities in the discrete manufacturing industries. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-store</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[In Life Sciences and Healthcare, SAP’s Industry Cloud Is Key to Innovation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/life-sciences-healthcare-sap-industry-cloud</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/life-sciences-healthcare-sap-industry-cloud</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP’s industry cloud is helping life sciences and healthcare customers preserve and improve human health one innovation at a time.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/healthcare</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>industry/life-sciences</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Consumer Industries Witness Surge of Innovation, Thanks to SAP’s Industry Cloud Partners]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/consumer-industries-innovation-sap-industry-cloud-partners</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/consumer-industries-innovation-sap-industry-cloud-partners</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Industry cloud solutions from SAP and our partners are changing the way consumer industries customers do business.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/consumer-goods-cpg</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-store</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Supports Utilities Across the EU to Enable Energy Transition]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/utilities-energy-transition-eu</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/utilities-energy-transition-eu</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP supports utilities in the energy transition across the EU to address the need for decarbonization along with volatile energy prices.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>industry/oil-gas-energy</category>
            <category>industry/utilities</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP’s Industry Cloud Success Depends on Partners]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/01/sap-industry-cloud-success-depends-on-partners</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/01/sap-industry-cloud-success-depends-on-partners</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[More than two and a half years after its introduction, evidence is mounting that SAP’s industry cloud is an idea whose time has come.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Five Ways Automakers and Suppliers Can Prepare for the Future of Mobility]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/five-ways-automotive-industry-future-of-mobility</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/five-ways-automotive-industry-future-of-mobility</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[EVs, mobility-as-a-service, operational resilience, and digital retail are shaping the future of mobility in the automotive industry.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/automotive</category>
            <category>news-tag/catena-x</category>
            <category>news-tag/electric-vehicles</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-e-mobility</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-industry-network-for-automotive</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Digital Innovations Behind the Booming Life Sciences Industry]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/digital-innovations-life-sciences-industry</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/digital-innovations-life-sciences-industry</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The pandemic has irrevocably disrupted the life sciences industry, revealing a new vision for innovation from cloud-based collaboration.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/covid-19</category>
            <category>news-tag/forrester</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>industry/healthcare</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>industry/life-sciences</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Making Innovation Consumption Easier for Customers]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/industry-cloud-enterprise-agreements-easier-innovation-consumption</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/industry-cloud-enterprise-agreements-easier-innovation-consumption</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Through industry cloud enterprise agreements, SAP is offering more innovation and value for customers with a flexible consumption model.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cashew Coast Modernizes Cashew Processing with SAP]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/cashew-coast-sap-rural-sourcing-management</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/cashew-coast-sap-rural-sourcing-management</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Cashew Coast chose SAP Rural Sourcing Management to help modernize nut processing and provide farmers with more transparent prices.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-rural-sourcing-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Take: Water, War, Weather and Wheat Ignite Interest in Farming Technology]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/the-take-farming-technology-water-war-weather-wheat</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/the-take-farming-technology-water-war-weather-wheat</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[An agricultural crisis has been brewing for years and now only 10 weeks of global consumption of wheat exists. Get SAP's take on how technology can help.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>content-type/perspective</category>
            <category>industry/agribusiness</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/the-take</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Helping Shape the Future of the Cell and Gene Therapy Supply Chain]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/cell-and-gene-therapies-future-supply-chain</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/cell-and-gene-therapies-future-supply-chain</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Cell and gene therapies are a new frontier of patient-centric care. A new SAP solution will fill the technology gap in administering CGT.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>industry/life-sciences</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Discover Cross-Industry Innovation in the Cloud and Become a Sustainable Intelligent Enterprise]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/03/cross-industry-innovation-in-cloud-sustainable-intelligent-enterprise</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/03/cross-industry-innovation-in-cloud-sustainable-intelligent-enterprise</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Create a new future for your industry. SAP MaxAttention can help you explore innovations from other industries for a strategic advantage.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1209fa9218a6020a66789a0550bc78dbeeb17891e.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1209fa9218a6020a66789a0550bc78dbeeb17891e.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1209fa9218a6020a66789a0550bc78dbeeb17891e.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Discover Cross-Industry Innovation in the Cloud and Become a Sustainable Intelligent Enterprise" src="./media_1209fa9218a6020a66789a0550bc78dbeeb17891e.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="discover-cross-industry-innovation-in-the-cloud-and-become-a-sustainable-intelligent-enterprise">Discover Cross-Industry Innovation in the Cloud and Become a Sustainable Intelligent Enterprise</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Lines between industries are blurring, and it isn’t enough for your business to be the best in its class. Automotive newcomers are uprooting long-standing industry leaders and embracing concepts from their friends in high tech. Manufacturers are taking notes from consumer products and debuting as-a-service offerings that increase revenue. Oil and gas companies are transforming into full-scale energy providers. The list goes on.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP solutions and services can help your business start thinking, acting, and innovating like a leader – a leader from another industry, that is. Through <a href="https://www.sap.com/services/premium-engagement/maxattention.html?sort=latest_desc">SAP MaxAttention</a>, you can lean on our expert knowledge and experience of your industry – and many more – as you explore new technologies on the way to a successful digital transformation. Take advantage of industry cloud solutions from SAP, including more than 200 industry-specific applications built by SAP and SAP partners.</p>
  <p>With SAP’s industry cloud, you can optimize and transform at a much faster pace. SAP MaxAttention can show you how to use these solutions to build innovations – without overhauling entire systems or putting limitations on what you can do with your data. With our help, you can:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Access innovation in modular, consumable packages</li>
    <li>Plug innovations in quickly without disrupting existing technologies and processes</li>
    <li>Reach across categories to get ideas, apps, and solutions from other industries</li>
  </ul>
  <p>SAP’s industry cloud can provide a foundation for innovation and transformation, connecting you to a community of in-depth SAP expertise, top thinkers, investors, and disruptors. Now, it’s your turn to create a new future with the cloud. When you trust <a href="/topics/sap-maxattention">SAP MaxAttention</a>, you’ll work with us to grow and evolve based on innovative technology trends and next practices – using SAP’s industry cloud – that cross industry lines.</p>
  <h2 id="assess-the-industry--and-your-it-architecture">Assess the Industry – And Your IT Architecture</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="subscribe-to-the-quarterly-sap-maxattention-newsletter">Subscribe to the quarterly SAP MaxAttention newsletter</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/nl/insights-customer-newsletter.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Trends and best practices are changing all the time, and it can be hard for a busy business to keep up. You may know your competitors use technologies such as the cloud to provide better customer experiences, but you can’t possibly know how their technology infrastructures look and perform. Yet, this knowledge is a prerequisite to creating a successful and competitive technology strategy.</p>
  <p>More specifically, we can help you uncover the potential that new technology holds for your business and what your IT architecture needs before it can take advantage of automation, artificial intelligence (AI), the Internet of Things (IoT), and other next-generation innovations. These innovations are key to realizing the transformation into a sustainable intelligent enterprise. For instance, leaders across industries are using automation to eliminate manual tasks and digital waste that contribute to their carbon footprint.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="access-the-services-methods-tools-and-expertise-that-you-need-to-succeed-with-sap-maxattention">Access the services, methods, tools, and expertise that you need to succeed with SAP MaxAttention</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/services/premium-engagement/maxattention.html?sort=latest_desc">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="what-about-retail">What about retail?</h3>
  <p>As the shift from bricks to clicks increases, we can help a retailer understand the imperative for omnichannel customer experiences, such as the ability to offer personalized products and experiences that boost customer retention. Our services can reveal how retail businesses can break down silos that separate valuable customer data insights from the systems that need them.</p>
  <h2 id="demonstrate-real-value-with-proof-of-concepts">Demonstrate Real Value with Proof of Concepts</h2>
  <p>Engagements with SAP MaxAttention are designed to help create both quick wins and long-term value. We help develop proof-of-concept (PoC) projects that demonstrate the real benefits of SAP’s industry cloud and how it can transform and optimize your existing business processes and create opportunities for new business models, such as:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Increased supply chain visibility across globally distributed production facilities</li>
    <li>Transparency into the logistics network (such as fleet, trucks, containers, and so on)</li>
    <li>Asset risk management and asset care strategies to improve plant reliability and safety</li>
    <li>Omnichannel solutions to orchestrate multichannel salesforce</li>
    <li>Personalized products for unique end-customer needs</li>
    <li>More competitive products made possible by providing origination and provenance data</li>
    <li>Better workforce planning thanks to better visibility into historical data and the ability to leverage forecasts</li>
  </ul>
  <p>Our experts can also help you measure success, setting success criteria for your PoC that you can present to the business and other stakeholders to prove the value of digital transformation.</p>
  <h3 id="what-about-the-automotive-industry">What about the automotive industry?</h3>
  <p>Carmakers, suppliers, and dealerships are under intense pressure to transform their businesses and prepare for the future of mobility. SAP solutions can help run traditional automotive businesses profitably and more sustainably while driving new growth with innovative new mobility business models.</p>
  <h2 id="extend-industry-innovation">Extend Industry Innovation</h2>
  <p>You can’t stop at achieving what the rest of your industry has already done. To create a competitive advantage, you need to take your innovations a step further. SAP MaxAttention can help bring your business up to speed with trends in your industry and others and then build upon those innovations using your unique business strengths as a strategic advantage.</p>
  <p>During this step, SAP MaxAttention can help integrate the innovations created with our experts into your technology landscape and connect them with existing applications. For instance, you can connect your industry applications on SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP) with your finance or logistics data in SAP S/4HANA or third-party solutions. SAP’s industry cloud can extend SAP S/4HANA, our line-of-business cloud solutions, and SAP Business Network with industry next practices.</p>
  <h3 id="what-about-consumer-products">What about consumer products?</h3>
  <p>Consumer products companies need to act with agility to meet the fast-changing needs of customers. SAP services can quickly demonstrate the value of AI by deploying a chatbot that helps handle simple customer service requests and empowers human agents to tackle higher-value tasks.</p>
  <h2 id="realize-your-digital-transformation">Realize Your Digital Transformation</h2>
  <p>After demonstrating the value of your PoC, we can help you build the rollout plan for the full-scale deployment of industry cloud solutions from SAP. SAP MaxAttention can help achieve a smooth activation of your new or enhanced solution for a go-live without business disruption.</p>
  <h3 id="what-about-manufacturing">What about manufacturing?</h3>
  <p>Working together, we can reveal how a manufacturer might use Industry 4.0 throughout its factories to gain real-time insight into asset performance. Industry 4.0 opens the door to a new level of predictive maintenance that helps manufacturers avoid disruption and stay as profitable as possible.</p>
  <h2 id="exceed-expectations-with-sap-maxattention-and-saps-industry-cloud">Exceed Expectations with SAP MaxAttention and SAP’s Industry Cloud</h2>
  <p>Whether you’re a business in wholesale distribution, automotive, professional services, high tech, consumer products, chemicals, retail, utilities, or any of the industries supported by SAP’s industry cloud, our services are designed for you. We’ve reinvented our services based on industry trends, next practices, and the needs of your business. You can expect our experts to focus holistically on your business – and not on a rigid set of steps or concepts that weren’t created with you in mind.</p>
  <p>Start creating real results based on the outcomes your business needs. To learn more about SAP MaxAttention, <a href="https://www.sap.com/services/premium-engagement/maxattention.html?sort=latest_desc">visit us online</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Markus Steer is Premium Engagement Services lead for Cloud Success Services at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/automotive</category>
            <category>industry/consumer-goods-cpg</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-maxattention</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Industry Cloud: Advancing Business Transformation for a Changing World]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/01/industry-cloud-solutions-business-transformation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/01/industry-cloud-solutions-business-transformation</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP makes industry cloud solutions available for organizations to optimize, extend, and transform their core business processes.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1757da8a7acfbe5a5106c2cdd6ac202a6380443f0.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1757da8a7acfbe5a5106c2cdd6ac202a6380443f0.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1757da8a7acfbe5a5106c2cdd6ac202a6380443f0.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Industry Cloud: Advancing Business Transformation for a Changing World" src="./media_1757da8a7acfbe5a5106c2cdd6ac202a6380443f0.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="industry-cloud-advancing-business-transformation-for-a-changing-world">Industry Cloud: Advancing Business Transformation for a Changing World</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Justifiably proud of their digital accomplishments, most companies still suffer from a false sense of digital capabilities. Their increasing attention on evolving customer experiences, product and service innovations, production efficiencies, and competitive advantages leaves little room for driving much needed change in core operations, such as facility management or payroll processing.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>But the world is changing, and keeping one foot on the gas pedal for higher visibility projects while pumping the brakes with the other foot for back-office changes is not enough to keep up. Businesses must rapidly move both aspects of their digital strategies in unison to drive significant progress so that competitors are challenged to keep pace.</p>
  <p>With <a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/industry-cloud.html?source=social-global-news-blog-IEumbrella-2021-industrycloud">industry cloud solutions</a>, organizations can achieve this balance.</p>
  <h2 id="modernizing-industries-to-meet-unique-expectations">Modernizing Industries to Meet Unique Expectations</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="shop-industry-cloud-solutions-on-sap-store">Shop industry cloud solutions on SAP Store</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://store.sap.com/dcp/en/industry-cloud">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP makes industry cloud solutions easier to discover, subscribe to, and use, offering customers access to unified user experiences, familiar design paradigms, and plug-and-play integrations to reinvent themselves and their markets simultaneously. Organizations from every industry can then deploy specialized solutions to optimize, extend, and transform their core business processes by digitalizing and automating operations across their business.</p>
  <p>For example, <strong>utilities</strong> companies are shifting operations to provide more <a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2021/06/2abac107-e87d-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html?source=social-global-news-blog-IEumbrella-2021-industrycloud">sustainable and renewable energy</a> in response to growing demand for decarbonization and decentralization. Industry cloud solutions can be used to combine Big Data-enabled energy data management for millions of end devices on a cloud-based, open platform with smart, industry-specific analytics and integration to support energy-related core processes.</p>
  <p>Meanwhile, <strong>logistics service providers</strong> can collect various types of information from their vehicle fleets with a <a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2021/06/e0f83fc4-f47d-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html?source=social-global-news-blog-IEumbrella-2021-industrycloud">digital vehicle hub</a> enabled by an asset network. By consolidating multiple data sources into a single network-based cloud platform, they can rapidly ramp up new business models, monetize vehicle information across customer channels, and enable collaboration and innovation with third-party participants.</p>
  <p><strong>Consumer products companies</strong> also have access to an intelligent virtual assistant that streamlines the <a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2021/09/e2ec4787-f77d-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html?source=social-global-news-blog-IEumbrella-2021-industrycloud">trade claims management</a> process and eliminates the need for manual matching and auditing. The solution leverages embedded machine learning to automate steps, reduce errors, and help avoid disputes. Organizations can then aggregate and enrich market activity in real time, accelerate balance sheet reconciliation with greater accuracy, lower the cost per claim, and enhance workflow productivity — all while establishing stronger customer relationships.</p>
  <p>With an industry cloud solution, <strong>retailers</strong> can improve their <a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2021/10/1cb575ce-fd7d-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html?source=social-global-news-blog-IEumbrella-2021-industrycloud">intelligent returns management</a> processes through embedded machine learning models and an analytics engine that accelerate and ease profitable decision-making. The solution turns the challenges of product returns into opportunities that improve customer retention and brand connection with a fluid returns experience for consumers, while increasing productivity and lowering processing costs across sales channels.</p>
  <p>Retailers can also benefit from an <a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2021/11/4e536978-087e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html?source=social-global-news-blog-IEumbrella-2021-industrycloud">order management foundation</a> developed to centralize the monitoring, analysis, and management of their omnichannel order processes. By optimizing nodes in their network — such as distribution centers, stores, dark stores, and third-party drop shipping — they can reduce costs, improve agility, and increase brand satisfaction by meeting their customer promises as expected.</p>
  <p>Industry cloud solutions can even enable emerging industries, such as <strong>automotive original equipment manufacturers (</strong> OEMs) installing and operating residential and commercial charging stations for electric vehicles. An <a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2021/11/509d5249-077e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html?source=social-global-news-blog-IEumbrella-2021-industrycloud">e-mobility</a> solution integrates end-to-end billing processes with one platform to lower energy costs and avoid expensive grid-connection expenditure through connections to energy service providers. And for their customers, the cost of improving their carbon footprint and impact on the planet becomes more affordable.</p>
  <h2 id="competing-as-an-ecosystem-forged-by-innovation">Competing as an Ecosystem Forged by Innovation</h2>
  <p>Business transformation begins with an idea – whether fixing a problem or discovering and creating new value. But eventually, companies translate ideas differently to address their industry’s unique market dynamics, customer demands, public expectations, and regulatory pressures.</p>
  <p>For SAP customers, the answer to turning their ideas into meaningful technologies, products, services, business models, or people experiences is an industry cloud solution designed to meet their unique reality. Doing so offers the scale, access, and support they need to adapt to emerging dynamics continuously and rapidly, without sacrificing process efficiency or disrupting their other innovation efforts.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="augment-your-intelligent-enterprise-with-industry-cloud-solutions">Augment your intelligent enterprise with industry cloud solutions</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/industry-cloud.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="visit-the-sap-store-site-to-explore-and-access-the-latest-industry-cloud-solutions-from-sap">Visit the <a href="https://store.sap.com/dcp/en/product/display-0000008655_live_v1?source=social-global-news-blog-IEumbrella-2021-industrycloud">SAP Store</a> site to explore and access the latest industry cloud solutions from SAP.</h3>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Joe Pacor is senior director of Industries Marketing at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/automotive</category>
            <category>industry/consumer-goods-cpg</category>
            <category>news-tag/electric-vehicles</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-store</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Brose, Capgemini, and SAP Turn Vision into Value with Co-Innovation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/brose-capgemini-sap-vision-value-co-innovation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/brose-capgemini-sap-vision-value-co-innovation</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Together, SAP, Brose, and Capgemini developed a secure and autonomous and self-service supplier portal application in the cloud.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f5b3863a99b077d04dca118f2028734b4b2d07ed.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f5b3863a99b077d04dca118f2028734b4b2d07ed.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1f5b3863a99b077d04dca118f2028734b4b2d07ed.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Brose, Capgemini, and SAP Turn Vision into Value with Co-Innovation" src="./media_1f5b3863a99b077d04dca118f2028734b4b2d07ed.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="brose-capgemini-and-sap-turn-vision-into-value-with-co-innovation">Brose, Capgemini, and SAP Turn Vision into Value with Co-Innovation</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>German automotive supplier Brose Fahrzeugteile SE &#x26; Co. KG has co-innovated with Capgemini and SAP on the development of a secure and autonomous self-service supplier portal application in the cloud.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In an era of business disruptions and rapid technology advancements, companies must adopt continuous innovation to stay ahead and win by leading the change. Co-innovation, as a form of inside-out open innovation, has evolved as a way of breaking down the traditional innovation silos.</p>
  <p>At SAP, co-innovation occurs every day in a multitude of ways. We work with partners, customers, universities, governments, standardization groups, and others — all of which contribute to creating sustainable and mutual competitive advantage.</p>
  <p>SAP has embraced an openness within our ecosystem that serves to accelerate the overall innovation process in creating solutions that deliver value. Co-innovation is part of SAP’s DNA.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="augment-your-intelligent-enterprise-with-industry-cloud-solutions">Augment your intelligent enterprise with industry cloud solutions</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/industry-cloud.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="handling-a-complex-network-of-suppliers">Handling a Complex Network of Suppliers</h2>
  <p>What does a co-innovation project look like? A collaboration with longtime customer Brose and trusted partner Capgemini offers a perfect — even <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/feed/update/urn:li:activity:6877628384382394369/">award-worthy</a> — example.</p>
  <p>Looking back at more than 100 years of corporate history, including numerous patent applications, Brose combines tradition with innovation. As the fourth-largest automotive supplier in family ownership, it has established itself as one of the top 40 companies in the industry worldwide, operating 65 locations in 24 countries. With that comes a complex network of suppliers, including more than 2,000 production-relevant suppliers and 8,000 supplier-employees who frequently provide different functional services to different Brose companies.</p>
  <p>With a self-service supplier portal solution, Brose created a space where the digital interaction between suppliers and Brose easily can take place, enabling suppliers to manage their accounts on their own. This way, they can both receive and maintain information and data needed. The supplier portal acts as the single point of contact, providing transparency over supplier users, making collaboration faster and more effective.</p>
  <p>“For me, innovation always starts with a business challenge that needs to be solved,” said Christian Ley, CIO at Brose Fahrzeugteile SE &#x26; Co. KG. “To see what we have achieved now, developing a solution tailored to our needs using state-of-the-art technology, is both exciting and a great example of what is possible through collaboration.”</p>
  <p>Working together with Capgemini, a global leader in consulting, digital transformation, technology, and engineering services – as well as one of SAP’s strategic partners for co-development and co-innovation in the automotive industry – Brose decided to bring the idea to the next level by making it available for other companies, as it addresses an industry-wide challenge.</p>
  <p>“We are delighted to co-innovate together with SAP and Brose in creating Capgemini’s Supplier Integration for Automotive (CSI4Auto),” Josean Mendez, vice president and global SAP partner executive lead at Capgemini, shared. “This solution is an excellent example of what we aspire to achieve in partnering with SAP. This innovative approach is a blueprint for future engagements and adds to SAP and Capgemini’s value in the automotive market.”</p>
  <h2 id="leveraging-the-power-of-the-cloud-and-sap-btp">Leveraging the Power of the Cloud and SAP BTP</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="deliver-innovative-solutions-on-the-road-to-new-mobility-with-sap-software">Deliver innovative solutions on the road to new mobility with SAP software</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/automotive.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP provides infrastructure ready to scale with <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">SAP Business Technology Platform</a> (SAP BTP), which supports integration, conversion of data to value, and extensibility for SAP and third-party application and data assets.</p>
  <p>Instead of building a custom development solution from scratch, the development team identified the right blend of services from SAP BTP to solve the problem at hand. The services helped the team to reduce both the development time and the custom software development to a minimum.</p>
  <p>Running in the cloud the application is planned to be part of SAP’s industry cloud solution portfolio, making it easy for future customers to extend their end-to-end processes and adopt at their own pace.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Stefan Krauss is senior vice president and general manager of Discrete Industries and Energy &#x26; Natural Resources</em> <em>at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/automotive</category>
            <category>news-tag/capgemini</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>