<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/industry/aerospace-defense/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Beyond Gravity’s All-Out Mission to the Cloud]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/beyond-gravity-all-out-mission-to-cloud</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/beyond-gravity-all-out-mission-to-cloud</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Beyond Gravity wants its new ERP system to leverage all the benefits of the cloud. That’s why it chose SAP S/4HANA Cloud, public edition.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_113a605ea1984c28f221f383c1bceeb834e36b214.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_113a605ea1984c28f221f383c1bceeb834e36b214.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_113a605ea1984c28f221f383c1bceeb834e36b214.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Beyond Gravity’s All-Out Mission to the Cloud" src="./media_113a605ea1984c28f221f383c1bceeb834e36b214.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="beyond-gravitys-all-out-mission-to-the-cloud">Beyond Gravity’s All-Out Mission to the Cloud</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>As it seeks to modernize its software environment, Beyond Gravity wants to take full advantage of the cloud. That’s why this leading supplier to the space industry is on an all-out mission to move its enterprise resource planning (ERP) system to SAP S/4HANA Cloud, public edition.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>While catastrophic asteroid impacts have been rare in Earth’s history, the threat asteroids pose to life on our planet is very real. With that in mind, NASA and ESA launched a mission in 2021 to test a method of planetary defense that involved deflecting Dimorphos – one part of the Didymos double-asteroid system – from its orbit by crashing a spacecraft into it. In part two of the mission, due to begin in October 2024, an orbiter known as “Hera” will lift off and, in October 2026, begin examining the effects of the test on Dimorphos.</p>
  <h2 id="beyond-gravity-space-technology-that-protects-the-planet">Beyond Gravity: Space Technology That Protects the Planet</h2>
  <p>“Protecting Earth from asteroids that could pose a threat to us all is an exciting and important task,” says Johan Eckerstein, CIO at <a href="https://www.beyondgravity.com/en">Beyond Gravity</a>. Headquartered in Switzerland, Beyond Gravity is one of a group of suppliers of high-tech equipment for Hera and is responsible for delivering the spacecraft’s two solar wings. In addition to a variety of satellite components, the space technology specialist also builds launch vehicles, and a third, smaller division serves the growing lithography market. According to <a href="https://tracxn.com/d/companies/beyond-gravity/__QK2dffK8fa4oRH-CPhnHBwvcMXuZWSoULX-BlkhJ9pg">market intelligence platform Tracxn</a>, Beyond Gravity ranks third among 21 competitors in its field.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_108755bdc5e12d7d14543f48c7855cb4f4c61bb27.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_108755bdc5e12d7d14543f48c7855cb4f4c61bb27.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_108755bdc5e12d7d14543f48c7855cb4f4c61bb27.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_108755bdc5e12d7d14543f48c7855cb4f4c61bb27.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="742">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>Image courtesy of Beyond Gravity.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14b0ad30a9b8b56ddb5fda4631cadf07d864b5982.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14b0ad30a9b8b56ddb5fda4631cadf07d864b5982.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_14b0ad30a9b8b56ddb5fda4631cadf07d864b5982.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_14b0ad30a9b8b56ddb5fda4631cadf07d864b5982.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="681">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>Johan Eckerstein. Image courtesy of Beyond Gravity.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="ezyone-transformation-project-flight-path-to-the-future">EZYOne Transformation Project: Flight Path to the Future</h2>
  <p>“Our ambition is to be the No. 1 space technology supplier, the most innovative and most exciting company to work for,” says Eckerstein. As CIO, his job is to put the technology in place to make that vision a reality. The EZYOne program he initiated in October 2022 was a crucial first step in that process.</p>
  <p>Beyond Gravity is the legal successor to RUAG Space, the space division of Swiss technology group RUAG International. So while it only began operating as a startup under its new name in May 2022, it has decades of experience in the space industry. With the company due to be privatized soon, its EZYOne digital transformation project is as necessary as it is challenging.</p>
  <p>As the name implies, the idea is to make things easier. Beyond Gravity has historically grown from various companies and locations. Currently, there are various sites with different IT systems that are not linked to each other.</p>
  <p>With EZYOne, Beyond Gravity is preparing to become a digital-first company that will leverage artificial intelligence (AI), machine learning, augmented reality (AR), and many other emerging technologies. The first step is to build a common digital core that will enable the company to unlock tremendous value and new ways to serve customers.</p>
  <h2 id="sap-s4hana-cloud-public-edition-seven-becomes-one">SAP S/4HANA Cloud, Public Edition: Seven Becomes One</h2>
  <p>Each of Beyond Gravity’s business divisions has built up its own vast pool of expertise over the years. But when it comes to IT, the company’s colorful history means it now has a mishmash of legacy systems – comprising seven different ERP systems alone – and, thus, an array of complex, inefficient, and costly processes.</p>
  <h2 id="it-solutions-in-use-at-beyond-gravity-in-2023">IT solutions in use at Beyond Gravity in 2023</h2>
  <ul>
    <li>7 ERP systems</li>
    <li>8 product lifecycle management (PLM) systems</li>
    <li>5 business process management systems</li>
    <li>2 manufacturing execution systems (MES)</li>
  </ul>
  <p>EZYOne lifted off in October 2022. “We began by defining the architecture we wanted for our new IT landscape,” explains Eckerstein. That process led to a number of design principles aimed at ensuring the project was a success. They included:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>One solution of each type for all business units</li>
    <li>Cloud first</li>
    <li>Standard first (out of the box)</li>
    <li>No technical data in the ERP system</li>
    <li>Rapid go-live in the first quarter of 2024</li>
  </ul>
  <p>When it came to selecting an ERP solution – and based on these criteria – Beyond Gravity opted for SAP S/4HANA Cloud, public edition. “From the perspective of an agile startup and the global market leader we aspire to become, cloud is the only way to go,” says Eckerstein. “When you choose a cloud solution, you are committing more to a provider’s road map than to a static product. And, as a midsize company, we can benefit from a vendor like SAP that has the infrastructure and resources to provide the solution reliably and securely.” This, he adds, eases the pressure on IT teams and frees up time for value-adding tasks.</p>
  <h2 id="standard-covers-92-of-processes">Standard Covers 92% of Processes</h2>
  <p>Eckerstein points out, however, that if you want to enjoy the benefits of the public cloud, you have to be consistent in your approach. Essentially, when you transform business processes, that means sticking as far as possible to the standard version of the public cloud solution. Beyond Gravity defined the following rules:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>80% of processes must be covered by the standard – and adapted to it if necessary.</li>
    <li>Key processes not covered by the standard must be added to SAP’s to-do list and implemented within a specified time frame.</li>
    <li>Where non-key processes are not covered by the standard, alternatives must be explored, such as a third-party solution, manual process, or other neat solution.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>The result of this approach surprised even Eckerstein: “We managed to cover 92% of all processes with the standard solution. And in finance, we didn’t find a single gap!” There were many other practical benefits, such as:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Managers can be able to call up a status overview of all projects in real time – for any country or currency – with just a few clicks.</li>
    <li>Intracompany processes can become more efficient, thanks to the option of using fully automated ordering and confirmation and in-transit goods tracking.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>The percentage of processes not covered by the standard may be small, but it can represent a huge gap if even one of those processes is mission-critical.</p>
  <p>Beyond Gravity has also got SAP – SAP Switzerland, to be precise – on board as an implementation partner to give it the most direct line possible to the SAP developers working on the cloud ERP solution.</p>
  <h2 id="public-cloud-erp-a-calculated-risk">Public Cloud ERP: A Calculated Risk</h2>
  <p>Beyond Gravity is now halfway along the project timeline. The solution was completed in September 2023 and is currently in its initial testing phase – with the first go-live scheduled for March 2024 in Sweden. “This kind of speed is only possible in the public cloud,” says Eckerstein, “and only if you adopt the right mindset.” In other words, if you want to enjoy the benefits of the public cloud, you have to be willing to take a certain amount of risk that you would avoid with an on-premise installation and trust that the provider’s road map will take you where you want to go. But, as Eckerstein adds, “This has nothing to do with blind trust; it’s about objectively calculating the risks involved.”</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Top image courtesy of SAP employee Trupti Warad</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/aerospace-defense</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unleashing Automation for a Resilient Aerospace & Defense Sector]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/unleashing-automation-resilient-aerospace-defense-sector</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/unleashing-automation-resilient-aerospace-defense-sector</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The aerospace and defense industry needs ways to overcome labor shortage-driven production challenges. Automation solutions and SAP can help]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/aerospace-defense</category>
            <category>news-tag/automation</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-twin</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-4-0</category>
            <category>news-tag/rpa</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-signavio</category>
            <category>product/sap-warehouse-robotics</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Take: In the Satellite Age, Weather Balloons Still Have a Use, Even for Weather]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/the-take-weather-balloons-satellite-age</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/the-take-weather-balloons-satellite-age</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[From satellites to weather balloons, weather information today is a conglomeration of various sources of data. Get SAP's take on its use.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>content-type/perspective</category>
            <category>industry/aerospace-defense</category>
            <category>news-tag/the-take</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sustainability Takes Flight across Aviation Industry]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/sustainability-aviation-industry</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/sustainability-aviation-industry</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Airplane manufacturers are moving towards a holistic strategy for sustainable design throughout an airplane’s entire life cycle. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/aerospace-defense</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-footprint</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-neutrality</category>
            <category>news-tag/circular-economy</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>product/sap-enterprise-product-development</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Take: Artemis to Lift Off to Innovate and Inspire]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/09/the-take-artemis-innovation-inspiration</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/09/the-take-artemis-innovation-inspiration</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Moon missions, in all their stages, inspire. What will NASA's Artemis give rise to? Get SAP's take on the opportunity for innovation.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>content-type/perspective</category>
            <category>industry/aerospace-defense</category>
            <category>news-tag/the-take</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Digital Learning Skyrockets as High-Growth Industries Invest in Top Talent]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/high-growth-industries-digital-learning-invest</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/high-growth-industries-digital-learning-invest</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In high-growth industries like aerospace and defense, leaders are building the workforce needed for growth with continuous digital learning.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/aerospace-defense</category>
            <category>news-tag/covid-19</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-work-zone</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Innovation Metrics: Figure Out Which Projects to Pursue]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/innovation-metrics-figure-out-which-projects-to-pursue</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/innovation-metrics-figure-out-which-projects-to-pursue</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Innovation metrics and KPIs help assess investments, knowing when to double down and when to kill an idea instead.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1adb1e63281d22597cfcd27c5e41facdffd03b393.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1adb1e63281d22597cfcd27c5e41facdffd03b393.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1adb1e63281d22597cfcd27c5e41facdffd03b393.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Businesswoman on laptop at window in morning sun" src="./media_1adb1e63281d22597cfcd27c5e41facdffd03b393.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1044">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="innovation-metrics-figure-out-which-projects-to-pursue">Innovation Metrics: Figure Out Which Projects to Pursue</h1>
        <p>Successful innovation requires assessing investments – and using metrics to decide whether to keep pursuing an idea or stop.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Paul Puopolo, who became executive vice president of innovation at Dallas Fort Worth International Airport (DFW) in August 2018, arrived at his new job with a clear mandate to standardize the innovation function.</p>
  <p>“DFW had always been innovative, but it was more of an ad hoc innovation model,” says Puopolo. Innovation was largely comprised of isolated early-stage initiatives with variable business cases and few formal tools or processes. Puopolo’s goal was to build an optimized innovation model – in his words, “repeatable, scalable, and pervasive” – capable of having a clear impact on the organization’s results.</p>
  <p>Plenty has been written about the importance of creating a culture of innovation – and doing so has been essential to the evolution that’s taking place at DFW. Less discussed is the need for what might seem anathema to innovation: process. For companies that are betting their future growth on their ability to innovate, creating a process for measuring it is critical.</p>
  <p>Veterans like Puopolo (who previously held innovation posts at MetLife, Highmark, and Humana) know that while innovation requires new thinking, it also demands rigor – and clear metrics for success – to deliver business value.</p>
  <p>Three years into Puopolo’s tenure, DFW is no longer flying blind when it comes to its innovation journey. The airport’s innovation business function (emphasis on <em>business</em> and <em>function</em>) has a dashboard that tracks innovation programs and key performance indicators (KPIs). Performance on goals, rather than instincts, drives decision-making.</p>
  <p>Among the innovation group’s projects are two designed to improve travelers’ experiences while meeting security requirements. In 2020, DFW began exploring Mastercard’s digital identity services and SITA’s Smart Path passenger processing application so that employees could access facilities using mobile face-scan technology (that ultimately could provide touchless passenger checkpoints). In December 2021, the group launched a self-service check-in and bag-drop process with Spirit Airlines that uses <a href="/blogs/biometrics-sensing-healthy-society">biometrics</a> and meets regulatory requirements for identifying travelers.</p>
  <p>For companies that are betting their future growth on their ability to innovate, creating a process for measuring it is critical.</p>
  <p>DFW also tested seven new technologies to support location-based services in the terminal and is moving forward on a proof-of-concept to manage curbside passenger traffic, congestion, and transportation usage.</p>
  <p>Corporate leaders across industries recognize the importance of innovation. According to a recent <a href="https://www.bcg.com/en-us/publications/2021/most-innovative-companies-overview">Boston Consulting Group survey</a>, three-quarters of CEOs (a 10% jump over the previous year) indicated that innovation was a top-three priority for their organizations. Among these large companies, the biggest innovation spenders devote tens of billions of dollars to their efforts each year. However, there is little connection between the amount of money a company <em>spends</em> on its innovation efforts and what it <em>achieves</em>. <a href="https://www.strategyand.pwc.com/gx/en/insights/innovation1000.html">PWC found</a> that there is no long-term correlation between innovation spend and a company’s overall financial performance. What matters most is how companies manage their innovation resources and measure their efforts throughout the innovation lifecycle.</p>
  <p>“Generating new ideas creates a lot of excitement, and so there’s a lot of focus there in companies,” says Andrew Binns, director with Change Logic, a consultancy that helps clients ideate, incubate, and scale new businesses inside existing organizations. “The difficulty is in making them happen.”</p>
  <p>What separates companies that innovate successfully in the long term is not the number of ideas they generate. It’s not simply setting up a shiny new innovation lab (though that can certainly help). It’s not necessarily disrupting a given industry or product category. It’s assessing whether the company is investing in the right kinds of activities to achieve its goals, weeding out underperforming initiatives, and pivoting to new opportunities. And it’s applying this kind of discipline in uncertain circumstances.</p>
  <p>Companies that derive value from their efforts have mastered the less sexy aspect of innovation: metrics. They expand beyond the traditional measures of success for R&#x26;D (innovation spend as a percentage of total sales, number of new ideas, and percentage of sales from new products). And they build an arsenal of benchmarks, such as:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Conditions conducive to innovation (the percentage of employees who have received innovation training and gained new competencies, adoption of collaboration and innovation management tools)</li>
    <li>Qualitative impact (number of innovations that significantly advance existing businesses, number of new-to-company opportunities, active customers or users)</li>
    <li>Financial impact (ROI of new products, services, or business models)</li>
    <li>Innovation sourcing (best performing business units, team, or categories; third-party innovation)</li>
    <li>Idea pipeline tracking (ideas-to-project ratios, number of projects stopped, innovation pipeline performance)</li>
  </ul>
  <p>If that sounds like a lot of work, that’s because it is. “This is the challenge,” says Binns, author of the forthcoming book <em><a href="https://www.amazon.com/Corporate-Explorer-Corporations-Entrepreneurs-Innovation/dp/1119838320">Corporate Explorer: How Corporations Beat Startups at the Innovation Game</a></em>. “Ideation is so exciting. Incubation is boring, hard work that you’ve got to sustain.”</p>
  <p>However, it’s doable. In fact, it’s being done. Companies that are reaping the benefits of innovation put in place specific metrics, mindsets, and processes to better manage their innovation resources and investments. For organizations that are serious about transformation and growth, metrics are mandatory.</p>
  <p>Scott Anthony, partner at global strategy and innovation consulting firm Innosight, says that innovation leaders have to make resource choices. “Which efforts should get more funding, and which shouldn’t? Which should be accelerated, and which should be killed? Is the overall spending on innovation too much or too little or just right? Without performance metrics, it’s hard to make these kinds of decisions,” says Anthony.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d4f8e441a5ad1343b84c74b4398ff3f1c2801ff5.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d4f8e441a5ad1343b84c74b4398ff3f1c2801ff5.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1d4f8e441a5ad1343b84c74b4398ff3f1c2801ff5.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Businesswoman explaining chart to coworker" src="./media_1d4f8e441a5ad1343b84c74b4398ff3f1c2801ff5.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="746" height="560">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="kpis-of-the-unknown-why-measuring-innovation-is-hard">KPIs of the unknown (why measuring innovation is hard)</h2>
  <p>Managing by measuring is nothing new and is typically straightforward. Traditional KPIs monitor things we already know something about; innovation is different by design. It’s the opposite of business as usual. Yet, to yield results, it also requires the rigorous application of unique metrics for success. Without metrics and processes specific to innovation, companies may pull the plug too early on ideas and efforts that fail to deliver early results in traditional corporate performance metrics. Conversely, they may invest too much ahead of real testing and learning, betting big on what they hope is the next big thing. Or they may generate a lot of new ideas but have no way to assess, manage, incubate, or scale them.</p>
  <p>So how <em>do</em> you measure innovation? Unfortunately, there are no one-size-fits-all metrics to deploy and few best practices to apply across initiatives or industries. The metrics will depend on what kinds of innovation an organization is pursuing, what the innovation goals are, where the efforts are in their innovation lifecycles, and how mature the organization’s innovation program or capabilities are – for a start.</p>
  <p>“Every organization is different, so you need to innovate in context,” says Puopolo of DFW. That means you need to speak, define, and measure innovation in a way that works for your organization.</p>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div data-valign="middle">Innovation is about managing uncertainty. Metrics tell you whether or not you are on track toward your goal and so increase confidence that the new venture will pay off. But they do not eliminate the need for judgment and leadership.</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div data-valign="middle">Andrew Binns, Director, Change Logic</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>For example, in a culture that values process, innovation metrics will emphasize the efficiency and effectiveness of the innovation pipeline. The metrics might include not just the number of ideas entering the pipeline but also the diversity of ideas (in terms of sourcing or business area application), the rate at which ideas move through each stage of the innovation process, or an innovation pipeline index that incorporates a number of salient metrics.</p>
  <p>At DFW, Puopolo began with some basic action-based process metrics to establish an innovation portfolio and pipeline. That meant tracking items like “the number of ideas in discovery” and the number of pilot tests and test programs transitioned to the business for implementation. It wasn’t until year two that his team began including culture-related metrics, such as the numbers of innovation training sessions, the training participants, and the executive sponsors of innovation. In year three, he put in place metrics to track the longer-term impact of the group’s projects in areas such as customer satisfaction, employee engagement, project and portfolio revenue generation or cost savings, number of new business models, and brand awareness.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_100438b4b1d3a44794458f4c5408bd26b51ca3282.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_100438b4b1d3a44794458f4c5408bd26b51ca3282.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_100438b4b1d3a44794458f4c5408bd26b51ca3282.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Businesswoman sitting on chair with laptop while colleagues walking around" src="./media_100438b4b1d3a44794458f4c5408bd26b51ca3282.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="843" height="560">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="building-a-game-changing-portfolio-of-innovation-metrics-and-kpis-takes-time">Building a game-changing portfolio of innovation metrics and KPIs takes time</h2>
  <p>In 2020, Central European insurer Uniqa Insurance (a Change Logic client) launched an innovation-focused business unit called SanusX with its own budget, staff, governance, and metrics to measure progress. The structure protects the unit from the short-term pressures of the core business. The unit’s two levels of innovation metrics help leaders determine what innovations to pursue and demonstrate their value to the business. At one level, there are lead indicators of progress toward a business goal, which will vary based on the goal (such as rate of customer adoption of a new app or increased customer retention).</p>
  <p>“These help them understand whether a proposed new venture is on track,” says Binns of Change Logic. There are also the more tactical objectives and key results measures that focus on execution in each sprint cycle.</p>
  <p>In the first year, SanusX ran more than 30 experiments related to seven new business ideas and terminated two unnecessary projects. The insurer now has a rich pipeline of opportunities that are being accelerated and scaled with its partners and potential acquisitions. In its first year, the SanusX team introduced a digital COVID-19 application (developed in less than a month) to help clients coordinate testing, sample collection, results delivery, and follow-up communication, which enabled thousands of tests per day at a rate ten times faster than standard testing protocols at the time.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="what-does-it-take-to-drive-innovation">What does it take to drive innovation?</h3>
        <p>One rule of thumb: Innovation = invention X commercialization.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="https://news.sap.com/2022/01/six-drivers-of-innovation-make-magic-happen-for-your-organization/">Read six more insights</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The outcomes don’t always happen overnight. They can take years. The innovations that win in the marketplace aren’t always a shiny new app or disruptive business model that rises from nowhere. Companies that take a <a href="https://insights.sap.com/what-is-enterprise-performance-management/">performance management</a> approach to innovation metrics aren’t wed to ideas; they’re focused on results that align with their business strategies. Sometimes the results look more like a slow march toward new products, business models, and ultimately growth, which involve partnerships, acquisitions, and new applications of existing technologies and resources — requiring consistent attention and potentially new roles from leaders including CEO, <a href="/blogs/the-changing-role-of-the-cio">CIO</a>, COO, and more.</p>
  <p>Analog Devices, for example, had long been known for its signal processing circuits and semiconductors empowering mobile phones, cars, manufacturing machinery, hospital scanners, and satellites. In 2013, new CEO Vince Roche sought to offer customers not just components but systems that incorporated hardware, software, and analytics.</p>
  <p>Working with Change Logic, Analog Devices reset its metrics for innovation. Managers who would otherwise be incentivized by short-term revenue gains needed new performance metrics to encourage innovation. All innovation projects were given a set of early success factors that, when tracked over time, would indicate if an initiative was heading in a positive direction. “They tell them whether the business is getting market traction,” says Binns. “A dashboard of lead indicators helps them manage uncertainty because they know whether the innovation is tracking to expectations or whether they need to pivot their approach.”</p>
  <p>Companies that take a performance management approach to innovation metrics aren’t wed to ideas; they’re focused on results that align with their business strategies.</p>
  <p>Eight years ago, Analog Device’s director of technology for the wireless communications business unit began exploring a software-defined radio solution that could accelerate 5G adoption using smaller, lower-cost, more energy-efficient technology capable of supporting eight times the bandwidth. Aside from engineering advances, key indicators were whether customers were committing to the end products that were signaling a shift toward 5G (such as new systems for base stations). That gave the company confidence that they were onto something. The system was an early win for the new innovation approach and today generates more than US$1.5 billion in revenue.</p>
  <p>“Innovation is about managing uncertainty. Metrics tell you whether or not you are on track toward your goal and so increase confidence that the new venture will pay off,” says Binns. “But they do not eliminate the need for judgment and leadership.”</p>
  <h2 id="where-to-begin-best-practices-for-innovation-performance-management">Where to begin: Best practices for innovation performance management</h2>
  <p>Managing innovation performance with the same rigor as traditional business factors (but using different metrics) is the key to long-term success. The specifics of metrics and governance will vary by an organization’s goals and needs. And achieving maturity in determining how best to measure and manage innovation will take time. There are several existing tools that leaders can use to determine where their organizations are on the innovation maturity scale (from ad hoc to optimized) and what gaps they need to address. Beyond that initial assessment, there are three categories of best practices that organizations can adopt to develop more effective innovation metrics over time:</p>
  <h3 id="identify-and-address-cultural-obstacles">1. Identify and address cultural obstacles</h3>
  <ul>
    <li><em>Insulate innovation from short-term pressure.</em> Many organizations address this by creating an innovation unit that is insulated from core business demands. Those without an innovation group can provide education on innovation-specific metrics, mindsets, and processes best suited to managing innovation resources and investments.</li>
    <li><em>Build behaviors.</em> Measuring behaviors – such as participation in innovation boot camps – better assesses a cultural shift than standard KPIs. “Training employees on how to be everyday innovators, running boot camps, or hosting tech talks can impact engagement, recruiting, and retention,” says Puopolo of DFW. “These activities build the innovation culture but are often overlooked.”</li>
    <li><em>Celebrate innovation “not invented here.”</em> The best use of innovation funding is not always building a new product or approach in-house. P&#x26;G, for example, tracks the number of ideas that come from <a href="https://us.pg.com/blogs/external-business-partners-honored-in-excellence-awards/">thousands of outside partnerships</a>.</li>
    <li><em>Communicate consistently and clearly.</em> Commit to a regular cadence to tell the innovation story and educate the organization. At DFW, this approach helped build transparency and consistency that was critical in the early stages of the new innovation programs, Puopolo says.</li>
  </ul>
  <h3 id="build-measurement-and-decision-making-processes">2. Build measurement and decision-making processes</h3>
  <ul>
    <li><em>Create some accountability metrics.</em> In the formative days, it’s important to show that innovation performance management is on the right track. This means holding the team accountable for practicing what it preaches and for the pipeline’s progress. “Impact metrics are required to keep the naysayers at bay and to provide cover while your program matures,” says Puopolo of DFW.</li>
    <li><em>Get clear about the destination.</em> It’s important to identify end goals <em>before</em> considering how to evaluate performance. Once you determine strategic areas to focus on, you can better determine what new initiatives to pursue. And thinking ahead to what might indicate whether each innovation is on track makes it easier to decide on success metrics for that initiative.</li>
    <li><em>Combine short- and long-term metrics.</em> Short-term metrics will focus on activities and long term on business impact. Puopolo says he tracked things such as number of business cases, pilot projects, killed projects, innovation training, and participants in the early days to build credibility and show early wins. Later, he added metrics such as revenue generation, cost savings, employee engagement, and customer satisfaction.</li>
    <li><em>Track the rejected ideas.</em> A good innovation program will nix a great number of ideas. This seemingly negative metric is a positive indicator: It suggests that the organization is investigating a broad swath of opportunities. When the number is low, the organization may not be trying hard enough. Providing an accounting of this activity is also useful to an innovation group’s development, according to Puopolo, who says, “While it seems negative, it shows the methodology and the value of the process.”</li>
  </ul>
  <h3 id="manage-innovation-metrics-at-the-portfolio-level">3. Manage innovation metrics at the portfolio level</h3>
  <ul>
    <li><em>Consider a balanced scorecard approach.</em> Innosight’s Anthony advises tracking a selection of metrics related to inputs and outputs to measure performance of innovation. Using the approach of a <a href="https://balancedscorecard.org/bsc-basics-overview/">balanced scorecard</a> (the performance management report that companies use to track strategy implementation activities and outcomes), innovation leaders can identify strategic goals and indicators in categories such as financial impact, customer impact, internal processes, and employee learning. Anthony says the purpose of an innovation scorecard is to track whether the organization has the right raw materials for innovation, how effective it has been at generating innovations, and what value those innovations have created.</li>
    <li><em>Measure portfolio returns.</em> Like a financial portfolio, organizations can measure their overall returns on innovation investment. A basic calculation takes the profits or cash flows produced (or expected) by innovation and divides that figure by the cumulative investment required to create those returns. Anthony offers a more nuanced approach to calculating innovation magnitude (financial contribution divided by successful ideas), innovation success rate (successful ideas divided by total ideas explored), and investment efficiency (ideas explored divided by total capital and operational investment).</li>
    <li><em>Leave room for learning.</em> There is the <a href="/blogs/thinkers-stop-metrics-mania">danger of being too beholden to metrics</a>. The process of measurement should serve the goal of innovation – not the other way around. Some of the greatest value of experimentation is the learning that emerges. Thus, it’s important to build some flexibility into the management and measurement of innovation.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1401fc0ecce8853bed65c4455c0a38eabf7c05026.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1401fc0ecce8853bed65c4455c0a38eabf7c05026.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1401fc0ecce8853bed65c4455c0a38eabf7c05026.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_1401fc0ecce8853bed65c4455c0a38eabf7c05026.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="840" height="560">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p>Innovation metrics will change over time. A focus on innovation pipeline metrics in the beginning should evolve to include other metrics as the innovation program grows. A mature innovation program can report real business impacts such as increased customer loyalty or satisfaction, revenue growth, cost savings, and efficiency gains.</p>
  <p>Puopolo’s DFW innovation group has seen its metrics evolve from scratch. Today, it has a one-page dashboard that highlights innovation processes and performance, including the number of ideas in different innovation stages, with a mix of initiative types (incremental, differentiating, transformational). The dashboard tracks which departments are innovation adopters and key strategic or cultural efforts that are underway. “As your innovation program matures, your metrics should adapt as well,” Puopolo says. “What numbers best measure the program’s progress will be based on where you are in your innovation journey.”</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>industry/aerospace-defense</category>
            <category>content-type/what-is</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>