<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/dynamic-teams/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dynamic Teams: How to Optimize the Outcomes of Increasingly Fluid Work Experiences]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/06/dynamic-teams-optimize-fluid-work-experiences</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/06/dynamic-teams-optimize-fluid-work-experiences</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Cohesive and cross-functional team strategies that support organizational agility unlock the door to dynamic teams. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/dynamic-teams</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-opportunity-marketplace</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-people-analytics</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-performance-goals</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP SuccessFactors Unlocks Global Innovation Velocity with Next-Generation Cloud Delivery]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/sap-successfactors-next-generation-cloud-delivery</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/sap-successfactors-next-generation-cloud-delivery</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Next-Generation Cloud Delivery creates the foundation for our SAP SuccessFactors innovation road map. Read to learn more about the campaign.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/dynamic-teams</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Future Workforce: Talent When You Need It, from Wherever People Want to Be]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/future-workforce-planning-talent-when-you-need-it</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/future-workforce-planning-talent-when-you-need-it</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The supply of people and the demand for skill sets have become more dynamic than ever. Read to find out how this affects workforce planning.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/dynamic-teams</category>
            <category>news-tag/future-of-work</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>news-tag/total-workforce-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP SuccessFactors Second Half 2022 Release: Building a Future-Ready Workforce Today]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/sap-successfactors-second-half-2022-release</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/sap-successfactors-second-half-2022-release</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The SAP SuccessFactors second half 2022 release introduces new innovations around creating an agile and future-ready workforce. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1074c8b37f11498501b456579a1cc6d70dabc96f4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1074c8b37f11498501b456579a1cc6d70dabc96f4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1074c8b37f11498501b456579a1cc6d70dabc96f4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP SuccessFactors Second Half 2022 Release: Building a Future-Ready Workforce Today" src="./media_1074c8b37f11498501b456579a1cc6d70dabc96f4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-successfactors-second-half-2022-release-building-a-future-ready-workforce-today">SAP SuccessFactors Second Half 2022 Release: Building a Future-Ready Workforce Today</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>In today’s business landscape, organizations must equip themselves to respond to workforce opportunities or challenges <em>before</em> they arise. If recent trends have taught us anything, it’s that by the time a business reacts to a market shift, a new one is already occurring. Staying a step ahead of workforce demands is no longer a step ahead – it’s step one.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The SAP SuccessFactors second half 2022 release, which is available for preview today, introduces new innovations focused on empowering organizations to create an agile and future-ready workforce in a rapidly changing workplace as well as further investments for individualized experiences and agile and compliant HR.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="realizing-a-people-centered-future-of-work-through-the-intelligent-enterprise">Realizing a People-Centered Future of Work Through the Intelligent Enterprise</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/06/people-centered-future-of-work-intelligent-enterprise-hxm">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="creating-a-future-ready-workforce">Creating a Future-Ready Workforce</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="change-the-world-of-work-for-good-with-the-next-generation-of-hcm-software-from-sap">Change the world of work for good with the next generation of HCM software from SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In the face of increasingly complex and more urgent transformations, organizations must accelerate their talent development at scale. At the core of such adaptability is an understanding of the skills organizations need to build and grow. As part of our early adopter care program, select customers will have access to skills ontology, growth portfolio, and dynamic teams, which work together to deliver greater intelligence on the skills and capabilities that currently exist and are needed within an organization.</p>
  <p><strong>The skills ontology</strong> is a major advancement for SAP SuccessFactors that’s connected to global skills databases to help ensure that organizations have a comprehensive and up-to-date view of the most important skills for their workforce. It delivers machine learning and artificial intelligence (AI) powered recommendations to employees about relevant and trending skills to prioritize for development.</p>
  <p><strong>The growth portfolio</strong>, also part of the early adopter care program, is how employees can reveal their skills, capabilities, education, language proficiencies, and certifications. In the second half release, this data will connect employees to the most relevant assignments in <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/opportunity-marketplace.html">SAP SuccessFactors Opportunity Marketplace</a>. While the skills ontology gives organizations the ability to align talent development to the ambitions of the organization, the growth portfolio enables employees to align their own talent development to their ambitions.</p>
  <p><strong>Dynamic teams</strong> is also part of the SAP SuccessFactors foundation and available to all customers. Within organizations today, there are countless teams that exist outside of traditional organizational structures – groups of people that work cross-functionally on a project for a certain amount of time. The dynamic teams functionality can provide organizations with visibility into these teams as well as tools to help manage and assemble teams. Team progress can be measured using objectives and key results (OKRs) and employees can find a dynamic team within SAP SuccessFactors Opportunity Marketplace to help learn new skills and continue to grow their career. This transparency within the organization levels the playing field and creates equal opportunity for employees.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11660a4ded960363037d3e57f808136c91669c786.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11660a4ded960363037d3e57f808136c91669c786.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_11660a4ded960363037d3e57f808136c91669c786.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_11660a4ded960363037d3e57f808136c91669c786.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="534">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p><em>Click to enlarge</em></p>
  <p>With richer data and greater talent intelligence, organizations can help ensure that employees are connected to the most relevant talent development opportunities that are aligned to the ambitions of employees and the needs of the organization. Skills ontology, growth portfolio, and dynamic teams provide significant updates to the foundation of <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/hxm-suite.html">SAP SuccessFactors Human Experience Management (HXM) Suite</a> – built into what customers already have instead of requiring an entirely new solution.</p>
  <p>Some more exciting features for our second half 2022 release are around individualized experiences and agile and compliant HR, including:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Chosen name and personal pronouns:</strong> As part of our commitment to diversity, equity, and inclusion, we are taking important steps to help every individual be seen and valued. People can now indicate their chosen name, personal pronouns, and gender directly within the people profile. This information is displayed consistently across SAP SuccessFactors solutions – from recruiting to learning, helping to foster a greater sense of belonging.</li>
    <li><strong>End-to-end visual redesign:</strong> We are enhancing the overall look and feel of SAP SuccessFactors by implementing the Horizon visual theme for SAP Fiori. This new theme enhances consistency while delivering a more informed and streamlined product experience. Employees will find nearly every element of the solution updated with new colors, typography, iconography, layouts, and visual hierarchy focused on intent and success. We remain on track to have every employee-facing SAP SuccessFactors experience unified with the theme by the end of 2023.</li>
    <li><strong>SAP SuccessFactors Work Zone guided onboarding experience:</strong> By bringing together SAP SuccessFactors solutions and third-party integrations, organizations can more efficiently handle an array of complex onboarding processes. This new feature helps ensure that employees receive individualized experiences, even before their first day. Covering key phases of the new hire journey, the guided onboarding experience for <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/workzone-hr.html">SAP SuccessFactors Work Zone</a> helps provide the tools and information employees need, both before and after hiring.</li>
    <li><strong>Cross-system workflow capability:</strong> We are unveiling a new cross-system workflow capability for processes that involve multiple users from multiple systems, such as SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central and the payroll component of SAP ERP Human Capital Management. A guided activity framework for key processes enables our on-premise customers to more rapidly unlock the value of the cloud with SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central and the latest HXM innovations while maintaining and progressively moving on-premise processes to the cloud over time.</li>
    <li><strong>Time management enhancements:</strong> We are continuing to <a href="/2022/09/sap-industry-leading-time-management-suite">enhance our capabilities in time management</a> with the much-anticipated ability to export leave events into calendar applications along with better support for public holidays and handling of grace rules. Time administrators can now copy time-related configuration objects, reducing the need for manual duplication during configuration. In addition, temporary work schedules and absence information on a per day basis will now be available for reporting in SAP SuccessFactors People Analytics.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>All these and many more exciting features will be available in our 2H 2022 release, in preview today and production on Friday, December 9. Please watch our <a href="https://dam.sap.com/mac/app/p/video/asset/preview/KvodB4Q?ltr=a&#x26;rc=10">second half 2022 release highlights video</a> for more information.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Amy Wilson is senior vice president of Products and Design for SAP SuccessFactors.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>news-tag/dynamic-teams</category>
            <category>news-tag/future-of-work</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-erp-hcm</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-opportunity-marketplace</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-work-zone</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP SuccessFactors Innovation: Supporting New Ways of Working in Dynamic Teams]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/supporting-working-in-dynamic-teams</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/supporting-working-in-dynamic-teams</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With future SAP SuccessFactors solutions, organizations will be able to bring people together in dynamic teams to drive better outcomes.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/dynamic-teams</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-opportunity-marketplace</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dynamic Teams Will Power the Future of Work]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/dynamic-teams-power-future-of-work</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/dynamic-teams-power-future-of-work</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Identify, track, measure and optimize the outcomes of dynamic teams within your workforce with SAP SuccessFactors software. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_12559a4c109c05d7d3f688b310b0124d46ae0bc39.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_12559a4c109c05d7d3f688b310b0124d46ae0bc39.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_12559a4c109c05d7d3f688b310b0124d46ae0bc39.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Dynamic Teams Will Power the Future of Work" src="./media_12559a4c109c05d7d3f688b310b0124d46ae0bc39.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="dynamic-teams-will-power-the-future-of-work">Dynamic Teams Will Power the Future of Work</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Each year when we host <a href="https://events.sap.com/successconnect/en/global-home">SuccessConnect</a>, it takes a village. For several months, a cross-functional group of people from sales, marketing, communications, product, and engineering come together to collaborate and put on an incredible program for our customers. At the end, the group celebrates their success, debriefs, then returns to their “day jobs.”</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>This is the perfect example of a <strong>dynamic team</strong>: a group of people with different skills, strengths, and work styles, that work together on a mission-critical initiative, and once the team’s goals are achieved, they disband. Increasingly, this is the way work gets done. Our research found that 82% of employees have participated in a dynamic team more than once in their current organizations.*</p>
  <p>Dynamic teams are sometimes the most innovative and productive groups within an organization, creating important networks and lasting impact. However, with today’s human capital management (HCM) systems, these teams – and their value – are hidden.</p>
  <p>Consider what happens today when a leader needs to assemble a team for an important, high-visibility project. They’re likely to pull in people they already know. But is this the best way to optimize both initial results and long-lasting effects? Does this serve diverse populations that may be hidden themselves?</p>
  <p>With dynamic teams hidden from view, organizations lack insight into how work is allocated, how to optimize and replicate results, and how well capabilities are building. Meanwhile, employees are not getting recognition for the skills they are gaining and the results they are delivering. And within the dynamic teams themselves, leaders and team members lack the visibility into what each person brings to the table and how they can most effectively work together.</p>
  <p>This lack of transparency is holding us back in our pursuit of personal and organizational sustainability and adaptability.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-successfactors-opportunity-marketplace-drives-internal-mobility-and-upskilling-to-help-organizations-future-proof-their-business">SAP SuccessFactors Opportunity Marketplace Drives Internal Mobility and Upskilling to Help Organizations Future-Proof Their Business</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="the-next-chapter-for-hxm-dynamic-teams">The Next Chapter for HXM: Dynamic Teams</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-more-news-and-coverage-from-successconnect">Read more news and coverage from SuccessConnect</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/topics/successconnect">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Today at SuccessConnect, we announced the <a href="/">delivery of SAP SuccessFactors Opportunity Marketplace</a>, backed by our center of capabilities, as the foundation for bottom-up learning, skilling, and self-development. It is an ever-evolving platform that extends beyond the traditional matching capabilities of HCM software to support a range of opportunities, from learning content and mentor relationships to temporary assignments and career roles, curated around an <a href="/2021/07/opportunity-in-x-redefine-employee-experience">individual’s whole self</a> — who they are today and who they are becoming.</p>
  <p>But we are not stopping there. We believe that dynamic teams are the pinnacle of opportunities. Just think about when you experienced your most significant growth – was it when you were holed up in your office studying or when you were surrounded by a team working together on an audacious goal? It was most likely the latter. Our research found that when an employee participates on a dynamic team, more than 70% of their line managers report a positive impact on their career development and engagement.</p>
  <p>Today, we shared our vision to bring dynamic teams to the forefront of <a href="https://www.sap.com/programs/experience-wins.html">human experience management</a> (HXM). With HXM technology to support dynamic teams, organizations can identify, track, measure and optimize the outcomes of these hidden groups, and individuals can access broader development and networking opportunities.</p>
  <p>The benefits of elevating the power of teams include:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Diversity and inclusion:</strong> By making dynamic teams and the roles within them transparent, organizations can open opportunities to a broader set of colleagues. With data and insight into diversity of thought, strengths and backgrounds, they can assemble teams with balance and belonging.</li>
    <li><strong>Trackable investments:</strong> Understanding where and how work is being done, organizations can gain greater insights into what and who is driving innovation and agility throughout their business.</li>
    <li><strong>Sustainable development and transformation:</strong> Participating in a cross-functional team helps people acquire new skills and strengthen their network. This growth benefits their “day jobs” by fostering ongoing adaptability and development. In turn, organizations can accelerate broad transformation initiatives that rely on the network effects of cross-functional skill development and behavioral change.</li>
    <li><strong>Health and prosperity:</strong> With a better understanding of who we are as individuals and what we can bring to a team, along with greater empathy and understanding of our teammates and how best to work together, we can optimize team dynamics. Not only does this help deliver tremendous results, but it also helps people have more fun in doing so.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>Human experience management is about putting people at the center of business. With our introduction of <a href="http://sap.com/opportunitymarketplace">SAP SuccessFactors Opportunity Marketplace</a> and the center of capabilities this year, and dynamic teams next year, we are reshaping the way we work and grow – as organizations and as humans. So together, we can change work for good.</p>
  <p>Our journey to bring our HXM vision to life would not be possible without the hundreds of customers who have partnered and co-innovated with us. To get involved, visit the <a href="https://training.sap.com/successfactors-community?redirectreason=notregistered&#x26;referer=https%3A%2F%2Fcommunity.successfactors.com%2F">SAP SuccessFactors Community page</a>.</p>
  <p>Learn more about dynamics teams by tuning into <a href="https://events.sap.com/successconnect/en/global-home">SuccessConnect</a> and reading our current research on <a href="https://community.successfactors.com/t5/SAP-SuccessFactors-HR-Research/ct-p/HRResearch">SAP SuccessFactors Community</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><em>Amy Wilson is senior vice president of Products and Design for SAP SuccessFactors.</em></p>
        <p><em>*Based on a survey of 1,492 dynamic team-members and line managers globally, conducted by the SAP SuccessFactors HR Research Team (March, 2021).</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/dynamic-teams</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/future-of-work</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-opportunity-marketplace</category>
            <category>sap-event/successconnect</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>