<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/sap-enterprise-support/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Jowat Doubles Productivity with Smarter Maintenance and Strategic Insight into Asset Management]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/jowat-smarter-maintenance-strategic-insight-asset-management</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/jowat-smarter-maintenance-strategic-insight-asset-management</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With SAP solutions, Jowat empowered its technicians to prioritize work more effectively and make smarter decisions about asset investments.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/asset-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-enterprise-support</category>
            <category>product/sap-integrated-business-planning-for-supply-chain</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Visualize and Accelerate Your Data Transformation to SAP S/4HANA Cloud]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/data-transformation-to-sap-s-4hana-cloud</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/data-transformation-to-sap-s-4hana-cloud</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Business Transformation Center helps guide you through the relevant steps required for your business transformation and data migration.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-transformation-center</category>
            <category>product/sap-cloud-alm</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-enterprise-support</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Reimagined Services and Support Portfolio and a New Era of Value Creation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/04/reimagined-services-and-support-portfolio</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/04/reimagined-services-and-support-portfolio</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is reimagining, simplifying, and sharpening its services and support portfolio by pivoting to focus heavily on adoption and consumption.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/cloud-success-services</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-journeys</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-enterprise-support</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-maxattention</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-preferred-success</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Reimagines Services and Support Portfolio for Success in the Cloud]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/04/simplified-services-and-support-portfolio-for-the-cloud</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/04/simplified-services-and-support-portfolio-for-the-cloud</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP's new simplified services and support portfolio is built for the cloud and designed to help customers achieve lasting success.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-journeys</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-enterprise-support</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-maxattention</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-preferred-success</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How to Navigate SAP Business Technology Platform to Drive True Transformation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/how-to-navigate-sap-business-technology-platform-to-drive-true-transformation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/how-to-navigate-sap-business-technology-platform-to-drive-true-transformation</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Enterprise Support value maps can help you understand everything that SAP BTP offers and move forward quickly and successfully.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a6fa4ce8b61627ae55fd8e1c48eca1e86b749942.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a6fa4ce8b61627ae55fd8e1c48eca1e86b749942.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1a6fa4ce8b61627ae55fd8e1c48eca1e86b749942.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="How to Navigate SAP Business Technology Platform to Drive True Transformation" src="./media_1a6fa4ce8b61627ae55fd8e1c48eca1e86b749942.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="how-to-navigate-sap-business-technology-platform-to-drive-true-transformation">How to Navigate SAP Business Technology Platform to Drive True Transformation</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>At the foundation of every business transformation is a mix of technologies working together to solve critical challenges. And when that foundation is as diverse as SAP Business Technology Platform, you need a well-defined value map that shows the best path to meaningful outcomes and lasting change.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Time is no one’s friend – and businesses know it. So gone are the days of being content with doing what the competition is doing, just slightly better. Instead, companies want to make the most of every moment, adapting their value chains to new markets, industries, and ecosystems before anyone else does.</p>
  <p>For SAP customers seeking a first-mover advantage, the flexibility and independence gained through <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">SAP Business Technology Platform</a> (SAP BTP) are essential elements of transforming business operations and preparing for a digital future. The platform supports the four fundamental pillars of digital innovation that help ensure success in the cloud: database and data management, analytics tools and services, intelligent technologies, and application development, extension, and integration capabilities.</p>
  <p>Depending on how the services are combined, organizations can deliver incredible transformations that leave competitors scrambling to catch up. But first, you are faced with a wide range of capabilities and services to determine the optimal mix to fulfill your unique vision or preferred business scenario.</p>
  <p>How can you understand everything that SAP BTP offers and move forward quickly and successfully? With <a href="https://support.sap.com/en/offerings-programs/enterprise-support/enterprise-support-academy/value-maps.html">SAP Enterprise Support value maps</a>, you can access critical guidance on the platform’s current and future state and connect those insights to your digital transformation, cloud adoption, or technology expansion.</p>
  <h2 id="securing-the-foundation-for-continuous-innovation">Securing the Foundation for Continuous Innovation</h2>
  <p>SAP Enterprise Support value maps lay out the knowledge, skills, technologies, and services needed to address specific business challenges at any given time. The value maps can enable you to achieve meaningful results and unlock new potential for growth with SAP BTP through learning opportunities that include prescriptive guidance, high-impact learning, social collaboration forums, and direct access to SAP experts made available in the value map for SAP BTP. With regular articles posted every week by experts, you will keep your team up-to-date with new tools, services, and features and can keep the technical foundation strong for your company.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-sap-enterprise-support-value-maps">Learn more about SAP Enterprise Support value maps</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://support.sap.com/en/offerings-programs/enterprise-support/enterprise-support-academy/value-maps.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="prescriptive-guidance">Prescriptive Guidance</h3>
  <p>The value map for SAP BTP features a catalog of structured content for all four pillars that includes more than 350 empowerment materials and services. For each request, our SAP experts will provide you with guidance on the platform’s solutions, tools, and services that should be used to deliver expected outcomes, help ensure business-wide adoption, and support the new process, application, or capability.</p>
  <p>The content is designed to address the needs of the majority of our customers, including basic information on the latest updates and additions to SAP BTP and cloud-focused offerings from SAP. This information gives you a foundational understanding of how your business can realize the platform’s full potential – whether moving to the cloud, expanding your cloud footprint, or extending existing solutions and functionalities.</p>
  <h3 id="high-impact-learning">High-Impact Learning</h3>
  <p>The program also gives you access to 17 learning journeys to explore, filter, and access a curated set of learning assets and services on the four pillars of SAP BTP. Every journey presents a block of interactive learning modules that provide the knowledge and nurture the skills needed to help realize successful deployment, use, and security of technologies, tools, and services from SAP BTP.</p>
  <h3 id="social-collaboration-forums">Social Collaboration Forums</h3>
  <p>Through the SAP Enterprise Support value map for SAP BTP, you can gain invaluable access to a dedicated and collaborative community. Our SAP experts and industry peers will quickly provide you with an answer on questions related to database and data management solutions, analytics tools, intelligent technologies, and application development, extension, and integration.</p>
  <p>The value maps serve as a one-stop shop for the latest information on SAP BTP. They house a library of self-consumable resources – such as articles, best-practice documentation, guided demos, and informational videos – that technology experts and business practitioners alike share with the community.</p>
  <h3 id="direct-access-to-experts">Direct Access to Experts</h3>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-business-technology-platform-accelerate-business-outcomes-with-integration-data-to-value-and-extensibility">SAP Business Technology Platform: Accelerate business outcomes with integration, data to value, and extensibility</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>For more personalized, one-on-one guidance, you have the option of requesting a call to get an expert recommendation tailored to your needs. Additionally, SAP experts are also available through live webcasts, where Q&#x26;A sessions allow you to ask about your particular topic. This differentiates value maps because it’s more than just a customer community for peers to exchange information.</p>
  <h2 id="becoming-empowered--not-overwhelmed--by-technology">Becoming Empowered – Not Overwhelmed – by Technology</h2>
  <p>Working with a broad portfolio like the one offered through <a href="/topics/business-technology-platform">SAP BTP</a> can be overwhelming at first. While no organization uses its entire portfolio at once, the platform does provide immediate access to the technologies and services you need to help deliver outcomes your customers expect, the experiences your employees need, and the future your business envisions.</p>
  <p>And with the support and guidance of the SAP Enterprise Support value maps, you can satisfy all those requirements with a clear and direct path to true transformation.</p>
  <p>To get started, request access to <a href="https://esasupportportal.hana.ondemand.com/esa2">SAP Learning Hub</a> or join the <a href="https://enrollment-ac82d52a4.dispatcher.hana.ondemand.com/index.html?itemID=LR_ValueMaps_EN">SAP Enterprise Support Value Maps Learning Room</a> if you already have access. Then, you can subscribe to our value map for SAP Business Technology Platform to start getting the full benefits of the platform.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Olga Tregub is global functional lead of SAP Business Technology Platform, SAP Enterprise Support Value Maps at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-enterprise-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Innovation Challenge: How to Make the Extraordinary Happen]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/innovation-challenge-make-extraordinary-happen</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/innovation-challenge-make-extraordinary-happen</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Innovation is immensely powerful when driving transformative change. SAP Innovation Awards celebrate those that've taken this lesson to heart.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_178431ff0f2c3efa5a2c191ea2f1455f4a21ff21a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_178431ff0f2c3efa5a2c191ea2f1455f4a21ff21a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_178431ff0f2c3efa5a2c191ea2f1455f4a21ff21a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="The Innovation Challenge: How to Make the Extraordinary Happen" src="./media_178431ff0f2c3efa5a2c191ea2f1455f4a21ff21a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="the-innovation-challenge-how-to-make-the-extraordinary-happen">The Innovation Challenge: How to Make the Extraordinary Happen</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>One of the most important lessons of the last two years has been the power of innovation when driving genuinely transformative change. With SAP Innovation Awards, we celebrate individuals and organizations that have taken this lesson to heart with a mix of ingenuity, SAP technology, and the support of knowledgeable experts.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Innovations are always top of mind for companies – especially SAP customers. But you won’t find them musing future-minded technology trends such as quantum computing, neural interfaces, or nanotechnology. Instead, they are accomplishing extraordinary feats and delivering meaningful outcomes with existing technology and expertise.</p>
  <p>Certainly, every business has a story of exceptional innovation to tell. And I am proud to share those of our customers – some of which were recognized by <a href="https://www.sap.com/idea-place/sap-innovation-awards.html">SAP Innovation Awards</a> in 2021 for making the world better with assistance from SAP Services and Support offerings.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-sap-innovation-awards">Learn more about SAP Innovation Awards</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/idea-place/sap-innovation-awards.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="enhancing-scale-and-performance-for-heavy-data-workloads">Enhancing Scale and Performance for Heavy Data Workloads</h2>
  <p>When under pressure to meet regulatory requirements, deliver higher margins, and improve customer experiences, companies must improve how they manage increasing volumes of data. But all too often, the limitation of an on-premise landscape does not allow the flexibility, agility, speed, and cost-effectiveness to meet that challenge.</p>
  <p>For one of the SAP Innovation Award winners, the answer was found in a proof of concept created through a joint effort between SAP and Google Cloud. <a href="https://www.sap.com/idea-place/sap-innovation-awards/submission-details-2021.html?idea_id=2376">PayPal Holdings</a> (PayPal), which adopted Google Cloud as its core IT partner, chose a combination of Google Cloud and SAP S/4HANA for financial products subledger on a 96 TB scale-out configuration of SAP HANA. The innovation leveraged Google Cloud’s expertise in building scalable, distributed systems and SAP’s relentless focus on delivering mission-critical business process automation.</p>
  <p>Bringing the best of SAP and Google Cloud engineering together, PayPal can benefit from groundbreaking capabilities with higher performance, lower costs, and more flexibility. The technology platform company now runs one of the world’s largest scale-out clusters of SAP HANA. And in return, it accelerated query runtime by 40 times through parallelization, reduced its memory footprint by 78% with dynamic data-tiering techniques, and experienced 24 weeks of continuous operations with zero downtime.</p>
  <h2 id="achieving-health-goals-through-process-standardization">Achieving Health Goals Through Process Standardization</h2>
  <p>During <a href="/covid-19">the COVID-19 pandemic</a>, businesses were concerned with maintaining operational continuity and keeping pace with demand while ensuring a safe and healthy environment for their workforce. However, as one of our award finalists discovered, a complex IT infrastructure involving multiple disparate enterprise resource planning (ERP) systems prevented the ability to run as quickly as possible.</p>
  <p>The European division of <a href="https://www.sap.com/idea-place/sap-innovation-awards/submission-details-2021.html?idea_id=2471">American Air Filter Company</a> addressed this issue by deploying cloud-based solutions to standardize processes and support localization requirements for different countries. With <a href="https://www.sap.com/services/support-plans/preferred-success-cloud.html">SAP Preferred Success</a>, <a href="https://www.sap.com/services/implementation/implementation-pkg.html">SAP Value Assurance</a>, and SAP development experts, the division consolidated 13 ERP systems into a single instance of SAP S/4HANA Cloud and gained the agility to achieve meaningful change.</p>
  <p>American Air Filter Company harmonized processes and gained a single view of the truth, providing more transparent and streamlined operations across all business areas. Additionally, its simplified IT infrastructure costs less to maintain and enables the business to take advantage of intelligent technologies to innovate new offerings.</p>
  <h2 id="setting-new-standards-with-embedded-analytics">Setting New Standards with Embedded Analytics</h2>
  <p>Every organization reaches a point where homegrown, mainframe-based business information systems must be replaced to enhance decision-making and enable higher standards for data governance, quality, and security. But the first step is not necessarily ripping out the legacy technology and implementing a completely new architecture, which in most cases can become too operationally disruptive and costly.</p>
  <p>For 2021 finalist <a href="https://www.sap.com/idea-place/sap-innovation-awards/submission-details-2021.html?idea_id=2036">Pennsylvania State University</a> (Penn State), expert guidance from SAP Enterprise Support services was needed to help upskill its IT team and pave the way for cutting-edge embedded analytics. The university worked with <a href="https://support.sap.com/en/offerings-programs/enterprise-support/enterprise-support-advisory-council.html">SAP Enterprise Support Advisory Council</a> to build a strong foundation in analytics, including through remote, recorded individual and group webinars, to support its digital transformation journey.</p>
  <p>Penn State relied on the <a href="https://support.sap.com/en/offerings-programs/enterprise-support/enterprise-support-academy/value-maps.html">SAP Enterprise Support value maps</a> for SAP Analytics solutions to help close any digital skills gaps. The organization engaged with experts, posting questions in value map forums and arranging collaborative sessions with peers. Plus, it used the <a href="https://cal.sap.com/">SAP Cloud Appliance Library</a> tool to help demonstrate and trial innovative data analytics and reporting tools, conduct scoping and sandboxing exercises, and create a proof of concept.</p>
  <p>Relating training material to workflows and real project scenarios enabled Penn State’s employees to apply knowledge more readily and apply feedback as they adopted SAP S/4HANA embedded analytics. And with access to experts who truly understand its challenges, Penn State’s administration staff now has the necessary skills to adapt and run embedded analytics, which will influence how it runs the university.</p>
  <h2 id="transforming-for-agility-speed-and-success">Transforming for Agility, Speed, and Success</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="discover-how-sap-can-help-enable-your-outcome-driven-business-imperatives">Discover how SAP can help enable your outcome-driven business imperatives</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/services/premium-engagement.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>During any significant organizational change such as a merger, acquisition, or spin-off, most companies find that their legacy landscape is too complex, lacking in technical depth, redundant, or costly to maintain. Another finalist, <a href="https://www.sap.com/idea-place/sap-innovation-awards/submission-details-2021.html?idea_id=2145">Hewlett Packard Enterprise</a> (HPE), is no stranger to this challenge.</p>
  <p>When HPE’s parent company, the Hewlett-Packard Company, spun off in 2015, the business needed to simplify applications and processes enterprise-wide to fulfill the world’s growing need for cloud services and intelligent technology. HPE implemented a wide variety of solutions and services to create a solid foundation for the business and enhance IT with powerful next-generation technologies. The <a href="https://www.sap.com/services/premium-engagement/maxattention.html?sort=latest_desc">SAP MaxAttention</a> program provided the guidance necessary to help validate, plan, execute, and test the design of its infrastructure.</p>
  <p>As a result of its efforts with SAP, HPE reduced recommitments to orders after removing the legacy processes that had resulted in rescheduled jobs. The company improved on-time delivery by focusing on its partners and helping them improve their shipping performance. Today, 99.5% of HPE’s customer orders are delivered on time, up from 90% in the past.</p>
  <h2 id="trailblazing-the-future-with-innovation">Trailblazing the Future with Innovation</h2>
  <p>All these stories are exceptional examples of how SAP customers are shaping their innovation effort to trailblaze a future of ongoing productivity and growth. And I am proud that my experts, who support SAP Services and Support offerings, are playing a key role in our customers’ success.</p>
  <p>Throughout the year, I hear our customers express their gratitude to my team of experts for helping them realize their potential as intelligent enterprises. Recently, I read a quote from SAP Innovation Award finalist <a href="https://www.sap.com/idea-place/sap-innovation-awards/submission-details-2021.html?idea_id=2118">Delivery Hero</a> that I think best sums up the best of what we offer.</p>
  <p>“Thanks to guidance from SAP Services and Support and the Intelligent Enterprise Institute, we better understand the dependency of customer experience on our delivery processes,” said Sebastian McClintock, global director of Customer Experience at Delivery Hero. “Leveraging SAP S/4HANA, Experience Management solutions from SAP and Qualtrics, and machine learning models, we now know how to improve data flows and best use our data to meet customers’ needs.”</p>
  <h2 id="do-you-have-a-story-to-tell">Do You Have a Story to Tell?</h2>
  <p>Such change is hard work, and extraordinary results deserve to be told. That’s why we host SAP Innovation Awards every year. It allows us to celebrate organizations that are improving business processes, providing faster and more effective customer service, making a difference for current and future employees, and more.</p>
  <p>And we invite all of you – especially if you selected services and support from SAP as your partner or co-partner – to submit a nomination. The call for nominations to <a href="https://www.sap.com/idea-place/sap-innovation-awards.html">SAP Innovation Awards 2022</a> is open now, but only for a few more months. Share your story with us!</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Oliver Huschke is vice president and global head of Marketing and Communications for Services and Support at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-enterprise-support</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-hana</category>
            <category>sap-award/sap-innovation-awards</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-maxattention</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-preferred-success</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Custom Guidance: The Secret to High-Value Transformation in the Cloud]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/custom-guidance-cloud-transformation-sap-preferred-success</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/custom-guidance-cloud-transformation-sap-preferred-success</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A Forrester study revealed the business benefits in the cloud that are enabled by SAP Preferred Success. Read about the highlights.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1fe50fe3db75fc6d5437a22dc37e75d23a81dacf4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1fe50fe3db75fc6d5437a22dc37e75d23a81dacf4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1fe50fe3db75fc6d5437a22dc37e75d23a81dacf4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Custom Guidance: The Secret to High-Value Transformation in the Cloud" src="./media_1fe50fe3db75fc6d5437a22dc37e75d23a81dacf4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="custom-guidance-the-secret-to-high-value-transformation-in-the-cloud">Custom Guidance: The Secret to High-Value Transformation in the Cloud</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Cloud technology may drive fast and agile change, but technical unknowns and strategic misdirection can lessen the impact of any degree of success. So how can businesses get on the right path to high-value transformation? The answer is proactive, ongoing, and personalized guidance, according to a study conducted by Forrester Consulting.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>When looking to the cloud to improve operational efficiencies, reduce costs, and meet customer demand with flexibility and speed, companies throw open the doors to a world of opportunities. But first, they need to become familiar with the landscape and available resources, discover capabilities that can benefit them most, and know how to scale the technology to fuel long-term, sustainable growth.</p>
  <p>Unfortunately, most internal IT organizations are too lean to manage it all. They do not have the time and budget needed to scrutinize road map strategies for the cloud and concentrate on continuous improvement after an initial implementation.</p>
  <p>The Forrester Consulting study commissioned by SAP, “<a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/07/aed54c54-ee7d-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">The Total Economic Impact™ of SAP Preferred Success</a>,” presents a solution to this common dilemma. In its assessment of the <a href="https://www.sap.com/services/support-plans/preferred-success-cloud.html">SAP Preferred Success</a> offering, the third-party global market research company revealed that access to success resources and customized guidance can yield a 380% ROI in cloud technology investments over three years.</p>
  <h2 id="fostering-adoption-and-optimization-for-long-term-growth">Fostering Adoption and Optimization for Long-Term Growth</h2>
  <p>To evaluate the potential economic impact of continuous cloud services, Forrester surveyed four companies actively using SAP Preferred Success. The participants’ experiences were then aggregated to create a single composite organization to determine the offering’s total economic impact (TEI).</p>
  <p>In this TEI study, Forrester emphasized how SAP Preferred Success helps SAP customers adopt, consume, and operate cloud solutions with greater ease, speed, and strategic value. Over a three-year period, this kind of guidance was shown to impact how businesses can quickly transform to meet the needs of a dynamic marketplace in four fundamental ways.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-preferred-success-prescriptive-guidance-for-a-world-of-uncertainty">SAP Preferred Success: Prescriptive Guidance for a World of Uncertainty</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2020/04/sap-preferred-success-prescriptive-guidance">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="shrink-implementation-time-by-two-months">1. Shrink Implementation Time by Two Months</h3>
  <p>With the assistance of customer success managers (CSMs), in-depth training materials, and support tools, surveyed businesses cited that their implementations and updates were completed faster and with lower risk. The more familiar they became with the cloud landscape and best-practice methodologies, the more confident their organizations were in supporting a cloud-based IT model. For example, deployment impediments and bugs were detected and addressed proactively, cloud investments were safeguarded, and technologies and capabilities that provide relevant benefits were chosen quickly without the fear of missing opportunities.</p>
  <h3 id="accelerate-time-to-value-with-faster-releases">2. Accelerate Time to Value with Faster Releases</h3>
  <p>The exercise of researching answers to new questions can delay planning by approximately 30%, pushing out the delivery of the solution and realization of its value. Businesses that leverage SAP Preferred Success during planning, deployment, and release preparation can add two more months of additional benefits each year after the initial implementation. Furthermore, those gains can be achieved without disrupting the everyday work experiences of internal teams.</p>
  <h3 id="facilitate-innovation-with-collaboration-and-insight">3. Facilitate Innovation with Collaboration and Insight</h3>
  <p>Interviewed organizations mentioned their interactions with customer communities and access to in-depth training materials through regular strategic reviews and ongoing informal exchanges with CSMs. They viewed this experience as a turning point in their ability to focus on their business priorities and identify opportunities to improve processes and implement new enhancements. Plus, based on Forrester’s calculation, gains in process optimization could raise productivity by, on average, 30% when the time saved is reinvested in constructive work.</p>
  <h3 id="resolve-incidents-faster-and-more-productively">4. Resolve Incidents Faster and More Productively</h3>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-resources-you-need-to-be-successful-in-the-cloud">Get the resources you need to be successful in the cloud</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/services/support-plans/preferred-success-cloud.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>With access to a dedicated CSM from SAP Preferred Success as a point of contact, interviewees from this TEI study reported resolving issues more quickly. Incidents that they raised were prioritized in SAP’s system to meet enhanced service-level agreements, supported by the CSM acting as their advocate, and connected to relevant experts to expedite resolution. This support reduced priority one and priority two incidents by half in the third year after the initial implementation while accelerating priority two incident resolution times by at least 40% and reducing effort by 30%.</p>
  <h2 id="creating-a-low-risk-flexible-foundation-for-transformation">Creating a Low-Risk, Flexible Foundation for Transformation</h2>
  <p>SAP Preferred Success is a premium add-on to SAP Enterprise Support, cloud editions. In an earlier <a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/dg/tei-on-sap-enterprise-support/index.html">TEI study covering the SAP Enterprise Support offering</a>, Forrester revealed that surveyed businesses felt they were well-equipped to move from on-premise solutions to the cloud smoothly. The offering’s prescriptive guidance enabled organizations to implement cloud solutions from SAP and find new ways to safeguard processes, optimize operations, and unlock innovations through continuous enhancements.</p>
  <p>But as Forrester emphasized in this TEI study on SAP Preferred Success, businesses that are unfamiliar with cloud solutions may want personalized assistance and advice on how to adopt, consume, and operate the technology. This is where an add-on, particularly SAP Preferred Success, can be helpful.</p>
  <p>SAP Preferred Success supports a combination of outcomes that can be critical for companies looking to transition and evolve with cloud technology. But more importantly, those advantages create an environment that empowers organizations to transform at their pace and toward their vision with less risk and greater flexibility.</p>
  <p>How can SAP Preferred Success help amplify your potential in the cloud? Find out by reading the full economic impact study by Forrester, “<a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/07/aed54c54-ee7d-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">The Total Economic Impact™ of SAP Preferred Success</a>.”</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Lisa Spangler is global vice president and chief product owner for SAP Preferred Success at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/forrester</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-enterprise-support</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-preferred-success</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Economic Impact of Proactive Planning and Readiness on Cloud-Based Innovation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/economic-impact-sap-enterprise-support-cloud-editions</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/economic-impact-sap-enterprise-support-cloud-editions</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A Forrester study shows that SAP Enterprise Support, cloud editions advance customers' overall journey to the cloud. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1fdc6152b9ae2eba1b41f327fb2674c16f9b4bd76.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1fdc6152b9ae2eba1b41f327fb2674c16f9b4bd76.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1fdc6152b9ae2eba1b41f327fb2674c16f9b4bd76.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="The Economic Impact of Proactive Planning and Readiness on Cloud-Based Innovation" src="./media_1fdc6152b9ae2eba1b41f327fb2674c16f9b4bd76.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="the-economic-impact-of-proactive-planning-and-readiness-on-cloud-based-innovation">The Economic Impact of Proactive Planning and Readiness on Cloud-Based Innovation</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>The cloud is increasingly becoming a choice that is catalyzing innovation and digital transformation for organizations worldwide. Yet, most companies are only beginning to realize the cloud’s vast potential for deployment scale, process efficiency, workforce productivity, and development speed – opening them up to the possibility of enabling long-term, sustainable business growth.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>At a time when businesses are working diligently to rejuvenate themselves by pioneering new business models, products, services, and experiences, operations optimization and continuous enhancement have never been more critical. However, services that support these needs are often overlooked when purchasing cloud subscriptions.</p>
  <p>Are businesses making a significant mistake by delaying proactive planning and readiness support services for another day or skipping them all together? The Forrester Consulting study commissioned by SAP, “<a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/dg/tei-on-sap-enterprise-support/index.html">The Total Economic Impact™ of SAP Enterprise Support, Cloud Editions</a>,” indicated the answer is a resounding “yes” in its analysis of <a href="https://www.sap.com/services/support-plans/enterprise.html">SAP Enterprise Support, cloud editions</a> – revealing a 30% higher process optimization rate over three years.</p>
  <h2 id="revealing-the-full-potential-of-the-cloud">Revealing the Full Potential of the Cloud</h2>
  <p>To better understand the benefits and costs associated with support services, Forrester interviewed five businesses that are using or have used any element from the cloud editions of the SAP Enterprise Support offering. The third-party global market research company engaged in an unbiased survey of the participants’ experiences and aggregated their insights into a single composite organization to calculate quantitative benefits.</p>
  <p>The TEI study highlighted how SAP Enterprise Support, cloud editions enable SAP customers to move from on-premise solutions to the cloud more smoothly. The offering gave prescriptive guidance to the surveyed businesses as they implemented cloud solutions from SAP and searched for ways to enable their business, safeguard their processes, optimize operations, and unlock innovations through continuous enhancements.</p>
  <p>How does this experience impact the way SAP customers advance their overall digital transformation journey in the cloud over a three-year period? Here are key insights that Forrester uncovered in its research.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-proactive-support-you-need-to-succeed-with-sap-enterprise-support">Get the proactive support you need to succeed with SAP Enterprise Support</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://support.sap.com/en/offerings-programs/enterprise-support.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="benefit-1-reduced-implementation-costs-by-27">Benefit #1: Reduced Implementation Costs by 27%</h3>
  <p>By working with a team of SAP experts and support specialists, the surveyed businesses felt more prepared to adopt the cloud and have confidence in their investment. The more informed they were about the capabilities of the cloud solutions, the more capable they were in assuring user readiness, accelerating adoption, and managing expanding use. In addition, emerging risks could be mitigated to safeguard the performance of their internal and partner project teams in realizing the value of their cloud solutions.</p>
  <h3 id="benefit-2-derived-20-more-efficiency-in-internal-it-teams">Benefit #2: Derived 20% More Efficiency in Internal IT Teams</h3>
  <p>When organizations understand the value of the technologies they choose to purchase, they are more likely to embrace best practices that drive greater efficiency. The companies surveyed by Forrester are no exception to this rule. By leveraging SAP Enterprise Support, cloud editions, research participants could manage IT incidents more effectively and perform application support activities with well-defined service-level agreements.</p>
  <h3 id="benefit-3-released-preparations-with-25-less-effort">Benefit #3: Released Preparations with 25% Less Effort</h3>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="why-now-is-the-time-to-differentiate-with-sap-services-and-support">Why Now Is the Time to Differentiate with SAP Services and Support</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/06/differentiate-with-sap-services-and-support">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP customers interviewed for Forrester’s research mentioned having access to enablement materials through SAP Enterprise Support, cloud editions. This allowed them to quickly adapt existing processes to meet changing market needs. As a result, organizations, on average, avoided two weeks of additional effort for each new release of a cloud solution.</p>
  <h2 id="setting-the-foundation-for-fast-time-to-value">Setting the Foundation for Fast Time to Value</h2>
  <p>Perhaps one of the most exciting findings in Forrester’s research is how the combination of reduced cost, greater efficiency, and less effort to prepare for new releases accelerates the overall time to value of cloud solutions. This impact of SAP Enterprise Support, cloud editions is particularly critical for companies that demand more frequent innovation cycles and faster realization of expected outcomes.</p>
  <p>One of the project managers interviewed by Forrester for this TEI study shared that the offering enabled an oil and gas company to launch its move to the cloud two months earlier than expected in an already aggressive timeline. Other interview participants indicated the same experience, in which, on average, SAP Enterprise Support, cloud editions helped deliver initiatives nearly one month earlier for a six-month deployment.</p>
  <p>Could your business gain the same advantage in your move to the cloud? Find out by reading the full economic impact study from Forrester, “<a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/dg/tei-on-sap-enterprise-support/index.html">The Total Economic Impact™ of SAP Enterprise Support, Cloud Editions</a>.”</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Keith Lamont is vice president of Customer Engagement and Experience at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/forrester</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-enterprise-support</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Seamless Support Experience in the Post-Pandemic World]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/seamless-support-experience-post-pandemic-world</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/seamless-support-experience-post-pandemic-world</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[At SAP, end-to-end support is about having a seamless, unified approach to all aspects of the support experience. Read to learn more!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_161d736f1f8909faa946ca3de7493588f42e18e60.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_161d736f1f8909faa946ca3de7493588f42e18e60.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_161d736f1f8909faa946ca3de7493588f42e18e60.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="A Seamless Support Experience in the Post-Pandemic World" src="./media_161d736f1f8909faa946ca3de7493588f42e18e60.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="a-seamless-support-experience-in-the-post-pandemic-world">A Seamless Support Experience in the Post-Pandemic World</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-enterprise-support-the-proactive-support-you-need-to-succeed">SAP Enterprise Support: The proactive support you need to succeed</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://support.sap.com/en/offerings-programs/enterprise-support.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>For many companies, moving to the <strong>cloud is the “next normal”</strong> in business environments. It’s not about “if” anymore – it’s about “when” and “how.” This trend has dominated discussions in the enterprise technology space for a long time and has been further accelerated by <a href="/covid-19">the global pandemic</a>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In a <a href="https://www.cio.com/article/3611419/cios-say-public-cloud-migration-is-essential-for-survival.html">recent survey</a> of U.S.-based CIOs, 85% of respondents said that moving to the cloud was the foundation for a future-ready enterprise, enabling improved productivity and providing the speed and flexibility businesses need to respond quickly to changing conditions. The more insecure environments get – and the pandemic, climate change, and many other elements today contribute strongly to insecurity – the more cloud benefits like flexibility and less bundled commitments to technology will play a role.</p>
  <p>Moving to the cloud is not like flipping a switch. Having built up extensive and customized on-premise hardware and software landscapes over time, many companies will need time to move their business processes to a cloud-based environment, especially taking into account the more standardized nature of software as a service (SaaS). This will result in having many different software deployment and consumption models: some will be public cloud, some private cloud or on hyperscalers, some staying on-premise at least in the mid-term. Despite such mixed IT landscapes, customers expect a seamless end-to-end experience from their vendor – especially in support.</p>
  <p>At SAP, this expectation is nothing new. In fact, this has always been core to our support strategy. Even before the days of cloud, SAP strove to offer a comprehensive set of business solutions tightly integrated for end-to-end business processes, with seamless experiences on user interfaces, data, and support. This core principle still fits perfectly in the cloud world and provides enormous opportunity for customer value in landscapes that are hybrid or in transition.</p>
  <p>So, what does end-to-end support mean? At SAP, this is about having a <strong>unified approach to all aspects of support</strong>. The goal is one feature-rich, foundational support offering, one customer-facing support interface, one support infrastructure, and one support organization that maintains a strong global culture of service and expertise.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="say-hello-to-your-digital-companion-sap-for-me">Say hello to your digital companion, SAP for Me</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://me.sap.com/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Currently, SAP solutions are accompanied by our flagship support offering <a href="https://support.sap.com/en/offerings-programs/enterprise-support.html">SAP Enterprise Support</a>, which is embedded in cloud subscriptions and is the offering of choice for on-premise SAP software solutions. This can provide our customers with the confidence that they will receive the same high-quality of support for their entire landscape, no matter the SAP solution they happen to be using at any given moment. We understand that one end-to-end business process might touch several systems and SAP software solutions and, therefore, a support issue will not exist in a vacuum of a single product only. We have the expertise and culture of collaboration to look at problems holistically across an integrated SAP environment.</p>
  <p>Here are some recent <strong>examples of our continued expansion of customer value</strong>:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>In 2020 we launched <a href="https://support.sap.com/en/alm/sap-cloud-alm.html">SAP Cloud ALM</a>, SAP’s next-generation <strong>cloud-based application lifecycle management solution</strong> that includes best practices and mechanisms to manage and monitor integrated landscapes, not siloed by specific products. Developed to support the implementation and operation of SAP solutions, it is continually expanding its coverage of cloud and on-premise deployments.</li>
    <li>We are always striving to find new ways of making access to support easier for our customers. In 2020, SAP launched a new <strong>unified “digital front door”</strong> called <a href="https://me.sap.com/">SAP for Me</a>. The vision for this personalized portal is that customers and partners can access all information, insights, and tasks related to SAP. During the next year, many more support-related tasks and reports will also be made available on SAP for Me to help give customers an end-to-end view of their SAP assets, services, interactions, and more.</li>
    <li>In the last few years, we have introduced new ways for customers to get <strong>direct access to support experts and managers</strong>. It started with <a href="https://support.sap.com/en/my-support/product-support.html#section_519294480">Expert Chat</a> – here, SAP has recently delivered the <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/pulse/sap-customers-get-on-the-spot-support-million-times-heckmann">1,000,000th on-the-spot support</a>. Customers can start a chat directly with a technical support engineer or <a href="https://support.sap.com/en/my-support/product-support.html#section_1575600800">schedule a meeting</a> at their convenience. They can even schedule a <a href="https://support.sap.com/en/my-support/product-support.html#section_193743618">meeting with a support manager</a>.</li>
    <li>Sometimes it’s even better if you can <strong>get a solution automatically</strong>. As you would expect from an industry leader, SAP is exploring the next frontier of support innovation: artificial intelligence (AI). For example, the <a href="https://support.sap.com/en/my-support/product-support.html#section_1903672625">Incident Solution Matching</a> service analyzes a customer’s problem description while they are typing it into the support case and suggests potential solutions. <a href="https://support.sap.com/en/my-support/product-support.html#section_1255553798">Built-In Support</a>, with its digital support assistant, is already available in SAP S/4HANA Cloud and will be integrated into more products in time. We have launched the <a href="https://blogs.sap.com/2020/11/27/machine-translation-integration-to-last-communication-from-sap-support-for-customer-incidents">automatic translation of the last incident</a> and support assets like <a href="https://blogs.sap.com/2018/03/07/self-service-machine-translation-for-sap-notes-and-knowledge-base-articles-in-the-sap-one-support-launchpad/">SAP Notes or a SAP Knowledge Base Article</a>. And artificial intelligence can also help spot problems before they occur and provide recommendations to prevent future issues.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>Through it all, SAP provides the <strong>flexibility</strong> customers need to make the most of their business while saving time and resources. Whether a company is moving to the public cloud, balancing cloud and on-premise solutions, or just exploring cloud elements at its edges, we can provide the support it needs to be agile and resilient in today’s markets.</p>
  <p>The next generation of support is the baseline. It is seamless, end-to-end, proactive, multi-channeled, and intelligent in order to let our customers focus on what matters most to them: driving their business.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/built-in-support</category>
            <category>news-tag/expert-chat</category>
            <category>news-tag/incident-solution-matching</category>
            <category>product/sap-cloud-alm</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-enterprise-support</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-for-me</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Enterprise Support Academy: Adapting Technology Support and Enablement for a Hybrid Workforce]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/06/sap-enterprise-support-academy-hybrid-workforce</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/06/sap-enterprise-support-academy-hybrid-workforce</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Work on closing your workforce’s digital skill gaps at any place, any time, and through any device with SAP Enterprise Support Academy.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ee7c3e15705811cfffe16aeee75b11a8a5115f9a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ee7c3e15705811cfffe16aeee75b11a8a5115f9a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1ee7c3e15705811cfffe16aeee75b11a8a5115f9a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Enterprise Support Academy: Adapting Technology Support and Enablement for a Hybrid Workforce" src="./media_1ee7c3e15705811cfffe16aeee75b11a8a5115f9a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-enterprise-support-academy-adapting-technology-support-and-enablement-for-a-hybrid-workforce">SAP Enterprise Support Academy: Adapting Technology Support and Enablement for a Hybrid Workforce</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>The traditional office space may not be disappearing entirely anytime soon. But, many SAP customers are preparing to make dramatic changes in how they support their employees no matter where they are with the SAP Enterprise Support Academy program.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>After a year of significant shifts in the employee experience, organizations worldwide are benefiting from cloud technologies, process automation, and collaborative applications. However, all these changes require a workforce that is skilled to leverage these new tools and user experiences efficiently to drive greater employee satisfaction and better business value.</p>
  <p><a href="https://support.sap.com/en/offerings-programs/enterprise-support/enterprise-support-academy.html">SAP Enterprise Support Academy</a> is designed to help handle this increasingly pressing challenge for SAP customers while reducing their IT costs. Around-the-clock access to expert guidance and high impact knowledge transfer services help enable employees across all roles to build their technical skills and get the full value of their organization’s SAP solutions.</p>
  <h2 id="flexible-access-to-self-paced-live-and-trusted-expertise">Flexible Access to Self-Paced, Live, and Trusted Expertise</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="welcome-to-the-next-generation-learning-management-infrastructure">Welcome to the next generation learning management infrastructure</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://support.sap.com/en/offerings-programs/enterprise-support/enterprise-support-academy/learn.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Since the beginning of this year, more than 17,500 customers have engaged in over 13,800 learning activities – 75% of which covered cloud and hybrid deployment topics. Best of all, they are accessing the program for free through an active subscription of SAP Enterprise Support or SAP Product Support for Large Enterprises.</p>
  <p>SAP Enterprise Support Academy offers a wide range of educational training offerings augmented with an ever-evolving database of 1,200 learning assets:</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="subscribe-to-the-innovation-and-transformation-newsletter">Subscribe to the Innovation and Transformation newsletter</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/nl/sap-innovation-and-transformation-newsletter/index.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="self-paced-learning">1. Self-Paced Learning</h3>
  <p>Guided by prescriptive and social-driven analysis of the individual user’s learning needs and style, SAP Enterprise Support Academy recommends live and on-demand learning support offerings and a personalized learning plan. In addition, our customers can visit <a href="https://support.sap.com/en/offerings-programs/enterprise-support/enterprise-support-academy/learn.html">the SAP Enterprise Support edition of SAP Learning Hub</a> to choose from a catalog of virtual learning options, allowing access to sessions whenever and wherever users want.</p>
  <h3 id="live-virtual-sessions-with-sap-experts">2. Live Virtual Sessions with SAP Experts</h3>
  <p>By collaborating with SAP experts through SAP Enterprise Support guides, our customers can participate in a high impact knowledge transfer on topics including integration, deployment, and system operations. Each session can range anywhere between a 60-minute call to a multi-day training workshop.</p>
  <p>Each live virtual interaction is tailored to help our customers prepare for a migration to SAP S/4HANA on their terms, get answers to their questions, and explore different options for their plans for future <a href="https://insights.sap.com/what-is-digital-transformation/">digital transformation</a>.</p>
  <h3 id="value-maps">3. Value Maps</h3>
  <p><a href="https://support.sap.com/en/offerings-programs/enterprise-support/enterprise-support-academy/value-maps.html">The SAP Enterprise Support value maps</a> work to lead our customers through the knowledge, skills, and services needed to address business challenges and adopt intelligent technologies. The value maps provide direct access to SAP experts, collaboration forums, high impact learning, and prescriptive guidance, so users can achieve meaningful results and unlock new potential for growth.</p>
  <h2 id="ever-expanding-learning-options-to-meet-unique-requirements">Ever-Expanding Learning Options to Meet Unique Requirements</h2>
  <p>No matter the learning experience and topic, we want to help our customers have access to the information they need to move their business forward. This mission underlying SAP Enterprise Support Academy drives our team of SAP experts and support engineers to continuously adapt, integrate, and expand the learning portfolio.</p>
  <p>Every month, we send registered users a newsletter detailing the latest content added to SAP Enterprise Support Academy and the highlights of upcoming sessions. Plus, promotional articles are featured to provide a first look into new offerings being extended to program users.</p>
  <h2 id="a-distinct-opportunity-to-maximize-the-value-of-sap-software">A Distinct Opportunity to Maximize the Value of SAP Software</h2>
  <p>With a good balance of self-paced learning, educational content, and expert guidance, our customers can close their workforce’s digital skill gaps at any place, any time, and through any device.</p>
  <p>That’s the beauty of SAP Enterprise Support Academy. Regardless of role, digital experience, or education, everyone can build up their proficiency in using SAP software – such as SAP S/4HANA and SAP SuccessFactors solutions. And over time, as they apply their new skills, innovative ideas, and process know-how, employees are prepared to successfully achieve expected business outcomes together.</p>
  <p><em>Learn more about <a href="https://support.sap.com/en/offerings-programs/enterprise-support/enterprise-support-academy.html">SAP Enterprise Support Academy</a>. Stay in the conversation by following the SAP Services and Support offerings on <a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/sapsupportinfo">YouTube</a>, <a href="https://twitter.com/SAPDigitalSvcs">Twitter</a>, <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/138840">LinkedIn</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/SAPDigitalBusinessServices">Facebook</a>.</em></p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Silvia Gaber is part of SAP Enterprise Support Academy at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-enterprise-support</category>
            <category>product/sap-learning-hub</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How to Move to the Cloud While Meeting the Pace of Change]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/06/move-to-cloud-meet-pace-of-change</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/06/move-to-cloud-meet-pace-of-change</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[While a move to the cloud usually means company-wide change, there are ways of getting work done without transforming the entire company.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f80efcd71148952b3772abbc140c8a076bd890ff.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f80efcd71148952b3772abbc140c8a076bd890ff.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1f80efcd71148952b3772abbc140c8a076bd890ff.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="How to Move to the Cloud While Meeting the Pace of Change" src="./media_1f80efcd71148952b3772abbc140c8a076bd890ff.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="how-to-move-to-the-cloud-while-meeting-the-pace-of-change">How to Move to the Cloud While Meeting the Pace of Change</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>As customers release pent-up demand and the pace of change doubles or triples, moving to the cloud has never been more urgent. But how do businesses shift quickly from an on-premise mindset when they lack the skills, expertise, and strategy to move forward? For SAP customers, the answer is SAP Enterprise Support services.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Never have businesses – even the most risk averse – had to transform themselves so rapidly and completely. After a year of reshaping how employees work, suppliers are engaged, and customers are served with digital technology, organizations must now evolve again to set a scalable foundation for today’s recovery and tomorrow’s growth.</p>
  <p>Business transformation can emerge in a variety of forms in the cloud. Some companies experience greater operational speed and agility by migrating their legacy data and capabilities to intelligent ERP. Other businesses enjoy the support of predictive analytics and extended visibility to proactively identify opportunities and mitigate risks. We’ve even helped organizations implement the latest intelligent technologies, such as <a href="https://insights.sap.com/what-is-artificial-intelligence/">artificial intelligence (AI)</a>, the <a href="https://insights.sap.com/what-is-iot-internet-of-things/">Internet of Things (IoT)</a>, and <a href="https://insights.sap.com/what-is-machine-learning/">machine learning</a>, to open the door to socially responsible and environmentally friendly outcomes.</p>
  <p>How do they accomplish such advantages at a time when the pace of change is perhaps one of the most significant disrupters? For many companies, it comes down to accessing hands-on, expert-led workstreams and step-by-step guidance from <a href="https://www.sap.com/services/support-plans/enterprise.html">SAP Enterprise Support</a> services.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="access-proactive-and-preventative-support-from-day-one-with-sap-enterprise-support">Access proactive and preventative support from day one with SAP Enterprise Support</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/services/support-plans/enterprise.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="matching-urgency-with-expert-led-guidance-and-support">Matching Urgency with Expert-Led Guidance and Support</h2>
  <p>Sometimes market dynamics, competition, and customer preferences shift so quickly that legacy systems, processes, and mindsets can become obsolete at a moment’s notice. But that doesn’t mean that businesses should respond immediately by heading to the cloud on their own. Instead, many of our customers have learned that relying on strategic support from a trusted partner can put them in an even better position for growth and innovation than they could achieve on their own.</p>
  <p>For <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/02/b4bb49c5-d07d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff.html">First National Operation &#x26; Maintenance Company</a> (NOMAC), this realization came during an upgrade of its core system, which spans across more than 10 countries in the Middle East, Africa, Eastern Europe, and Asia. NOMAC turned to <a href="https://support.sap.com/en/offerings-programs/enterprise-support/enterprise-support-advisory-council.html">SAP Enterprise Support Advisory Council</a> for guidance during its implementation of the extended edition of <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/s4hana-erp.html">SAP S/4HANA Cloud</a>. With direct access to SAP experts, prescriptive learning, and social collaboration forums, the company had at its disposal the relevant tools, best practices, and resources needed to move to the cloud faster and with less expense.</p>
  <p><a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/04/56010402-d97d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff.html">Sorrifácil Franchising Ltda.</a> also took advantage of the expertise of SAP Enterprise Support Advisory Council, but with a different goal in mind. Serving 1.3 million patients at more than 100 dental clinics throughout Brazil, the company already relied on <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm.html">cloud-based customer relationship management (CRM) solutions</a> to drive its customer experience. But the Sorrifácil team wanted to better understand the functionality of these solutions, as well as their integration capabilities, best practices, and benefits. This desire led to its engagement with SAP Enterprise Support Advisory Council, increasing the independence and self-sufficiency needed to make the most of future innovations.</p>
  <p><a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2021/04/044c10c7-dc7d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff.html">Eczacibaşi Group</a> underwent an even more profound transformation with the assistance of SAP Enterprise Support. In an enterprise-wide transformation impacting five companies in four locations across four countries, the company connected its cloud technologies to business objectives – all within a tight timeline during a worldwide pandemic. By leveraging a tailored engagement plan and SAP Enterprise Support guides early on, the company fully understood potential limitations and requirements. SAP experts also provided a steady schedule of continuous quality checks and remote live learning sessions on data migration methodologies and best practices to help ensure a low-risk and smooth go-live.</p>
  <h2 id="easing-transitions-to-reshape-business-functions">Easing Transitions to Reshape Business Functions</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="watch-recordings-from-the-virtual-sap-enterprise-support-day">Watch recordings from the virtual SAP Enterprise Support Day</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://event.on24.com/eventRegistration/EventLobbyServlet?target=reg20.jsp&#x26;referrer=&#x26;eventid=2958819&#x26;sessionid=1&#x26;key=6373C804FAC9AE94B1AB050A6594D415&#x26;regTag=&#x26;V2=false&#x26;sourcepage=register">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>While cloud migrations are usually associated with sweeping company-wide change, there are projects where individual business areas find better ways of getting work done without transforming the entire company. Such situations may come in the digitalization of back-office processes or those for HR and finance and specific capabilities that enhance decision-making.</p>
  <p>Take <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/03/0c110bb5-d17d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff.html">San Miguel S.A.</a>, for example. To unify employee data and standardize HR management across global operations, the fruit and vegetable producer and exporter chose the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/employee-central-hris.html">SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central</a> solution. Through SAP Enterprise Support, the company used a continuous quality check service that helped ensure a smooth production system launch in line with recommended best practices, enabling maximum efficiency of the centralized cloud-based HR system.</p>
  <p><a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/04/6e4f8fc0-d87d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff.html">Oriental Union Chemical Corporation</a> (OUCC) also took a targeted cloud transformation approach to enhance a critical business capability – insight-driven decision-making. To optimize the value the<br><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/cloud-analytics.html">SAP Analytics Cloud</a> solution brings to OUCC, the company engaged SAP Enterprise Support services to leverage enablement workshops, proactive remote services, and ongoing support. OUCC also received training on key product features and solution overviews through various demos, use cases, insights, and tools. This expert guidance gave the clarity to implement and fine-tune the analytics solution, reducing training costs significantly and cutting the overall load time for some story templates by 10%.</p>
  <h2 id="accelerating-meaningful-change-in-an-ever-evolving-world">Accelerating Meaningful Change in an Ever-Evolving World</h2>
  <p>While each of our customer’s transformation stories are unique in their own way, they are all taking part in a massive transformation happening worldwide.</p>
  <p>That’s the beauty unfolding when we watch businesses transform with SAP Enterprise Support. With hands-on, expert-led workstreams and step-by-step guidance, our customers see the pace of change not as a business disrupter, but rather as a motivator that’s helping them realize their full potential in the cloud.</p>
  <p>Explore how SAP Enterprise Support can help your business move to the cloud without letting the pace of change become a disruption by registering and watching the recordings of our <a href="https://gateway.on24.com/wcc/eh/1904844/category/44624/event-for-americas-region">virtual SAP Enterprise Support day</a> held in March 2021.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>Stay in the conversation by following SAP Services and Support on<br><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/sapsupportinfo">YouTube</a>, <a href="https://twitter.com/SAPDigitalSvcs">Twitter</a>, <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/138840">LinkedIn</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/SAPDigitalBusinessServices">Facebook</a>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Chad Crook is senior vice president and global head of Customer Engagement and Experience Success Center at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-enterprise-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Enterprise Support Value Maps: Fundamental Guidance to an Intelligent ERP Transformation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/sap-enterprise-support-value-maps-guidance-intelligent-erp</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/sap-enterprise-support-value-maps-guidance-intelligent-erp</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Enterprise Support value maps empower customers to control their transformation, with SAP S/4HANA at the center. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1cdc91b81daf0476924ff05f31c003e711465b721.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1cdc91b81daf0476924ff05f31c003e711465b721.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1cdc91b81daf0476924ff05f31c003e711465b721.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Enterprise Support Value Maps: Fundamental Guidance to an Intelligent ERP Transformation" src="./media_1cdc91b81daf0476924ff05f31c003e711465b721.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-enterprise-support-value-maps-fundamental-guidance-to-an-intelligent-erp-transformation">SAP Enterprise Support Value Maps: Fundamental Guidance to an Intelligent ERP Transformation</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Every transformation journey can run faster and avoid uncertainty with a well-defined road map. With the latest expansion of the SAP Enterprise Support value maps, organizations can gain a clear view to fulfill their true potential with a best-fit enterprise resource planning (ERP) foundation and secure their future with new capabilities.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Far from a catchphrase, the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/intelligent-enterprise.html">Intelligent Enterprise</a> concept helps organizations break through the paralysis of unanticipated change. This framework advocates for the use of an organized backbone of data knowledge, digital skills and services, and intelligent technologies to actively resolve business challenges, pivot operations, and respond intelligently to disruptive situations.</p>
  <p>Many SAP customers rely on the <a href="https://support.sap.com/en/offerings-programs/enterprise-support/enterprise-support-academy/value-maps.html">SAP Enterprise Support value maps</a> to quickly restructure and ramp up new approaches to innovate products, services, and experiences that their customers and employees require. The value maps fuel these changes by providing the clarity to choose and set up a best-fit digital foundation with prescriptive guidance, interactive learning, social collaboration, and access to SAP experts and industry peers throughout the application lifecycle.</p>
  <p>Whether enabling the Intelligent Enterprise or unlocking its power, the value maps help customers adopt and run SAP offerings, including SAP S/4HANA, SAP Analytics, SAP Customer Experience, and SAP SuccessFactors solutions. Additionally, the value maps provide guidance for topics such as application lifecycle management, security, data volume management, business process improvement, or digital innovation – which are all foundational elements.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="explore-sap-enterprise-support-value-maps">Explore SAP Enterprise Support value maps</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="http://support.sap.com/valuemaps">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="adapting-and-thriving-with-a-best-match-intelligent-erp">Adapting and Thriving with a Best-Match Intelligent ERP</h2>
  <p>Moving from a legacy IT system to the modern ERP capabilities of <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/s4hana-erp.html">SAP S/4HANA</a> is a critical part of securing the foundation to become an intelligent enterprise. The future-ready ERP comes with built-in intelligent technologies, such as artificial intelligence (AI), machine learning, advanced analytics, and a modern user experience.</p>
  <p>More importantly, SAP S/4HANA can be deployed and used with flexibility and control. Our customers can choose one of three deployment options:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Private cloud:</strong> Benefit from a subscription-based, cloud implementation that safeguards pre-existing investments in legacy ERP customizations, configurations, and partner add-ons. <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/rise.html">Incremental transformation</a> into a pure software-as-a-service (SaaS) landscape is supported by software, support, technical managed services, and infrastructure made available through one point of contact with one set of service-level agreement terms.</li>
    <li><strong>Public cloud:</strong> Reimagine business processes and take advantage of standardized best practices without converting legacy ERP processes and configurations. This complete, modern, and native SaaS ERP solution provides the fastest path to innovation and the lowest total cost of ownership.</li>
    <li><strong>On premise:</strong> Gain complete control and ownership of your applications and data landscape to manage unique, customer-specific needs that cannot be addressed in the cloud. Organizations can leverage existing IT departments, infrastructure, budget, and infrastructure-as-a-service (IaaS) vendor agreements while remaining compliant with industry- and country-specific regulations.</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="moving-closer-to-becoming-an-intelligent-enterprise">Moving Closer to Becoming an Intelligent Enterprise</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="keep-your-systems-running-at-peak-performance-with-services-and-support-from-sap">Keep your systems running at peak performance with services and support from SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/support.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>With the assistance of the SAP Enterprise Support value maps, our customers can determine the deployment option and transformation path that best fit their needs, so they can orchestrate their move with confidence. More importantly, they can adopt and run scenarios with guided enablement – ranging from lifecycle management and extensibility to data security and analytics – to help secure the changes needed to achieve the expected transformation.</p>
  <p>The value maps empower our customers to control their transformation, with SAP S/4HANA at the center. We provide knowledge transfer, analysis and recommendations, and guidance, including:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Comparison of each edition:</strong> Determine which edition can support a transformation that benefits the organization the most.</li>
    <li><strong>Content on transition options:</strong> Explore possible transition paths, such as new implementation, system conversion, or selective data transition.</li>
    <li><strong>Readiness checks and planning:</strong> Get guidance on planning and preparation activities for moving to SAP S/4HANA, then define a straightforward process of structured and solution-specific practices to adopt and extend new and differentiating capabilities.</li>
    <li><strong>Continuous quality check services:</strong> Provide an expert analysis of the customer landscape and deliver best practice improvement recommendations to help ensure a smooth go-live and rapid user adoption.</li>
    <li><strong>Insight on extending value:</strong> Explore the benefits of SAP Fiori apps, embedded analytics, and other innovation possibilities to get the most benefit from the deployment of SAP S/4HANA.</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="accessing-the-core-essentials-for-a-self-paced-transformation-journey">Accessing the Core Essentials for a Self-Paced Transformation Journey</h2>
  <p>The outcomes that our customers are achieving are proof of the power of choice, guided learning, and expertise during an ERP migration experience. Some businesses <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/01/045d12e7-c77d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff.html">integrate their innovations</a> through expert training and support services to uphold a vision of brand excellence and trusted consumer experiences. Other organizations <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2019/09/323544fa-637d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff.html">migrate their ERP software and replace legacy systems</a> to minimize risk and help ensure an efficient transition without disrupting operations. And many more companies <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2020/02/ac3e1cbc-877d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff.html">simplify and automate IT operations</a> and optimize their database to prepare for a smooth move to the cloud.</p>
  <p>Remember, there isn’t one right way to becoming an intelligent enterprise. But the SAP Enterprise Support value maps for SAP S/4HANA, SAP S/4HANA Cloud, and SAP S/4HANA Cloud, private edition, could undoubtedly make your path clearer by helping you ensure your success in adopting and running an intelligent ERP.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Don’t miss out:</strong> Sign up for <a href="http://support.sap.com/valuemaps">the SAP Enterprise Support value maps</a> by requesting access to <a href="https://support.sap.com/en/offerings-programs/enterprise-support/enterprise-support-academy/learn.html">SAP Learning Hub</a> or join the <a href="https://enrollment-ac82d52a4.dispatcher.hana.ondemand.com/index.html?itemID=LR_ValueMaps_EN">SAP Enterprise Support Value Maps Learning Room</a> if you already have access.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Stay in the conversation by following SAP Services and Support on<br><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/sapsupportinfo">YouTube</a>, <a href="https://twitter.com/SAPDigitalSvcs">Twitter</a>, <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/138840">LinkedIn</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/SAPDigitalBusinessServices">Facebook</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Ami Patel is global program lead for SAP Enterprise Support Value Maps at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="subscribe-to-the-innovation-and-transformation-newsletter">Subscribe to the Innovation and Transformation Newsletter</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/nl/sap-innovation-and-transformation-newsletter/index.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-erp</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-enterprise-support</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>