<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/content-type/what-is/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[What Is Deep Learning?]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/what-is-deep-learning</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/what-is-deep-learning</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn all about deep learning in AI: what it is, how it works, how it relates to machine learning, and common applications.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d1d46fd9dea9b8d0462524c202ed54614725e2a7.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d1d46fd9dea9b8d0462524c202ed54614725e2a7.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1d1d46fd9dea9b8d0462524c202ed54614725e2a7.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Conceptual illustration of AI" src="./media_1d1d46fd9dea9b8d0462524c202ed54614725e2a7.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1732" height="1732">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="what-is-deep-learning">What is deep learning?</h1>
        <p>Deep learning is a subset of artificial intelligence (AI) that mimics a brain’s neural networks to learn from large amounts of data, enabling machines to solve complex problems.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="deep-learning-definition">Deep learning definition</h2>
  <p>Deep learning is a type of <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/what-is-machine-learning.html">machine learning</a> that enables computers to process information in ways similar to the human brain. It's called "deep" because it involves multiple layers of neural networks that help the system understand and interpret data. This technique allows computers to recognize patterns and manage complex tasks, such as translating languages and driving cars autonomously. Similar to how humans learn from experience, these systems improve their skills and accuracy over time by analyzing vast amounts of data, without needing manual updates from humans.</p>
  <h2 id="understanding-neural-networks">Understanding neural networks</h2>
  <h4 id="from-theory-to-perceptron">From theory to Perceptron</h4>
  <p>In the 1940s, Warren McCulloch, a neuroscientist, and Walter Pitts, a mathematician, collaborated to create the first artificial neural network concept. Their goal was to understand how the brain could produce complex thought patterns from the simple binary responses of neurons. They introduced a model of the neuron, which they believed could mimic the brain's ability to perform complex calculations using binary logic.</p>
  <p>In the neural network model developed by McCulloch and Pitts, inputs act like the electrical impulses a neuron receives. If some inputs are more crucial for a specific result, the model emphasizes these through greater weight. When these weighted inputs exceed a certain level, the neuron activates; if not, it remains off. This basic on-off mechanism enabled their model to mimic simple brain-like decision-making processes, setting the stage for deep learning's evolution.</p>
  <p>In 1957, the introduction of the Mark I Perceptron, a room-sized machine built by computer scientist and psychologist Frank Rosenblatt, showcased the first practical use of artificial neurons. This device used photocells and artificial neural networks to recognize and categorize images, demonstrating the effectiveness of McCulloch and Pitts' ideas. Rosenblatt's Perceptron not only confirmed that machine learning could work but also paved the way for the development of today's more sophisticated deep learning technologies.</p>
  <h2 id="how-does-deep-learning-work">How does deep learning work?</h2>
  <p>Deep learning works by using the process of prediction to determine which algorithms in their neural networks are the most successful at producing outputs that meet human expectations. Then, the networks use backpropagation to refine those algorithms so that their rate of success improves. Here’s an example:</p>
  <p>Imagine you're teaching a computer to recognize different genres of music. The neural network analyzes thousands of music files, gradually learning to notice features like instrumentation, beats, and chord progressions. When it makes a prediction, like identifying a piece as a rock song, and is then told whether it's correct, it uses a method called backpropagation to adjust its algorithm.</p>
  <p>This is like learning from mistakes. For example, if the computer mistakes a classical piano sonata for a rock song, it learns from this error, refining its ability to distinguish between classical and rock songs in future predictions. Over time, this process enables the artificial neural network to make highly accurate predictions, turning it into a powerful tool for everything from recommending movies based on what you like to enabling self-driving cars to interpret road signs and signals.</p>
  <h3 id="a-deeper-dive-into-deep-neural-network-layers">A deeper dive into deep neural network layers</h3>
  <p>This list explains the essential components of a deep neural network and the general order in which they function. However, neurons, activation functions, and regularization techniques are not isolated steps, but rather features that operate throughout the network and its learning process.</p>
  <ol>
    <li>Input layer</li>
  </ol>
  <p>The input layer is the gateway into the network, where each neuron represents a unique feature of the input data. This layer's primary function is to receive the raw data and pass it to the subsequent layers for further processing.</p>
  <ol start="2">
    <li>Neurons (nodes)</li>
  </ol>
  <p>Neurons, or nodes, are the fundamental processing units of a neural network. Each neuron receives input, processes it (using a weighted sum and then applying an activation function), and sends the output to the next layer.</p>
  <ol start="3">
    <li>Activation functions</li>
  </ol>
  <p>These are like the decision-makers in a neural network, helping it determine what to learn and what to ignore. They add a kind of flexibility to the network, allowing it to capture and learn complex patterns. Common activation functions include <a href="https://community.sap.com/t5/artificial-intelligence-and-machine-learning-blogs/logistic-regression-in-machine-learning/ba-p/13427397">sigmoid</a>, ReLU (rectified linear unit), and tanh.</p>
  <ol start="4">
    <li>Weights and biases</li>
  </ol>
  <p>Weights are parameters within the network determine the influence of input data on the outputs within the network's layers. Along with weights, biases ensure that activation functions can produce non-zero outputs, enhancing the network's ability to activate and learn effectively.</p>
  <ol start="5">
    <li>Hidden layers</li>
  </ol>
  <p>Situated between the input layers and output layers, hidden layers perform the bulk of computations within a neural network. They’re called "hidden" because unlike the input and output, they don’t interact with the external environment. The complexity and capability of a neural network are largely determined by the number and architecture of hidden layers.</p>
  <ol start="6">
    <li>Output layer</li>
  </ol>
  <p>This is the final layer in a neural network. It presents the results, transforming the information from the hidden layers into a format that solves the task at hand, such as classification, regression, or any other type of prediction.</p>
  <ol start="7">
    <li>Loss function</li>
  </ol>
  <p>The loss function, or cost function, quantifies the difference between the predicted outputs and actual outputs. Minimizing this function is the goal of training, enabling the model to predict more accurately.</p>
  <ol start="8">
    <li>Optimization algorithms</li>
  </ol>
  <p>These algorithms fine-tune the model to improve its accuracy over time. They tweak the weights and biases to reduce errors during predictions. Some popular methods include stochastic gradient descent, Adam, and RMSprop.</p>
  <ol start="9">
    <li>Backpropagation</li>
  </ol>
  <p>This deep learning algorithm is crucial because it helps the model learn and improve from its mistakes. It figures out how changes to the model's weights affect its accuracy. Then, it adjusts these settings by tracing errors backward through the model to make it better at making predictions.</p>
  <ol start="10">
    <li>Regularization techniques</li>
  </ol>
  <p>Models often learn the training data too closely, causing them to not perform as well on new data (known as overfitting). To adjust for this, techniques like L1 and L2 regularization and batch normalization are used to fine-tune the size of weights and speed up the training process.</p>
  <ol start="11">
    <li>Batch normalization</li>
  </ol>
  <p>This technique normalizes the inputs of each layer, aiming to improve the stability, performance, and speed of the neural network. It also helps in reducing the sensitivity to the initial starting weights.</p>
  <ol start="12">
    <li>Dropout</li>
  </ol>
  <p>Another regularization method, dropout randomly ignores a set of neurons during training. This helps to reduce overfitting by preventing the network from becoming too dependent on any single neuron.</p>
  <h2 id="common-applications-of-deep-learning">Common applications of deep learning</h2>
  <p>Deep machine learning has come a long way since the Perceptron. Instead of needing to install room-sized machines, organizations can now create <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/data-intelligence/features/machine-learning.html">deep learning solutions on the cloud</a>. The ability of today’s deep neural networks to handle complex datasets make them valuable tools across diverse sectors, opening new avenues for innovation that were once considered futuristic.</p>
  <h4 id="automotive">Automotive</h4>
  <p>Deep learning allows vehicles to interpret sensor data for navigation. It also improves driver assistance systems, with features like hazard detection and collision avoidance, and contributes to better vehicle design and manufacturing.</p>
  <h4 id="business-operations">Business operations</h4>
  <p><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/what-is-conversational-ai.html">Conversational AI chatbots</a> and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/developer-tools.html">virtual assistant copilots</a> are popular business deep learning applications. They reduce human error by <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/process-automation/what-is-process-automation.html">automating manual tasks</a>, accelerate data analysis and decision-making, and make it easier to find information stored across different systems.</p>
  <h4 id="finance">Finance</h4>
  <p>Algorithmic trading powered by deep learning is used to analyze market data for predictive insights and identifies complex patterns to enhances fraud detection. Deep learning also aids in risk management, evaluating credit risks and market conditions for more informed decision-making.</p>
  <h4 id="healthcare">Healthcare</h4>
  <p>Deep learning algorithms can help improve diagnostic accuracy and detect anomalies like tumors at early stages from medical images. There are also opportunities for drug discovery by predicting molecular behavior, facilitating the development of new treatments.</p>
  <h4 id="manufacturing">Manufacturing</h4>
  <p>Predictive maintenance uses the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/what-is-iot.html">Internet of Things</a> and deep learning to anticipate machinery failures, minimizing downtime. Visual inspection systems trained on extensive image datasets can enhance quality control by identifying defects.</p>
  <h4 id="media-and-entertainment">Media and entertainment</h4>
  <p>The entertainment industry uses deep learning applications to power content recommendations on streaming platforms, and to help creators develop realistic CGI and compose music using <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/generative-ai.html">generative AI</a>. It also analyzes viewer preferences, helping creators tailor content and predict future trends.</p>
  <h4 id="retail">Retail</h4>
  <p>Deep learning has revolutionized <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm/service-cloud.html">retail customer experiences</a> with personalized product recommendations. It also improves inventory management by using predictive analytics to forecast demand and optimize stock levels.</p>
  <h4 id="supply-chain">Supply chain</h4>
  <p>Logistics operations are using deep machine learning to optimize delivery scheduling by identifying traffic disruptions in real time. Deep learning also enhances demand and supply forecasting accuracy, enabling proactive strategy adjustments.</p>
  <h2 id="deep-learning-benefits-and-challenges">Deep learning benefits and challenges</h2>
  <p>While the benefits of deep learning are truly impressive, the complexity of this technology brings challenges, too. And because deep learning solutions require considerable planning and resources, it’s critical that organizations establish <a href="https://www.sap.com/insights/viewpoints/a-playbook-for-machine-learning-projects-that-work.html">clearly defined goals</a> and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/what-is-responsible-AI.html">responsible AI practices</a> prior to designing and deploying this technology.</p>
  <div class="table">
    <div>
      <div data-valign="middle"><strong>Benefits</strong></div>
      <div data-valign="middle"><strong>Challenges</strong></div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div data-valign="middle">
        <ul>
          <li>High accuracy in tasks like image and speech recognition</li>
          <li>Ability to process and analyze vast amounts of data</li>
          <li>Improves over time as it's exposed to more data</li>
          <li>Automates feature extraction, reducing the need for manual intervention</li>
          <li>Enables personalized experiences in services and products</li>
        </ul>
      </div>
      <div data-valign="middle">
        <ul>
          <li>Requires large datasets for training</li>
          <li>Computationally intensive, needing significant processing power</li>
          <li>Can be a “black box,” making it difficult to understand models’ decision processes</li>
          <li>Susceptible to perpetuating unfair biases when training data is faulty</li>
          <li>Needs continuous data and monitoring to maintain performance over time</li>
        </ul>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="deep-learning-vs-machine-learning-vs-ai">Deep learning vs. machine learning vs. AI</h2>
  <p>There are some key differences between traditional machine learning and deep learning:</p>
  <p>Machine learning relies on humans to manually identify and select the features or characteristics of the data that are important for a task, such as edges in images or specific words in text. This process of training requires a lot of expertise and effort.</p>
  <p>Deep learning enables machines to automatically determine which features of the data are most important for performing specific tasks. This is done by processing the raw data, such as pixels in an image, through multiple layers of a neural network. Each layer transforms the data into a more abstract form, building on the previous layer's output. As the model is exposed to more data, it continuously refines these transformations to improve accuracy and performance, becoming more effective over time.</p>
  <h3 id="ai-vs-deep-learning-vs-machine-learning-example">AI vs. deep learning vs. machine learning example</h3>
  <p>If you’re unsure of the differences between AI, machine learning, and deep learning, you’re not alone. Here’s a real-world AI vs. deep learning vs. machine learning example about self-driving vehicles:</p>
  <p>AI is the overarching technology used to give self-driving vehicles human-like intelligence and autonomy. It includes machine learning and deep learning.</p>
  <p>Machine learning is the subtype of AI that allows self-driving systems to learn and improve from data without being specifically programmed for every scenario.</p>
  <p>Deep learning is the specialized subtype of machine learning that processes and interprets the complex inputs, including visual data from cameras, making sense of the environment in real-time.</p>
  <h3 id="deep-learning-vs-deep-learning-models">Deep learning vs. deep learning models</h3>
  <p>It’s also not uncommon to see the terms “deep learning” and “deep learning models” used interchangeably, but there’s a nuanced difference between them:</p>
  <p>Deep learning refers to the entire field of study. It encompasses the theories, techniques, algorithms, and processes used to train artificial neural networks.</p>
  <p>Deep learning models refer to the specific neural networks that have been designed and trained to solve a particular problem or perform a specific task. Each model is unique, tailored to its specific data, training, and task. A model's performance depends upon:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>How well it’s been trained, including the quality and quantity of the data, and its learning rate.</li>
    <li>The design and computational power of the computer infrastructure it runs on.</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="what-are-deep-neural-networks">What are deep neural networks?</h2>
  <p>Deep learning networks, often called deep neural networks, learn complex patterns in large datasets by adjusting neural connections through training. There are several major types: artificial neural networks, convolutional neural networks, recurrent neural networks, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/what-is-generative-ai.html">generative neural networks,</a> and autoencoders.</p>
  <h4 id="deep-neural-network-types">Deep neural network types</h4>
  <div class="table">
    <div>
      <div data-valign="middle"><strong>Feature/Type</strong></div>
      <div data-valign="middle"><strong>Artificial Neural Network</strong></div>
      <div data-valign="middle"><strong>Convolutional Neural Network</strong></div>
      <div data-valign="middle"><strong>Recurrent Neural Network</strong></div>
      <div data-valign="middle"><strong>Generative Neural Network</strong></div>
      <div data-valign="middle"><strong>Autoencoders</strong></div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div data-valign="middle"><strong>Primary use</strong></div>
      <div data-valign="middle">General purpose, ranging from regression to classification.</div>
      <div data-valign="middle">Image and video recognition, image classification.</div>
      <div data-valign="middle">Natural language processing, speech recognition.</div>
      <div data-valign="middle">Image generation, style transfer, data augmentation.</div>
      <div data-valign="middle">Dimensionality reduction, noise reduction, feature learning, and anomaly detection.</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div data-valign="middle"><strong>Key characteristics</strong></div>
      <div data-valign="middle">Simplicity and versatility.</div>
      <div data-valign="middle">Use of convolutional layers to adaptively learn spatial hierarchies of features.</div>
      <div data-valign="middle">Ability to process information in sequences, preserving information from one step of the sequence to the next.</div>
      <div data-valign="middle">Ability to generate new data similar to the input data.</div>
      <div data-valign="middle">Uses an encoder to compress data and a decoder to reconstruct it, learning efficient data representations.</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div data-valign="middle"><strong>Basic concept</strong></div>
      <div data-valign="middle">A network of neurons/nodes that simulate the human brain.</div>
      <div data-valign="middle">Specialized for processing grid-like topology data.</div>
      <div data-valign="middle">Designed for sequential or time-series data.</div>
      <div data-valign="middle">Consists of two networks (generator and discriminator) competing in a game.</div>
      <div data-valign="middle">Designed for unsupervised learning, typically for data compression and feature extraction.</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div data-valign="middle"><strong>Advantages</strong></div>
      <div data-valign="middle">Flexible. Can be applied to a broad spectrum of tasks.</div>
      <div data-valign="middle">High efficiency and performance in tasks related to visual data.</div>
      <div data-valign="middle">Capable of learning long-term dependencies with modifications like long short-term memory.</div>
      <div data-valign="middle">Powerful for generating new data instances; enhances the realism and diversity of data.</div>
      <div data-valign="middle">Efficient at data compression and learning salient features without labels; useful in pretraining for other tasks.</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div data-valign="middle"><strong>Challenges</strong></div>
      <div data-valign="middle">May struggle with complex pattern recognition in raw, high-dimensional data.</div>
      <div data-valign="middle">Requires a significant amount of training data for optimal performance.</div>
      <div data-valign="middle">Difficulty in training over long sequences due to vanishing gradient problem.</div>
      <div data-valign="middle">Training stability and mode collapse can be challenging to manage.</div>
      <div data-valign="middle">Prone to overfitting if not regularized or if the data is not diverse enough; can be tricky to tune the latent space.</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div data-valign="middle"><strong>Architectural features</strong></div>
      <div data-valign="middle">Layers of fully connected neurons.</div>
      <div data-valign="middle">Convolutional layers, pooling layers, followed by fully connected layers.</div>
      <div data-valign="middle">Chains of repeating units that process sequences.</div>
      <div data-valign="middle">Two networks: a generator to create data, and a discriminator to evaluate it.</div>
      <div data-valign="middle">Uses an encoder and decoder to reduce and then reconstruct the input.</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div data-valign="middle"><strong>Data handling</strong></div>
      <div data-valign="middle">Handles a wide range of data types.</div>
      <div data-valign="middle">Efficiently handles spatial data.</div>
      <div data-valign="middle">Excels at handling sequential or time-dependent data.</div>
      <div data-valign="middle">Learns to generate data that is indistinguishable from real data.</div>
      <div data-valign="middle">Efficient in learning compressed representations for a given dataset.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="deep-learning-infrastructure-requirements">Deep learning infrastructure requirements</h2>
  <p>Deep learning requires specialized computing and networking infrastructure to process its complex models and massive datasets. It’s not practical to run deep learning models on general computer hardware or networks, so many organizations adopt <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/what-is-enterprise-AI.html">enterprise AI</a> platforms to meet the necessary requirements. Here are the main infrastructure considerations:</p>
  <h4 id="high-performance-gpus">High-performance GPUs</h4>
  <p>The backbone of deep learning infrastructure is high-performance graphics processing units (GPUs). Originally designed for rendering graphics in video games, GPUs have processing capabilities that make them well-suited for deep learning. Their ability to perform multiple calculations simultaneously greatly reduces training time for models, making them indispensable for modern AI research and applications.</p>
  <h4 id="scalable-storage-solutions">Scalable storage solutions</h4>
  <p>The more data a model can learn from, the better its performance. This creates a need for scalable and fast storage solutions that can handle petabytes of data without creating bottlenecks in data retrieval. Solid state drives and distributed file systems are commonly used to meet these demands, offering high-speed data access that keeps pace with the computational speed of GPUs.</p>
  <h4 id="efficient-data-processing-frameworks">Efficient data processing frameworks</h4>
  <p>Frameworks and libraries such as TensorFlow, PyTorch, and Keras simplify the development of deep learning models by providing pre-built functions, reducing the need for coding from scratch. These tools not only speed up the development process but also optimize the computational efficiency of training and inference, allowing for the effective utilization of underlying hardware.</p>
  <h4 id="cloud-computing-platforms">Cloud computing platforms</h4>
  <p><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/what-is-cloud-computing.html">Cloud computing platforms</a> play a pivotal role in making deep learning widely accessible. They provide access to high-performance computing resources on-demand, eliminating the need for significant upfront investment in physical hardware. These platforms offer various services, including GPU instances, scalable storage, and machine learning frameworks, making it easier for individuals and organizations to create and deploy deep learning models.</p>
  <h4 id="network-infrastructure">Network infrastructure</h4>
  <p>Deep learning models are often trained across multiple GPUs and even across different geographical locations, so a robust network infrastructure is crucial. High-bandwidth connectivity ensures that data and model parameters can be efficiently transferred between nodes in a distributed training setup, minimizing delays and optimizing the training process.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div data-valign="middle">
        <h3 id="explore-ai-built-for-business">Explore AI built for business</h3>
        <p>See how to enhance and better connect your people, data, and processes.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence.html">Learn more</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="faq">FAQ</h2>
  <div class="accordion">
    <div>
      <div data-valign="middle">What is deep learning in simple words?</div>
      <div data-valign="middle">Deep learning, sometimes also called deep machine learning, is a type of artificial intelligence that teaches computers to learn by example, much like humans do. It uses a layered structure of algorithms called neural networks to process data, recognize patterns, and make decisions.</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div data-valign="middle">What is an example of deep learning?</div>
      <div data-valign="middle">A notable example of deep learning is in medical imaging, where algorithms analyze images like X-rays, MRIs, or CT scans to detect diseases such as cancer. By training on vast datasets of medical images, these deep learning systems can identify subtle patterns that might be missed by human eyes, assisting doctors in early diagnosis and personalized treatment planning.</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div data-valign="middle">What are three types of deep learning?</div>
      <div data-valign="middle">
        <ol>
          <li><strong>Convolutional neural networks:</strong> A familiar example is the face unlock feature on smartphones. Convolutional neural networks analyze the facial features from the camera input to verify the user’s identity, allowing secure and quick access to the device. This process involves the network learning from various images to accurately recognize and confirm the user’s face.</li>
          <li><strong>Recurrent neural networks:</strong> Ideal for tasks involving sequences, such as predicting the next word in a sentence. This makes them great for applications like predictive text on your smartphone, where the network learns from the sequence of your typing to suggest the next word you might type.</li>
          <li><strong>Autoencoders:</strong> A practical example is image compression, where autoencoders reduce the size of images for storage or transmission and then restore them to their original quality when needed. This process helps in reducing the space needed to store images while maintaining their quality.</li>
        </ol>
      </div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div data-valign="middle">What is the difference between machine learning and deep learning?</div>
      <div data-valign="middle">Machine learning refers to the broader concept of computers learning from data to make decisions or predictions. Deep learning is a subset of machine learning that uses neural networks with many, or “deep,” layers. The main difference is the depth of learning; deep learning automatically discovers the most relevant data to be used for learning, but machine learning requires the data to be specified manually. Additionally, deep learning performs better with larger datasets, while traditional machine learning can be more effective with smaller datasets.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
<div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div data-valign="middle">
        <h3 id="explore-ai-built-for-business-1">Explore AI built for business</h3>
        <p>See how to enhance and better connect your people, data, and processes.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence.html">Learn more</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>sidebar</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
<div>
  <h2 id="share-this-article">Share this article</h2>
  <div class="social-sharing"></div>
  <h2 id="explore-related-content">Explore related content</h2>
  <div class="tags"></div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>content-type/what-is</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[What is Enterprise AI?]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/what-is-enterprise-ai</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/what-is-enterprise-ai</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn what enterprise AI is, key types, and how it’s being used to enhance operations, decision-making, and innovation in different businesses and industries.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div data-valign="middle">
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11c7f67f94c6a779d1d54804435fb56c1f7034f29.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11c7f67f94c6a779d1d54804435fb56c1f7034f29.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_11c7f67f94c6a779d1d54804435fb56c1f7034f29.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Automated robot carriers in a modern distribution warehouse" src="./media_11c7f67f94c6a779d1d54804435fb56c1f7034f29.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2309" height="1299">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="what-is-enterprise-ai">What is enterprise AI?</h1>
        <p>Enterprise AI is the use of artificial intelligence (AI) to make business and manufacturing processes less manual, time-consuming, and prone to human error. Using enterprise AI platforms, many businesses across all industries are beginning to adopt AI at scale.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="why-has-enterprise-ai-become-so-popular">Why has enterprise AI become so popular?</h2>
  <p>Just like with the development of the internet in the 1990s and cloud computing in the 2010s, many businesses have approached AI with caution: Would it live up to the buzz? Or would it just be a fad that wouldn’t add real value to business and industry?</p>
  <p>For many early adopters of enterprise AI, the results have shown that it creates a tangible competitive advantage. These businesses have seen significant improvements and efficiency gains across a spectrum of AI use cases, from data analysis, forecasting, and decision-making, to process automation, workplace productivity, and product development. Some examples:</p>
  <div class="fast-facts">
    <div>
      <div data-valign="middle">
        <h4 id="92">92</h4>
        <h5 id="-2">%</h5>
        <p><strong>Faster forecasting time</strong></p>
        <p>by automotive engineering company ZF Friedrichshafen</p>
        <p><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/customer-stories/zf-friedrichshafen.html">Read the customer story</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div data-valign="middle">
        <h4 id="75">75</h4>
        <h5 id="-1">%</h5>
        <p><strong>Reduction in time spent</strong></p>
        <p>on filing expense reports by yogurt maker Chobani</p>
        <p><a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2023/12/7879d188-9e7e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Read the customer story</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div data-valign="middle">
        <h4 id="27">2.7</h4>
        <h5 id="m">M</h5>
        <p><strong>Documents processed</strong></p>
        <p>in just three weeks to help cultural workers in Germany access financial support at the start of the pandemic</p>
        <p><a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2022/12/101267bd-537e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Read the customer story</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Along with the benefits, businesses also need to understand the challenges of adopting AI, how to apply it to their own use cases and systems, the technical and training requirements, and costs. In this article, we’ll explore:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Types of enterprise AI.</li>
    <li>Benefits and challenges.</li>
    <li>Generative AI in CRM and ERP.</li>
    <li>Industry use cases.</li>
    <li>Implementation strategies and planning.</li>
    <li>What to look for when considering a business AI platform.</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="types-of-enterprise-ai">Types of enterprise AI</h2>
  <p>One of the most interesting aspects of enterprise AI is that it can be used to perform both routine and transformational tasks. Examples:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Routine:</strong> An employee saves a few minutes (and some frustration) by using an AI copilot to find a document that’s been stored in the wrong place. Routine use cases may sound small, but they can really boost productivity at scale.</li>
    <li><strong>Transformational:</strong> A manufacturer saves millions of dollars by using deep learning to predict when its machines will need to have parts replaced – before they break.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>This extreme diversity in AI use cases is impressive but can also make it hard to decide where to begin with AI adoption. A good place to start is by becoming familiar with the main types of business AI and their common applications.</p>
  <h4 id="main-types-of-enterprise-ai">Main types of enterprise AI</h4>
  <div class="table">
    <div>
      <div data-valign="middle"><strong>Type</strong></div>
      <div data-valign="middle"><strong>Description</strong></div>
      <div data-valign="middle"><strong>Common Uses</strong></div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div data-valign="middle">Enterprise machine learning</div>
      <div data-valign="middle">Foundational technologies designed to analyze large volumes of data to identify patterns, make predictions, and learn from outcomes. Includes <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/what-is-deep-learning.html">deep learning</a> for advanced speech recognition and computer vision.</div>
      <div data-valign="middle">Retail personalization, predictive maintenance, financial risk management, supply chain and logistics optimization, crop yield prediction, and disease detection.</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div data-valign="middle">AI copilots and assistants</div>
      <div data-valign="middle">Applications that act as personal assistants for employees. They adapt and improve over time by learning from user interactions.</div>
      <div data-valign="middle">Automating administrative tasks, transcribing meetings, accelerating coding, identifying security and quality issues, and aiding in resource location across extensive networks.</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div data-valign="middle">Generative AI</div>
      <div data-valign="middle">Tools that use human-like logic and language to assist in the creation of new content and data models. Capable of generating marketing content, designing products.</div>
      <div data-valign="middle">Creating sales and marketing content, designing new products, generating realistic synthetic data for AI model training, and supporting rapid prototyping and innovation.</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div data-valign="middle">Natural language processing (NLP)</div>
      <div data-valign="middle">Underlying AI capability that understands, interprets, and generates human language.</div>
      <div data-valign="middle">Enabling chatbots and virtual assistants to interact with humans to automate routine customer support, allowing human workers to spend more time on higher-value interactions.</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div data-valign="middle">Robotic process automation (RPA)</div>
      <div data-valign="middle">Applications that perform tasks that are routine, repetitive, and time-consuming for humans, integrating across different software systems to manage complex workflows.</div>
      <div data-valign="middle">Enhancing ERP and CRM systems by streamlining operations across <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/sales.html">sales and customer service</a>, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/human-resources.html">HR</a>, and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/cloud-analytics/features/generative-ai.html">analytics</a> by handling data entry, processing transactions, automating other digital tasks.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="enterprise-ai-benefits">Enterprise AI benefits</h2>
  <p>As AI tools for business like copilots, chatbots, and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/what-is-generative-ai.html">generative AI</a> become more sophisticated and widely adopted, organizations using these technologies are constantly discovering innovative new ways to use them. Before we explore more specific AI use cases, let’s look at some of the high-level benefits of business AI.</p>
  <h3 id="workplace-experience">Workplace experience</h3>
  <p>AI plays a crucial role in improving the workplace environment by supporting and augmenting the capabilities of employees:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Employee productivity tools:</strong> AI copilots allow employees to focus on higher-value work by helping manage emails, schedule meetings, and prioritize tasks.</li>
    <li><strong>Adaptive learning systems:</strong> AI-driven learning platforms provide personalized training and development, adapting to the learning preferences and speeds of individual employees, making professional growth more engaging and effective.</li>
    <li><strong>Workplace analytics:</strong> AI tools empower teams to enhance employee satisfaction and performance by analyzing work patterns and providing suggestions for optimizing workflows.</li>
  </ul>
  <h3 id="strategic-decision-making">Strategic decision-making</h3>
  <p>The integration of AI into decision-making processes helps businesses enhance accuracy and timeliness:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Data-driven insights:</strong> AI copilots and other enterprise <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/what-is-machine-learning.html">machine learning</a> tools help teams make informed decisions swiftly by analyzing extensive datasets and providing strategic recommendations.</li>
    <li><strong>Enhanced forecasting:</strong> Enterprise generative AI tools equip businesses to better anticipate market demands and consumer behavior by using past data to predict future trends.</li>
    <li><strong>Scenario analysis:</strong> Advanced simulation models help businesses explore various strategic scenarios, enabling effective risk management and planning.</li>
  </ul>
  <h3 id="customer-experience">Customer experience</h3>
  <p>AI transforms how businesses interact with their customers by providing personalized and responsive services:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Personalization at scale:</strong> AI analyzes customer data to tailor marketing messages and product recommendations.</li>
    <li><strong>24x7 customer support:</strong> Chatbots provide instant responses to customer inquiries at any time, improving service availability and customer satisfaction.</li>
    <li><strong>Customer insights:</strong> By collecting and analyzing customer feedback and behavior, AI helps businesses understand and anticipate customer needs, leading to better service and product offerings.</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="enterprise-ai-challenges">Enterprise AI challenges</h2>
  <p>In addition to the benefits, there are some common challenges that businesses interested in becoming AI enterprises should plan for. These are primarily cultural resistance, ethical concerns, and technical barriers. Effective navigation of these issues is crucial for the long-term success of enterprise AI adoption.</p>
  <h3 id="cultural-and-organizational-hurdles">Cultural and organizational hurdles</h3>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Challenge:</strong> While some employees may be enthusiastic about adopting AI because they see it as a tool to enhance their work, others may see it as a threat to their jobs.</li>
    <li><strong>Best practices:</strong> Having transparent discussions about AI’s benefits and its role in the organization can help align employee perspectives with strategic goals. Be understanding and compassionate if employees express concerns. Offering training programs can also help employees gain confidence with new AI tools.</li>
  </ul>
  <h3 id="ethical-and-security-considerations">Ethical and security considerations</h3>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Challenge:</strong> AI introduces ethical and security considerations that require special guidelines and security protocols.</li>
    <li><strong>Best practices:</strong> Developing <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2023/03/7211ee96-647e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">responsible AI guidelines</a> helps ensure everyone in the organization uses AI safely and fairly. Also, implementing advanced security measures helps protect sensitive data.</li>
  </ul>
  <h3 id="integration-complexity">Integration complexity</h3>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Challenge:</strong> Successfully integrating AI into existing systems requires strategic planning and careful implementation.</li>
    <li><strong>Best practices:</strong> Beginning with pilot projects allows for gradual integration and helps identify and address potential challenges in a controlled environment.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18b6d38fc43df81b75bed84aac4d1c9eae7f7b0d7.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18b6d38fc43df81b75bed84aac4d1c9eae7f7b0d7.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_18b6d38fc43df81b75bed84aac4d1c9eae7f7b0d7.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Autonomous robot transportation in a warehouse." src="./media_18b6d38fc43df81b75bed84aac4d1c9eae7f7b0d7.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2190" height="1369">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="generative-ai-enterprise-ai-for-erp-and-crm">Generative AI: enterprise AI for ERP and CRM</h2>
  <p>One of the most exciting and broadly applicable types of enterprise AI is <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/ai-assistant.html">copilots for ERP</a> systems, which are powered by <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/what-is-generative-ai.html">generative AI</a>. AI copilots infuse companies’ existing ERP and CRM systems with natural language AI capabilities, which can dramatically enhance how employees operate and innovate by making processes more adaptive, intelligent, and optimized – usually without requiring major overhauling of existing systems.</p>
  <h3 id="innovative-applications-and-strategic-impact">Innovative applications and strategic impact</h3>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Improved user experience and productivity:</strong> Generative AI enables natural language interactions with ERP systems, streamlining processes and boosting productivity. For instance, large language models can simplify compliance by interpreting legal texts and identifying relevant criteria. This extends to CRM, where AI enhances sales and service interactions by automating responses and personalizing communication based on customer data insights.</li>
    <li><strong>Automation of manual tasks:</strong> In addition to chat applications, enterprise generative AI tools can be used to reduce manual labor in processes like supply chain logistics and customer data management. For example, AI can automate the digitization of delivery notes and customer interaction records, drastically cutting down costs and processing times.</li>
    <li><strong>Business process optimization:</strong> By analyzing data generated by business systems, enterprise generative AI tools identify patterns to optimize processes across ERPs and CRMs. They can generate ready-to-use process models and insights, and help businesses to implement best practices.</li>
    <li><strong>Analytics and decision-making:</strong> AI democratizes data-driven decision-making by making it easier for leaders and teams alike to work with complex analytics.</li>
  </ul>
  <h3 id="erp-and-crm-cloud-integration">ERP and CRM cloud integration</h3>
  <p>AI capabilities for ERP and CRM systems are typically cloud-based. Organizations that rely on on-premise or private cloud infrastructures may need to adopt a public cloud to implement AI solutions. Businesses wanting to keep IT on premise can create a hybrid cloud environment by adding a public cloud to their existing infrastructure. Hybrid clouds allow businesses to maintain control over critical data while benefiting from advanced AI, cybersecurity, and scalability solutions offered by cloud providers.</p>
  <h2 id="enterprise-ai-examples-across-industries">Enterprise AI examples across industries</h2>
  <p>Beyond general-purpose business solutions, enterprise AI also includes <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/industries.html">industry-specific solutions</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Automotive</strong></p>
  <p>Automotive companies are using AI to enhance quality control and develop technologies for safe autonomous driving.</p>
  <p><strong>Energy</strong></p>
  <p>By forecasting demand precisely and adjusting supply, AI helps amplify the integration and value of renewable energy sources.</p>
  <p><strong>Entertainment</strong></p>
  <p>Streaming services are using AI to personalize viewer recommendations, and game developers and platforms are creating more responsive, realistic environments.</p>
  <p><strong>Finance</strong></p>
  <p>Advanced fraud detection systems and robo-advisors, powered by AI, significantly improve efficiency and security in the financial sector.</p>
  <p><strong>Healthcare</strong></p>
  <p>AI has had a dramatic impact in healthcare, improving the accuracy of diagnostics, allowing care providers to personalize medicine, and enhancing treatment outcomes through cognitive analysis of clinical data.</p>
  <p><strong>Life sciences</strong></p>
  <p>Companies in drug discovery and genomic research have seen reduced costs and time to market thanks to AI, and clinicians are now able to tailor medical treatments to individual genetic profiles.</p>
  <p><strong>Manufacturing</strong></p>
  <p>Many manufacturers are using enterprise AI to boost production efficiency, minimize downtime with predictive maintenance, and improve sustainability.</p>
  <p><strong>Public sector</strong></p>
  <p>AI is allowing organizations to automate administrative processes, optimize urban management systems for traffic and emergency services, and increase civic engagement.</p>
  <p><strong>Software development</strong></p>
  <p><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/developer-tools.html">Enterprise generative AI tools</a> streamline coding and testing processes to accelerate development cycles, identify security vulnerabilities, and help developers learn new languages and frameworks faster.</p>
  <p><strong>Telecom</strong></p>
  <p>In the telecom industry, AI-powered predictive analytics enhance service delivery and network management, helping prevent outages and offering personalized customer experiences.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div data-valign="middle">
        <h2 id="meet-joule-your-ai-copilot"><strong>Meet Joule: your AI copilot</strong></h2>
        <p>Learn how to get work done faster and make every touchpoint count with Joule by your side.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/ai-assistant.html">Learn more</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="enterprise-ai-strategy-and-planning">Enterprise AI strategy and planning</h2>
  <p>Becoming an AI enterprise involves more than just selecting the right platform or product—it also involves smart planning and teamwork. Businesses get the most value from their AI investments when they set clear objectives, encourage cross-team collaboration, and commit to ongoing learning. Here are some key considerations when getting started:</p>
  <h3 id="in-house-vs-partner-led-implementation">In-house vs. partner-led implementation</h3>
  <p>An important early step is deciding whether to plan and implement an enterprise AI platform or solution using in-house resources or to hire an expert partner.</p>
  <p><strong>In-house implementation</strong></p>
  <p>Implementing enterprise AI solutions without the help of an external partner can be cost-effective if the organization has the necessary technical expertise, resources, and bandwidth. This also offers advantages like total control over project execution and confidentiality of sensitive information. However, in-house implementations may pose challenges for some organizations, including a steep learning curve and substantial investment of employees’ time.</p>
  <p><strong>Partner implementation</strong></p>
  <p>While initially costly, hiring an <a href="https://www.sap.com/partners/find.html">enterprise AI partner</a> provides businesses with specialized knowledge, resources, and experience. It allows organizations to confidently implement their solution knowing they’re following industry best practices. Working with a partner can also help mitigate skills gaps, and generally accelerates the process. Partner-led implementations require careful selection of vendors who align with the organization's objectives and culture.</p>
  <h3 id="assessment-and-goal-setting">Assessment and goal setting</h3>
  <p>It’s critical to assess existing capabilities and set clear goals:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Goal alignment:</strong> Define specific, measurable goals that the AI solution should meet. These goals should align with broader business objectives and have clear metrics for success. For instance, if reducing operational costs is a priority, set a target percentage reduction as a goal for AI initiatives.</li>
    <li><strong>Data audit:</strong> Perform a robust audit of data to evaluate quality, accessibility, and security. This assessment will be crucial to identify blockers and areas that need to be improved before the technical implementation begins.</li>
  </ul>
  <h3 id="resource-allocation">Resource allocation</h3>
  <p>Assessing budgetary and human capabilities are vital to success:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Budgeting:</strong> Allocate adequate financial resources not just for the acquisition of enterprise AI technology but also for ongoing expenses like software updates, cloud storage, and cybersecurity measures.</li>
    <li><strong>Talent acquisition:</strong> Hiring skilled personnel or training existing employees to handle new AI tools is imperative. The technological investment will only work as planned if the people using it have the right skills.</li>
  </ul>
  <h3 id="collaboration">Collaboration</h3>
  <p>Business AI projects are most successful when everyone benefiting from them participates:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Cross-functional teams:</strong> Form teams that include members from IT, data analytics, leadership, and end-users. This inclusive strategy helps ensure that all potential impacts and benefits are considered from the outset.</li>
    <li><strong>Regular reviews:</strong> Set up regular review sessions to evaluate the progress of AI integration against the project goals. These reviews can help realign efforts with business objectives and adapt to new challenges or opportunities.</li>
  </ul>
  <h3 id="adaptation-and-learning">Adaptation and learning</h3>
  <p>As enterprise AI continues evolves, businesses need to expect that their strategies and practices around using it need to evolve, too:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Continuous training:</strong> Develop ongoing training programs for employees to keep up with AI advancements helps staff stay informed and confident in their abilities.</li>
    <li><strong>Feedback mechanism:</strong> Establish mechanisms to collect feedback on AI implementations from all stakeholders. This feedback is invaluable for refining AI strategies and tools, helping to ensure they remain effective and aligned with user needs over time.</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="conclusion-how-enterprise-ai-is-redefining-business">Conclusion: How enterprise AI is redefining business</h2>
  <p>Enterprise AI – including well-established types like machine learning and newer types like copilots and generative AI – are transforming businesses by enhancing their productivity, decision-making, and innovation. The positive results experienced by early adopters of business AI indicate that AI tools for business are not just a passing trend, but a necessity for remaining competitive in the digital world.</p>
  <p>However, becoming a successful AI enterprise isn’t just about choosing the right enterprise AI platform. It’s also necessary to foster a workplace culture that thrives with AI. This involves training, data security investments, and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/what-is-responsible-AI.html">using AI responsibly</a>.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div data-valign="middle">
        <h2 id="explore-ai-for-enterprises">Explore AI for enterprises</h2>
        <p>See how to enhance and better connect your people, data, and processes.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence.html">Learn more</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
<div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div data-valign="middle">
        <h2 id="explore-ai-for-enterprises-1">Explore AI for enterprises</h2>
        <p>See how to enhance and better connect your people, data, and processes.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence.html">Learn more</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>sidebar</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
<div>
  <h2 id="share-this-article">Share this article</h2>
  <div class="social-sharing"></div>
  <h2 id="explore-related-content">Explore related content</h2>
  <div class="tags"></div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>content-type/what-is</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[What Is Conversational AI?]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/what-is-conversational-ai</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/what-is-conversational-ai</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn what conversational AI is, the different types – including conversational bots, common use cases, and how to choose a conversational AI platform.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>content-type/what-is</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[What is procurement? A comprehensive guide]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/l3-proxy-cards/what-is-procurement</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/topics/l3-proxy-cards/what-is-procurement</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Procurement is the process of sourcing and purchasing the goods, services, and raw materials a business requires to operate.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <h1 id="what-is-procurement-a-comprehensive-guide">What is procurement? A comprehensive guide</h1>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>content-type/what-is</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[What Is Responsible AI?]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/what-is-responsible-ai</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/what-is-responsible-ai</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Discover what responsible AI is and how its principles can be used to foster fairness and accountability – while preventing bias and inequality – in an era of rapidly evolving AI.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a60a0e08e86ab32c6b07a7dab7c7c02b109bb714.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a60a0e08e86ab32c6b07a7dab7c7c02b109bb714.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1a60a0e08e86ab32c6b07a7dab7c7c02b109bb714.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Employee reviewing multiple screens of ID data" src="./media_1a60a0e08e86ab32c6b07a7dab7c7c02b109bb714.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2309" height="1299">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="what-is-responsible-ai">What is responsible AI?</h1>
        <p>Responsible AI is the ethical development and use of artificial intelligence (AI), focusing on prioritizing fairness, transparency, and human control. Its goal is to prevent harm, avoid biases, and benefit society.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="responsible-ai-definition">Responsible AI definition</h2>
  <p>Responsible AI is the practice of using <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/what-is-artificial-intelligence.html">AI</a> in a way that emphasizes human oversight and societal well-being. It's about ensuring that AI models, datasets, and applications are developed and deployed ethically and legally, without causing harm or perpetuating biases. It’s important because misusing AI, or using it carelessly, can cause harm to users, society, and businesses.</p>
  <h2 id="what-is-responsible-ai-vs-trustworthy-ai-vs-ethical-ai">What is responsible AI vs. trustworthy AI vs. ethical AI?</h2>
  <p>The terms responsible AI, trustworthy AI, and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/ai-ethics.html">ethical AI</a> are closely related but there are some key differences:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Responsible AI</strong> encompasses the overall ethical implications, governance, oversight, legal, and long-term repercussions of AI.</li>
    <li><strong>Trustworthy AI</strong> refers specifically to the design of AI systems so that they’re reliable, fair, transparent, explainable, and secure.</li>
    <li><strong>Ethical AI</strong> focuses on the moral principles of how AI is designed and used so that it doesn’t harm humanity or human dignity.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>We must always keep in mind that because AI is not human, it’s incapable of having the human traits of responsibility, trustworthiness, or ethics. Therefore, it’s important to attribute these terms to the people who create or use this technology, and not to the technology itself.</p>
  <h2 id="how-responsible-ai-works">How responsible AI works</h2>
  <p>There are human and technology aspects to making responsible AI work:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>People</strong> must understand the benefits and risks of using AI – and commit to using it ethically. Individuals and people in organizations and governments all have a role to play.</li>
    <li><strong>AI technology</strong> must be developed, deployed, and governed in ways that prioritize human rights and well-being.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>Establishing formalized <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/ai-ethics.html?pdf-asset=940c6047-1c7d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff&#x26;page=2">responsible AI principles</a> is a good way to align everyone in an organization to a shared vision of responsible AI. But establishing principles is just a start: the organization must also implement effective AI governance, training, and technical processes to put the principles into action.</p>
  <p>Responsible AI principles vary between organizations. For example, financial services companies might place a higher emphasis on fairness and non-discrimination, while social media companies might focus more on transparency or privacy. Here’s an example of principles summarized from the <a href="https://digital-strategy.ec.europa.eu/en/library/ethics-guidelines-trustworthy-ai">European Commission’s ethics guidelines</a> for creating trustworthy AI systems:</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14d561d886624870db3ddad320b8245984c7d8dc7.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14d561d886624870db3ddad320b8245984c7d8dc7.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_14d561d886624870db3ddad320b8245984c7d8dc7.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="AI program learning from traffic data" src="./media_14d561d886624870db3ddad320b8245984c7d8dc7.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2309" height="1299">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="example-of-responsible-ai-principles">Example of responsible AI principles</h2>
  <p><strong>Human agency and oversight:</strong> AI should augment human decision-making, uphold human rights, and have mechanisms for human oversight.</p>
  <p><strong>Technical robustness and safety:</strong> AI systems should be secure, resilient, safe, accurate, and reliable with a contingency plan to prevent unintentional harm.</p>
  <p><strong>Privacy and data governance:</strong> Systems should fully respect privacy and regulate the quality, privacy, and legitimate access to data.</p>
  <p><strong>Transparency:</strong> Systems must be traceable and transparent. They should be clearly marked as AI and their capabilities and limitations should be communicated effectively.</p>
  <p><strong>Diversity, non-discrimination, and fairness:</strong> AI should avoid promoting bias, should support diversity, ensure equal accessibility, and involve stakeholders in the development process.</p>
  <p><strong>Societal and environmental well-being:</strong> AI systems should benefit all human beings, including future generations. They must be sustainable and environmentally friendly, and their societal impact should be carefully considered.</p>
  <p><strong>Accountability:</strong> Mechanisms should be put in place to ensure responsibility and accountability for AI systems and their outcomes. Auditability and accessibility should be ensured.</p>
  <h2 id="responsible-ai-development-practices">Responsible AI development practices</h2>
  <p>Developers and researchers who create or implement AI systems must follow <a href="https://news.sap.com/sea/2024/01/creating-the-next-generation-of-responsible-ai-developers/">trustworthy AI technical best practices</a> and continuously assess their systems’ adherence to their organizations responsible AI principles. Here are some common practices:</p>
  <h4 id="assessing-model-training-data">Assessing model training data</h4>
  <p>Having diverse datasets helps represent various cohorts, improving the robustness and inclusiveness of the AI system. Understanding the data that’s used to train models is necessary for uncovering or mitigating issues like AI bias.</p>
  <h4 id="causal-analysis">Causal analysis</h4>
  <p>Understanding how cause-and-effect relationships work in AI models can aid in ethical decision-making about how deploy them, or if they should even be deployed at all. This analysis makes predictive models more robust by revealing interactions among different variables.</p>
  <h4 id="counterfactuals-analysis">Counterfactuals analysis</h4>
  <p>This is the process of improving model fairness and decision-making by using "what-if" queries to reveal AI biases and logic problems. It works by asking the model how its decisions would change if the input, such as data about a person or situation, had been different.</p>
  <h4 id="fairness-in-machine-learning">Fairness in machine learning</h4>
  <p>Eliminating AI bias is critical to ensuring systems treat different groups or individuals equitably. This is done by identifying unbalanced representation or unfair treatment in <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/what-is-machine-learning.html">machine learning</a> training data and algorithms, and typically has three phases:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Pre-processing of data</strong> to identify and remove biases.</li>
    <li><strong>Applying fairness constraints</strong> during model testing.</li>
    <li><strong>Post-processing adjustments</strong> to the model’s decision-making.</li>
  </ul>
  <h4 id="model-error-assessment">Model error assessment</h4>
  <p>Evaluating and correcting errors in models’ predictions is critical for avoiding risky or embarrassing outcomes. Common methods for assessing errors include confusion matrix, precision, recall, F1 score, and ROC curve.</p>
  <h4 id="model-interpretability">Model interpretability</h4>
  <p>To promote trust and transparency with users and regulators, developers must be able to interpret and explain why their models make specific decisions and demonstrate certain behaviors. Some commonly used interpretability techniques:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Feature importance</strong> identifies and ranks the most influential variables or “features” used by the model to make predictions.</li>
    <li><strong>Partial dependence</strong> plots are graphs that visualize the relationship between a selected variable and a specific outcome, with all other variables being constant.</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="why-is-responsible-ai-important">Why is responsible AI important?</h2>
  <p>AI is having a profound impact on society, influencing how we work and interact. Responsible AI can be a catalyst for innovation by encouraging novel, human-first approaches to problem-solving and product development. However, irresponsible AI use poses significant risks, like exacerbating inequalities and generating harmful content.</p>
  <h4 id="ethical-imperatives-for-businesses-and-governments">Ethical imperatives for businesses and governments</h4>
  <p>All organizations and individuals must uphold high ethical standards in their AI usage. Beyond meeting legal requirements, businesses and governments must also prioritize data privacy, transparency, and fairness in their AI endeavors.</p>
  <h4 id="societal-expectations-for-ethical-technology-use">Societal expectations for ethical technology use</h4>
  <p>The demand for accountability and transparency from technology companies is growing as AI becomes more widely used. Society expects AI systems to be engineered to respect human rights, embrace diversity, and prioritize the public good.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a05864709735c3924b8228e4ff7a1fd9de295dad.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a05864709735c3924b8228e4ff7a1fd9de295dad.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1a05864709735c3924b8228e4ff7a1fd9de295dad.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Engineer working on robot" src="./media_1a05864709735c3924b8228e4ff7a1fd9de295dad.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2121" height="1414">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="responsible-ai-benefits">Responsible AI benefits</h2>
  <p>As organizations accelerate their AI adoption, it’s natural that some may see responsible AI as a speed bump – or as something to implement later on. But establishing guiding principles before starting major AI projects is critical to helping prevent technology mistakes, harm to people, and reputational damage.</p>
  <h4 id="competitive-advantage">Competitive advantage</h4>
  <p>Organizations can position themselves as leaders in <a href="https://www.accenture.com/us-en/insights/artificial-intelligence/ai-compliance-competitive-advantage">ethical innovation</a> and attract customers who prioritize ethical values in their purchasing decisions. In addition to the efficiency and innovation benefits of AI, responsible use allows businesses to implement AI with less risk than competitors who don’t.</p>
  <h4 id="cost-savings-and-efficiency">Cost savings and efficiency</h4>
  <p>Proactively addressing AI biases and ensuring the accuracy of model data can help prevent harm to people, expensive mistakes, and improve efficiency. Also, transparent and explainable AI models are usually more accurate than those that aren’t.</p>
  <h4 id="enhanced-brand-trust">Enhanced brand trust</h4>
  <p>Openly communicating how AI systems are designed, deployed, and governed demonstrates a commitment to ethical values and customer well-being. This can elevate brand perception, customer loyalty, and help build trust with customers and partners.</p>
  <h4 id="improved-decision-making">Improved decision-making</h4>
  <p>By identifying and mitigating biases in data and algorithms, organizations can be more confident that AI-driven insights and recommendations are accurate, equitable, and aligned with ethical standards. This benefit applies across various business functions, including product development, customer service, and strategic planning.</p>
  <h4 id="risk-mitigation">Risk mitigation</h4>
  <p>Cases of AI bias, data breaches, or unethical deployment can damage an organization’s reputation and lead to costly lawsuits. Adhering to responsible AI principles can help avoid these risks.</p>
  <h2 id="responsible-ai-challenges">Responsible AI challenges</h2>
  <p>It’s important to understand that creating a set of responsible AI principles is just the first step to establishing the necessary mindset and operational approach for creating and deploying AI responsibly. Here are some the challenges of responsible AI:</p>
  <h4 id="ai-bias-identification-and-mitigation">AI bias: Identification and mitigation</h4>
  <p>AI systems can reflect or amplify existing biases present in their training data, potentially leading to unfair outcomes in applications like job hiring or loan approvals. To mitigate these biases, organizations must make sure their datasets are diverse, conduct regular audits, and employ bias mitigation algorithms.</p>
  <h4 id="ai-governance-ensuring-ethical-compliance">AI governance: Ensuring ethical compliance</h4>
  <p>Without a robust AI governance framework in place, organizations can face privacy, security, and control issues. Establishing clear policies, embracing transparency, and engaging stakeholders are essential for maintaining compliance and accountability in AI systems.</p>
  <h4 id="regulatory-compliance-and-standardization">Regulatory compliance and standardization</h4>
  <p>The rapid evolution of AI has surpassed many regulatory frameworks, creating a gap that could lead to ethical violations. Adaptive legal frameworks and international cooperation are necessary to help ensure AI systems are built to comply with updated regulations and standards.</p>
  <h4 id="scalability-of-ethical-ai-practices">Scalability of ethical AI practices</h4>
  <p>Scaling ethical AI practices is challenging, especially for organizations lacking resources or expertise. Training AI professionals in ethics and using technology to automate ethical checks can help scale responsible practices effectively.</p>
  <h4 id="malicious-use-of-ai">Malicious use of AI</h4>
  <p>Spreading misinformation, unauthorized surveillance, and discriminatory profiling are matters of serious concern. Addressing these risks requires stringent regulatory measures, strict ethical guidelines, and continuous human oversight.</p>
  <h2 id="responsible-ai-use-cases">Responsible AI use cases</h2>
  <h4 id="healthcare-enhancing-diagnostic-accuracy">Healthcare: Enhancing diagnostic accuracy</h4>
  <p>AI can help clinicians to diagnose diseases more accurately from medical images. By ensuring model fairness and transparency, using AI can lead to more equitable health outcomes across diverse demographics.</p>
  <h4 id="finance-fair-lending-decisions">Finance: Fair lending decisions</h4>
  <p>By actively monitoring and adjusting credit scoring algorithms to eliminate AI biases, banks and lending institutions can provide more equitable access to financial products, reducing discrimination.</p>
  <h4 id="retail-personalized-customer-experiences">Retail: Personalized customer experiences</h4>
  <p><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/what-is-generative-ai.html">Generative AI</a> allows retailers to create highly personalized content and product recommendations. By being transparent about how they’re using this technology, retailers can build deeper trust with consumers, leading to increased loyalty and sales.</p>
  <h4 id="automotive-safer-vehicles">Automotive: Safer vehicles</h4>
  <p>Through rigorous testing and adherence to ethical AI standards, manufacturers aim to reduce accidents and improve road safety.</p>
  <h4 id="human-resources-bias-free-recruiting">Human resources: Bias-free recruiting</h4>
  <p>By applying algorithms that are regularly audited for fairness, HR departments can make more unbiased hiring decisions, promoting diversity and inclusion within the workplace.</p>
  <h2 id="types-of-responsible-ai">Types of responsible AI</h2>
  <p>In addition to ethical AI and trustworthy AI, there are several other types of responsible AI:</p>
  <p><strong>Explainable AI</strong> refers to AI systems designed to provide human-understandable explanations of their operations or decisions. This transparency helps build trust among users and stakeholders, ensuring that AI decisions can be audited and validated for fairness and accuracy.</p>
  <p><strong>Sustainable AI</strong> focuses on developing AI technologies in an environmentally friendly way. This includes optimizing energy usage of systems, using greener infrastructure, and considering the lifecycle impacts of AI deployments to minimize carbon footprints and environmental impact.</p>
  <p><strong>Regulatory-compliant AI</strong> aims to ensure that all AI operations and technology adhere to relevant laws and regulations. This type of responsible AI is crucial in highly regulated industries like finance and healthcare, where adhering to legal standards is as important as technical performance.</p>
  <p><strong>Human-centered AI</strong> prioritizes human values and welfare, involving stakeholders in the development process and focusing on technologies that augment human beings without replacing them.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-responsible-ai">Learn more about responsible AI</h3>
        <p>Deepen your understanding of responsible AI concepts, including transparency, human agency, and model bias with the SAP AI Ethics Handbook.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/ai-ethics.html">Get the handbook</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="faq">FAQ</h2>
  <div class="accordion">
    <div>
      <div data-valign="middle">What is AI governance?</div>
      <div data-valign="middle">AI governance is the framework that guides how AI technologies are researched, developed, implemented, and monitored to ensure they comply with ethical norms, laws, and regulations.</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div data-valign="middle">What is AI bias?</div>
      <div data-valign="middle">AI bias refers to systematic and unfair discrepancies that arise in the data or algorithmic processes of AI systems, often leading to prejudiced outcomes against certain groups or individuals.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
<div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-responsible-ai-1">Learn more about responsible AI</h3>
        <p>Deepen your understanding of responsible AI concepts, including transparency, human agency, and model bias with the SAP AI Ethics Handbook.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/ai-ethics.html">Get the handbook</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>sidebar</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
<div>
  <h2 id="share-this-article">Share this article</h2>
  <div class="social-sharing"></div>
  <h2 id="explore-related-content">Explore related content</h2>
  <div class="tags"></div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>core-topic/responsible-ai</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>content-type/what-is</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[What is Generative AI?]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/l3-proxy-cards/what-is-generative-ai</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/topics/l3-proxy-cards/what-is-generative-ai</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Generative AI is a form of artificial intelligence that can produce text, images, and varied content based on the data it is trained on.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>content-type/what-is</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Close the Labor Gap with Socially Conscious Hiring]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/close-the-labor-gap-with-socially-conscious-hiring</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/close-the-labor-gap-with-socially-conscious-hiring</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Turn random acts of social good into programs that benefit marginalized workers, their communities, and the business itself]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f04c09c36bcc5fddd8e1cb43a7c965a5d71b13a5.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f04c09c36bcc5fddd8e1cb43a7c965a5d71b13a5.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1f04c09c36bcc5fddd8e1cb43a7c965a5d71b13a5.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Diverse group of employees standing arm in arm in an office hallway" src="./media_1f04c09c36bcc5fddd8e1cb43a7c965a5d71b13a5.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1044">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="close-the-labor-gap-with-socially-conscious-hiring">Close the Labor Gap with Socially Conscious Hiring</h1>
        <p>Turn random acts of social good into programs that benefit marginalized workers, their communities, and the business itself.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Throughout the world, countries are struggling with an acute labor shortage that shows no sign of abating. In the United States, a smaller workforce will be the key economic challenge of the foreseeable future, according to the <a href="https://www.uschamber.com/economy/what-to-expect-from-the-economy-in-2024#:~:text=Curtis%20Dubay&#x26;text=A%20smaller%20workforce%20will%20define,that%20can%20support%20their%20spending.">U.S. Chamber of Commerce</a>. The numbers are daunting: Even if every unemployed worker today were to fill an open job in their respective industry, the organization says, there would still be millions of unfilled positions.</p>
  <p>But what if businesses redefined the labor pool itself? Doing so would mean looking beyond the ranks of the statistically employed and unemployed. Instead, businesses would tap into a less obvious but large group of people who are not participating in the formally recognized labor market. Many of these people would like to work but have been marginalized from the workforce for a variety of systemic or discriminatory reasons.</p>
  <p>This includes people from less-advantaged populations; individuals with a criminal record; people with physical, mental health, or developmental challenges; those with a history of substance abuse; and people with low educational attainment or without traditional qualifications.</p>
  <p>A study by <a href="https://www.hbs.edu/managing-the-future-of-work/Documents/research/hiddenworkers09032021.pdf">Harvard Business School</a> (HBS) estimates there are more than 27 million of these “hidden workers” in the United States, and similar proportions across the UK and Germany. “The sheer magnitude of this population reveals the potential impact that their substantial re-absorption into the workforce would have,” the study says.</p>
  <p>Many businesses have reached out to engage these populations through their corporate social responsibility (CSR) efforts. Such measures might include changing degree/educational attainment requirements for a small segment of jobs. Or businesses might hire two or three people with a physical or mental disability, or a criminal record, or who belong to an underrepresented population in the local community.</p>
  <p>But often, these are ad hoc measures that, while admirable, tend to fizzle out. Even if they do have some success, they may fail to grow or expand. As the HBR study points out, such isolated CSR efforts can “inherently reinforce the myth that hiring hidden workers is an act of charity or corporate citizenship, rather than a source of competitive advantage.”</p>
  <p>By taking a more purposeful approach with their hiring programs and other CSR-driven initiatives, organizations can transform random acts of corporate social responsibility into long-lasting, far-reaching, repeatable programs. These programs would benefit marginalized workers, the communities they live in, and the business itself.</p>
  <p>Such initiatives would need to address the needs of both the community and the business. They should involve agencies that deeply understand the specific needs of the demographic being hired. Additionally, they should provide wraparound services that go beyond the job. Vitally, these programs need to use data and technology to identify community needs, track the effects of initiatives and encourage uptake in other parts of the business. In other words, it’s not just about <em>doing</em> – it’s about doing with purpose and a goal in mind.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="managing-social-impact--the-s-in-esg">Managing social impact – the S in ESG</h3>
        <p>A complete guide to measuring and managing social impact.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="/resources/measuring-social-impact-s-in-esg">Dive in</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“There is a need, says Eric Eng, a college admission expert and the founder and CEO of <a href="https://admissionsight.com/">AdmissionSight</a>, “for companies to shift from piecemeal initiatives to systemic and strategic approaches that can truly impact underserved communities and build a stronger labor market.”</p>
  <p>By taking a more purposeful approach with their hiring programs and other CSR-driven initiatives, organizations can transform random acts of corporate social responsibility into long-lasting, far-reaching, repeatable programs. These programs would benefit marginalized workers, the communities they live in, and the business itself.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e2a750a701d40250060dbc25b71ca98b07f07ad9.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e2a750a701d40250060dbc25b71ca98b07f07ad9.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1e2a750a701d40250060dbc25b71ca98b07f07ad9.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="A diverse group of smiling businesspeople talking together during a meeting in an office boardroom" src="./media_1e2a750a701d40250060dbc25b71ca98b07f07ad9.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="from-isolated-acts-to-full-fledged-efforts">From isolated acts to full-fledged efforts</h2>
  <p>There are as many wrong ways to pursue a CSR hiring initiative as there are right ways. Often, these efforts are started by a passionate employee whose enthusiasm is a key part of what drives the program. But with that dependency, the program is apt to languish should the employee leave or lose interest.</p>
  <p>Initiatives also fail if their benefits – whether to the business or the community – go unrecognized. This can be due to a lack of rigor in measuring results or a failure to adequately match program elements to community or demographic needs.</p>
  <p>For instance, a study by workforce researcher <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/starbucks-founder-howard-schultz-you-can-do-right-by-your-people-and-your-shareholders-at-the-same-time/ar-AA1kY8vg">The Burning Glass Institute</a> found that simply dropping degree requirements doesn’t significantly affect the hiring of people from diverse groups. The act of applying for a job, the organization says, is contingent not just on whether the individual has the required education credentials but also on whether they could imagine themselves working for a particular company or in a specific sector. This finding reinforces the importance of – beyond removing candidate qualifications – actively encouraging applicants who may never have considered themselves as potential employees.</p>
  <p>A company that has fully embraced socially conscious hiring is MOD Pizza, a fast-casual pizza brand founded by a husband-and-wife team (former owners of Seattle Coffee Company, later acquired by Starbucks). <a href="https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Why-MOD-Pizza-Loves-Hiring-Ex-Cons-13205951.php">Their vision</a>: building a business with a positive social impact.</p>
  <p>Soon after opening, MOD Pizza embraced what’s known as impact hiring, including people with backgrounds of incarceration, homelessness, drug addiction, and intellectual and physical disabilities. It worked with local and national organizations to learn what these individuals needed to thrive on the job, from skill-building to financial assistance during a crisis. It then partnered with various nonprofits to encourage candidates to apply.</p>
  <p>Today, MOD Pizza credits its rapid growth largely to its hiring method. The business today has more than 2,500 employees, <a href="https://www.scrapehero.com/location-reports/Modpizza-USA/">over 550 locations</a> in the United States and Canada, and <a href="https://www.zippia.com/mod-pizza-careers-31728/revenue/">revenues of US$398 million</a>. Ninety-nine percent of company-owned MOD stores have hired people with employment barriers, <a href="https://news.sap.com/2023/09/mod-pizza-driving-positive-outcomes-investing-in-employees/#:~:text=Today%2C%2099%25%20of%20company%2D,retention%20rate%2C%E2%80%9D%20Eberhardt%20says.">according to Dayna Eberhardt</a>, chief people officer at the company, and these hiring practices have led to a more engaged and equitable workforce. These workers “have a higher sense of belonging, a faster rate of promotion, and a higher retention rate,” she says.</p>
  <h2 id="building-a-socially-conscious-hiring-program">Building a socially conscious hiring program</h2>
  <p>MOD Pizza offers several best practices for creating a socially conscious hiring method that benefits both marginalized workers and the business. Some of these core elements include the following:</p>
  <h3 id="match-efforts-to-the-needs-of-the-local-community">1. Match efforts to the needs of the local community</h3>
  <p>Businesses need to understand the specific barriers preventing people in the community from attaining stable employment. They can get these insights by mapping the company’s locations with external data sources that reveal challenges affecting nearby neighborhoods, such as a lack of public transportation, low graduation rates, poor access to healthcare, or limited housing affordability.</p>
  <p>Similarly, businesses can map the geographic location of where employees and job candidates tend to live to identify “applicant deserts” – areas in the community where the company has not historically hired, despite their proximity to their operations. Knowing this, businesses can increase their outreach and visibility in these areas.</p>
  <p>Romanita Matta-Barrera, Chief Workforce Officer for <a href="https://greatersatx.com/">greater:SATX</a>, an economic development partnership in San Antonio, Texas, is leading efforts to address the gap between available jobs and community members who could fill them – 56% of whom are Hispanic.</p>
  <p>“There are jobs available, and often employers wonder where the people are and, at the same time, we see a lot of individuals who have been systematically looking for jobs and have not had access,” she says. “So, we’ve taken a very serious, deep dive into how we can address this to meet not only the needs of our growing employers but to also ensure that our community and its members are being maximized.”</p>
  <p>The organization has worked with Accenture Federal Services, which has embarked on a program to recruit individuals with little to no IT experience from an area of the city with a high level of poverty and a low level of educational attainment. Accenture partnered with several workforce agency partners to identify potential employees and provide them with basic skills training. They also offered wraparound services to address issues like transportation and childcare.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_168db644370231078a951e04cc321e367c1167f1c.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_168db644370231078a951e04cc321e367c1167f1c.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_168db644370231078a951e04cc321e367c1167f1c.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Group of people at a bus stop" src="./media_168db644370231078a951e04cc321e367c1167f1c.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div data-valign="middle">Often employers wonder where the people are and, at the same time, we see a lot of individuals who have been systematically looking for jobs and have not had access.</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div data-valign="middle">Romanita Matta-Barrera, Chief Workforce Officer, greater:SATX</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Training is run similarly to an apprenticeship program, with candidates given three to six months of skill-building, which often leads to full employment, she says. Accenture also targeted a summer high school internship program in the same region to engage the youth population.</p>
  <p>As AdmissionSight’s Eng notes, “addressing systemic poverty and adverse childhood experiences requires a multifaceted approach.” It’s a way of thinking, he says, that “involves creating pathways to quality education and vocational training, ensuring that these are accessible to all individuals.”</p>
  <h3 id="match-efforts-to-business-needs">2. Match efforts to business needs</h3>
  <p>The actions companies take to address community barriers should ideally reflect what the company produces, the services it provides, and what employees are passionate about. This ensures not only that CSR initiatives are meaningful to the community but that they also resonate with the company’s core mission and values.</p>
  <p>Enter MOD Pizza, whose industry faces particularly acute hiring challenges. According to the <a href="https://www.restaurantdive.com/news/national-restaurant-association-job-growth-not-recession-likely-in-2023/643664/">National Restaurant Association</a>, 79% of restaurant operators report difficulty hiring, and 62% are understaffed. This is amid a monthly labor turnover in the hospitality and food service sector at 5.4%, which is twice the national average.</p>
  <p>Meanwhile, <a href="https://aspe.hhs.gov/topics/human-services/incarceration-reentry-0">more than 600,000 individuals</a> are released from prison each year in the United States, and <a href="https://www.prisonpolicy.org/blog/2022/02/08/employment/">60% of those with federal convictions are jobless</a>. Yet <a href="https://www.fair360.com/medialib/uploads/2016/09/Paulk-Presentation-Hiring-Ex-Offenders-09142016.pdf">multiple case studies</a> have shown this population of workers to exhibit high employee loyalty. MOD Pizza’s matchup of business and community needs is a win for both employer and employee.</p>
  <p>In San Antonio, meanwhile, Ernst &#x26; Young (EY) has become more innovative in its hiring process by tapping into the local pool of two-year college students. This matches EY’s specific business needs because – as Matta-Barrera points out – even if applicants had a four-year college degree, they would have to be retrained for EY’s system anyway. As part of the process, EY revamped its onboarding process and engaged its employee resource groups to ensure these new hires were not overwhelmed by entering a corporate environment.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_194e89449df2729abb70702953fc9701b20dcc70f.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_194e89449df2729abb70702953fc9701b20dcc70f.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_194e89449df2729abb70702953fc9701b20dcc70f.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="A businessperson is making a presentation for his colleagues, using a digital tablet and pointing to the board." src="./media_194e89449df2729abb70702953fc9701b20dcc70f.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p>The actions companies take to address community barriers should ideally reflect what the company produces, the services it provides, and what employees are passionate about.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="benefits-of-having-neurodiverse-workers">Benefits of having neurodiverse workers</h3>
        <p>Unlock the potential of neurodiverse workers with the right hiring approach.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="/resources/the-win-win-potential-of-hiring-neurodiverse-workers">Learn more</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="go-beyond-the-job-to-provide-wraparound-services">3. Go beyond the job to provide wraparound services</h3>
  <p>Businesses soon discover that socially conscious hiring extends far beyond offering a job. It also means providing additional supports that are specific to the demographic. For instance, one manufacturer that wanted to increase local hiring learned that many potential applicants did not have reliable transportation to the jobsite. The company worked with employees to become qualified ride-share drivers and provided them with a company car to give these new hires a ride to work.</p>
  <p>In another case, when an automotive supplier began hiring people who were homeless to work at the company, it realized it needed to provide these workers with new shoes.</p>
  <p>Jeffrey Korzenik, economist and author of <em>Untapped Talent: How Second Chance Hiring Works for Your Business and the Community,</em> emphasizes the need for combining quality candidates with cost-effective support systems. <a href="https://hbr.org/2022/10/how-employers-can-set-formerly-incarcerated-workers-up-for-success">In a recent article</a>, he says the most advanced practitioners of what he calls the “second-chance model” of hiring provide social workers, “navigators,” psychologists, or life coaches to these employees. For example, he says, U.S. Rubber Recycling employs a psychiatric rehabilitation counselor, and Nehemiah Manufacturing uses social workers instead of HR professionals.</p>
  <p>One manufacturer that wanted to increase local hiring learned that many potential applicants did not have reliable transportation to the jobsite. The company worked with employees to become qualified ride-share drivers and provided them with a company car to give these new hires a ride to work.</p>
  <p>Businesses should work with local agencies, nonprofits, and community organizations that are already supporting the hiring demographic. These organizations understand these individuals’ most pressing issues and the most effective interventions. As the HBR report says, groups like these have credibility with the workers and understand their needs. “Partnering with such groups helps companies develop, launch, and refine a program to make hidden workers integral to their talent management programs,” the report says.</p>
  <p>When Toyotetsu Texas, a supplier to Toyota Motor Manufacturing Texas’s San Antonio plant, began hiring individuals with intellectual and physical disabilities, it partnered with the Texas Workforce Commission’s Vocational Rehabilitation Services agency, which provides wraparound services to these individuals. The company also created internal job coaches and mentors, and provided plant tours and hands-on experiences to help potential employees determine whether the environment would be a good fit for them.</p>
  <p>“These are individuals who have the competencies to work well in this type of environment with the right internal processes such as mentorship coaching and other accommodations,” Matta-Barrera says.</p>
  <h3 id="measure-success-and-scale">4. Measure success and scale</h3>
  <p>Lastly – but also essentially – businesses need to understand the effect their programs are having in order to sustain and grow these efforts. Too often, the program becomes a line item with a cost assigned to it and no measure of the value it’s providing.</p>
  <p>Businesses should collect data such as the number of individuals hired through these programs, their retention rates, and their progression within the company, and pull it together into a dashboard for quick and easy access.</p>
  <p>Data collection is something MOD Pizza has been intentional about doing. For all of 2022 and into early 2023, employees with justice involvement were promoted at a rate 1.2% greater than the company baseline, <a href="https://flaggerforce.com/blog/industry-interview-with-mod-pizza/">says Robin Hamm, MOD Pizza’s vice president of social impact.</a> Some of these employees hold leadership positions in the company’s stores and support centers. Some also serve as general managers, district managers, and regional directors. And in an industry with staggering attrition rates, these employees were also retained at a rate 6% greater than the company baseline.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d724f8eb4b3bedea8080c9b894ac7dbd1d7c01e0.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d724f8eb4b3bedea8080c9b894ac7dbd1d7c01e0.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1d724f8eb4b3bedea8080c9b894ac7dbd1d7c01e0.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Three coworkers reviewing data on a laptop in an office." src="./media_1d724f8eb4b3bedea8080c9b894ac7dbd1d7c01e0.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1493" height="1120">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p>Dashboards can also help businesses share the details of successful CSR programs across different locations within the company so they can be replicated without reinventing the wheel – or making costly mistakes. For instance, if one business unit has established a program to donate used laptops to underserved students, other divisions could see what makes this program work well and set up similar programs in their communities.</p>
  <p>Businesses should collect data like the number of individuals hired through these programs, their retention rates, and their progression within the company, and pull it together into a dashboard for quick and easy access.</p>
  <p>These dashboards could work as a sort of recommendation engine if they’re populated with pre-vetted agencies and organizations to work with, or actions proven to support communities, based on the barriers to employment they help overcome, including transportation and mentorship programs, charitable giving, and educational and employment opportunity programs.</p>
  <p>Beyond the business itself, organizations should also measure how their efforts are affecting the community overall. Even if it’s not a direct result, are rates of homelessness, graduation rates, Internet access, or poverty levels rising or falling?</p>
  <p>For instance, <a href="https://stories.starbucks.com/uploads/2023/05/2022-Starbucks-Global-Environmental-Social-Impact-Report.pdf">the Burning Glass Institute</a> conducted a project with Starbucks examining the effect of the company’s tuition assistance program on employees’ career trajectories after they left the company. What they learned: These employees often went on to increasingly successful careers that – over time – would strengthen the overall community by fueling economic growth and improving the standard of living for their own families.</p>
  <h2 id="a-new-way-of-hiring">A new way of hiring</h2>
  <p>When it comes to the labor shortage, the problem is not that there aren’t enough people – it’s that employers are not using the potential of the whole community. This is forcing organizations to rethink how they design their hiring programs so they can be more employable to more people.</p>
  <p>Going even further, they need to discover how they can help people coming from these communities who face challenges many employers cannot even imagine.</p>
  <p>By investing in efforts to aid marginalized workers, businesses can make use of formerly untapped labor resources, and by doing so, support their own growth, boost economic development in the community and, ultimately, elevate their brand reputation in the eyes of consumers, employees, and investors.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/what-is</category>
            <category>stage/acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Support Employee Caregivers to Boost Engagement, Loyalty]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/support-employee-caregivers-to-boost-engagement-loyalty</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/support-employee-caregivers-to-boost-engagement-loyalty</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[More than 70% of workers provide care to someone – burnout is just one result. Leading companies show how to help.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/what-is</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Widening Your Sustainability Scope]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/widening-sustainability-scope-2-scope-3</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/widening-sustainability-scope-2-scope-3</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Businesses are measuring Scope 2 and 3 effects of their operations beyond their corporate walls. That requires strong supply chain data.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>core-topic/environmental-compliance</category>
            <category>industry/automotive</category>
            <category>content-type/what-is</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Agile 101: Terms and Concepts for Business Leaders]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/agile-101-terms-and-concepts-for-business-leaders</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/agile-101-terms-and-concepts-for-business-leaders</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Can other corporate functions adopt the software world’s Agile methodology? We explore what works best and where.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/what-is</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Upskilling Your Workforce for the AI Era]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/upskilling-your-workforce-for-the-ai-era</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/upskilling-your-workforce-for-the-ai-era</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Get advice on how companies and employees can incorporate AI into existing work and seizing opportunities to elevate skills.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>content-type/what-is</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Four-Day Workweek Paradox]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/the-four-day-workweek-paradox</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/the-four-day-workweek-paradox</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Shorten the week, and productivity may go up instead of down. But getting those results takes careful program design.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15b07fc0e7bd5a3b3f19d042af067ca38930006d9.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15b07fc0e7bd5a3b3f19d042af067ca38930006d9.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_15b07fc0e7bd5a3b3f19d042af067ca38930006d9.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="portrait Of Businesswoman In Office Standing By Window" src="./media_15b07fc0e7bd5a3b3f19d042af067ca38930006d9.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1044">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="the-four-day-workweek-paradox">The Four-Day Workweek Paradox</h1>
        <p>Shorten the week, and productivity may go up instead of down. But getting those results takes careful program design.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>By Caitlynn Sendra and Lin Grensing-Pophal</p>
  <p>In the summer of 2019, <a href="https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2019/nov/04/microsoft-japan-four-day-work-week-productivity">Microsoft Japan</a> implemented a pilot project – the Work-Life Choice Challenge – providing its 2,300 employees with the opportunity to work a four-day workweek with Fridays off. The specific changes to the work schedule included giving employees paid leave on Fridays, encouraging shorter meetings (30 minutes or less), and promoting remote communication instead of face-to-face meetings. The pilot project lasted the entire month of August. Despite a reduction in workdays, the company reported a 40% boost in productivity. They were also able to conserve resources, like electricity consumption, which dropped by 23%. Based on the results of the pilot, Microsoft Japan has continued to offer a four-day week.</p>
  <p>That, of course, was before the pandemic knocked over work models, norms, preconceived notions, and expectations. Since then, interest in the idea of a shorter workweek has only gained momentum.</p>
  <p>A <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/03/02/is-a-four-day-work-week-catching-on-in-asia-it-depends-on-the-country.html">global study by nonprofit 4 Day Week Global</a> and researchers from Boston College, University College Dublin, and Cambridge University, has shown that most of the 33 companies and 903 employees who took part in the four-day workweek trials are unlikely to return to a standard five-day workweek. The majority of the firms were in the United States and Ireland, although trials have also taken place in the UK, Japan, Iceland, Spain, and New Zealand. Microsoft Japan claimed productivity rose by just under 40% during their four-day workweek pilot, while a trial in Iceland between 2015 and 2019 saw 2,500 workers participate with well-being increasing in areas such as stress, burnout, health, and work-life balance.</p>
  <p>It may not work for every type of job or industry. On the other hand, some countries – well, <a href="https://www.brusselstimes.com/325240/four-day-working-week-comes-into-effect-who-can-use-it-and-how-to-apply">Belgium</a> and Iceland, so far – may require that most types of companies offer employees the option. Regardless, given today’s burgeoning demand for workers with specialized skills, it pays to explore the potential of a four-day week to attract and keep talent.</p>
  <p>There are several options for structuring this work model to meet your organizational and employee needs. The primary concern organizational leaders express is productivity – ensuring that employees can, and will, accomplish the same (or more), whether they’re working the same hours in fewer days, or fewer hours overall. Some companies also fret over responsiveness to customers, although this often can be addressed with overlapping work schedules. However, there is a wide range of variables to consider and a lot of complexity in implementation.</p>
  <p>Since it’s not a decision to take lightly, this article walks through evidence of the potential benefits and downsides, different ways to structure work requirements and insights into how to increase your chances of success. These range from the seemingly obvious (train your managers!) to some easier to overlook (such as actively encouraging paid time off).</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_184537c8c3ecd543c84d5ccbb7e268d1b04229f8c.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_184537c8c3ecd543c84d5ccbb7e268d1b04229f8c.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_184537c8c3ecd543c84d5ccbb7e268d1b04229f8c.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Two executives having a business conversation sitting in a coffee shop" src="./media_184537c8c3ecd543c84d5ccbb7e268d1b04229f8c.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="240" height="160">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="why-consider-a-four-day-workweek">Why consider a four-day workweek?</h2>
  <p>It’s interesting to note and may come as a surprise, but the five-day workweek really hasn’t been around that long. It was promoted in the 1920s by <a href="https://firmspace.com/theproworker/from-strikes-to-labor-laws-how-the-us-adopted-the-5-day-workweek#:~:text=The%20five%2Dday%2C%2040%2D,no%20changes%20in%20employee%20compensation.">Henry Ford</a>, who felt that giving people more free time – not having them work every day – would help spur the economy. In 1930, <a href="https://www.adeccogroup.com/future-of-work/latest-insights/the-advantages-and-disadvantages-of-the-four-day-work-week/">economist John Maynard</a> Keynes predicted that by 2030 people might only work 15 hours per week. That prediction appears quite off track so far, but the idea of working fewer hours while accomplishing the same (or even better) outcomes has lingered.</p>
  <p>In fact, there are many who believe that “work will expand to fill the time allotted for its completion”– a phenomenon referred to as <a href="https://asana.com/resources/parkinsons-law">Parkinson’s Law</a>. In this view, even in models with fewer total hours worked, employees may accomplish just as much as before, and be happier doing it.</p>
  <p>It’s not a crazy notion. Both research and practical experience with four-day workweek models point to real benefits for organizations, says Lili Tenney, director of outreach and programs at the <a href="https://coloradosph.cuanschutz.edu/research-and-practice/centers-programs/chwe">Center for Health, Work &#x26; Environment at the Colorado School of Public Health</a>, and a renowned expert in workplace productivity. These include employee satisfaction, heightened productivity, and cost savings. Let’s dig into them.</p>
  <h2 id="increased-employee-satisfaction-and-well-being">Increased employee satisfaction and well-being</h2>
  <p>Tenney emphasizes that a four-day workweek can enhance employee satisfaction and overall well-being. Employees may experience reduced stress levels, increased motivation, and a stronger sense of work-life balance. This leads to higher job satisfaction, improved mental health, and decreased burnout rates. Consequently, organizations witness higher employee retention rates and attract top talent.</p>
  <p>A <a href="https://static1.squarespace.com/static/60b956cbe7bf6f2efd86b04e/t/63f3df56276b3e6d7870207e/1676926845047/UK-4-Day-Week-Pilot-Results-Report-2023.pdf">study in the UK</a> found that people who worked the equivalent of four days instead of five “experienced decreased absenteeism (65%) and reduced employee turnover (57%), while employees benefited from improved well-being, including reduced stress (39%) and levels of burnout (71%). These companies also maintained or even increased revenue (by 1.4%), despite the significant reduction in work hours.”</p>
  <h2 id="heightened-productivity">Heightened productivity</h2>
  <p>Contrary to concerns about productivity loss, Tenney highlights the research findings that a condensed workweek can actually <em>boost</em> productivity. Employees can become more focused, driven, and efficient, utilizing their limited time wisely. The compressed schedule encourages individuals to prioritize tasks, eliminate time-wasting activities, and seek innovative solutions to streamline workflows. In addition, the increased downtime allows employees to recharge, resulting in improved concentration and creativity.</p>
  <h2 id="improved-work-life-balance">Improved work-life balance</h2>
  <p>An obvious corollary to a four-day workweek is the extra day off, often creating three-day weekends. This gives employees more time for personal pursuits, family commitments, travel, or leisure activities. This enhanced balance positively affects their mental and physical well-being, fostering higher levels of engagement and satisfaction when they return to work. Employers who prioritize work-life balance experience reduced absenteeism and increased employee loyalty.</p>
  <p>This is especially important for working parents, says Kati Lechner, director of people operations and talent strategies at <a href="https://wonderlic.com/">Wonderlic</a>, a company known for its success with flexible work arrangements. “It eliminates the need for an extra day of childcare when kids aren’t in school,” she notes. In addition, she says, the combination of flexible policies and the four-day workweek “supports employees’ unique needs in the workplace by allowing for better work-life integration for everyone, supporting our commitment to diversity and inclusion.”</p>
  <h2 id="potential-cost-savings">Potential cost savings</h2>
  <p>Tenney notes that there also are potential cost savings associated with a shorter workweek. These include reduced energy consumption, lower utility bills, decreased office supply expenses, and fewer employee-related costs, such as transportation and meals. In addition, the reduced turnover and improved employee satisfaction lead to savings in recruitment and training.</p>
  <p>Research tells us that employees are coming to demand the type of flexibility a four-day workweek can provide. <a href="https://www.mercer.com/en-ca/insights/talent-and-transformation/attracting-and-retaining-talent/four-day-workweek-the-cure-for-burnout/#:~:text=A%20stat%20that%20speaks%20volumes,employers%20to%20tackle%20wage%20inflation.">Mercer research</a>, for instance, indicates that “one in three employees would give up a pay increase this year in return for a fully flexible or compressed workweek. With cost-of-living concerns and an uncertain economic outlook, offering time off could be one way for employers to tackle wage inflation.” Mercer’s 2022–2023 Global Talent Trends Study collected insights from 11,000 executives, HR leaders, and workers across 16 countries in 2022 and 2023.</p>
  <p>While there are certainly still companies that are resistant to a move to a shorter workweek or other flexible scheduling options, they may ultimately be forced to move in this direction, says Lechner. “Flexibility in work arrangements is becoming increasingly important for attracting and retaining talent,” she says. In fact, Wonderlic has received as many as 6,000 applicants for a single job posting, indicating, Lechner believes, the high demand for the type of flexibility the company provides.</p>
  <p>In addition, the United States and other countries are introducing regulations and requirements for organizations to at least consider the four-day workweek option. <a href="https://stateline.org/2023/03/28/a-4-day-workweek-gains-lawmaker-support-in-some-states/">According to <em>Stateline</em></a>, "In the past three years, at least six states – California, Hawaii, Maryland, New York, Pennsylvania, and Washington – have considered bills to mandate, incentivize, or allow the switch to a four-day week.”</p>
  <p>Short weeks aren’t a one-size-fits-all proposition. Organizations can consider a number of approaches in the search forthe right workweek structure for their needs.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1484049ebf7598757dfa2209b8921cc47cef6acc3.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1484049ebf7598757dfa2209b8921cc47cef6acc3.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1484049ebf7598757dfa2209b8921cc47cef6acc3.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="man playing with his little daughter in nature" src="./media_1484049ebf7598757dfa2209b8921cc47cef6acc3.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="employee-experience-management">Employee Experience Management</h3>
        <p>Bridge the employee experience gaps by listening to your people's needs.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/employee-experience-management.html">Learn more</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="different-ways-to-structure-work">Different ways to structure work</h2>
  <p>If a five-day week seems onerous, consider the “996” working hour system common in parts of Asia until quite recently: employees worked from 9 a.m. to 9 p.m., six days a week.</p>
  <p>The Chinese Supreme Court <a href="https://www.npr.org/2021/08/30/1032458104/12-hour-6-day-996-work-schedule-illegal-china-deaths-tech-industry">deemed this practice illegal</a> in 2021. And overall, long workweeks are becoming less common around the globe.</p>
  <p>Even in Asia, CNBC notes, some countries – Singapore, Vietnam, Thailand, the Philippines, and Indonesia – are open to a four-day week. And in Europe, the concept is quite popular. Iceland, in fact, led a large four-day workweek pilot between 2015 and 2019, with very positive results. “As of 2022, workers represented by unions in Iceland – close to 90% of the workforce – have won the right to request a shorter workweek,” <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/04/14/countries-that-are-embracing-or-experimenting-with-a-4-day-workweek.html#:~:text=Iceland,work%2Dlife%20balance%20and%20productivity.">CNBC reports</a>. Iceland isn’t the only country where unions are leading the switch – the UK, Portugal, Spain, and others are <a href="https://www.euronews.com/next/2023/06/21/the-four-day-week-which-countries-have-embraced-it-and-how-s-it-going-so-far">also moving in this direction</a>, or testing through pilots. The United States lags well behind in corporate enthusiasm.</p>
  <p>So how much do employees actually work during these four-day weeks? Programs can take on a number of different variations depending on the organization and its needs. Common forms include:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong><a href="https://www.zavvy.io/blog/how-to-implement-a-4-day-workweek">Condensed workweek</a></strong>: Employees work the same number of hours but across four days instead of five.</li>
    <li><strong><a href="https://www.4dayweek.com/us-ireland-results">Reduced workweeks</a></strong>: Employees work 32 instead of 40 hours a week, with no reduction in pay, and typically the same productivity expectations.</li>
    <li><strong>Reduced output:</strong> Employees have the option to work fewer days and hours — with a corresponding cut in productivity and pay.</li>
    <li><strong><a href="https://www.hcamag.com/us/specialization/benefits/what-are-the-most-popular-ways-to-structure-4-day-workweeks/451948">Staggered schedules</a></strong>: Employees work in one of the structures above, but with different four-day schedules to allow for continuous coverage of key business operations.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>There are many tradeoffs to consider. For example, staggered schedules might mean the office remains open on all weekdays, yielding less energy savings. This might not be the driving factor for choosing one model over another, but it could be important in getting a full, accurate picture of the results.</p>
  <p>Each company will need to determine what works best for them, given their legal requirements, industry, structure, employee, and customer needs. The way this looks in most settings is that the workweek is shortened to 32 hours instead of the traditional 40, while each employee’s workload remains the same. The idea is that without typical workplace distractions and fewer personal stressors (commute times, fewer opportunities for work-life balance, etc.) productivity gains will help to cover those eight hours.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11887c56a7fdeaded8019ce34d547849a192208ea.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11887c56a7fdeaded8019ce34d547849a192208ea.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_11887c56a7fdeaded8019ce34d547849a192208ea.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Four woman sitting around a conference table" src="./media_11887c56a7fdeaded8019ce34d547849a192208ea.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="245" height="160">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="making-it-happen">Making it happen</h2>
  <p>One of the greatest barriers to moving to a four-day workweek is internal resistance. Organizational leaders, and managers in particular, can be resistant to flexibility of work hours; their primary concern is the fear of decreased productivity.</p>
  <p>Just as Microsoft Japan did, starting with a pilot can be a good way to dip your toes into the reality of a four-day workweek while identifying potential barriers and how to get around them. That’s what Wonderlic did when it embarked on its shorter workweek journey, Lechner says. They conducted their pilot in the summer of 2021 and have continued to operate in a four-day workweek model. They’ve experienced an increase in employee engagement and happiness without a significant drop in productivity and found that flexibility helps to attract new candidates to the organization.</p>
  <p>Lechner and other veterans of the shift offer the following strategies effectively implementing a four-day workweek structure.</p>
  <h2 id="pilot-first">Pilot first</h2>
  <p>Mini experiments, or pilots, can help organizations see exactly how a four-day workweek will affect their organizations and their productivity, easing resistance and revealing processes and supporting decisions that can make the idea work better. Every organization is different, and a pilot project, like Microsoft Japan’s, will help uncover unique requirements.</p>
  <h2 id="equip-your-managers-to-keep-their-teams-humming">Equip your managers to keep their teams humming</h2>
  <p>Tackling the many misconceptions about the four-day workweek can be an important first step in getting managers on board. For example, the four-day workweek doesn’t necessarily mean all employees will get Friday or Monday off. But it could mean that companies get the same amount of productivity out of people in fewer hours by making schedules more flexible, giving people more personal and vacation time, making allowances for family duties, and so on. And is particularly important for managers to understand – that they are still in control. Managers often report a sense of being “out of sight, out of mind” when seeing workers less often and feel a loss of control. In truth, of course, that’s not the case. What it may be, though, is a sign that managers aren’t adept at this new type of management and may not be evaluating employee performance based on objective outcomes. They may need training and support to help them feel more confident managing in a condensed work week.</p>
  <p>At Wonderlic, Lechner says, managers implemented different strategies, such as rotating schedules or skeleton crews to address customer support needs on employees’ designated days off. Deliberate planning of meetings and organizational sessions was crucial to optimize time and collaboration, she says.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="the-digital-distractions-problem">The digital distractions problem</h3>
        <p>How managers can avoid decreased productivity, stress, and burnout.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="/resources/addressing-digital-distractions">Get advice</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="ensure-the-right-balance-of-a-focus-on-short--and-long-term-objectives">Ensure the right balance of a focus on short- and long-term objectives</h2>
  <p>There’s an important balance to be struck between productivity and innovation, says Tenney, who refers to this as the “mere urgency effect” – a phenomenon where people focus more on urgent, short-term tasks, neglecting long-term more strategic thinking and innovation. The creative and innovative nature of work is important, Tenney says. In order to nurture that, employees need unstructured, or free time.</p>
  <p>“Focus on productivity measures, but not everything needs to be structured – provide flexibility to allow employees to connect with others,” Tenney advises. One way to do this, she suggests, is to provide employees the flexibility to block time on their calendars to provide them the opportunity to focus on what she calls “deep work.”</p>
  <h2 id="provide-time-management-training-and-resources-for-employees">Provide time management training and resources for employees</h2>
  <p>Time management isn’t a skill that comes naturally to all employees. Companies can benefit from providing time management training and ongoing resources for employees to help them learn about and adopt best practices for being as productive as possible. This might include formal training as well as support groups where employees can share their own best practices with others.</p>
  <h2 id="encourage-pto">Encourage PTO</h2>
  <p>Another must: encouraging employees to take time off and use their paid time off (PTO) to prevent burnout, which is a real risk. “We have to be deliberate about encouraging people to take their time off,” Lechner says. “We’ve seen PTO usage drop dramatically, and it’s important for people to take breaks to be fully present at work.”</p>
  <h2 id="evaluate-learn-and-adjust">Evaluate, learn, and adjust</h2>
  <p>In some cases, Tenney says, companies may try a four-day workweek only to realize it just wasn’t right for them. She cites a company that attempted to implement a four-day workweek but eventually found it challenging: employees ended up working more hours, and the fluctuating demands of the workload caused stress levels to become unpredictable. As a result, the company decided to revert to a five-day workweek with flexible schedules, allowing employees to work fewer than 40 hours per week while still prioritizing productivity focused on performance goals versus hours worked.</p>
  <p>Others have also found that they couldn’t make a four-day workweek work. Lachy Gray, managing director at <a href="https://www.yarno.com.au/">Yarno</a>, for instance, shared his company’s experience in a <a href="https://www.yarno.com.au/blog/4-day-work-week-failure/">post on the company’s website</a> saying: “We wanted it to work because we believe in the principles behind it. But we have to face the facts, that it's not working as we thought it would.” The company is going back to a five-day week, although Gray says, “we’re still committed to flexible working hours on those five days.”</p>
  <p>In the UK’s four-day workweek trial, <a href="https://static1.squarespace.com/static/60b956cbe7bf6f2efd86b04e/t/63f3df56276b3e6d7870207e/1676926845047/UK-4-Day-Week-Pilot-Results-Report-2023.pdf">about 8%</a> of respondents found that the four-day model simply didn’t work for them. <a href="https://www.bbc.com/worklife/article/20230319-four-day-workweek-trial-the-firms-where-it-didnt-work">Reporting for Work: In Progress, Alex Christian says</a>: “Even those firms continuing with reduced hours are navigating new challenges arising from shortened workweeks. Though this reflects a small portion of the trial’s participants, it means the four-day workweek isn’t an automatic solution for all.”</p>
  <h2 id="is-the-four-day-workweek-right-for-your-team">Is the four-day workweek right for your team?</h2>
  <p>Microsoft Japan has never looked back since its successful pilot in 2019, joining <a href="https://tech.co/news/companies-4-day-work-week">several other large companies</a> that have successfully adopted this model. By prioritizing clear communication, flexible scheduling, and effective time management, organizations can navigate the transition to a four-day workweek successfully and reap the rewards this increasingly popular work model provides.</p>
  <p>As with any major undertaking, of course, “the devil is in the details.” In a follow-up article, we will take a closer look into the many details — from labor laws to visas to anti-discrimination regulations — you need to consider to ensure your four-day workweek efforts deliver the best results.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <h4 id="read-more-in-this-series">Read more in this series</h4>
  <div class="collection">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h6 id="best-practice-guide">Best Practice Guide</h6>
        <p><a href="/resources/7-due-diligence-steps-for-the-four-day-workweek">7 Due Diligence Steps for the Four-Day Workweek</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>
        <h6 id="explainer">Explainer</h6>
        <p><a href="/resources/the-four-day-workweek-paradox">The Four-Day Workweek Paradox</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>sidebar</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/what-is</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Measuring Social Impact – the S in ESG]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/measuring-social-impact-s-in-esg</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/measuring-social-impact-s-in-esg</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Defining terms, setting scope, tracking regulations – it’s messy. Here’s how to start measuring and managing social impact.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>core-topic/environmental-compliance</category>
            <category>content-type/what-is</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[What is a data fabric?]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/what-is-data-fabric</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/what-is-data-fabric</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn how data fabric architecture can help you connect and manage all your data in real time, across different systems and applications.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/business-transformation</category>
            <category>topic/data-analytics</category>
            <category>content-type/what-is</category>
            <category>stage/acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[What is digital transformation?]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/what-is-digital-transformation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/what-is-digital-transformation</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Digital transformation is more than a technology initiative. Learn more about how to prepare your business and your teams with solid business transformation planning and services.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c6e86e2a7d144ff4657e3478c4d6df0f55aa52f7.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c6e86e2a7d144ff4657e3478c4d6df0f55aa52f7.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1c6e86e2a7d144ff4657e3478c4d6df0f55aa52f7.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="City lights at night" src="./media_1c6e86e2a7d144ff4657e3478c4d6df0f55aa52f7.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1648">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="what-is-digital-transformation">What is digital transformation?</h1>
        <p>Digital transformation happens when organizations embed digital technologies across all their operations. This helps businesses scale and compete by responding to changing markets and better serving their customers.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Digital transformation is a key component of an overall business transformation strategy, and while not the only factor, it’s critical to the success or failure of any transformation effort. The right technologies – coupled with people, processes, and operations – give organizations the ability to adapt quickly to disruption and/or opportunities; meet new and evolving customer needs; and drive future growth and innovation, often in unexpected ways.</p>
  <p>In the first of the four Industrial Revolutions, steam power was the disruptive technology that changed the world. In the second it was the assembly line; in the third it was the computer. Today, we are in the fourth Industrial Revolution and it is digital. Intelligent digital technologies like <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/what-is-artificial-intelligence.html">artificial intelligence (AI)</a>, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/what-is-machine-learning.html">machine learning</a>, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/what-is-iot.html">Internet of Things</a> (IoT) networks, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/cloud-analytics/what-is-analytics.html">advanced analytics</a>, and robotics, have the power to reinvent how we work and do business – and how companies engage with their customers and the world.</p>
  <h2 id="digital-transformation-definition">Digital transformation definition</h2>
  <p>Digital transformation involves integrating digital technologies and solutions into every area of a business. This is as much a cultural change as a technological one as it requires organizations to make fundamental shifts in the ways they operate and how they deliver customer experiences and benefits. Digital solutions also help to augment the workforce and can lead to <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/process-automation/what-is-process-automation.html">business process</a> and <a href="/resources/business-model-innovation-xaas">business model transformation</a>.</p>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_19a6caff42ede02777b312cf00e80feaca87d4968.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_19a6caff42ede02777b312cf00e80feaca87d4968.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_19a6caff42ede02777b312cf00e80feaca87d4968.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Screenshot of a video about digital transformation" src="./media_19a6caff42ede02777b312cf00e80feaca87d4968.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1280" height="720">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://d.dam.sap.com/m/1qxxfyZ/hls.m3u8">How are Digital Innovations Driving Business Transformation?</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>de-DE</div>
      <div>German</div>
      <div><a href="https://d.dam.sap.com/o/kqfxAvx/SAP848152-de%5C%5C_de-German?rc=19">https://d.dam.sap.com/o/kqfxAvx/SAP848152-de\\_de-German?rc=19</a></div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>fr-FR</div>
      <div>French (France)</div>
      <div><a href="https://d.dam.sap.com/o/JXfWqqn/SAP848152-fr%5C%5C_fr-French?rc=19">https://d.dam.sap.com/o/JXfWqqn/SAP848152-fr\\_fr-French?rc=19</a></div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>ja-JP</div>
      <div>Japanese</div>
      <div><a href="https://d.dam.sap.com/o/xBGpfEm/SAP848152-ja%5C%5C_jp-Japanese?rc=19">https://d.dam.sap.com/o/xBGpfEm/SAP848152-ja\\_jp-Japanese?rc=19</a></div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>es-CO</div>
      <div>Spanish - LATAM</div>
      <div><a href="https://d.dam.sap.com/o/DV5zL4z/SAP848152-es%5C%5C_co-Spanish?rc=19">https://d.dam.sap.com/o/DV5zL4z/SAP848152-es\\_co-Spanish?rc=19</a></div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>pt-BR</div>
      <div>Portuguese - Brazil</div>
      <div><a href="https://d.dam.sap.com/o/fVL1gip/SAP848152-pt%5C%5C_br-Portuguese?rc=19">https://d.dam.sap.com/o/fVL1gip/SAP848152-pt\\_br-Portuguese?rc=19</a></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><em>Explore how digital innovations are driving business transformation</em></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><strong>Digitization:</strong> Converting information and documents from analog to digital formats.</p>
  <p><strong>Digitalization:</strong> Integrating digital technologies into existing business processes.</p>
  <p><strong>Digital transformation:</strong> A fundamental rethinking of customer experience, business models, and operations. It’s about finding new ways to deliver value, generate revenue, and improve efficiency.</p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div data-valign="middle">style</div>
      <div data-valign="middle">additional reading</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
<div>
  <h2 id="the-importance-of-digital-transformation-in-todays-business-climate">The importance of digital transformation in today’s business climate</h2>
  <p>As we move into the 2020s, it has become increasingly apparent that if businesses are to grow and compete, they must take steps to become more resilient, competitive, and responsive. Companies must develop and transform their digital landscape – starting from <a href="/resources/how-to-make-sustainable-materials-use-matter">raw materials</a> and the earliest supply chain tiers, to meeting <a href="/resources/what-are-the-essentials-for-successful-digital-transformation-dx">rapidly changing customer demands</a> for more personalized service and fulfillment, and to modernizing and innovating traditional business models.</p>
  <p>In its <a href="https://www.mckinsey.com/business-functions/mckinsey-digital/our-insights/the-new-digital-edge-rethinking-strategy-for-the-postpandemic-era">latest survey</a> of senior business executives, McKinsey found that since the pandemic, there is a palpable sense of urgency among business leaders to digitalize and modernize their processes and legacy systems. According to the survey, many respondents recognize that their companies’ business models have become obsolete. Only 11% believe their current business models will be economically viable through 2023, while another 64% say their companies need to build new digital businesses to help them get there.</p>
  <p>For today’s businesses, it’s no longer a matter of <em>if</em> they need <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/digitization-vs-digitalization.html">digitalization</a> to compete in the current business climate, but <em>how soon</em> they can get started on their <a href="/blogs/digital-transformations-force-multiplier-sustainability">digital transformation</a> journey.</p>
  <h2 id="business-innovation-and-three-facets-of-digital-transformation">Business innovation and three facets of digital transformation</h2>
  <p>Today’s businesses are in a time of rapidly increasing competition and customer demands. A major objective of digital transformation initiatives is to help support business leaders and teams in making their operations more streamlined and competitive. New technologies (discussed below) play a central role in driving transformation, but so do business process, business models, organizational culture, and receptiveness to transformation.</p>
  <p>Any transformation plan should look at these three areas:</p>
  <ol>
    <li><strong>Business process transformation:</strong> This involves changing and adapting core – often long-standing – processes and workflows to meet changing business goals, competition, and customer demands often through <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/process-automation/what-is-process-automation.html">process automation</a>. Despite the terms often being used interchangeably, digital transformation is a subset of business transformation – it builds a connected, technological framework that underpins and supports process changes.<br><br>Evidence of business process transformation can be seen from end to end within business operations thanks to improvements in <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/workflow-management.html">workflow management</a>. For example, by implementing a digitalized, cloud-based supply chain management system, businesses can lower downtime, streamline production, and <a href="https://www.mckinsey.com/business-functions/operations/our-insights/digital-transformation-raising-supply-chain-performance-to-new-levels">increase profitability</a>.</li>
    <li><strong>Business model transformation:</strong> Business process transformation focuses on workflows and task-related areas of the business whereas <a href="/resources/business-model-innovation-xaas">business model transformation</a> aims at the foundational building blocks of how value is delivered in a specific industry. In essence, companies are using digital transformation to change traditional business models.<br><br>In the auto industry, digital technologies give the ability to centralize and automate subscription-based business models and billing processes. Coupled with rapidly changing customer demands and a general cultural shift, traditional car buying is being transformed with subscription-based models.</li>
    <li><strong>Organizational and cultural transformation:</strong> A successful digital transformation should align itself with the culture and values of the organization. An internal loss of faith in corporate culture can impact the productivity, initiative, and wellness of the workforce. Slow or pessimistic adoption of new digital technologies can cause missed targets and lead to a loss of competitiveness, revenue, and brand value.<br><br>Organizational transformation is best achieved through collaboration and open discussions from the top down – as to how this digital transformation will impact roles and workflows and why the leadership teams feel that it will be worth the risk and effort in the long run.</li>
  </ol>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div data-valign="middle">Changing customer preferences, among them the waning interest in owning physical products, have been accelerating the shift to subscription-based offerings beyond software and digital service.</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div data-valign="middle"><a href="https://www.bcg.com/en-ca/publications/2021/how-car-subscriptions-impact-auto-sales">Boston Consulting Group 2021</a></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="digital-transformation-benefits">Digital transformation benefits</h2>
  <p>Digital transformation integrates every level and function in a modern business. Intelligent technologies give organizations the essential tools they need to survive and thrive. Here are some potential impacts of transformation:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Delivers deep insights to inform real-time decision-making:</strong> For many businesses, assessing performance and ROI has often been a backward-looking process. By the time data is gathered, processed, and manually analyzed, the ship of opportunity has long since sailed. With a modern <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp.html">ERP system</a> and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/cloud-analytics.html">advanced analytics</a>, businesses can see real-time data and customize powerful analysis algorithms to make the best decision in the moment.</li>
    <li><strong>Improves efficiency and productivity:</strong> IoT network devices and machines continually transmit data, machine logs, and performance reports. Through the application of advanced analytics, this data can support predictive maintenance, lowered downtime, and deliver insights for more productive and efficient workflows.</li>
    <li><strong>Enhances customer experiences:</strong> Your customers want their needs met on their terms. Personalization, omnichannel access, customized service plans, and real-time access to data can help you deliver to their ever-changing expectations while increasing leads and driving retention and loyalty.</li>
    <li><strong>Helps drive business model innovation:</strong> There’s no question that changing consumer and market demands are seeing an increased focus on business model innovation as a means of value creation. But to change and modernize fundamental business models and customer experiences, companies require the ability to gather and analyze real-time data and develop automated and intelligent processes to manage new business, payment, and service models.</li>
    <li><strong>Supports a robust and competitive corporate growth strategy:</strong> When businesses digitalize their operations and optimize their services with connected technologies, they find new ways to connect and collaborate and to streamline future business growth strategies, including:
      <ul>
        <li>Developing new products and services</li>
        <li>Improving profitability and strengthening revenue channels</li>
        <li>Attracting and retaining new leads and customers</li>
      </ul>
    </li>
    <li><strong>Fosters agility and resistance to disruption:</strong> The COIVD-19 pandemic served to shine a light on a lot of vulnerabilities in modern business processes and models. But it was only one of many cultural, economic, political, and market changes that businesses have been increasingly facing in the past few years. Modern companies now look to digital transformation to equip them with the tools for rapid new product and service development, and predictive analytics to help better see disruptions coming, or anticipate market changes and opportunities. They want to be able to scale up and down with ease and have a full suite of cloud-connected solutions that can drive innovation – without having to jump from provider to provider.</li>
  </ul>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="the-essentials-for-successful-dx">The Essentials for Successful DX</h3>
        <p>Digital technology can reinvigorate customer service. Here’s what to focus on.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="/resources/what-are-the-essentials-for-successful-digital-transformation-dx">Read the article</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="technology-transformation-enables-business-transformation">Technology transformation enables business transformation</h2>
  <p>Digital transformation is underpinned by some of these core and new technologies:</p>
  <h3 id="modern-erp-and-database-technologies">Modern ERP and database technologies</h3>
  <p>The <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp.html">best cloud ERP</a> solutions use in-memory database technology, making them highly scalable and adaptable. This is important because they are essentially the “brains” behind digital business transformation. ERP takes all the core processes needed to run a company (such as finance, HR, manufacturing, and supply chain) and integrates them into a single system. And when a modern ERP is powered by AI technologies, it has the power to not only manage and process <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/what-is-big-data.html">Big Data</a>, but to analyze and learn from it.</p>
  <h3 id="advanced-analytics">Advanced analytics</h3>
  <p>In order to deliver value, data needs to be harnessed and understood. Using AI and machine learning algorithms, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/cloud-analytics/what-is-analytics.html">advanced analytics</a> provides insights and reports that are deep, accurate, and actionable. Businesses can also customize data analysis configurations on demand. This gives business leaders the power to act quickly and decisively – by seizing an opportunity or responding to risk.</p>
  <h3 id="cloud-connectivity">Cloud connectivity</h3>
  <p>Cloud-based infrastructure is an essential component to successful digital transformation and the establishment of IoT networks and connected business systems. On-demand, centralized access to all systems, assets, and data allows organizations to scale infrastructure as needed and rapidly change or automate workflows. This helps to support rapidly changing business priorities and operational models. And as <a href="https://www.forrester.com/report/Adoption+Profile+Public+Cloud+In+North+America+Q2+2018/-/E-RES141975">Forrester</a> tells us, as of 2021, almost 60% of enterprises in North America rely on cloud platforms, which is five times the percentage it was just five years ago.</p>
  <h3 id="ai-and-machine-learning-solutions">AI and machine learning solutions</h3>
  <p>Big Data grew up alongside <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/what-is-artificial-intelligence.html">AI</a> and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/what-is-machine-learning.html">machine learning</a>. In order to process and make sense of Big Data, it’s necessary to have the power of AI and machine learning. For AI and machine learning to deliver accurate and meaningful results, both must have large enough data sets to support robust learning and analysis. The partnership of Big Data, AI, and analytics is at the core of business and digital transformation – driving predictive planning and responsive automation.</p>
  <h3 id="internet-of-things">Internet of Things</h3>
  <p>Devices and machines in an <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/what-is-iot.html">IoT</a> network can send and receive digital data. Machine logs and maintenance reports are analyzed to optimize performance and efficiency. AI-powered business systems continuously analyze this information for patterns, trends, and correlations. These insights help drive predictive maintenance and automated workflows, increasing efficiency and productivity over time as the machine learning applications “learn” from the IoT data.</p>
  <h3 id="robotics-and-robotic-process-automation-rpa">Robotics and robotic process automation (RPA)</h3>
  <p>Both robotics and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/process-automation/features.html#robotic-process-automation">RPA</a> use automated processes to accomplish repetitive or pre-programmed tasks. Robotic devices are comprised of moving, mechanical parts set to execute specific, physical tasks. RPA processes are similarly programmed and automated – however, they exist as software processes rather than physical devices, and the tasks they perform are administrative in nature.</p>
  <h2 id="digital-transformation-examples">Digital transformation examples</h2>
  <p><strong>Supply chain, procurement, and manufacturing</strong></p>
  <p>In a <a href="https://www.gartner.com/smarterwithgartner/gartner-top-8-supply-chain-technology-trends-for-2020/">report</a> from July 2020, Gartner points out that if businesses are to thrive and optimize their supply chains, “They must look to innovative technologies that have the potential to disrupt supply chain operating models and provide a competitive advantage.” Digital transformation in supply chains and manufacturing provides centralized visibility – from raw materials to end customers – and drives <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/integrated-business-planning/what-is-a-resilient-supply-chain.html">resilience</a>.</p>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1fbf45c40ec892fdb53020651d958ca40b0bd868e.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1fbf45c40ec892fdb53020651d958ca40b0bd868e.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1fbf45c40ec892fdb53020651d958ca40b0bd868e.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Learn how SAP S/4HANA helped South African pharmaceutical manufacturing and healthcare solutions company Kiara Health transition seamlessly to a new ownership and leadership team in just five months. With the solution in place, the company is enjoying greater efficiency and is future-proofed for Industry 4.0 innovation." src="./media_1fbf45c40ec892fdb53020651d958ca40b0bd868e.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="319" height="179">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://d.dam.sap.com/m/Q2iXiX3/hls.m3u8">SAP S/4HANA was the right medicine for a painless ownership transition for pharma company Kiara Health.</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>ja-JP</div>
      <div>Japanese</div>
      <div><a href="https://d.dam.sap.com/o/T2seFm1/SAP836178-ja%5C%5C_jp-Japanese?rc=19">https://d.dam.sap.com/o/T2seFm1/SAP836178-ja\\_jp-Japanese?rc=19</a></div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>fr-FR</div>
      <div>French (France)</div>
      <div><a href="https://d.dam.sap.com/o/Lw5oJ29/SAP836178-fr%5C%5C_fr-French?rc=19">https://d.dam.sap.com/o/Lw5oJ29/SAP836178-fr\\_fr-French?rc=19</a></div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>es-CO</div>
      <div>Spanish - LATAM</div>
      <div><a href="https://d.dam.sap.com/o/NpsB3oT/SAP836178-es%5C%5C_co-Spanish?rc=19">https://d.dam.sap.com/o/NpsB3oT/SAP836178-es\\_co-Spanish?rc=19</a></div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>de-DE</div>
      <div>German</div>
      <div><a href="https://d.dam.sap.com/o/hj2TZon/SAP836178-de%5C%5C_de-German?rc=19">https://d.dam.sap.com/o/hj2TZon/SAP836178-de\\_de-German?rc=19</a></div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>pt-BR</div>
      <div>Portuguese - Brazil</div>
      <div><a href="https://d.dam.sap.com/o/cCHafYW/SAP836178-pt%5C%5C_br-Portuguese?rc=19">https://d.dam.sap.com/o/cCHafYW/SAP836178-pt\\_br-Portuguese?rc=19</a></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><em>Hear from pharmaceutical manufacturing and healthcare solutions company, Kiara Health, and how it has greater efficiency and has future proofed its business thanks to its ERP system.</em></p>
  <p><strong>Service industries and HR</strong></p>
  <p>In the past decade, digital technologies have been driving change in the workplace. VR, chatbots, and mobile devices are customizing the onboarding process, as well as improving employee service and support. Blockchain is securing the privacy and accuracy of information. Machine learning is helping to <a href="https://www.sap.com/insights/viewpoints/how-ai-can-end-bias.html">eliminate bias</a> and ensure that businesses are champions for diversity and inclusion.</p>
  <p><strong>Healthcare and life sciences</strong></p>
  <p>Digital technologies in healthcare have a complex workload. Research and diagnostic programs rely heavily on AI and machine learning. Surgical and medical devices require the speed and accuracy of powerful cloud and database technologies. Healthcare workers providing patient care and support are improving mobile and monitoring options so users can feel safe and confident with self-serve mobile technologies.</p>
  <p><strong>Banking</strong></p>
  <p>A 2020 JD Power <a href="https://www.jdpower.com/business/press-releases/2020-us-retail-banking-advice-satisfaction-study">report</a> states that “…it is safe to say we’ve reached the tipping point, where banks that get their digital formulas right are seeing strong gains in both adoption and satisfaction.” Digital transformation in the financial services sector delivers customized and hyper-personalized services, better mobile functionality, and free remote access to more complex services such as financial planning and credit management.</p>
  <p><strong>Retail</strong></p>
  <p>Digital transformation in retail can automate and optimize logistics networks – customizing and speeding up delivery. And as in every consumer sector, the growing demand for personalized services is also driving digital innovation. A recent Epsilon <a href="https://us.epsilon.com/pressroom/new-epsilon-research-indicates-80-of-consumers-are-more-likely-to-make-a-purchase-when-brands-offer-personalized-experiences">study</a> saw 80% of shoppers more likely to choose a retailer that offers personalized services – including 24×7 chatbots, personalized product suggestions, predictive recommendations, and fluid omnichannel mobility.</p>
  <p><strong>Automotive</strong></p>
  <p>The automotive industry was an early adopter of manufacturing robotics and digital automation. But as one of the world’s most competitive industries, many of its latest digital innovations relate to customer service and retention. Personalization and driver interface applications provide safety and enjoyment to the driver and give the business valuable data to help with more accurate product development, marketing, and customer experience provision.</p>
  <h2 id="the-greatest-challenges-to-digital-transformation">The greatest challenges to digital transformation</h2>
  <p>Studies from thought leaders like <a href="https://www.mckinsey.com/featured-insights/Mckinsey-live/webinars/the-secrets-to-transformation-success">McKinsey</a> and <a href="https://hbr.org/2013/04/change-management-needs-to-cha">Harvard Business Review</a> have shown us that up to 70% of business and digital transformation initiatives do not succeed. But if you dig a bit deeper, you learn that it’s not really the new technologies or the business innovations that are flawed. The weaknesses lay in poor planning, poor communication and change strategies, and the general failure of leaders and project managers to include and seek buy-in from all teams impacted by the change. In other words, of the three main areas of digital transformation mentioned above, “cultural transformation” is often the least talked-about but in reality may be the most crucial of all.</p>
  <h2 id="preparing-for-digital-business-transformation">Preparing for digital business transformation</h2>
  <p>In a challenging business climate, companies need to seize every competitive advantage – and increasingly, those advantages are digital. By 2018,<a href="https://cdn2.hubspot.net/hubfs/1624046/Digital%20Business%20Executive%20Summary_FINAL.pdf"> over 89% of executives</a> had adopted a digital-first business policy. And by 2021, that number has only grown. However, as we discussed earlier, many digital transformation projects get stalled by poor communication and planning.</p>
  <p>Consider these four early steps as you progress on your digital transformation journey, and speak to your software vendor to help you get started with crafting a <a href="/resources/digital-transformation-strategy-road-map">transformation strategy and road map</a> and learning which solutions are best for your unique business needs.</p>
  <ol>
    <li><strong>Determine your starting point.</strong> Audit your existing systems and assets. Which machines are already digitalized? Which ones will require IoT gateways? Is your ERP modern and scalable, or is it still running on disk-based database memory? To give your project an early leg up, look first for processes within your business that are a high operational priority and have the least complicated path to transformation.</li>
    <li><strong>Define your priorities.</strong> Don’t plan a marathon before you’ve even made it around the first block. The beauty of digital transformation is that it does not have to happen all at once. Like building blocks, smart technologies are designed to evolve, scale, and integrate.</li>
    <li><strong>Build your roadmap.</strong> A significant benefit to smart technologies lies in their immense scalability and capacity for rapid adaptation and reconfiguration. A great transformation road map should allow for agility and growth but start with a road map that has a few strong and attainable goals. Build solid change management and migration strategies into your plan as well – digital transformation is as much a human journey as a technological one. These are important early steps. Look for support from specialized professionals who understand your unique needs and can help chart the best course for your business.</li>
    <li><strong>Prepare your teams.</strong> Thoreau said, “Things do not change; we change.” Smart technologies can help reduce repetitive and tedious tasks, improve employee engagement, and support collaboration. But these benefits can only be realized when all your people are on board. Don’t spring the news on your teams. Learn from their input and ideas, openly address their concerns, and give them time to change.</li>
  </ol>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="start-your-digital-transformation-today">Start your digital transformation today</h3>
        <p>Chart your transformation road map with a modern ERP.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp.html">Learn more</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="faqs-common-questions-about-digital-transformation">FAQs: Common questions about digital transformation</h2>
  <div class="accordion">
    <div>
      <div>What are the biggest challenges to digital transformation?</div>
      <div>Digital transformation is a business transformation and a company-wide change management project. When digital transformation projects fail or stall, it is seldom a technical problem – it is almost always a cultural one. In reports and articles from <a href="https://www.mckinsey.com/business-functions/mckinsey-digital/our-insights/why-digital-strategies-fail">McKinsey</a> and others, we learn that poor planning, misaligned goals, and unclear strategies are the cause of the bulk of transformation setbacks.</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>Who typically "owns" digital transformation in a business?</div>
      <div>In their fifth annual <em><a href="https://www.prophet.com/download/the-state-of-digital-transformation/">State of Digital Transformation</a></em> report, the Altimiter research group finds that, typically, the bulk of ownership is shared between the CIO and the CEO. But as digital transformation is no longer seen as an exclusively technological initiative, businesses are starting to rely more upon internal business process specialists to ensure that digital technology integrations have the best benefit for all.</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>Which technologies should I start with?</div>
      <div>Of course, this varies from business to business, but for most companies a modern, AI-powered <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp.html">cloud ERP</a> with an in-memory database is at the center of any digital enterprise. Within the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/what-is-erp.html">ERP</a> system are the brains that analyze, direct, and process all the data and information from across the business.</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>How can I measure ROI of a digital transformation project?</div>
      <div>Start simple by choosing a few key metrics that are most important to your specific industry and organization (lead acquisition, manufacturing productivity, predictive planning). Figure out where you are today on those criteria, set realistic target goals, and measure again at fixed points in time.</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>How can I be sure my digital transformation roadmap is a good one?</div>
      <div>Unlike software upgrades of the past, digital transformation is not an isolated IT project. Digital transformation affects all areas and functions in a business and requires technological and cultural adaptation and resilience. Before this kind of project, reach out to your software vendor to ensure you’re charting the best path for your unique situation.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="start-your-digital-transformation-today-1">Start your digital transformation today</h3>
        <p>Chart your transformation road map with a modern ERP.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp.html">Learn more</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h4 id="read-more-in-this-series">Read more in this series</h4>
  <div class="collection">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h6 id="explainer">Explainer</h6>
        <p><a href="/resources/what-is-digital-transformation">What is digital transformation?</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>
        <h6 id="best-practice-guide">Best Practice Guide</h6>
        <p><a href="/resources/digital-transformation-strategy-road-map">Building a digital transformation strategy: A guide to creating your road map</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>sidebar</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>topic/business-transformation</category>
            <category>content-type/what-is</category>
            <category>stage/acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[What is Zero Trust?]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/what-is-zero-trust</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/what-is-zero-trust</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Find out why zero trust architecture and solutions are more important than ever and learn more about zero trust principles and best practices.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>content-type/what-is</category>
            <category>stage/acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Manage Social Factors Like Other Governance Risks]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/manage-social-factors-like-other-governance-risks</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/manage-social-factors-like-other-governance-risks</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Unsafe factories and other social factors can fast become a liability. Learn how to put the issue on the board’s agenda.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>core-topic/environmental-compliance</category>
            <category>content-type/what-is</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Contract Manufacturing: Supply Chains’ Blind Spot]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/contract-manufacturing-supply-chains-blind-spot</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/contract-manufacturing-supply-chains-blind-spot</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn how to build trust with partners and not just demand it.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>content-type/what-is</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How to Keep Boomers, an Essential Talent Resource]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/how-to-keep-baby-boomers-an-essential-talent-resource</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/how-to-keep-baby-boomers-an-essential-talent-resource</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Effective moves: learn older workers’ specific needs. Embrace flexible scheduling. Foster older-younger collaborations.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>content-type/what-is</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Industry 4.0 Factories Can Still Embrace the Past]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/how-industry-4-0-factories-can-still-embrace-the-past</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/how-industry-4-0-factories-can-still-embrace-the-past</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn how retrofitting old equipment can help digitalize operations without breaking the bank.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/business-transformation</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>content-type/what-is</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How to Offset the Rise in Workplace Retaliation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/how-to-offset-the-rise-in-workplace-retaliation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/how-to-offset-the-rise-in-workplace-retaliation</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn how to minimize workplace retaliation and have systems in place to deal with it effectively.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1fdaca4b7993d1a2478e2398d027a8c5271fe2396.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1fdaca4b7993d1a2478e2398d027a8c5271fe2396.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1fdaca4b7993d1a2478e2398d027a8c5271fe2396.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Woman seen from above sitting on a modern wood bench with a tablet on her lap having a difficult conversation on her cellphone." src="./media_1fdaca4b7993d1a2478e2398d027a8c5271fe2396.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1044">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="how-to-offset-the-rise-in-workplace-retaliation">How to Offset the Rise in Workplace Retaliation</h1>
        <p>79% of U.S. employees report experiencing some form of retaliation at work. Here’s how to minimize these occurrences and have systems in place to deal with them effectively.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>By Caitlynn Sendra and Stacy Collett</p>
  <p>In the aftermath of two Boeing 737 Max airliner crashes in 2018 and 2019, investigations pointed to two reasons why the aircrafts’ catastrophic design flaw was not identified and resolved. Both underlying conditions were related to the manufacturer’s organizational culture: a hyper-focus on bottom-line business results over design safety and fear of retaliation for speaking up.</p>
  <p>“My pay was docked for putting quality concerns in writing,” says one Boeing quality manager, speaking in the Netflix <a href="https://www.netflix.com/title/81272421">documentary</a> <em>Downfall: The Case Against Boeing</em>. Whistleblowers at the company said anybody who reported a problem was either fired, let go, or moved on, according to aviation analyst Michael Goldfarb in the documentary.</p>
  <p>These experiences were emblematic of a retaliation culture that had infected the organization. “Boeing quit listening to their employees. So every time I would raise my hand, they would attack the messenger and ignore the message,” says yet another quality manager.</p>
  <p>The severity of the Boeing case may make workplace retaliation seem like a rare occurrence – something that many senior managers would attest “doesn’t happen here.” But retaliation at work – in various forms – is very much on the rise. Since 2019, incidents of retaliation at work skyrocketed globally. According to <a href="https://www.ethics.org/global-business-ethics-survey/">a study</a> by the Ethics and Compliance Initiative, a Vienna, Virginia-based nonprofit that helps organizations build and sustain high-quality ethics and compliance programs, 79% of U.S. employees and 61% of global employees reported experiencing some type of retaliation in the workplace in 2021. Additionally, more than half of cases (55.8%) formally filed with the U.S. Equal Employment Opportunity Commission in 2020 were for some form of retaliation.</p>
  <p>Granted, in most organizations, retaliatory action can be far more subtle than what Boeing’s employees experienced. It could come in the form of a supervisor withholding constructive feedback, or leaving an employee out of an important meeting after they disagree with a management decision, or exercising their rights in a way that goes against the grain of the culture. However, the negative effect on the victims of retaliation and the business itself can be just as serious.</p>
</div>
<div>
  <h2 id="more-on-how-leaders-can-build-better-workplace-cultures">More on how leaders can build better workplace cultures</h2>
  <p>Including <a href="/resources/how-to-repair-toxic-workplace-culture">how to combat workplace toxicity</a> , what to do about <em><a href="/resources/strategies-to-head-off-quiet-quitting">quiet quitting</a></em>, and how to view the forces that are redefining what it means to be <a href="/blogs/going-to-the-office-every-day-is-over">connected to an office</a>.</p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>Style</div>
      <div>Additional Reading</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
<div>
  <p>Left unchecked, a culture of retaliation can spread throughout the organization, “creating entire climates of abuse,” says Villanova professor Manuela Priesemuth in <a href="https://hbr.org/2020/06/times-up-for-toxic-workplaces">her article</a>, “<a href="https://hbr.org/2020/06/times-up-for-toxic-workplaces">Time’s Up for Toxic Workplaces</a>.” “Because employees look to and learn from managers, they come to understand that this type of interpersonal mistreatment is acceptable behavior in the company.”</p>
  <p>Researchers attribute the rise in retaliation, in part, to increased pressure on employees to compromise business standards. Since 2020, such pressure is the highest it has ever been, according to ECI. Globally, 29% of employees reported pressure in 2020, up from 20% in 2019.</p>
  <p>For their part, employees are more willing to speak up about observed misconduct, thanks to heightened sensitivity following the Me Too movement, increased diversity and inclusion awareness, and a new age of employee empowerment brought on by the demand for workers. In 2020, 86% of employees were more likely to report misconduct, compared with 69% in 2017, according to ECI. The move to remote work in 2020 also created more opportunities for inappropriate behavior through digital channels. Inappropriate comments, jokes, GIFs sent through e-mail, chat messages, and texts could all be considered digital harassment with grounds for reporting.</p>
  <p>In this climate, businesses need to be alert to signs of a retaliation culture and stop retaliatory behavior before it starts. This starts with creating an environment of psychological safety and extends to middle management training. Companies also need to put mechanisms in place for employees to address concerns promptly and transparently and provide multiple reporting channels to any employee who feels the need to raise an issue or report on a retaliatory event.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="fundamentals-of-employee-experience">Fundamentals of employee experience</h3>
        <p>Everything you need to know about the employee journey and tools to support.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/workzone-hr/what-is-employee-experience.html">Get the guide</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="what-retaliation-actually-looks-like">What retaliation actually looks like</h2>
  <p>Although retaliation is defined in multiple ways, two basic elements are always present: an issue is raised, and the person who raised it suffers as a result. The suffering can be overt or subtle and can be triggered by management or peers.</p>
  <p>Often, retaliatory actions can be indirect or can even take the form of a lack of action. In fact, “exclusion is the number one form of subtle retaliation,” says Skip Lowney, senior researcher at ECI. For example, an employee who’s seen as too outspoken at meetings might find information being withheld that’s essential to them doing their job. Team members could also be discouraged from listening to an employee’s expertise or contributions after the employee challenges the direction a project is going. It could even be as subtle as an executive giving a disapproving look to a senior manager who speaks up at a meeting, signaling that they’re in trouble.</p>
  <p>Such subtle acts of retaliation can be difficult to recognize, but they can still have a devastating effect. Subtle retaliation destroys careers, erodes the targeted individual’s sense of worth, and damages workforce effectiveness and productivity. Further, retaliation can diminish business performance because it discourages employees from offering input that could lead to innovation or steer management away from making poor decisions.</p>
  <h2 id="the-reverberating-effect-of-a-culture-of-retaliation">The reverberating effect of a culture of retaliation</h2>
  <p>Even companies that don’t have a culture of retaliation may have to deal with its damaging effects. Employees who experienced retaliation at a previous employer may be extremely sensitive to any nuance of it at any new workplace, or suspicion may be raised by retaliation claims on social media. Some workers are so distrustful that they won’t complete employee surveys for fear it will be linked back to them and used against them.</p>
  <p>Jeffrey, a data scientist who asked that his real name not be used, is still haunted by the retaliation he suffered at a former employer. “It has shaped how I interact with everyone else for the rest of my career,” he says.</p>
  <p>While working remotely for a small company, he was locked out of the company’s network and communication tools after voicing his frustration to the CEO in a group email about the team’s health insurance that had been stopped and restarted repeatedly. He later learned he had been fired.</p>
  <p>“I was scared. My family is a single-income household,” he recalled. “Then I started spiraling. How am I going to pay for my wife’s meds? How do we not become homeless?” Jeffrey found a new job within weeks – but the experience had lingering effects on him and his former co-workers.</p>
  <p>“There was a lot of fear on the team after I was fired. They were afraid to speak out and get fired themselves,” Jeffery says.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15de7ef3b5018dbd66f539cc6427fa896c06ac485.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15de7ef3b5018dbd66f539cc6427fa896c06ac485.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_15de7ef3b5018dbd66f539cc6427fa896c06ac485.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Viewed from above, two people in a conversation, seated in leather lounge chairs at a small table in a corporate lounge setting." src="./media_15de7ef3b5018dbd66f539cc6427fa896c06ac485.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="psychological-safety--good-decision-making">Psychological safety = good decision-making</h2>
  <p>Organizational psychologists agree that the first step to avoiding or repairing a culture of retaliation is to promote and reinforce a culture of psychological safety. Psychological safety is grounded in an unwritten contract of behavior expectations between employer and employee. These expectations create an interpersonal climate where people feel free to speak up honestly and openly. The perception that there will not be consequences for taking interpersonal risks at work is at the core of psychological safety, says Amy Edmonson, professor at Harvard Business School.</p>
  <p>“The most important thing that psychological safety enables for executive teams is good decision-making,” Edmonson says in a <a href="https://512solutions.com/psychological-safety-podcast/">podcast</a>. “They will not fall prey to a very common trap, which is to make a consequential decision in a particular direction that one or more people had grave doubts about but didn’t feel safe to speak up about them.” This isn’t a rare occurrence, she adds.</p>
  <p>“Some of that is just slightly below conscious awareness. You sort of hold back,” Edmonson says. Even if it’s not a matter of feeling unsafe about speaking up, people may not want to come across as unpleasant, or they may doubt themselves because the area of discussion is somewhat outside of their area of expertise. “One executive described it as, ‘I didn’t want to be the skunk at the picnic,’” she says. “In an executive team of high psychological safety, that just doesn’t happen.”</p>
  <h2 id="the-vital-role-of-middle-managers-and-supervisors">The vital role of middle managers and supervisors</h2>
  <p>While executives set the cultural tone, middle managers and supervisors are central to avoiding a culture of retaliation or repairing one damaged by it. <a href="https://news.gallup.com/businessjournal/182792/managers-account-variance-employee-engagement.aspx">Data from Gallup</a> going back to 2015 indicates that managers account for 70% of the variances in employee engagement, which means a good manager can make a world of difference in every employee’s perception of the culture.</p>
  <p>On the flip side, middle managers and supervisors at every level in the organization can create distinctive microcultures, even when they are subject to the same corporate policies and organization-wide practices. Empowering managers has many advantages, but autonomy also leaves more space <a href="/resources/how-to-repair-toxic-workplace-culture">to create a toxic subculture</a>. <a href="https://sloanreview.mit.edu/article/how-to-fix-a-toxic-culture/">In their research</a>, senior lecturer at the MIT Sloan School of Management, Donald Sull, and cofounder of Culture X, Charles Sull, found that middle managers were more than twice as likely to be the source of a toxic subculture compared with other companywide factors.</p>
  <p>To curb a culture of retaliation, executives and managers need the tools to deepen their self-awareness regarding the actions they take and their effect on the people who report to them. Education programs can help managers learn to identify mental patterns that block them from absorbing and accepting new ideas that allow them to change their behavior, says Robert Kegan, co-author of <em>Immunity to Change: How to Overcome It and Unlock the Potential in Yourself and Your Organization.</em></p>
  <p>Managers should also be encouraged to examine their conscious or unconscious ulterior motives. To what extent are their actions a result of ego, stress, or self-protection? What effect has that had on others?</p>
  <p>They must also examine their relationships with those around them and identify how they might treat their inner circle and outer circles differently. From here, managers can start to recreate a culture that is open and inclusive.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_190249664dedc86c74415791a01eb3f1c3a4bb6fd.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_190249664dedc86c74415791a01eb3f1c3a4bb6fd.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_190249664dedc86c74415791a01eb3f1c3a4bb6fd.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Group of five colleagues in an open office setting, two are seated and three are standing, two that are standing are high-fiving" src="./media_190249664dedc86c74415791a01eb3f1c3a4bb6fd.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1678" height="1120">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="exposing-and-eliminating-retaliation-culture">Exposing and eliminating retaliation culture</h2>
  <p>As important as it is to discourage a culture of retaliation, it’s just as vital to have plans and mechanisms in place for when these transgressions occur. Organizations should consider the following when developing strategies and processes for managing instances of misconduct.</p>
  <h2 id="develop-clear-policies-and-communicate-them">Develop clear policies and communicate them</h2>
  <p>Employees need to be aware of the channels for reporting on both misconduct and retaliatory behaviors. Companies may use human resources, an anonymous hotline, supervisors, a complaint process, or a combination of these and other methods, to encourage employees to report concerns. The entire organization needs to know what retaliation looks like, and the definition needs to be shared repeatedly with all employees.</p>
  <h2 id="hear-out-employees">Hear out employees</h2>
  <p>Managers need to intentionally set aside time to talk with their direct reports and allow them to air out any concerns, says Dr. Anthony Klotz, an associate professor of organizational behavior at University College London School of Management. “But they’re so stretched, they usually don’t have time or feel stressed, and when they do have time, they’re usually in defensive mode.” Klotz suggests setting aside time weekly to hear how employees are experiencing work. “Then their job is to funnel that up to higher levels of the organization so they can make changes and adjust accordingly,” Klotz says.</p>
  <p>Managers should also be trained to recognize appearances of unfair behavior, including their own, and address it immediately, Lowney says. “If a problem comes to the supervisor, they are supposed to resolve it, but also report that to the ethics and compliance office to monitor and track it,” he says.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="how-to-support-stressed-workers">How to support stressed workers</h3>
        <p>Learn how managers can respond to employees’ mental health needs.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="/resources/how-managers-can-support-stressed-workers">Explore</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="set-manageable-expectations">Set manageable expectations</h2>
  <p>Employees need to understand what will happen once a report is made and how long it’s likely to take, from reporting through evaluation and investigation to potential disciplinary actions.</p>
  <p>It needs to be made clear that just because a report is made; it does not mean specific actions will be taken. If a formal investigation is to be launched, the employee should be notified and made aware of how long the investigation may take.</p>
  <p>Employees who file a complaint will likely be especially sensitive to others’ behavior – suddenly, even the most minor interactions can feel like retaliation, such as a boss who doesn’t say hello in the hallway, or their peers who suddenly seem quiet. To ameliorate such fears, employees should be made aware of what is and is not retaliation, so they know how to manage any heightened sensitivity while awaiting a response to their report and thereafter.</p>
  <h2 id="keep-the-lines-open">Keep the lines open</h2>
  <p>While it is not necessary or feasible for employees to be alerted to every step of the formal process, it is important for them to know there is a process and generally what it entails so they feel confident that something is being done, their allegations are being taken seriously, and their complaint is heading toward some type of conclusion. Employees should be told what leaders found in their examination of reported unethical or retaliatory behavior, what they’ve done with that information to resolve the problem, the progress made, and then follow through on changes leaders have identified as being necessary.</p>
  <p>All these steps can equip individuals to speak up for themselves and for the benefit of the organization. Employees who work in a culture of psychological safety feel valued and are more productive, and organizations benefit from better decision-making and, ideally, greater innovation.</p>
  <p>“You want a culture where people feel it is safe to speak up,” Klotz says. “If it’s a climate of support and psychological safety, having a voice leads to very positive outcomes for the organization.”</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/what-is</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How AI Transforms Agriculture]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/how-ai-transforms-agriculture</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/how-ai-transforms-agriculture</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn how next-generation farming processes promise higher yields, greater efficiency, and better sustainability, improving business performance.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_110073b3f26e477cf3ec92294b3cc1fa8cd859357.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_110073b3f26e477cf3ec92294b3cc1fa8cd859357.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_110073b3f26e477cf3ec92294b3cc1fa8cd859357.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Farmer with a computer tablet squatting between rows of corn." src="./media_110073b3f26e477cf3ec92294b3cc1fa8cd859357.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1044">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="how-ai-transforms-agriculture">How AI Transforms Agriculture</h1>
        <p>Next-generation farming processes promise higher yields, greater efficiency, and better sustainability, all of which will improve business performance.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>By Cedrik Kern, Oliver Rueckert and Lauren Gibbons Paul</p>
  <p>That last ice cream cone you enjoyed was creamy, sweet, and refreshing. It was also the product of data. This includes data about weather and soil conditions, crop protection, and livestock well-being. Data that measures improvements in productivity. Data that tracks the efficient use of resources so future generations of farmers can continue to tend their crops – and future consumers will enjoy frosty treats that originate with their harvests, like the sugar, cream (or oat milk if you want) and flour for the crunchy cone.</p>
  <p>The journey from farm to table is a long one. It can take years for farmers to cultivate inputs (seeds, plants, livestock) and manage resources just to get their products ready for sale and distribution. Then it’s time to prepare for the next season. And then do everything all over again, only better.</p>
</div>
<div>
  <h2 id="more-on-how-intelligent-technologies-can-help-the-agricultural-industry-lift-poor-farmers-and-heal-the-planet">More on how intelligent technologies can help the agricultural industry lift poor farmers and heal the planet.</h2>
  <p>Read “<a href="/blogs/the-future-of-feeding-the-world">The Future of Feeding the World</a>.”</p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>Style</div>
      <div>Additional Reading</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
<div>
  <p>The digitalization of farming practices is closely connected with the concept of precision agriculture. It’s a concept that has been studied for decades, starting in the 1980s with the advent of geographic information systems that tracked crop production and field conditions. Since then, the amount of data that is captured around fields and farms has increased steadily.</p>
  <p>But while the introduction of AI and machine learning applications injects fresh promise of productivity gains in agriculture, today’s farming companies face two major challenges. The first is cultural: because farmers have been familiar with their processes for years if not generations, it can take extra effort to overcome skepticism and subsequently adopt new practices that take advantage of those growing data sources. The second challenge is data-centric and technical: there is often a lack of standards to use the data in AI and analytics applications efficiently that can help companies improve farming processes.</p>
  <p>These challenges confront farmers in a global context that affects all industries and raises the stakes for farmers using data to improve productivity and resource management. Factors include:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Extreme weather:</strong> The environment is more precarious than ever, with extreme weather events threatening to render time-tested farming practices obsolete at a time when the world needs productive farms more than ever.</li>
    <li><strong>Conflict:</strong> When war breaks out, as it did when Russia invaded Ukraine in February 2022, it disrupts the global movement of agricultural products such as wheat, exacerbating supply shortages in regions such as the Horn of Africa, as NPR <a href="https://www.npr.org/sections/goatsandsoda/2023/07/19/1188714712/russias-nixing-of-ukraine-grain-deal-deepens-worries-about-global-food-supply">reported</a>.</li>
    <li><strong>Global hunger:</strong> In July 2023, there were 643 million people in 88 countries who did not have sufficient food available to them, according to <a href="https://static.hungermapdata.org/insight-reports/latest/global-summary.pdf">estimates</a> from the United Nations World Food Program.</li>
    <li><strong>Population growth:</strong> UN projections note the world’s population is expected to rise by nearly 2 billion in the next three decades, to reach <a href="https://www.un.org/en/global-issues/population">9.7 billion in 2050</a>.</li>
    <li><strong>Consumer demands for transparency:</strong> In developed economies, more demanding consumers want to see where their food comes from and how it’s produced. A 2022 survey of U.S. households found consumers want food brands and retailers to share not just the ingredients in the food they buy but also information about manufacturing practices, ingredient sourcing, and company sustainability efforts, <em>Supermarket News</em> <a href="https://www.supermarketnews.com/consumer-trends/survey-consumers-demand-deeper-transparency-food-brands-retailers">reported</a>.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>The better use of data and technologies like AI to inform decision-making promises to put agribusinesses on a path to address these challenges so that enterprises (many of which include their own farming operations or collaboration with other farmers) can improve their business processes. The adoption of what experts call precision agriculture is still in its early period, but there’s no question it’s spreading.</p>
  <p>A 2023 McKinsey <a href="https://www.mckinsey.com/industries/agriculture/our-insights/agtech-breaking-down-the-farmer-adoption-dilemma">report</a> found that “though agricultural technology adoption is slow, farmers are open to innovation.” Agribusinesses based in North and South America were more likely to have adopted, or have plans in place to implement, precision agriculture systems such as yield monitoring, variable rate fertilizer applications, and in-field soil sensors, the report notes. Even so, momentum is building.</p>
  <p>But first, farmers have to trust that the data will help them.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f8b88f033ee7b5d48e8a5d182cea1ffc51c912fb.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f8b88f033ee7b5d48e8a5d182cea1ffc51c912fb.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1f8b88f033ee7b5d48e8a5d182cea1ffc51c912fb.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Five people of different ethnicities smiling and standing together in a greenhouse garden." src="./media_1f8b88f033ee7b5d48e8a5d182cea1ffc51c912fb.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="gaining-the-trust-of-farmers">Gaining the trust of farmers</h2>
  <p>Business process shifts that call for using data to drive decision-making are challenging by definition. Adopting AI and data-driven agricultural processes is like an aircraft pilot accustomed to flying visually shifting to instruments to guide their flight. A farmer can’t always see the data that goes into the decision-support systems. There has to be trust in the systems that indicate the next-best irrigation setting or pest-control treatment.</p>
  <p>In our experience, this change in mindset needs to take root in different levels of the agribusiness organization. It’s not enough for the top decision-makers to buy in. The farm managers and those closest to the field need to adopt the new ways of working. We’ve witnessed large organizations that invest in producing impressive data-driven models to guide improving irrigation and fertilization programs, to improve a farm’s efficiency and sustainability. However, if managers on the ground are skeptical of this new information, and a change fails to occur, the company risks missing out.</p>
  <p>What’s needed: a deliberate, incremental, iterative approach that brings data to agriculture in ways that mirror farmers’ experiences. Going step-by-step makes it possible to make small changes and gain support from farmers used to planting and harvesting the same way they always have. Many farming companies want to build upon the business practices they have honed over time. It’s their secret sauce. They want to ensure that the farming experience they have had for many years is one of the ingredients for future success. By using AI models that produce recommendations in discrete parts of the process – fertilization, irrigation, crop protection, and variety selection – farmers can start to adopt digital decision-support models in a non-interrupting way. The AI models can be tested, and farmers can build confidence in the systems’ recommendations. Feedback loops and continuous improvement are another crucial success factor.</p>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div data-valign="middle">What’s needed: a deliberate, incremental, iterative approach that brings data to agriculture in ways that mirror farmers’ experiences.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>At the Royal Swatini Sugar Corporation (RES) based in the Swazi nation in southern Africa, executives have made real progress in adopting new precision agriculture systems. The 4,500-employee company produces as much as <a href="https://www.res.co.sz/admin/documents/RES%20integratd%20report%202022.pdf">470,00 metric tons</a> of sugar per season for use in ethanol, fertilizer products, and beverages to customers in Africa, Europe, and Asia. It manages approximately 24,450 hectares (more than 60,000 acres) of irrigated sugarcane fields, which include both its farms and partnerships with smaller third-party growers.</p>
  <p>As RES worked to deploy systems to manage farm and field data more consistently to automate tasks and improve decision-making, including the third-party growers was a major focus. In 2023, the company cited numerous benefits from the data-driven farming solutions: a marked improvement in farmers’ ability to plan, implement, and measure the progress of key tasks. It also provides a better understanding for growers about the right time to harvest and higher grower yields.</p>
  <p>The acceptance of the new systems has been vital to improving operations, says Rob Coombe, Group IT manager at RES. “As well as giving us insights into their crop, it lets us learn when is the best time to harvest,” Coombe says in a short <a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2023/05/96a400eb-737e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">video</a> about the company’s efforts. “It’s going to be a key component of our business going forward as it helps us to be more sustainable and efficient on the farm.”</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1cdad9aafb436a68adcd2279e4215bbec6943a751.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1cdad9aafb436a68adcd2279e4215bbec6943a751.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1cdad9aafb436a68adcd2279e4215bbec6943a751.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="White hands holding a computer tablet showing an image of the sugar cane in front of the tablet. A virtual reality image overlays the person’s hands and the tablet, showing real-time plant data." src="./media_1cdad9aafb436a68adcd2279e4215bbec6943a751.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="standardizing-the-use-of-data">Standardizing the use of data</h2>
  <p>The second challenge facing agribusiness companies – collecting and managing the right data so that decision-support models are accurate and valuable – is tied to the first. Getting farmers to trust what systems tell them starts with having good data.</p>
  <p>Today, agribusiness companies are faced with an increasing amount of data collected from the field. But there is often a lack of standard processes and data management practices to make efficient use of that data, so it helps farmers improve their processes.</p>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div data-valign="middle">In the future, we will get more and more data from the fields. This will help our farming customers to optimize the input from fertilizers, water, and crop protection so that they can work as sustainable as possible.</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div data-valign="middle">Jens Hittmeyer, head of global IT and CIO, KWS</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>At KWS, a Germany-based producer of seeds for farmers around the world cultivating crops like corn, sugar beet, cereals, rapeseed, sunflowers, and soybeans, investments in systems to track conditions on the ground and then use that data to improve productivity and quality have been a priority in recent years. The company, the world’s fourth-largest seed producer, has been in business since 1856.</p>
  <p>KWS <a href="https://www.kws.com/us/en/company/press/world-of-farming/how-farmers-benefit-from-drones-in-plant-breeding/">applies</a> analytics to aerial photos of fields to speed up the collection and analysis of data to detect factors such as fungal infestation, soil conditions (such as moisture), and chlorophyll levels. The analysis is not only more efficient but more accurate than the human eye test.</p>
  <p>Jens Hittmeyer, head of global IT and CIO at KWS, <a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2023/05/8c8100eb-737e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">says</a> plans call for digitizing the company’s entire logistics value chain – from field to plant and then to backend systems.</p>
  <p>“In the future, we will get more and more data from the fields. This will help our farming customers to optimize the input from fertilizers, water, and crop protection so that they can work as sustainable as possible,” he says.</p>
  <p>Think again about that ice cream cone (or other favorite food) that you enjoy. It takes a lot of resources to make up the ingredients – even before it gets to the people who prepare them for consumption. With a growing population and a warming planet, every seed, every plant, and every ounce of water and fertilizer is crucial. Data can make a difference. But only if the farmers who can use that data to their advantage trust what they see in an analytics readout as much as they are accustomed to trusting what they see happening on their farms. This is not just any farms, but <em>their</em> farms. Industrious farmers will yield the fruit of this data harvest.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>core-topic/environmental-compliance</category>
            <category>content-type/what-is</category>
            <category>stage/acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Why DEI Backlash Exists and What to Do About It]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/why-dei-backlash-exists</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/why-dei-backlash-exists</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn why clear, ongoing, two-way communication is the foundation for truly inclusive diversity and DEI programs that yield business payoff.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/what-is</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>stage/acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Supply chain digital transformation: Look to the cloud]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/supply-chain-digital-transformation-cloud</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/supply-chain-digital-transformation-cloud</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[For better supply chain visibility and innovation, the best businesses optimize their supply chain operations in the cloud. Find out how supply chain digital transformation can work for you.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>topic/business-transformation</category>
            <category>content-type/what-is</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Compensating Sales for Consumption-Based Pricing]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/compensating-sales-for-consumption-based-pricing</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/compensating-sales-for-consumption-based-pricing</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Five key questions for CEOs, CFOs, and sales VPs to make the switch to consumption-based pricing models a success for your staff and customers.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/what-is</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>stage/acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[What are the Benefits of a Vendor Management System?]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/benefits-vendor-management-system</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/benefits-vendor-management-system</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Explore the benefits of a VMS, or vendor management system, to automate your external workforce processes, build a more agile workforce, and more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/what-is</category>
            <category>stage/acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Learning in the Flow of Work: A More Engaging Learner Experience]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/learning-in-the-flow-of-work</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/learning-in-the-flow-of-work</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learning in the flow of work seamlessly incorporates learning into employees’ workdays through an LMS – boosting employee engagement and productivity.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>content-type/what-is</category>
            <category>stage/acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[What is Contingency Planning?]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/contingency-planning</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/contingency-planning</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Creating an emergency-response framework results in retaining a healthy, motivated, dedicated workforce during crises – and better business after.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/business-transformation</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/what-is</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>stage/acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Workforce Management & Organizational Charts: Past, Present, & Future]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/organizational-charts-digitalization-and-workforce-management-past-present-and-future</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/organizational-charts-digitalization-and-workforce-management-past-present-and-future</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Explore why the hierarchical organizational chart is no longer an effective way to guide workforce management decisions in a digitalized world.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>topic/business-transformation</category>
            <category>content-type/what-is</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How HR Can Direct Use of AI and ChatGPT]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/how-hr-can-direct-use-of-ai</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/how-hr-can-direct-use-of-ai</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn why as adoption of AI spreads, HR has an opportunity to shape how it is used to benefit the business and its employees.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>core-topic/responsible-ai</category>
            <category>content-type/what-is</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>stage/acquisition</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>