<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/topic/hcm/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP SuccessFactors Accelerates AI Capabilities in HR to Make Every Employee a Success Story]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-successfactors-accelerates-ai-capabilities</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-successfactors-accelerates-ai-capabilities</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Announced at SAP Sapphire Orlando, SAP SuccessFactors streamlines HR operations with AI-enabled capabilities for a new way of working.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors-hcm-suite</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP's New AI Innovations and Partnerships Deliver Real-World Results]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/ai-innovations-partnerships-sap-sapphire</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/ai-innovations-partnerships-sap-sapphire</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Explore the AI capabilities and ecosystem innovations presented at SAP Sapphire in 2024, all aimed at delivering real-world results.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>news-topic/financial-management</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/abap-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/accenture</category>
            <category>news-tag/ai-ethics</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/aws</category>
            <category>news-tag/bcg</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP SuccessFactors Partners Recognized for Outstanding Achievements]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/sap-successfactors-partners-recognized-for-achievements</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/sap-successfactors-partners-recognized-for-achievements</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP SuccessFactors partners received SAP Global Line of Business Partner Excellence Awards for 2024. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>sap-award/sap-global-lob-partner-excellence-awards</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Kyndryl Adopts Next-Generation Tools for Sales Performance Management]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/kyndryl-adopts-tools-for-sales-performance-management</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/kyndryl-adopts-tools-for-sales-performance-management</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Kyndryl adopted SAP SuccessFactors sales performance management solutions to streamline compensation and territory and quota management.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/sales-performance-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Case for Pay Transparency]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/the-case-for-pay-transparency</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/the-case-for-pay-transparency</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Author and academic Jake Rosenfeld explodes our fondest beliefs about compensation, especially that employees are paid their worth.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10f00a4c6b9f3c2e482a9a639ba5a8ab676d36d6a.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10f00a4c6b9f3c2e482a9a639ba5a8ab676d36d6a.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_10f00a4c6b9f3c2e482a9a639ba5a8ab676d36d6a.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Two business people sitting at a desk in an office talking to each other." src="./media_10f00a4c6b9f3c2e482a9a639ba5a8ab676d36d6a.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1044">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="the-case-for-pay-transparency">The Case for Pay Transparency</h1>
        <p>Author and academic Jake Rosenfeld explodes our fondest beliefs about compensation, especially that employees are paid their worth.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The setting of pay rates – why exactly people make the amount they do – is shrouded in mystery. Ever was it thus. Companies have never wanted to shine a bright light on employees’ paychecks nor delve too deeply into what they should pay.</p>
  <p>Few employees are willing to enter a frank discussion about the digits on their checks, either. It’s one of the most enduring taboos of corporate life.</p>
  <p>Everyone has their reasons. Employers face too many imponderables – it’s hard to figure out what most employees contribute to corporate coffers – and transparency could open all kinds of cans of worms. Many people would rather not know how they are valued compared to their peers, considering how much our jobs and pay rate underpin our identities.</p>
  <p>But the result, says Jake Rosenfeld, author, and sociology professor at Washington University in St. Louis, is an often unequal playing field. Most pay rates are based on history – the pay rate a company has offered in the past, plus employees’ previous earnings – and market rates. Few other factors come into play.</p>
  <p>In his book <a href="https://www.amazon.com/Youre-Paid-What-Worth-Economy-ebook/dp/B08TJ6J2H8/ref=sr_1_1?crid=PF9EWWA3QX50&#x26;dib=eyJ2IjoiMSJ9.K1WecBmDbRyHHZ0vOmYBCDEX47nNY_4iULlY-0rf4gsiw-NWo6-E1_zuly-kbtQLHDZoZNdQ7lHEYq0dhpycP4UdbXk0UbZ5qITucc72cDY310w6CerWhji676HMoGlglAYWmCJwOCdyujtCKBJDU0xueCz40s5ljymEyWTc9ncW1BNCAVRaT7uXMXgxQ0UtS6zoYGgwBn1-FAKwBhJ9zJr2ZlY4VPuc2kSi34uONIA.VvHlHxX6tUUdKfWZgP_czhx5YSsbSg9icjfHbGspKG4&#x26;dib_tag=se&#x26;keywords=you%27re+paid+what+you%27re+worth&#x26;qid=1711487199&#x26;sprefix=you%27re+paid+%2Caps%2C506&#x26;sr=8-1">You’re Paid What You’re Worth: And Other Myths of the Modern Economy</a>, Rosenfeld blows the doors off the vault of stubborn but unfounded beliefs that underlie our notion of employee compensation.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14a9e86e0f052a504889ced35e43c015b1a7342e5.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14a9e86e0f052a504889ced35e43c015b1a7342e5.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_14a9e86e0f052a504889ced35e43c015b1a7342e5.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Image of Jake Rosenfeld" src="./media_14a9e86e0f052a504889ced35e43c015b1a7342e5.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2740" height="1541">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p><em>Jake Rosenfeld, author of You’re Paid What You’re Worth: And Other Myths of the Modern Economy.</em></p>
  <p>We asked Rosenfeld about the most persistent myths associated with employee compensation, why they are so enduring (and harmful), and what it will take for employers to do better.</p>
  <p>Spoiler alert: There is no magic formula.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1db86572a7958b83644355876a24c89bfc828cf38.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1db86572a7958b83644355876a24c89bfc828cf38.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1db86572a7958b83644355876a24c89bfc828cf38.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Man taking a photo of a check with his cell phone." src="./media_1db86572a7958b83644355876a24c89bfc828cf38.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="sap-insights-in-your-book-you-discuss-pay-transparency-in-depth-giving-the-history-of-the-topic-and-why-both-bosses-and-workers-traditionally-have-avoided-it-but-its-documented-that-pay-opacity-leads-to-unfairness-how-come-this-is-such-a-thorny-issue">SAP Insights: In your book, you discuss pay transparency in depth, giving the history of the topic and why both bosses and workers traditionally have avoided it. But it’s documented that pay opacity leads to unfairness. How come this is such a thorny issue?</h2>
  <p><strong>Jake Rosenfeld:</strong> I'm absolutely fascinated by the salary taboo. It’s taken for granted in the academic literature that we have a reluctance to discuss pay. There are exceptions like Norway, where you can look up everyone’s tax returns to see what they made. But elsewhere, there seems to be something fundamental about our unwillingness to disclose our pay.</p>
  <p>That said, it does seem to be changing, especially among younger workers. They're much more willing to share their wages and salaries. This taboo could be crumbling underneath our feet.</p>
  <h2 id="q-is-that-due-to-a-difference-in-orientation-and-temperament-with-younger-people-or-do-you-think-younger-workers-know-talking-about-salaries-will-help-decrease-unfair-wages">Q: Is that due to a difference in orientation and temperament with younger people? Or do you think younger workers know talking about salaries will help decrease unfair wages?</h2>
  <p><strong>Rosenfeld:</strong> People are beginning to understand it's important to share and gather as much information as they can to make sure that they're getting what they think they deserve. I also take seriously the idea that as younger generations grow into their prime earning years, the reluctance to share may come back.</p>
  <p>But I also wouldn't be surprised if the ground is shifting. Many U.S. states are passing laws requiring disclosure of pay ranges for recruitment purposes. The topic has captured media attention, too. Word has gotten out that you should be much less reluctant to talk about pay because you may be getting underpaid and not know it.</p>
  <h2 id="q-as-you-write-employees-have-tended-to-be-reluctant-to-discuss-pay-because-they-dont-want-to-know-whether-their-pay-is-higher-or-lower-versus-their-colleagues-meanwhile-you-argue-that-bosses-dont-want-anyone-to-discuss-pay-to-keep-unfair-pay-structures-under-wraps-saving-the-organization-money-overall-their-interests-though-different-have-aligned-to-keep-pay-rates-secret">Q: As you write, employees have tended to be reluctant to discuss pay because they don’t want to know whether their pay is higher or lower versus their colleagues. Meanwhile, you argue that bosses don’t want anyone to discuss pay to keep unfair pay structures under wraps, saving the organization money overall. Their interests, though different, have aligned to keep pay rates secret.</h2>
  <p><strong>Rosenfeld:</strong> Absolutely. On the worker side, especially as you get into the upper-middle-class professions, our jobs are tied up with our sense of purpose and identity. People also tend to believe that our pay is ultimately tied to how well we're doing at work.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_172966442f9d1bad55e4b77140f60ff6ea8ede5a6.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_172966442f9d1bad55e4b77140f60ff6ea8ede5a6.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_172966442f9d1bad55e4b77140f60ff6ea8ede5a6.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Two serious-looking business people sitting at a table in an office, looking at data on a tablet." src="./media_172966442f9d1bad55e4b77140f60ff6ea8ede5a6.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="q-why-did-you-write-this-book-who-are-you-hoping-to-reach">Q: Why did you write this book? Who are you hoping to reach?</h2>
  <p><strong>Rosenfeld:</strong> Not many academics share my fascination with pay setting. But the more I dug in, the more I read case studies, the more I surveyed U.S. workers, the messier and more interesting it was. It quickly became clear the textbook models bear little resemblance to the real world of pay setting.</p>
  <p>Although I’m hoping to reach my colleagues in academia, business leaders have their own questions. I've talked to employers, and they tell me about feeling insecure when setting pay rates. They say they often feel they really don't know what they are doing when it comes to pay.</p>
  <p>I try to reassure them there's no exact science here. Everyone must deal with the messy, real phenomenon of trying to put a price on human labor. That's always going to be a challenge and will raise all sorts of thorny moral concerns.</p>
  <h2 id="q-at-the-beginning-of-your-book-you-sketch-out-four-dynamics-that-influence-how-and-what-people-are-paid-equity-or-fairness-mimicry-power-and-inertia-would-you-please-take-them-one-by-one-and-tell-us-what-concerns-you-about-them">Q: At the beginning of your book, you sketch out four dynamics that influence how and what people are paid: equity or fairness, mimicry, power, and inertia. Would you please take them one by one and tell us what concerns you about them?</h2>
  <p><strong>Rosenfeld:</strong> Let’s take fairness first. You're dealing with human beings, who often think they are underpaid. We all would like more money. And when you survey workers, very few say they’re overpaid.</p>
  <p>Employers have to be very delicate when approaching pay issues because they affect employee morale. But if they have a compensation structure they can defend openly, and explain why person X is making more than person Y, that generally goes a long way to engendering worker buy-in. Too often employers either don't have anything as organized as that, or they feel that if they share it, their employees won't support it. And that's where real issues can arise.</p>
  <p>Mimicry is paying the market rate, which is an understandable shortcut. But it means only that employers are surveying similar employers, finding out what they're doing, and making tiny adjustments to go a little above or a little below the average. It's easy to justify to workers: “Hey, we can't go that far above what our competitors are paying, because that will put us at a disadvantage.”</p>
  <p>Then there’s power. In the United States, power is held primarily with whoever pays. Workers have some power, but it differs according to their position in the organization, from the cleaning staff to the C-suite. They also come into the organization with different levels of power. That affects their ability to stake their claim for their share of revenue – that is, their wages and salaries. Their success will be based on where they're positioned and whether they have any other sources of power, such as a labor union.</p>
  <p>And the last factor is inertia. You do a job interview, and you're offered a starting wage or salary. It has a lot to do with what that company has been paying for that position for time immemorial. Sometimes it's the exact same rate they’ve paid for years because no one has the time to reevaluate every position every six months to decide what it should really be. There is no clear guidance for making that calculation, so inertia often takes hold. And then pay rates are taken for granted.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="strategies-for-managing-ai-disruption">Strategies for Managing AI Disruption</h3>
        <p>How HR leaders understand the changes AI brings and give employees a fair voice.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="/research/three-hr-strategies-for-managing-ai-disruption">Learn more</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="q-you-write-about-ceo-pay-and-how-disproportionate-it-has-gotten">Q: You write about CEO pay and how disproportionate it has gotten.</h2>
  <p><strong>Rosenfeld:</strong> There's vast literature showing only a very loose correlation between company performance and CEO pay – or none whatsoever.</p>
  <p>The idea that you have to pay at the top of the market to attract great talent presumes that you know what’s great. A lot of the time we don't know that. Meanwhile, CEOs have been able to bid up their collective pay because they are being hired from a kind of international market for floating CEOs, rather than being cultivated from inside the organization.</p>
  <p>When you ask American workers what they think the average ratio of CEO to worker pay is at a particular firm, respondents say something like 20 to one. When you ask what they think it should be, they say something like five or six to one.</p>
  <p>The reality is that overall, a CEO salary is roughly 400 times the average worker’s pay. That said, there doesn’t seem to be a movement to put real pressure on bringing down CEO pay. There are straightforward policies that could accomplish this, but there’s this question of whether the will is there.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f75594d2d1751e7b65c6c75922ed28dbeaed689a.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f75594d2d1751e7b65c6c75922ed28dbeaed689a.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1f75594d2d1751e7b65c6c75922ed28dbeaed689a.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Close-up image of a businessperson in a meeting room signing a contract." src="./media_1f75594d2d1751e7b65c6c75922ed28dbeaed689a.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="q-as-you-describe-it-the-explosion-of-ceo-pay-corresponds-with-the-rise-in-shareholder-capitalism-you-make-a-case-in-the-book-that-running-companies-for-the-benefit-of-shareholders-above-everyone-else-is-a-foe-of-equity-quality-and-safety-in-the-modern-world-including-that-it-induces-companies-to-pay-workers-as-little-as-they-can-get-away-with">Q: As you describe it, the explosion of CEO pay corresponds with the rise in shareholder capitalism. You make a case in the book that running companies for the benefit of shareholders above everyone else is a foe of equity, quality, and safety in the modern world. Including that it induces companies to pay workers as little as they can get away with.</h2>
  <p><strong>Rosenfeld:</strong> There were justifiable reasons the system needed to get shaken up a bit, especially for climbing out of the malaise of the ’70s and ’80s. A lot of corporations were ruled by longtime CEOs. They were pretty unproductive, not innovating in any way, and often getting beaten by international competitors. Shareholders were rightfully upset and wanted to see some returns they weren't getting.</p>
  <p>It's just that this activist shareholder movement has a lot of perverse incentives that are doing a real disservice for the companies. For starters, shareholders often view pay increases for average workers warily since that’s money not being redistributed upward.</p>
  <p>In the last five to ten years, CEOs have been saying they're tired of it, because they are trading higher CEO pay for less control over what they can do at the company. They are beholden to what the shareholders are demanding – who often do everything they can to jack up short-term stock prices.</p>
  <p>There is a widespread belief that CEOs have a fiduciary duty to shareholders, but they don’t, formally. And they are stymied from implementing any investment plan that’s not going to pay off for years, where they invest in new facilities and train up the workforce.</p>
  <h2 id="q-in-your-view-what-will-be-the-likely-effect-of-ai-on-wages-ever-downward-pressure-for-those-that-are-lucky-to-retain-their-jobs">Q: In your view, what will be the likely effect of AI on wages? Ever downward pressure, for those that are lucky to retain their jobs?</h2>
  <p><strong>Rosenfeld:</strong> Technological innovations often get interpreted as the death knell of millions and millions of jobs. That’s yet to happen, right? We’re sitting at a 3.7% unemployment rate.</p>
  <p>There will be reshuffling, for sure. The question is whether the reshuffled workers will be able to land in equal, or even possibly more highly paid positions. The extent to which that happens is often due to policy decisions that can be made to cushion the impact of technological innovations. The United States often takes none of those choices. The job retraining policies here are really skimpy, but other countries do it differently.</p>
  <h2 id="q-what-do-you-want-senior-business-leaders-to-do-about-pay">Q: What do you want senior business leaders to do about pay?</h2>
  <p><strong>Rosenfeld:</strong> It goes back to transparency. There’s more and more evidence that in the American economy today that workers are generally satisfied with their jobs and trust their bosses. Employers should take advantage of that and share their compensation strategy.</p>
  <p>I see in my own industry, academia, how everyone feels like they're underpaid. And universities are so deeply reluctant to give even one sentence about “here's how pay is determined here.” That just engenders ill will and distrust, because we then personalize everything: “Oh, my employer doesn't like me, doesn't see the value in my work.” We can see the same dynamic at work in every industry.</p>
  <p>Another point: we're in this wave of unionization efforts. But we are seeing kind of a ferocious pushback on the part of employers. I get that in an environment where few of your competitors are unionized, you could be terrified that if your company goes union, you're going to be at a competitive disadvantage. That said, the pushback has its own set of <a href="https://jacobin.com/2024/02/starbucks-workers-united-master-contract-bargaining">negative consequences</a>.</p>
  <p>I have a perhaps naïve hope for this country and the corporate class going forward that there's a way to carve out much more cooperative labor-management relationships where unionization efforts won't be fought to the death and won't be seen as the end of the firm. Because we know from the cross-national picture and from our own history that, in many cases, need not be the case. And higher wages for the average worker will be the welcome result.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/expert-opinions</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[AI-Enabled Recruitment Is the Name of the Game for FC Bayern with SAP SuccessFactors]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/fc-bayern-sap-successfactors-ai-enabled-recruitment</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/fc-bayern-sap-successfactors-ai-enabled-recruitment</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[FC Bayern is leveraging the SAP SuccessFactors HCM suite and SAP Business AI capabilities to drive excellence on and off the pitch.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>industry/media: industry/sports-entertainment</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>industry/sports-entertainment</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Growing Your Business Begins with Growing Your People]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/growing-your-business-begins-with-growing-your-people</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/growing-your-business-begins-with-growing-your-people</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[An Oxford Economics study, sponsored by SAP, reveals how to optimizing talent management with best practices for HR and IT. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/sme</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors-hcm-suite</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-learning</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-opportunity-marketplace</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-performance-goals</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-recruiting</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Meeting Workout: A Game to Improve the Meeting Experience]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/meeting-workout-game-to-improve-meeting-experience</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/meeting-workout-game-to-improve-meeting-experience</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[To address the challenge of unproductive meetings, SAP's Future of Work team and SAP AppHaus created the Meeting Workout board game.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-engagement</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/future-of-work</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-apphaus</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP SuccessFactors Takes Home 12 Top Rated Awards from TrustRadius]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/sap-successfactors-12-top-rated-awards-from-trustradius</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/sap-successfactors-12-top-rated-awards-from-trustradius</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[TrustRadius has recognized SAP SuccessFactors with 12 Top Rated awards in 2024. Read to learn more about the recognition.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a157e78734853652179498700d8b366ba88f70cd.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a157e78734853652179498700d8b366ba88f70cd.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1a157e78734853652179498700d8b366ba88f70cd.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP SuccessFactors Takes Home 12 Top Rated Awards from TrustRadius" src="./media_1a157e78734853652179498700d8b366ba88f70cd.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-successfactors-takes-home-12-top-rated-awards-from-trustradius">SAP SuccessFactors Takes Home 12 Top Rated Awards from TrustRadius</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>SAP SuccessFactors has once again been recognized as a leader in human resources software by <a href="https://auth.trustradius.com/login?state=hKFo2SAxeFdmN3FRNFYweERQdWtYOUNrZlBpbXFSZE9QbXZRWqFupWxvZ2luo3RpZNkgVk5pZ3luZ0ZsZ1hGZVFvQjFzRVUwakNMZzlvOXRHTGmjY2lk2SAxQm41NHNobVlWMmpFbE5qZ1NZb2dKNHZWeHZBT3hhSw&#x26;client=1Bn54shmYV2jElNjgSYogJ4vVxvAOxaK&#x26;protocol=oauth2&#x26;prompt=login&#x26;scope=openid%20profile%20email&#x26;response_type=code&#x26;redirect_uri=https%3A%2F%2Ftrustradius.com%2Fapi%2Fauth%2Fcallback&#x26;login_hint=&#x26;customParams=%7B%22visitorId%22%3A%22662c047f7334ebca8f8661aa%22%2C%22visitId%22%3A%2266311414bf33ad1060cf30ff%22%2C%22returnTo%22%3A%22%2Freviews%2Fnew%22%7D&#x26;allow_signup=true&#x26;nonce=hYwbKE36k0mTMvPhuGwjobXr7VnrKjlPTnVy0Kbn5sQ&#x26;code_challenge_method=S256&#x26;code_challenge=0aAJd5l2mbjUn1d0SW7Qvrv5DkDvBp6W-0szabD3FVQ">TrustRadius</a>, earning 12 Top Rated awards in 2024. TrustRadius is a peer research and review platform designed to help business leaders find and select the right software to meet their needs.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“At TrustRadius, we pride ourselves on providing unbiased and transparent insights into the software industry,” said Allyson Havener, senior vice president of Marketing and Community at TrustRadius. “Receiving a TrustRadius Top Rated award is a testament to SAP SuccessFactors HCM’s exceptional performance as validated by unbiased user feedback. This recognition highlights SAP SuccessFactors’ commitment to delivering innovative human capital management solutions that truly meet the needs of businesses.”</p>
  <p>This year, <a href="/topics/human-resources">SAP SuccessFactors</a> earned awards across the following categories: Applicant Tracking, Compensation Management, Talent Management, Workforce Analytics, Sales Incentive Compensation Management, HR Management, Workforce Management, Employee Performance Management, Sales Performance Management, Corporate Learning Management, Succession Planning, and Internal Payroll.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="adopt-the-latest-in-hr-innovation-with-sap-successfactors-hcm">Adopt the latest in HR innovation with SAP SuccessFactors HCM</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>We are grateful to our more than 10,000 global customers whose partnership allows us to help make every employee a success story by harnessing the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/human-resources.html">power of AI</a> to elevate every experience, guide every people decision, and connect HR across every aspect of the business.</p>
  <p>In the past year, SAP has introduced new AI capabilities that span the entire SAP SuccessFactors HCM suite and help transform how organizations unlock individual and collective potential. <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/ai-joule-product-tour.html">Joule</a>, SAP’s natural language generative AI copilot, helps employees and managers work faster and smarter by making it easier to find information and complete common HR tasks. With an embedded AI-driven skills framework, SAP SuccessFactors solutions help power an organization’s learning and talent strategy and address critical skills gaps. The combined force of these innovations helps customers better meet the business challenges of today and tomorrow.</p>
  <p>Below are a few reviews from our customers:</p>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div>We chose SAP SuccessFactors over competitors for its comprehensive HR suite, superior integration capabilities with SAP systems, and global scalability. Its user-friendly interface and extensive analytics stood out, <strong>offering more in-depth insights and a seamless experience compared to other solutions in the market</strong>.</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div><a href="https://www.trustradius.com/reviews/sap-successfactors-2023-12-15-07-43-30">Solution Architect, Barclays</a></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div>“<strong>The benefit of [SAP] SuccessFactors is its flexibility</strong>. I have implemented [SAP] SuccessFactors at companies with as little as 1,500 employees and also with as many as 120,000 users. It can handle the complexities of global requirements while still being able to scale to a small, midsized business in a cost-effective manner.”​</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div><a href="https://www.trustradius.com/reviews/sap-successfactors-2023-10-16-10-44-42">HRIS Manager, Great Lakes Cheese</a></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div>“SAP SuccessFactors has a clean employee view of data and offers a wide range of functionality to <strong>support midsize to large companies</strong>.”​</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div><a href="https://www.trustradius.com/reviews/sap-successfactors-2023-10-21-10-48-58">Software Engineer, John Deere</a></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Learn more about <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm.html?url_id=ctabutton-us-hcm-trustradius-freetrial">SAP SuccessFactors HCM</a> and read our customer reviews on <a href="https://www.trustradius.com/products/sap-successfactors/reviews">TrustRadius</a>. For more information about these recognitions, visit the <a href="https://www.trustradius.com/static/about-trustradius-scoring">TrustRadius scoring FAQ page</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Aaron Green is chief marketing &#x26; solutions officer for SAP SuccessFactors.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors-hcm-suite</category>
            <category>news-tag/trustradius</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Close the Labor Gap with Socially Conscious Hiring]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/close-the-labor-gap-with-socially-conscious-hiring</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/close-the-labor-gap-with-socially-conscious-hiring</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Turn random acts of social good into programs that benefit marginalized workers, their communities, and the business itself]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f04c09c36bcc5fddd8e1cb43a7c965a5d71b13a5.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f04c09c36bcc5fddd8e1cb43a7c965a5d71b13a5.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1f04c09c36bcc5fddd8e1cb43a7c965a5d71b13a5.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Diverse group of employees standing arm in arm in an office hallway" src="./media_1f04c09c36bcc5fddd8e1cb43a7c965a5d71b13a5.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1044">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="close-the-labor-gap-with-socially-conscious-hiring">Close the Labor Gap with Socially Conscious Hiring</h1>
        <p>Turn random acts of social good into programs that benefit marginalized workers, their communities, and the business itself.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Throughout the world, countries are struggling with an acute labor shortage that shows no sign of abating. In the United States, a smaller workforce will be the key economic challenge of the foreseeable future, according to the <a href="https://www.uschamber.com/economy/what-to-expect-from-the-economy-in-2024#:~:text=Curtis%20Dubay&#x26;text=A%20smaller%20workforce%20will%20define,that%20can%20support%20their%20spending.">U.S. Chamber of Commerce</a>. The numbers are daunting: Even if every unemployed worker today were to fill an open job in their respective industry, the organization says, there would still be millions of unfilled positions.</p>
  <p>But what if businesses redefined the labor pool itself? Doing so would mean looking beyond the ranks of the statistically employed and unemployed. Instead, businesses would tap into a less obvious but large group of people who are not participating in the formally recognized labor market. Many of these people would like to work but have been marginalized from the workforce for a variety of systemic or discriminatory reasons.</p>
  <p>This includes people from less-advantaged populations; individuals with a criminal record; people with physical, mental health, or developmental challenges; those with a history of substance abuse; and people with low educational attainment or without traditional qualifications.</p>
  <p>A study by <a href="https://www.hbs.edu/managing-the-future-of-work/Documents/research/hiddenworkers09032021.pdf">Harvard Business School</a> (HBS) estimates there are more than 27 million of these “hidden workers” in the United States, and similar proportions across the UK and Germany. “The sheer magnitude of this population reveals the potential impact that their substantial re-absorption into the workforce would have,” the study says.</p>
  <p>Many businesses have reached out to engage these populations through their corporate social responsibility (CSR) efforts. Such measures might include changing degree/educational attainment requirements for a small segment of jobs. Or businesses might hire two or three people with a physical or mental disability, or a criminal record, or who belong to an underrepresented population in the local community.</p>
  <p>But often, these are ad hoc measures that, while admirable, tend to fizzle out. Even if they do have some success, they may fail to grow or expand. As the HBR study points out, such isolated CSR efforts can “inherently reinforce the myth that hiring hidden workers is an act of charity or corporate citizenship, rather than a source of competitive advantage.”</p>
  <p>By taking a more purposeful approach with their hiring programs and other CSR-driven initiatives, organizations can transform random acts of corporate social responsibility into long-lasting, far-reaching, repeatable programs. These programs would benefit marginalized workers, the communities they live in, and the business itself.</p>
  <p>Such initiatives would need to address the needs of both the community and the business. They should involve agencies that deeply understand the specific needs of the demographic being hired. Additionally, they should provide wraparound services that go beyond the job. Vitally, these programs need to use data and technology to identify community needs, track the effects of initiatives and encourage uptake in other parts of the business. In other words, it’s not just about <em>doing</em> – it’s about doing with purpose and a goal in mind.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="managing-social-impact--the-s-in-esg">Managing social impact – the S in ESG</h3>
        <p>A complete guide to measuring and managing social impact.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="/resources/measuring-social-impact-s-in-esg">Dive in</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“There is a need, says Eric Eng, a college admission expert and the founder and CEO of <a href="https://admissionsight.com/">AdmissionSight</a>, “for companies to shift from piecemeal initiatives to systemic and strategic approaches that can truly impact underserved communities and build a stronger labor market.”</p>
  <p>By taking a more purposeful approach with their hiring programs and other CSR-driven initiatives, organizations can transform random acts of corporate social responsibility into long-lasting, far-reaching, repeatable programs. These programs would benefit marginalized workers, the communities they live in, and the business itself.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e2a750a701d40250060dbc25b71ca98b07f07ad9.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e2a750a701d40250060dbc25b71ca98b07f07ad9.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1e2a750a701d40250060dbc25b71ca98b07f07ad9.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="A diverse group of smiling businesspeople talking together during a meeting in an office boardroom" src="./media_1e2a750a701d40250060dbc25b71ca98b07f07ad9.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="from-isolated-acts-to-full-fledged-efforts">From isolated acts to full-fledged efforts</h2>
  <p>There are as many wrong ways to pursue a CSR hiring initiative as there are right ways. Often, these efforts are started by a passionate employee whose enthusiasm is a key part of what drives the program. But with that dependency, the program is apt to languish should the employee leave or lose interest.</p>
  <p>Initiatives also fail if their benefits – whether to the business or the community – go unrecognized. This can be due to a lack of rigor in measuring results or a failure to adequately match program elements to community or demographic needs.</p>
  <p>For instance, a study by workforce researcher <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/companies/starbucks-founder-howard-schultz-you-can-do-right-by-your-people-and-your-shareholders-at-the-same-time/ar-AA1kY8vg">The Burning Glass Institute</a> found that simply dropping degree requirements doesn’t significantly affect the hiring of people from diverse groups. The act of applying for a job, the organization says, is contingent not just on whether the individual has the required education credentials but also on whether they could imagine themselves working for a particular company or in a specific sector. This finding reinforces the importance of – beyond removing candidate qualifications – actively encouraging applicants who may never have considered themselves as potential employees.</p>
  <p>A company that has fully embraced socially conscious hiring is MOD Pizza, a fast-casual pizza brand founded by a husband-and-wife team (former owners of Seattle Coffee Company, later acquired by Starbucks). <a href="https://www.sfgate.com/news/article/Why-MOD-Pizza-Loves-Hiring-Ex-Cons-13205951.php">Their vision</a>: building a business with a positive social impact.</p>
  <p>Soon after opening, MOD Pizza embraced what’s known as impact hiring, including people with backgrounds of incarceration, homelessness, drug addiction, and intellectual and physical disabilities. It worked with local and national organizations to learn what these individuals needed to thrive on the job, from skill-building to financial assistance during a crisis. It then partnered with various nonprofits to encourage candidates to apply.</p>
  <p>Today, MOD Pizza credits its rapid growth largely to its hiring method. The business today has more than 2,500 employees, <a href="https://www.scrapehero.com/location-reports/Modpizza-USA/">over 550 locations</a> in the United States and Canada, and <a href="https://www.zippia.com/mod-pizza-careers-31728/revenue/">revenues of US$398 million</a>. Ninety-nine percent of company-owned MOD stores have hired people with employment barriers, <a href="https://news.sap.com/2023/09/mod-pizza-driving-positive-outcomes-investing-in-employees/#:~:text=Today%2C%2099%25%20of%20company%2D,retention%20rate%2C%E2%80%9D%20Eberhardt%20says.">according to Dayna Eberhardt</a>, chief people officer at the company, and these hiring practices have led to a more engaged and equitable workforce. These workers “have a higher sense of belonging, a faster rate of promotion, and a higher retention rate,” she says.</p>
  <h2 id="building-a-socially-conscious-hiring-program">Building a socially conscious hiring program</h2>
  <p>MOD Pizza offers several best practices for creating a socially conscious hiring method that benefits both marginalized workers and the business. Some of these core elements include the following:</p>
  <h3 id="match-efforts-to-the-needs-of-the-local-community">1. Match efforts to the needs of the local community</h3>
  <p>Businesses need to understand the specific barriers preventing people in the community from attaining stable employment. They can get these insights by mapping the company’s locations with external data sources that reveal challenges affecting nearby neighborhoods, such as a lack of public transportation, low graduation rates, poor access to healthcare, or limited housing affordability.</p>
  <p>Similarly, businesses can map the geographic location of where employees and job candidates tend to live to identify “applicant deserts” – areas in the community where the company has not historically hired, despite their proximity to their operations. Knowing this, businesses can increase their outreach and visibility in these areas.</p>
  <p>Romanita Matta-Barrera, Chief Workforce Officer for <a href="https://greatersatx.com/">greater:SATX</a>, an economic development partnership in San Antonio, Texas, is leading efforts to address the gap between available jobs and community members who could fill them – 56% of whom are Hispanic.</p>
  <p>“There are jobs available, and often employers wonder where the people are and, at the same time, we see a lot of individuals who have been systematically looking for jobs and have not had access,” she says. “So, we’ve taken a very serious, deep dive into how we can address this to meet not only the needs of our growing employers but to also ensure that our community and its members are being maximized.”</p>
  <p>The organization has worked with Accenture Federal Services, which has embarked on a program to recruit individuals with little to no IT experience from an area of the city with a high level of poverty and a low level of educational attainment. Accenture partnered with several workforce agency partners to identify potential employees and provide them with basic skills training. They also offered wraparound services to address issues like transportation and childcare.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_168db644370231078a951e04cc321e367c1167f1c.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_168db644370231078a951e04cc321e367c1167f1c.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_168db644370231078a951e04cc321e367c1167f1c.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Group of people at a bus stop" src="./media_168db644370231078a951e04cc321e367c1167f1c.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div data-valign="middle">Often employers wonder where the people are and, at the same time, we see a lot of individuals who have been systematically looking for jobs and have not had access.</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div data-valign="middle">Romanita Matta-Barrera, Chief Workforce Officer, greater:SATX</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Training is run similarly to an apprenticeship program, with candidates given three to six months of skill-building, which often leads to full employment, she says. Accenture also targeted a summer high school internship program in the same region to engage the youth population.</p>
  <p>As AdmissionSight’s Eng notes, “addressing systemic poverty and adverse childhood experiences requires a multifaceted approach.” It’s a way of thinking, he says, that “involves creating pathways to quality education and vocational training, ensuring that these are accessible to all individuals.”</p>
  <h3 id="match-efforts-to-business-needs">2. Match efforts to business needs</h3>
  <p>The actions companies take to address community barriers should ideally reflect what the company produces, the services it provides, and what employees are passionate about. This ensures not only that CSR initiatives are meaningful to the community but that they also resonate with the company’s core mission and values.</p>
  <p>Enter MOD Pizza, whose industry faces particularly acute hiring challenges. According to the <a href="https://www.restaurantdive.com/news/national-restaurant-association-job-growth-not-recession-likely-in-2023/643664/">National Restaurant Association</a>, 79% of restaurant operators report difficulty hiring, and 62% are understaffed. This is amid a monthly labor turnover in the hospitality and food service sector at 5.4%, which is twice the national average.</p>
  <p>Meanwhile, <a href="https://aspe.hhs.gov/topics/human-services/incarceration-reentry-0">more than 600,000 individuals</a> are released from prison each year in the United States, and <a href="https://www.prisonpolicy.org/blog/2022/02/08/employment/">60% of those with federal convictions are jobless</a>. Yet <a href="https://www.fair360.com/medialib/uploads/2016/09/Paulk-Presentation-Hiring-Ex-Offenders-09142016.pdf">multiple case studies</a> have shown this population of workers to exhibit high employee loyalty. MOD Pizza’s matchup of business and community needs is a win for both employer and employee.</p>
  <p>In San Antonio, meanwhile, Ernst &#x26; Young (EY) has become more innovative in its hiring process by tapping into the local pool of two-year college students. This matches EY’s specific business needs because – as Matta-Barrera points out – even if applicants had a four-year college degree, they would have to be retrained for EY’s system anyway. As part of the process, EY revamped its onboarding process and engaged its employee resource groups to ensure these new hires were not overwhelmed by entering a corporate environment.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_194e89449df2729abb70702953fc9701b20dcc70f.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_194e89449df2729abb70702953fc9701b20dcc70f.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_194e89449df2729abb70702953fc9701b20dcc70f.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="A businessperson is making a presentation for his colleagues, using a digital tablet and pointing to the board." src="./media_194e89449df2729abb70702953fc9701b20dcc70f.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p>The actions companies take to address community barriers should ideally reflect what the company produces, the services it provides, and what employees are passionate about.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="benefits-of-having-neurodiverse-workers">Benefits of having neurodiverse workers</h3>
        <p>Unlock the potential of neurodiverse workers with the right hiring approach.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="/resources/the-win-win-potential-of-hiring-neurodiverse-workers">Learn more</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="go-beyond-the-job-to-provide-wraparound-services">3. Go beyond the job to provide wraparound services</h3>
  <p>Businesses soon discover that socially conscious hiring extends far beyond offering a job. It also means providing additional supports that are specific to the demographic. For instance, one manufacturer that wanted to increase local hiring learned that many potential applicants did not have reliable transportation to the jobsite. The company worked with employees to become qualified ride-share drivers and provided them with a company car to give these new hires a ride to work.</p>
  <p>In another case, when an automotive supplier began hiring people who were homeless to work at the company, it realized it needed to provide these workers with new shoes.</p>
  <p>Jeffrey Korzenik, economist and author of <em>Untapped Talent: How Second Chance Hiring Works for Your Business and the Community,</em> emphasizes the need for combining quality candidates with cost-effective support systems. <a href="https://hbr.org/2022/10/how-employers-can-set-formerly-incarcerated-workers-up-for-success">In a recent article</a>, he says the most advanced practitioners of what he calls the “second-chance model” of hiring provide social workers, “navigators,” psychologists, or life coaches to these employees. For example, he says, U.S. Rubber Recycling employs a psychiatric rehabilitation counselor, and Nehemiah Manufacturing uses social workers instead of HR professionals.</p>
  <p>One manufacturer that wanted to increase local hiring learned that many potential applicants did not have reliable transportation to the jobsite. The company worked with employees to become qualified ride-share drivers and provided them with a company car to give these new hires a ride to work.</p>
  <p>Businesses should work with local agencies, nonprofits, and community organizations that are already supporting the hiring demographic. These organizations understand these individuals’ most pressing issues and the most effective interventions. As the HBR report says, groups like these have credibility with the workers and understand their needs. “Partnering with such groups helps companies develop, launch, and refine a program to make hidden workers integral to their talent management programs,” the report says.</p>
  <p>When Toyotetsu Texas, a supplier to Toyota Motor Manufacturing Texas’s San Antonio plant, began hiring individuals with intellectual and physical disabilities, it partnered with the Texas Workforce Commission’s Vocational Rehabilitation Services agency, which provides wraparound services to these individuals. The company also created internal job coaches and mentors, and provided plant tours and hands-on experiences to help potential employees determine whether the environment would be a good fit for them.</p>
  <p>“These are individuals who have the competencies to work well in this type of environment with the right internal processes such as mentorship coaching and other accommodations,” Matta-Barrera says.</p>
  <h3 id="measure-success-and-scale">4. Measure success and scale</h3>
  <p>Lastly – but also essentially – businesses need to understand the effect their programs are having in order to sustain and grow these efforts. Too often, the program becomes a line item with a cost assigned to it and no measure of the value it’s providing.</p>
  <p>Businesses should collect data such as the number of individuals hired through these programs, their retention rates, and their progression within the company, and pull it together into a dashboard for quick and easy access.</p>
  <p>Data collection is something MOD Pizza has been intentional about doing. For all of 2022 and into early 2023, employees with justice involvement were promoted at a rate 1.2% greater than the company baseline, <a href="https://flaggerforce.com/blog/industry-interview-with-mod-pizza/">says Robin Hamm, MOD Pizza’s vice president of social impact.</a> Some of these employees hold leadership positions in the company’s stores and support centers. Some also serve as general managers, district managers, and regional directors. And in an industry with staggering attrition rates, these employees were also retained at a rate 6% greater than the company baseline.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d724f8eb4b3bedea8080c9b894ac7dbd1d7c01e0.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d724f8eb4b3bedea8080c9b894ac7dbd1d7c01e0.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1d724f8eb4b3bedea8080c9b894ac7dbd1d7c01e0.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Three coworkers reviewing data on a laptop in an office." src="./media_1d724f8eb4b3bedea8080c9b894ac7dbd1d7c01e0.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1493" height="1120">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p>Dashboards can also help businesses share the details of successful CSR programs across different locations within the company so they can be replicated without reinventing the wheel – or making costly mistakes. For instance, if one business unit has established a program to donate used laptops to underserved students, other divisions could see what makes this program work well and set up similar programs in their communities.</p>
  <p>Businesses should collect data like the number of individuals hired through these programs, their retention rates, and their progression within the company, and pull it together into a dashboard for quick and easy access.</p>
  <p>These dashboards could work as a sort of recommendation engine if they’re populated with pre-vetted agencies and organizations to work with, or actions proven to support communities, based on the barriers to employment they help overcome, including transportation and mentorship programs, charitable giving, and educational and employment opportunity programs.</p>
  <p>Beyond the business itself, organizations should also measure how their efforts are affecting the community overall. Even if it’s not a direct result, are rates of homelessness, graduation rates, Internet access, or poverty levels rising or falling?</p>
  <p>For instance, <a href="https://stories.starbucks.com/uploads/2023/05/2022-Starbucks-Global-Environmental-Social-Impact-Report.pdf">the Burning Glass Institute</a> conducted a project with Starbucks examining the effect of the company’s tuition assistance program on employees’ career trajectories after they left the company. What they learned: These employees often went on to increasingly successful careers that – over time – would strengthen the overall community by fueling economic growth and improving the standard of living for their own families.</p>
  <h2 id="a-new-way-of-hiring">A new way of hiring</h2>
  <p>When it comes to the labor shortage, the problem is not that there aren’t enough people – it’s that employers are not using the potential of the whole community. This is forcing organizations to rethink how they design their hiring programs so they can be more employable to more people.</p>
  <p>Going even further, they need to discover how they can help people coming from these communities who face challenges many employers cannot even imagine.</p>
  <p>By investing in efforts to aid marginalized workers, businesses can make use of formerly untapped labor resources, and by doing so, support their own growth, boost economic development in the community and, ultimately, elevate their brand reputation in the eyes of consumers, employees, and investors.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/what-is</category>
            <category>stage/acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Modernizing Benefits Enrollment to Boost Employee Satisfaction and Retention]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/modernizing-benefits-enrollment-boost-employee-satisfaction-retention</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/modernizing-benefits-enrollment-boost-employee-satisfaction-retention</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central Global Benefits empowers employees to take control of their benefits with an intuitive, guided experience.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1330c66286be6108050da7ab27c52e68fc719102b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1330c66286be6108050da7ab27c52e68fc719102b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1330c66286be6108050da7ab27c52e68fc719102b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Modernizing Benefits Enrollment to Boost Employee Satisfaction and Retention" src="./media_1330c66286be6108050da7ab27c52e68fc719102b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="modernizing-benefits-enrollment-to-boost-employee-satisfaction-and-retention">Modernizing Benefits Enrollment to Boost Employee Satisfaction and Retention</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Employee satisfaction is driven by more than paychecks and perks – it’s also about everyday work experiences. One often-overlooked aspect that can significantly impact how employees feel about their workplace is the benefits enrollment experience.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>A confusing benefits enrollment experience is a significant source of frustration for many employees and can leave them feeling uncertain about their benefits elections. The majority of employees struggle to understand their benefits options and navigate through the enrollment process.</p>
  <p>As a result, many employees choose to simply roll over their previous year’s elections rather than review and update their choices to ensure they are getting the most out of their benefits. This often leads to missed opportunities to take advantage of lower-cost options or benefits that are a better fit for them and their family and can even lead to increased attrition of top talent.</p>
  <p>With <a href="/2024/04/sap-successfactors-first-half-2024-release">the first half 2024 release</a>, updates to the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/employee-central-hris/features.html#benefits?url_id=ctabutton-us-hcm-EC-freetrial">SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central Global Benefits</a> solution can enable you to empower your employees to take control of their benefits with an intuitive guided enrollment experience.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="extend-your-benefits-capabilities-with-sap-successfactors">Extend your benefits capabilities with SAP SuccessFactors</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/employee-central-hris/features.html#benefits">Learn how</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="making-benefits-enrollment-more-seamless-simple-and-intuitive">Making Benefits Enrollment More Seamless, Simple, and Intuitive</h2>
  <p>The new benefits enrollment experience in <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/employee-central-hris/features.html#benefits?url_id=ctabutton-us-hcm-EC-freetrial">SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central Global Benefits</a> introduces a process-driven approach to benefits enrollment that helps simplify and streamline the activity. Available for insurance, savings plans, and pension benefit types, this new enrollment experience can enable employees to make better, more informed benefits choices without the unnecessary hurdles.</p>
  <p>Here are some key highlights:</p>
  <h3 id="guided-enrollment">Guided Enrollment</h3>
  <p>A step-by-step progression flow guides employees through the process, working to simplify navigation and helping them complete benefits enrollment. Real-time benefits eligibility updates help employees continually understand the choices and options available by presenting them with all the benefits for which they are eligible to enroll.</p>
  <h3 id="personalized-user-experience">Personalized User Experience</h3>
  <p>Customizable text and instructions enable a tailored enrollment experience aligned with organizational policies.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c17ad14f21e83c7450704c1afdf399c3a412c660.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c17ad14f21e83c7450704c1afdf399c3a412c660.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1c17ad14f21e83c7450704c1afdf399c3a412c660.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Screenshot of benefits enrollment welcome page in SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central Global Benefits" src="./media_1c17ad14f21e83c7450704c1afdf399c3a412c660.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="580">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>Benefits enrollment welcome page. Click to enlarge.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="flexible-framework">Flexible Framework</h3>
  <p>Benefits admins can now have more flexibility in designing the enrollment experience to meet their organization’s needs with a new framework that helps support the capture of life insurance guaranteed issue amounts, customizable terms and conditions, and enhanced localization capabilities.</p>
  <h3 id="anytime-anywhere-access">Anytime, Anywhere Access</h3>
  <p>Available on both desktop and the SAP SuccessFactors Mobile app, employees can complete benefits enrollment from any location using a mobile-friendly platform that helps ensure a seamless experience across devices.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c77980d26be6e40ac83dd9b643d8a7c3585a72b5.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c77980d26be6e40ac83dd9b643d8a7c3585a72b5.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1c77980d26be6e40ac83dd9b643d8a7c3585a72b5.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Screenshots of benefits enrollment on mobile device and desktop" src="./media_1c77980d26be6e40ac83dd9b643d8a7c3585a72b5.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="452">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>Benefits enrollment on a mobile device or desktop. Click to enlarge.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="employee-educational-resources">Employee Educational Resources</h3>
  <p>Simplified on-screen access to additional resources and information helps employees better understand their benefits and can promote more informed decision-making throughout the enrollment process.</p>
  <p>Side-by-side benefit plan comparisons of costs and plan details help employees assess their plan options and select the best-fit plan. Localizable instructional text on each page helps ensure that the benefits and enrollment processes are well understood. Additionally, flexible options for defining contribution amounts within the IRS limits can make it easier for employees to make decisions regarding savings plans and pension elections.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a34b6a531c49ffa414de06cd26af9eae0983046c.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a34b6a531c49ffa414de06cd26af9eae0983046c.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1a34b6a531c49ffa414de06cd26af9eae0983046c.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Screenshot showing flexible options for defining HSA contribution amount" src="./media_1a34b6a531c49ffa414de06cd26af9eae0983046c.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="601">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>Flexible options for defining HSA contribution amount. Click to enlarge.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="consolidated-benefits-enrollment-process">Consolidated Benefits Enrollment Process</h3>
  <p>Employees can complete all benefits-related tasks including reviewing and updating dependents, completing health declarations, enrolling in benefits, managing beneficiaries, and more through a single consolidated process, helping to improve employee engagement and satisfaction.</p>
  <p><a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2024/03/72d228c0-b77e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html?url_id=ctabutton-us-hcm-benefits-demo">Watch the demo</a> to learn more about the new enrollment experience in SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central Global Benefits.</p>
  <p>To learn about all the other innovations in the SAP SuccessFactors first half 2024 release, read the <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2024/04/300e8c6d-b77e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">release highlights brochure</a> and watch the <a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2024/04/8c907f14-b77e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">1H 2024 release highlights video</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Nicole Ramirez is senior director of Product Marketing at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-employee-central</category>
            <category>news-tag/ux</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Support Employee Caregivers to Boost Engagement, Loyalty]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/support-employee-caregivers-to-boost-engagement-loyalty</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/support-employee-caregivers-to-boost-engagement-loyalty</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[More than 70% of workers provide care to someone – burnout is just one result. Leading companies show how to help.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/what-is</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP SuccessFactors First Half 2024 Release: Make Every Employee a Success Story]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-successfactors-first-half-2024-release</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-successfactors-first-half-2024-release</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[To help take HR to the next level, the SAP SuccessFactors first half 2024 release delivers more than 250 features and enhancements.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_115cc4b7786cb688433caf45dec5bf248f041afdb.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_115cc4b7786cb688433caf45dec5bf248f041afdb.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_115cc4b7786cb688433caf45dec5bf248f041afdb.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP SuccessFactors First Half 2024 Release: Make Every Employee a Success Story" src="./media_115cc4b7786cb688433caf45dec5bf248f041afdb.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-successfactors-first-half-2024-release-make-every-employee-a-success-story">SAP SuccessFactors First Half 2024 Release: Make Every Employee a Success Story</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Success can take many forms. It’s achieving AI-driven results faster and smarter. It’s unlocking more meaningful and aspirational career development experiences. It’s empowering employees and managers through simple HR-related tasks in the flow of work, freeing up more productive time across the organization.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>And for you and your business, you can tell all those success stories – and more – with the SAP SuccessFactors HCM suite and our first half 2024 release.</p>
  <p>As your organization and employees begin to embrace AI, <a href="/topics/human-resources">HR</a> has the opportunity to drive new levels of employee productivity, engagement, and growth. SAP SuccessFactors HCM can give you everything you need – the global foundation, skills framework, people-first experiences, and purpose-built AI capabilities – to help take HR to the next level. With the SAP SuccessFactors first half 2024 release, we are delivering more than 250 innovative features and enhancements.</p>
  <h2 id="sap-business-ai">SAP Business AI</h2>
  <p>In 1H 2024, we are thrilled to introduce more than 25 new AI capabilities to enable better employee experiences and new levels of productivity.</p>
  <p>Among these capabilities include the ability for applicants to provide skills during the application process. This can enable recruiters to see a skills compatibility for each applicant based on matching the applicant’s skills and the job requisition, helping improve applicant screening and time to hire. Furthermore, personalization in SAP SuccessFactors Opportunity Marketplace is enhanced with new AI-driven recommendation categories, “Ignite Your Role” and “Reach Your Aspirations.” These guided experiences can enable employees to proactively take steps to reach their development goals.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e755ea739e2394a3bec10a53f644e2d9cd718123.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e755ea739e2394a3bec10a53f644e2d9cd718123.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1e755ea739e2394a3bec10a53f644e2d9cd718123.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Screenshot of the assisted screening and skills match capabilities" src="./media_1e755ea739e2394a3bec10a53f644e2d9cd718123.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="803" height="521">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>Assisted screening and skills match available in 1H 2024 release. Click to enlarge.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Generative AI continues to be embedded across the SAP SuccessFactors HCM suite, including new capabilities to help employees create ready-made performance and development goals and AI-assisted writing to help improve the quality, clarity, and conciseness of writing across a variety of areas within SAP SuccessFactors solutions.</p>
  <p>Further, with this release, insights based on an employee’s compensation and job history are available to help support managers in having effective and well-informed compensation discussions.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="the-ai-copilot-that-truly-understands-your-business">The AI copilot that truly understands your business</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/ai-assistant.html">Meet Joule</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>We have also added more than 15 new <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/ai-assistant.html">Joule</a> capabilities in this release to help both managers and employees get work done in a conversational way, such as creating or changing a position, creating spot awards, clocking in and out, and viewing pay statements as well as time capabilities like requesting time off, checking leave balances, and syncing holidays to Outlook calendars while managers can review and approve time off. Further, employees can now clock in and out using Joule, Microsoft Teams, or the SAP SuccessFactors Mobile app.</p>
  <h2 id="sap-successfactors-employee-central">SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central</h2>
  <p>We are excited to unveil two new people profile experiences – the profile preview and the spotlight view. The profile preview can provide a snapshot of key areas of the employee profile, including job, manager, location, and contact details, to quickly view and connect with others. Additionally, the spotlight view can showcase employee skills and competencies, mentoring and target roles, and other relevant personal and organizational information.</p>
  <p>We are also introducing a new org chart experience with a refreshed look and feel. Available on desktop and mobile, users can explore their organizational structure with improved expand and collapse capabilities, which helps provide full accessibility to an employee’s profile preview, with an option to open the new spotlight view.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b181ba5a94a8b936ff644a1c243245079ecbbab4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b181ba5a94a8b936ff644a1c243245079ecbbab4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1b181ba5a94a8b936ff644a1c243245079ecbbab4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Screenshot of the new org chart experience" src="./media_1b181ba5a94a8b936ff644a1c243245079ecbbab4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="576">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>The new org chart experience. Click to enlarge.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Customers can now automatically process new hires from SAP SuccessFactors Recruiting and SAP SuccessFactors Onboarding into SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central. This capability helps further reduce the time to hire, which is especially important with mass, seasonal, and high-volume hiring.</p>
  <h2 id="sap-successfactors-employee-central-global-benefits">SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central Global Benefits</h2>
  <p>With this release, we are pleased to introduce a new benefits enrollment experience for insurance, savings, and pension benefit types. Available on both desktop and mobile, the guided experience for benefits elections can give employees increased convenience with improved navigation and increased confidence with side-by-side plan comparisons and embedded instructional text. Additionally, employees can update dependent information and manage beneficiaries directly from the benefits enrollment process, which helps further streamline the enrollment experience.</p>
  <h2 id="sap-successfactors-time-tracking">SAP SuccessFactors Time Tracking</h2>
  <p>We are thrilled to share the launch of a new time sheet experience that integrates the latest version of My Timesheet in SAP S/4HANA with SAP SuccessFactors. Employees can now record time for payroll, as well as against activities and cost objects, from a single time sheet across applications. This helps organizations leverage real-time connectivity between HR and finance operations to keep track of employee activity and labor costs and to pay employees accurately and on time.</p>
  <p>Additionally, a new monthly calendar view for time sheets can give employees and managers a complete picture of recorded time over a month. Users can drill down into specific days and submit or approve time for pay periods beyond a week, such as biweekly or monthly.</p>
  <p>For managers, a new time approval center helps simplify approvals with a centralized dashboard highlighting anomalies for swift resolution. Managers can monitor team working hours effectively, helping to ensure accurate and timely payroll processing.</p>
  <h2 id="sap-successfactors-onboarding">SAP SuccessFactors Onboarding</h2>
  <p>With enhancements to the onboarding journey experience, new hires can now use the new Your Onboarding Checklist page to reference and complete all tasks – onboarding data collection, compliance tasks, additional onboarding tasks, and exploring the onboarding guide – from one place with a single view. Available for new hires, rehires, internal hires, and employees with global assignments, this improved experience can save time for onboarding participants while helping to ensure productivity from the start.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e12cd49909a64b18778552665ee0147fcacdc707.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e12cd49909a64b18778552665ee0147fcacdc707.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1e12cd49909a64b18778552665ee0147fcacdc707.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Screenshot of the new onboarding journey experience" src="./media_1e12cd49909a64b18778552665ee0147fcacdc707.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="576">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>The new onboarding journey experience. Click to enlarge.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>And that’s only a fraction of all the innovations we’re bringing to customers in 1H 2024. There’s much more in the release, including new and exciting updates in:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Generative AI and Joule capabilities</li>
    <li>SAP SuccessFactors Opportunity Marketplace</li>
    <li>SAP SuccessFactors Compensation</li>
    <li>SAP SuccessFactors Succession &#x26; Development</li>
    <li>SAP SuccessFactors Incentive Management</li>
    <li>SAP SuccessFactors Work Zone</li>
  </ul>
  <p>Read the <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2024/04/300e8c6d-b77e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">SAP SuccessFactors first half 2024 release highlights brochure</a> and watch the <a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2024/04/8c907f14-b77e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">1H 2024 release highlights video</a> to find out more.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Bianka Woelke is group vice president of Application Product Management at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-employee-central</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors-hcm-suite</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-onboarding</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-opportunity-marketplace</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-recruiting</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Building a Dynamic Organization with a Skills-Based Approach to Talent]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/building-dynamic-organization-skills-based-approach-to-talent</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/building-dynamic-organization-skills-based-approach-to-talent</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A skills-based approach to talent management can help organizations build a dynamic and resilient workforce. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/recruiting</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-learning</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-opportunity-marketplace</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-recruiting</category>
            <category>news-tag/talent-acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[7 Due Diligence Steps for the Four-Day Workweek]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/7-due-diligence-steps-for-the-four-day-workweek</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/7-due-diligence-steps-for-the-four-day-workweek</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[From employee visas to overtime requirements, ironing the devil out of these details will help you to avoid legal issues and hit your goals.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>stage/acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[GROW with SAP: Add-On Packages Expand the Value of Cloud ERP for Growing Businesses]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/grow-with-sap-add-on-packages-expand-cloud-erp-value</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/grow-with-sap-add-on-packages-expand-cloud-erp-value</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New GROW with SAP add-on packages strengthen financial and HR management practices to become strategic pillars for growth.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/financial-management</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/grow-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Who Really Runs Your Organization]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/who-really-runs-your-organization</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/who-really-runs-your-organization</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Organizational network analysis provides a data-based view into the informal interactions that make companies work.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1bee56882580d353aa873b9348fc4133202e579b5.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1bee56882580d353aa873b9348fc4133202e579b5.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1bee56882580d353aa873b9348fc4133202e579b5.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Magnifying glass on woman’s headshot among others in a yearbook-style layout." src="./media_1bee56882580d353aa873b9348fc4133202e579b5.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1044">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="who-really-runs-your-organization">Who Really Runs Your Organization</h1>
        <p>Organizational network analysis provides a data-based view into the informal interactions that make companies work.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Large companies with geographically dispersed workforces, an ongoing need for the best talent, and the desire to have an adaptive collaborative organization are finding a decades-old academic instrument – organizational network analysis (ONA) – has fresh relevance. ONA, a technique originated by sociologists, maps the informal networks that play just as crucial a role as formal organizational charts in shaping employee experiences, delivering business benefits, and improving operational efficiencies.</p>
  <p>Analyzing how people work together, the networks they form to get work done, make decisions, and act on them, reveals how organizations really operate. And it’s typically not the command-and-control structures that leaders have drawn up.</p>
  <p>For decades, companies have relied on static organizational charts to clarify roles, improve communication, and streamline decision-making. “Julius Caesar organized his army into commanders and lieutenants – a hierarchy that is basically how employees work today,” says Maya Bodan, leader of the organization strategy and design talent group for Deloitte LLP in San Francisco, California.</p>
  <p>ONA is a tool for creating visual representations of how communications, information, and decisions flow through an organization using data from employee surveys, enterprise systems, and other sources. Unlike an organizational chart’s breakdown structure, ONA provides “an x-ray” into how a company actually works by “mapping patterns of connectivity and collaboration inside the organization,” says Rob Cross, an expert on ONA and SVP of research at the Institute for Corporate Productivity.</p>
  <p>By making strategically important individuals visible, the analysis sheds light on informal relationships and invisible patterns, providing deep insight into how information flows, the identity of key influencers, and the existence of silos that can lead to bottlenecks. This has never been more important – or more possible – than in today’s geographically dispersed employees working together using virtual collaboration tools.</p>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div data-valign="middle">A very small set of people have a disproportionate impact on how work gets done.</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div data-valign="middle">Rob Cross, SVP of research, Institute for Corporate Productivity</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Experts describe how the results of an organizational analysis highlight different types of individual contributors. Cross says ONA can reveal, for example, who in the company is a <strong>central connector</strong>, someone whom other members of the network consult frequently for information and hold the network together; <strong>knowledge brokers</strong>, people who connect different groups or teams within a network, and <strong>peripheral</strong>, those who have limited connections with the rest of the network.</p>
  <p>These characterizations can reveal who the major influencers and actors are in an organization, as well as those who could benefit from more engagement. (As you will learn in this article, there are additional employee archetypes.)</p>
  <p>Consider this hypothetical. Mark serves as a central connector in a large pharmaceutical company. As an entry-level data administrator, Mark is low on the corporate hierarchy, but he is critical in that he connects human resources, sales, and marketing colleagues by serving as a conduit for the exchange of ideas and information. Mia, on the other hand, is an expert coder who is great at developing apps, but she is peripheral – disconnected from others in the employee network who could assist and collaborate with her. On paper, Mia’s programmer title may be higher in the organizational hierarchy. However, she is unable to make the connections she needs to progress and be selected for high-value projects.</p>
  <p>These are the kinds of situations and relationships that exist in organizations of any substantial size. Understanding them in depth can help leaders foster more collaboration, enhance employee engagement, and promote talent development.</p>
  <p>But these benefits rely on good data. Organizations need to allay fears about data privacy, communicate the advantages of ONA to employees, and remain clear-eyed about the technology’s limitations.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_157d0358d0a6015b3e3aae97be8899e42f73f7091.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_157d0358d0a6015b3e3aae97be8899e42f73f7091.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_157d0358d0a6015b3e3aae97be8899e42f73f7091.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Man and woman coworkers having a discussion and looking at post-it notes on a clear whiteboard." src="./media_157d0358d0a6015b3e3aae97be8899e42f73f7091.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="visibility-into-far-flung-workforces">Visibility into far-flung workforces</h2>
  <p>Organizational network analysis emerged in the 1930s as a framework for sociologists to study the social interactions of prison inmates and reform school girls. Then, the work was done through observation and paper diagrams. In recent years, ONA has found a foothold in the corporate world for two reasons: the changing nature of work and the ability to analyze communications and other data.</p>
  <p>Over the past few years, organizations of all kinds have gone to great lengths to set up distributed, geographically dispersed, flexible teams. The workplace changes that occurred during the COVID-19 pandemic only reinforce the idea that employees need to be able to respond quickly to change and have the necessary space to pivot and experiment.</p>
  <p>However, companies’ work to make this shift has led to a new challenge: gaps of knowledge and awareness that prevent leaders from knowing who’s working effectively with whom on a wide range of projects.</p>
  <p>This is where the data comes in. Never before have organizations had access to vast volumes of passive data – information that exists within the company, such as e-mail, chat, calendar, and collaboration-software data. Unlike active data, gathered from time-consuming surveys typically administered by human resources teams, passive data provides a more objective, less biased view of workplace dynamics without requiring direct input from employees.</p>
  <p>ONA applications are also becoming easier to use, notes Bodan of Deloitte. “In the past, you needed a data science degree [to understand ONA],” says Bodan. “But there are many user-friendly platforms now that allow non-technical users like HR professionals to easily interpret the data and drive insights.”</p>
  <p>Together, the rise of remote work, passive data, and easier-to-use ONA tools are encouraging organizations to make ONA a key component of their talent strategy, experts say.</p>
  <h2 id="revealing-the-most-valuable-network-players">Revealing the most valuable (network) players</h2>
  <p>As its name suggests, ONA is about analyzing the networks among people who work together. Its value lies in helping companies identify important connections and potential obstacles to information flow and collaboration. ONA can serve like a tide that washes away the sand to reveal what’s hidden underneath. The results of an analysis can pinpoint different employee archetypes that don’t always show up in organizational charts. For example:</p>
  <h3 id="hidden-value-creators">Hidden-value creators</h3>
  <p>One important node in an organizational network is hidden-value creators – employees who contribute significantly to an organization yet are easily overlooked due to factors, such as geographic location, communication style, or corporate rank.</p>
  <p>“A very small set of people have a disproportionate impact on how work gets done,” says Cross of i4cp. He notes that, based on his work with more than 300 organizations, he has found that, on average, 2% to 3% of employees account for 20% to 35% of an organization’s key collaborative work. The problem, he says, is “if these workers are overlooked, they’re far more likely to leave the organization and take their networks with them.”</p>
  <p>ONA can cast a light on these unsung heroes, giving leaders the opportunity to offer incentives for them to stay and keep valuable networks intact.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="the-only-path-forward-is-together">The only path forward is together</h3>
        <p>Discover how business networks find new avenues for growth and innovation.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="/blogs/ext-business-networks-the-only-path-forward">Read more</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="energizers">Energizers</h3>
  <p>Energizers are positive thinkers who are quick to support coworkers’ ideas and “leave people feeling better after an interaction,” says Peter Gray, an ONA expert and professor of commerce at the University of Virginia’s McIntire School of Commerce in Charlottesville, Virginia.</p>
  <p>Gray’s research highlights the role human behavior can play in building a network. The most effective networks include energizers, says Gray. A single energizer in a network can greatly reduce the risk of attrition among team members while leading high performance.</p>
  <p>Organizational network analysis can help identify these such contributors, Gray says, by asking employees in a survey to identify the people in the company who make them feel good about themselves.</p>
  <h3 id="fast-movers">Fast movers</h3>
  <p>Employees who make a concerted effort to discover coworkers’ needs are also more likely to establish mutually beneficial and meaningful connections with coworkers. For example, while researching employee relationships, Cross discovered that 10% to 15% of employees are “fast movers” who become well-connected in less than a year after hiring (most workers require three to five years to become well-connected.) These fast movers, Cross says, share an interesting trait: When asked to disclose information about themselves, “fast movers are much more likely to pivot in that moment and say, ‘I can, but can you first give me a sense of what your priorities are? What are you excited about? What keeps you up at night?’”</p>
  <p>By investing in coworkers’ needs, Cross says fast movers are not only able to infiltrate powerful networks at rapid speed, but they are also more likely to be tapped for high-value projects.</p>
  <h3 id="weak-nodes">Weak nodes</h3>
  <p>As one might expect, the analysis can also highlight employees who are not well-connected to their networks. These weak nodes represent a situation that can “undercut an organization’s ability to deliver enterprise value,” Cross says. Underutilized and at higher risk of departure, he says these siloed workers can create “breakdowns in connectivity that are likely to hurt a company in terms of revenue potential, innovation, scale, or efficiencies – quantifiable points of impact.”</p>
  <p>In this scenario, knowledge is power. By identifying disconnected employees, organizations can stage team-building exercises and launch cross-functional projects that connect these peripheral players to central connectors and knowledge brokers for a more solid network.</p>
  <p>The good news is organizations are finding ways to bridge the gaps of knowledge created by issues related to scalability, engagement, and context. These best practices are not only helping organizations identify key influencers and isolated figures within a network, but also gaining a better understanding of how people work in today’s modern world and why some succeed – and others don’t.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1357353a61bace47c09b540d83a232c12e79cf37f.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1357353a61bace47c09b540d83a232c12e79cf37f.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1357353a61bace47c09b540d83a232c12e79cf37f.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Man working at a creative office using his computer with blurred coworkers moving in the background." src="./media_1357353a61bace47c09b540d83a232c12e79cf37f.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="2160">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="when-insight-leads-to-new-organizational-structures">When insight leads to new organizational structures</h2>
  <p>Retaining hidden talent and connecting valuable outliers aren’t the only business benefits of using ONA. Organizations can also realize substantial operational gains by visualizing the informal relationships that exist within an organization.</p>
  <p>Deloitte’s Bodan describes one client who had 14 different functions, including legal, finance, and accounts payable, all working within a single business unit. Desperate to break down these functional silos, Bodan says the company turned to ONA. Upon analyzing the company’s passive and active data, “we discovered that the natural communities that existed, based on how people operate on a day-to-day basis, was actually four,” she says. Moreover, although the company’s organizational chart dictated that employees collaborate according to function, networks had formed naturally around customer segments.</p>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div data-valign="middle">The modern workplace “is moving away from functional fiefdoms to a much more collaborative environment.</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div data-valign="middle">Maya Bodan, leader of the organization strategy and design talent group, Deloitte LLP</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In response, Bodan says the company whittled down its 14 functional silos into six key collaborative groups, each one dedicated to a particular customer segment. Creating these more meaningful and connected groups not only provided employees “with much more of an end-to-end view of how they’re working,” says Bodan, but also helped to increase speed to market, improve customer experience, and streamline decision-making.</p>
  <p>That’s a case when the analysis leads to organizational change. However, realizing such a result requires overcoming a set of challenges.</p>
  <h2 id="addressing-challenges-to-implementing-ona">Addressing challenges to implementing ONA</h2>
  <p>To achieve the benefits of ONA, companies will need to address technological, cultural, and organizational challenges to effectively apply it.</p>
  <h3 id="confronting-privacy-concerns">Confronting privacy concerns</h3>
  <p>As with any data-crunching tool, privacy concerns can limit the value organizations derive from ONA. Although employees can opt out of participating in a survey, passive data is generated from e-mail, texting, calendars, and collaboration applications without any employee involvement – or expressed consent.</p>
  <p>“Privacy has to be handled incredibly carefully in terms of how and what you're disclosing and to whom,” says Cross.</p>
  <p>But while establishing privacy practices related to disclosure can help protect employees, most ONA tools are already limited in terms of the data they’re able to gather, according to Gray, the University of Virginia professor.</p>
  <p>For example, Gray says, “Passive network data collection software programs that mine e-mail and meeting data are excellent at stripping out any information that could get a company in trouble.” That’s not to suggest, however, that passive data isn’t worth parsing. Rather, by examining the nature of e-mail exchanges, not the communication itself, organizations can discover patterns of collaboration, including which employees are most likely to respond to messages after work hours, and from whom – telltale signs of important relationships.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="hr-and-the-use-of-ai">HR and the Use of AI</h3>
        <p>Learn how HR can lead the way for AI adoption in your organization.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="/resources/how-hr-can-direct-use-of-ai">Read more</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="managing-scalability-limitations">Managing scalability limitations</h3>
  <p>Another obstacle to effective ONA is the nature of work itself – especially when the organization itself is very large. Multinational corporations have hundreds of thousands of employees, making it impractical to chart every single worker and their respective networks. Many employees simply don’t have the time to respond to lengthy surveys, which can prevent companies from achieving the response rates needed for accuracy. Passive data in isolation can fail to provide the necessary context for truly understanding the ties that bind employees.</p>
  <p>For example, is a particularly intense rally of text messages about a business-critical project or Sunday brunch plans? And what exactly constitutes a positive link between two employees? There are simply no standards for what a good network should look like.</p>
  <p>Leaders need to account for these potential weaknesses – just as they adjust their sights when evaluating outputs from business analytics systems with the knowledge that the results reflect incomplete data.</p>
  <h3 id="securing-employee-acceptance">Securing employee acceptance</h3>
  <p>Even the most clearly marked targets can be missed if employees aren’t on board with ONA. “There is sometimes a concern that ONA will be used in regressive ways – that it will be used to fire people,” says Gray. For this reason, he recommends that managers earn employee trust by assuring them that the insights generated by ONA will be used in ways that will benefit them directly, such as improving performance, pinpointing places to build strong connections, and uncovering hidden factors for success.</p>
  <p>Leaders must also take steps to present the discoveries made by ONA as compelling information rather than intractable truths. Consider, for example, the damage that could be done if a veteran manager learns that his energizer score is a fraction of the department’s latest hire. To avoid conflict and bruised egos, Gray says employees should be offered training on how to become more of an energizer, because “there are actual behaviors they can adopt to change their energizing score. You have to help them see that this is a function of behaviors that are malleable and change over time. No one is doomed.”</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1135fcc02c642fb46d5450b14b8a4a9b76968a37e.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1135fcc02c642fb46d5450b14b8a4a9b76968a37e.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1135fcc02c642fb46d5450b14b8a4a9b76968a37e.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Diverse group of businesspeople around a desk smiling cheerfully during an office meeting." src="./media_1135fcc02c642fb46d5450b14b8a4a9b76968a37e.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="adopting-a-data-first-method-to-organizational-thinking">Adopting a data-first method to organizational thinking</h2>
  <p>Adopting ONA will require leaders to use a data-first method to measure and illustrate the collaboration patterns among employees, says Bodan. Moreover, she adds, an “adaptable mindset” is crucial, because ONA’s analysis of the strength, frequency, and nature of employee interactions may reveal some counterintuitive truths about which employees really wield influence in the organization and which ones are simply coasting on their titles.</p>
  <p>Either way, says Bodan, the modern workplace “is moving away from functional fiefdoms to a much more collaborative environment”– one in which ONA can serve as a valuable tool and the hierarchy of Caeser’s legions really is history.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>topic/data-analytics</category>
            <category>content-type/use-case</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[2024 HR Trends: The Year of AI]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/2024-hr-trends-the-year-of-ai</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/2024-hr-trends-the-year-of-ai</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP research reveals the latest HR trends and how organizations can stay ahead of the curve with innovative strategies and technology.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ff8cf0ed03433df1c0da682bcb037e6567eeae0d.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ff8cf0ed03433df1c0da682bcb037e6567eeae0d.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1ff8cf0ed03433df1c0da682bcb037e6567eeae0d.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="2024 HR Trends: The Year of AI" src="./media_1ff8cf0ed03433df1c0da682bcb037e6567eeae0d.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="hr-trends-the-year-of-ai">2024 HR Trends: The Year of AI</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Over the past few years, HR has steadily evolved into one of the most critical functions for any organization. HR not only has a seat at the table, but the ability to become a driving force behind organizational change and growth. Most customers I speak with recognize this opportunity, but many have the same question: how can HR make the most impact?</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Each year, the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/resources.html">SAP SuccessFactors Growth &#x26; Insights team</a> conducts in-depth research on the latest trends and predictions impacting the HR function. Our PhD-level organizational psychologists and market intelligence experts aggregate and analyze a mountain of HR trends and predictions data to deliver a list of actionable “meta-trends.” For 2024, a list of 611 individual trends were broken down into nine key themes.</p>
  <p>Above all, there is no question that 2024 is the year of <a href="/topics/ai">artificial intelligence (AI)</a>. No longer just hype or speculation, AI is officially here. Exciting possibilities have become realities and organizations must embrace AI or risk being left behind. And while our number one HR trend is AI, you can also see its effects across every trend.</p>
  <p>Below is a snapshot of the top three 2024 HR meta-trends, with examples of how SAP SuccessFactors solutions can help organizations stay ahead of the curve.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <picture>
          <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d0e8557e1e73aae25728990f5b73d21af5fff939.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
          <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d0e8557e1e73aae25728990f5b73d21af5fff939.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
          <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1d0e8557e1e73aae25728990f5b73d21af5fff939.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
          <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_1d0e8557e1e73aae25728990f5b73d21af5fff939.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="208">
        </picture>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="ai-upends-the-world-of-work-as-we-know-it">1. AI Upends the World of Work as We Know It</h2>
  <p>I don’t go a day – or maybe 10 minutes – without a customer asking for all the latest and greatest on AI innovation. That makes sense, as AI has dominated the 2024 trends discourse and it’s increasingly become seen as a way to augment human work.</p>
  <p>Trends indicate that using all forms of AI to improve day-to-day productivity will be top of mind for organizations in 2024. In particular, self-serve AI tools like copilots are poised to increase employee productivity on various day-to-day tasks. As employee sentiment about using AI tools at work has improved, so has the ability of these tools to make employees more efficient and effective.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="be-ready-for-ai-built-for-business">Be ready for AI built for business</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/ai-assistant.html">Meet SAP’s AI copilot, Joule</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>HR use cases abound, particularly within talent acquisition, but concerns continue about data privacy, ethics, and regulatory compliance. There’s a lot of noise and movement in the space, and regulators and enforcement agencies are acting quickly to keep up.</p>
  <p>With the tech landscape and market realities in mind, the HR leaders who head AI implementation programs, maintain a strong policy posture, and avoid overhyped or underbaked propositions to take advantage of the most valuable capabilities will steer their organizations down the right AI path.</p>
  <p>Embedding an AI copilot in HR solutions, like <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/ai-joule-product-tour.html">Joule in SAP SuccessFactors solutions</a>, can help employees and managers work faster and smarter by making it easier to find information and complete common HR tasks, such as updating personal data, giving feedback, and initiating a promotion.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_102dca27542b692c9688525999ebc7b6cc402f1b5.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_102dca27542b692c9688525999ebc7b6cc402f1b5.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_102dca27542b692c9688525999ebc7b6cc402f1b5.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_102dca27542b692c9688525999ebc7b6cc402f1b5.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="614">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>Joule, SAP’s AI copilot. Click to enlarge.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="skills-become-the-center-of-hr-practices">2. Skills Become the Center of HR Practices</h2>
  <p>As AI needs rise within organizations, many organizations will need to immediately respond to determine what AI skills are needed, who possesses those skills, and how to fill skill gaps – whether build, borrow, buy, or bot. On the other hand, AI capabilities will also drive the ability for organizations to more effectively engage in strategic workforce planning.</p>
  <p>Furthermore, in today’s increasingly complex business environment, traditional top-down human resources approaches fail to address employees’ increasing expectations for flexible and personalized career development. In 2024, HR will need to meet employees’ growing expectations for bespoke career paths while also solving the broader organization’s growing skills gaps and talent shortages, which present a major concern for leaders.</p>
  <p>Looking forward, it will be interesting to see whether the average organization fully engages in long-term, strategic, skills-based workforce planning, which has long been a strategic objective for many but often remains out of reach as they react to immediate priorities. AI skills could work as a forcing function here – and contribute to other trend areas like learning and employee potential.</p>
  <p><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/talent-management.html">SAP SuccessFactors solutions for talent management</a> can drive better employee experiences and business outcomes by using a common skills framework across recruiting, learning, performance management, internal mobility, and development.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d381f1111939f272d8dd076b837ed2de4dd9aa20.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d381f1111939f272d8dd076b837ed2de4dd9aa20.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1d381f1111939f272d8dd076b837ed2de4dd9aa20.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_1d381f1111939f272d8dd076b837ed2de4dd9aa20.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="576">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>Overview of skills and aspirations in a growth portfolio for SAP SuccessFactors. Click to enlarge.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="hybrid-work-returns-to-the-office">3. Hybrid Work Returns to the Office</h2>
  <p>Looking back at our yearly analyses of HR meta-trends, we saw the hybrid work topic shift from a focus on remote work as a reactive tactic to protect employees’ health and safety in 2020, to a focus on flexibility in 2021, to maintaining productivity and collaboration while working flexibly in 2022, and finally to an emphasis on underlying flexibility and the need for and benefit of malleable guidelines and principles in 2023. With the recent increase in partial and full return-to-office (RTO) policies, 2024 trends data suggests that the pendulum has swung back to hybrid, referring specifically to work location versus a broader perspective centered on flexibility.</p>
  <p>Companies in 2024 will continue to experiment with motivating employees to return to the office in ways that promote productivity, collaboration, and cost savings but don’t alienate their top talent. But some organizations are focusing more on redesigning the nature of work rather than just mandating where or when work gets done.</p>
  <p><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/core-hr-payroll.html">SAP SuccessFactors solutions for core HR, time, and payroll</a> help employees adopt a hybrid working model by providing options for common HR tasks regardless of when and where they are working, such as clocking in and out via desktop, mobile, or Microsoft Teams.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16e1bb2544e733655fa31281e9dcd8f5220ded6f8.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16e1bb2544e733655fa31281e9dcd8f5220ded6f8.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_16e1bb2544e733655fa31281e9dcd8f5220ded6f8.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_16e1bb2544e733655fa31281e9dcd8f5220ded6f8.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="576">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>Clock in and out via Microsoft Teams with SAP SuccessFactors solutions. Click to enlarge.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>There are plenty more strategic takeaways in the full report – the entire paper is a must-read for HR leaders to learn more from our research team on the latest trends in:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Diversity, equity, inclusion, and belonging (DEI&#x26;B)</li>
    <li>Employee mental health</li>
    <li>Leadership trust</li>
    <li>HR skills and agility</li>
    <li>Compensation</li>
    <li>Sustainability</li>
  </ul>
  <p>For additional insights, <a href="https://www.sap.com/registration/protected/default-overlay.html?gated_asset_path=%2F%2Fwww.sap.com%2Fdocuments%2F2024%2F02%2F883d4dde-ad7e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.rc.html&#x26;pdf-asset=883d4dde-ad7e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b&#x26;page=1?url_id=ctabutton-us-hcm">read the full report</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Dan Beck is president and chief product officer for SAP SuccessFactors.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-sap-news-on-linkedin">Connect with SAP News on LinkedIn</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news">Follow us to stay up-to-date</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors-hcm-suite</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Agile 101: Terms and Concepts for Business Leaders]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/agile-101-terms-and-concepts-for-business-leaders</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/agile-101-terms-and-concepts-for-business-leaders</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Can other corporate functions adopt the software world’s Agile methodology? We explore what works best and where.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/what-is</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Adapting Agile for the Enterprise]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/adapting-agile-for-the-enterprise</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/adapting-agile-for-the-enterprise</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Can other corporate functions adopt the software world’s Agile methodology? We explore what works best and where.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/use-case</category>
            <category>stage/acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Convista Harmonizes Workplace Culture with SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central and SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/convista-harmonizes-workplace-culture-with-sap-successfactors</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/convista-harmonizes-workplace-culture-with-sap-successfactors</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Convista's people culture and respected brand built on trust and transparency is supported by SAP S/4HANA Cloud and SAP SuccessFactors.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11a18052b07fa380b0a184821d2508dc2d57d515a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11a18052b07fa380b0a184821d2508dc2d57d515a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_11a18052b07fa380b0a184821d2508dc2d57d515a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Convista Harmonizes Workplace Culture with SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central and SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition" src="./media_11a18052b07fa380b0a184821d2508dc2d57d515a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="convista-harmonizes-workplace-culture-with-sap-successfactors-employee-central-and-sap-s4hana-cloud-public-edition">Convista Harmonizes Workplace Culture with SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central and SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>In a merger between two well-matched organizations, cultural integration can be the key to successfully transforming into a single high-performing entity ready to take on new opportunities. Notably, more than a few high-profile mergers have failed due to cultural incompatibility. Add a third organization into the merger and the cultural complexities increase exponentially. But some multi-organization mergers do successfully navigate these challenges and reap the transformational benefits.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="https://www.convista.com/en/">Convista</a>, a consultancy and SAP partner based in Cologne, Germany, emerged stronger and better positioned to serve its clients following a <a href="https://www.convista.com/en/news/axxiome-health-and-enowa-become-part-of-the-new-convista/">recent merger</a> that brought together three former consultancies: Axxiome Health, ConVista Consulting, and enowa. With 25 years of experience delivering transformation projects to its clients, Convista used that expertise in its own rebranding to present its capabilities to clients and employees: a vibrant people culture as well as a respected and trusted brand supported by <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/s4hana.html">SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition</a> for ERP and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/employee-central-hris/features.html">SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central</a> for core HR.</p>
  <p>“Trust and transparency are common values that we share at Convista,” declares Convista CEO Martin Hinz. “Combined with a dynamic team spirit and passion, it’s what we bring to our clients every day.”</p>
  <p>With a workforce of around 1,200 employees, Convista has made a name for itself through its dedication and expertise providing end-to-end solutions to clients throughout the world with a presence in Germany, Austria, Switzerland, Poland, Spain, Brazil, Israel, and further locations across the globe. It supports client projects primarily in four sectors: insurance, industry, healthcare, and energy/utilities. In recent years, Convista has twice been awarded SAP <a href="https://www.convista.com/en/news/for-the-second-time-in-a-row-sap-partner-of-the-year-award-in-the-financial-services-sector/">Partner of the Year</a> in the Financial Services sector.</p>
  <p>“At Convista you meet everyone on the same level, independent of your skill level or where you are in your career,” says Stefanie Weber, project lead of People and Culture – HR Systems, Convista. “Also, when we’re working with customers, we try to approach them at eye level, which makes quite a good working environment. The implementation of SAP SuccessFactors came as a natural extension to our brand and our culture.”</p>
  <h2 id="the-challenges-of-data-siloed-in-three-systems">The Challenges of Data Siloed in Three Systems</h2>
  <p>Weber says one of the reasons she joined Convista in 2012 while studying business at university was the high priority its leaders place on trust and transparency, values that permeate the entire organization and empower employees in their work and career development. “Trust is one of our main values,” she underscores. “Also, the trust that people are willing to do their best to get motivated and move the company ahead.”</p>
  <p>Convista grew quickly both organically and as a result of mergers with other consultancies. In 2019, IT service provider Axxiome Health joined the ConVista Group to deepen the organization’s expertise in the health insurance sector. In 2021, enowa joined the group, infusing its knowledge of industries and insurance. With the mergers complete, the incipient organization became <a href="https://www.convista.com/en/news/axxiome-health-and-enowa-become-part-of-the-new-convista/">the new Convista</a> on January 1, 2023.</p>
  <p>Though team members were highly motivated to collaborate from the start, Convista’s vision for itself as a modern organization was held back in both its daily work for projects and internal services. Using disparate tools based on older technology and a patchwork of third-party solutions that lacked integration proved to be inefficient and unsuitable as a basis for decision-making.</p>
  <p>“Whenever we wanted to have a report, even something as simple as a headcount, we always had to go into three different systems, collect the data, and report on that,” Weber recalls. “It’s just one of the many examples of why we really urgently needed one IT platform.”</p>
  <h2 id="project-one-achieves-milestone-integration">Project ONE Achieves Milestone Integration</h2>
  <p>To build a strong foundation for future growth, Convista embarked on “Project ONE” with the goal to have one digital platform flexible and powerful enough for the entire organization. For this, it chose SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition and SAP SuccessFactors solutions with self-service capabilities for employees to log time-off.</p>
  <p>Overall, implementing SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central with SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition can result in streamlined HR processes; end-to-end integration with seamless connectivity between HR and finance functions for accurate and up-to-date employee data across the organization; greater transparency of data for analytics and reporting on workforce trends, costs, and profitability to enable better strategic planning and resource allocation; and compliance with regulatory requirements and data security.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-successfactors-solutions-can-fuel-the-success-of-every-individual-and-drive-org-agility-at-scale">SAP SuccessFactors solutions can fuel the success of every individual and drive org agility at scale</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm.html">Learn how</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Among the key advantages is the ability for employees to access their own HR-related information, such as personal details and time-off balances. This self-service capability helps empower employees, improve transparency, and enhance the overall employee experience.</p>
  <p>Convista’s project team decided for a phased approach to the implementation by first introducing the SAP solutions in Poland and later in Germany, Austria, and Switzerland – with SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition planned to launch in the German-speaking countries during the course of 2024. To optimize success, the project team used the combined best practices of Convista and SAP and hosted regular meetings that provided clear communication to steer the project. “We were always aligned on the requirements of the other teams,” says Weber, who managed the HR workstream. “We all knew the main goal of the implementation. This was helpful for everyone on the project.”</p>
  <p>In-house experts from Convista certified on SAP SuccessFactors solutions contributed valuable knowledge for the implementation. Consultants from SAP Services and Support successfully integrated the cost center replication from SAP S/4HANA Cloud to SAP SuccessFactors and the workforce replication from SAP SuccessFactors to SAP S/4HANA Cloud, and delivered a detailed administration guide on the integration setup for Convista. Additionally, they provided an overview, the architecture guidance, and the navigation through major hurdles in performing the configuration to set up identity access governence (IAG), identity provisioning service (IPS), and identity authentication services (IAS). The SAP Early Adopter Care program supported Convista for the master data integration (MDI) during the implementation and helped to solve all roadblocks efficiently.</p>
  <p>On January 1, 2023, Convista’s 80-person team in Poland was the first to go live with the new SAP solutions. “It was really a great experience for them and quite an advancement,” says Weber, citing the benefits of the new solutions that provide optimizations and intuitive workflows. The project took a pivotal turn on January 1, 2024, with the launch of SAP SuccessFactors solutions for Convista’s 800 employees in the German-speaking countries.</p>
  <p>“The biggest milestone was to have [SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition and SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central] speaking with each other,” says Weber, who emphasizes how valuable it is for the team “to have an end-to-end process within one platform.” With an integrated IT platform in place, she says that it is no longer necessary to do workflows, authorizations, or any other processes in other systems.</p>
  <p>The seamless synchronization of data by using a common data model for SAP business applications helps reduce the need for manual data entry and redundant processes. This means, for example, employee data that is maintained in SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central is available in real-time in SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition; while master data, like cost center data, flows seamlessly from SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition to SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central. Eliminating data silos enables the HR and finance teams to work with consistent, accurate data for all-important employment decisions and legal reporting obligations.</p>
  <p>Now Convista’s team is unified in its brand, values, spirit – and employee data.</p>
  <h2 id="more-transparency-and-intuitive-workflows-are-just-the-beginning">More Transparency and Intuitive Workflows Are Just the Beginning</h2>
  <p>Feedback has been overwhelmingly positive, according to Weber, with employees speaking favorably about the improved transparency and workflows. “The first thing I heard from everyone was, well, this is simple and intuitive. They were so happy about it,” she says. “They are big fans of the mobile application. They find it very transparent and easy to use.”</p>
  <p>For some colleagues, the new solution lets them view their own data for the first time. “When we went live, everyone was viewing their profile,” says Weber. “This was also quite new that you are able to see what data is maintained for your person, your address, but also job information – to view it and have this transparency. People like this very much and also the ability to have the self-services in SAP SuccessFactors.”</p>
  <p>To strengthen communication between HR and employees, Convista will bring more people processes onto the new digital platform. In fact, the team very recently implemented the SAP SuccessFactors Performance &#x26; Goals solution for annual employee appraisals, goal setting, and project feedback. “It’s just the beginning,” Weber says. “There’s still a lot of work ahead of us.”</p>
  <p>Hinz says, “We have been careful to preserve our workplace culture during the transformation. Now that we are rebranded as one organization, we are seeing the benefits of that early effort. With SAP, we now have the digital platform to build people-centered processes that advance our vision as a unified, high-performing organization serving our clients.”</p>
  <p>Find out more about <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/solutions.html?url_id=ctabutton-us-hcm-convista">SAP SuccessFactors solutions</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Jacqueline Prause is a journalist at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-sap-news-delivered-to-your-inbox-once-a-week">Get the latest SAP news delivered to your inbox once a week</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/nl/sap-news-center-newsletter/index.html">Sign up today</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-employee-central</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP SuccessFactors Strategy for Building Future-Ready Workforces]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/sap-successfactors-strategy-building-future-ready-workforces</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/sap-successfactors-strategy-building-future-ready-workforces</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The SAP SuccessFactors HCM suite provides HR cloud software to help organizations meet the challenges of today and innovate for tomorrow.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1aa60aead41f035043e44cbfe1f53c8c65e859485.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1aa60aead41f035043e44cbfe1f53c8c65e859485.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1aa60aead41f035043e44cbfe1f53c8c65e859485.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP SuccessFactors Strategy for Building Future-Ready Workforces" src="./media_1aa60aead41f035043e44cbfe1f53c8c65e859485.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-successfactors-strategy-for-building-future-ready-workforces">SAP SuccessFactors Strategy for Building Future-Ready Workforces</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Without a doubt, the world of work has dramatically transformed over the past several years, with generative AI initiating the latest wave of change for organizations around the world. In a more complex and less homogenous business landscape, top-down HR processes of the past no longer meet the rising demands of employees for flexible career paths, intuitive work processes, and two-way communication – not to mention the growing skills gaps and talent shortages that keep leaders up at night.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Leaders need to embrace generative AI as a way to address these challenges with talent intelligence and advanced analytics. According to <a href="https://emt.gartnerweb.com/ngw/globalassets/en/human-resources/documents/trends/hr-top-priorities-ebook-2024.pdf?_gl=1*1bmqwvn*_ga*NjU0NzU1ODk5LjE3MDY4MDI5MDY.*_ga_R1W5CE5FEV*MTcwNjgwMjkwNS4xLjEuMTcwNjgwMzA4Mi4yNi4wLjA.">Gartner</a>, 26% of CEOs rank the talent shortage as the top damaging factor to business outlook, and 76% of HR leaders agree they will be lagging in organizational success if they don’t adopt and implement generative AI in the next 12 to 24 months.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="adopt-the-latest-in-hr-innovation-with-sap-successfactors-solutions">Adopt the latest in HR innovation with SAP SuccessFactors solutions</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>At SAP, we have a proven track record of providing <a href="/topics/human-resources">HCM</a> solutions in the cloud for leading organizations around the globe. Our customers trust us to not only manage their sensitive employee data and payroll, but to help them understand their workforces as they prepare for the skills they need in the future.</p>
  <p>The <a href="http://sap.com/hr">SAP SuccessFactors HCM suite</a> provides truly global HR cloud software with powerful AI capabilities to help organizations meet the challenges of today and innovate for tomorrow. Our more than 10,000 customers – from startups and midmarket companies to large enterprises – use our solutions to help bring out the best in their people by harnessing the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/human-resources.html">power of AI</a> to elevate every experience, guide every people decision, and connect HR across every aspect of the business. We do this with:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/solutions.html#active_tab_item_1602592257238">Core HR and payroll</a></strong>: A single source of truth is key for any organization to enable insight into the entirety of its workforce: employees, contingent workers, and dynamic teams. The SAP SuccessFactors HCM suite can provide localized support for over 100 countries and territories and cloud payroll for 50 countries and territories, plus additional modular solutions for time, benefits, and HR service delivery.</li>
    <li><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/solutions.html#active_tab_item_1602592296240">Talent and learning</a></strong>: Skills gaps and talent shortages have been persistent challenges that continue to exist across all industries. Addressing them starts with an understanding of skills that currently exist, followed by pathways for employees to find new opportunities, learn new skills, and access mentors and feedback. The talent intelligence hub across SAP SuccessFactors solutions uses AI to continuously help organizations and employees understand their skills and match people with personalized career pathways.</li>
    <li><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/solutions.html#active_tab_item_1602592051931">A modern user experience</a></strong>: Every person has unique needs and preferences – in how they work, how they communicate, and what’s required for their role. Along with a refreshed, modern user experience, we’ve built in generative AI capabilities throughout our solutions to help people work smarter. And with Joule, SAP’s copilot, they can quickly complete HR tasks and get conversational responses to their questions.</li>
    <li><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/hr-and-finance.html">HR connected to ERP, finance, and more</a></strong>: Having access to people data connected across the business is critical to building agility, speed, and resilience within an organization. With the power of the broader SAP portfolio, organizations can improve end-to-end business processes across the entire business. This is also complemented with our partner ecosystem, which includes over 350 apps for HR.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>We firmly believe that when organizations invest in their people – in their passions and potential – they return the investment over and over. And with the rapid acceleration of AI, it’s more important than ever to build pathways to employee growth, including new ways to upskill, reskill, and discover opportunities that align with a person’s skills, interests, and aspirations.</p>
  <p>Learn more about the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm.html?url_id=text-us-hcm-hr-freetrial">SAP SuccessFactors HCM suite</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Dan Beck is president and chief product officer for SAP SuccessFactors.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors-hcm-suite</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Upskilling Your Workforce for the AI Era]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/upskilling-your-workforce-for-the-ai-era</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/upskilling-your-workforce-for-the-ai-era</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Get advice on how companies and employees can incorporate AI into existing work and seizing opportunities to elevate skills.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>content-type/what-is</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Recognized as a Strategic Challenger in 2024 Fosway 9-Grid™ for Learning Systems]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/sap-strategic-challenger-2024-fosway-9-grid-for-learning-systems</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/sap-strategic-challenger-2024-fosway-9-grid-for-learning-systems</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP was recently named a Strategic Challenger in the 2024 Fosway 9-Grid for Learning Systems. Read to learn more about the recognition.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1909b111011bdb2e7f1b173d6614d6bdebec89073.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1909b111011bdb2e7f1b173d6614d6bdebec89073.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1909b111011bdb2e7f1b173d6614d6bdebec89073.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Recognized as a Strategic Challenger in 2024 Fosway 9-Grid™ for Learning Systems" src="./media_1909b111011bdb2e7f1b173d6614d6bdebec89073.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-recognized-as-a-strategic-challenger-in-2024-fosway-9-grid-for-learning-systems">SAP Recognized as a Strategic Challenger in 2024 Fosway 9-Grid™ for Learning Systems</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>SAP was recently named a Strategic Challenger in the <a href="https://www.fosway.com/9-grid-2/learning-systems/">2024 Fosway 9-Grid<sup>TM</sup> for Learning Systems</a>, a multidimensional learning market analysis model. As a Strategic Challenger, SAP is recognized as demonstrating solid performance with solutions that have a rich and broad suite of capability compared to the market.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>With the widened availability of AI, the race for skills is impacting both people and organizations. While people are learning how to use AI to drive more efficiency within their individual roles, organizations are also under pressure to adopt AI technology that can deliver more personalized development opportunities and greater talent intelligence.</p>
  <p>Over the last year, SAP has made significant investments across <a href="http://sap.com/hr">SAP SuccessFactors solutions</a>, specifically in <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/corporate-lms.html">SAP SuccessFactors Learning</a>, to deliver these capabilities.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="boost-employee-skills-while-helping-ensure-compliance-with-sap-successfactors-learning">Boost employee skills while helping ensure compliance with SAP SuccessFactors Learning</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/corporate-lms.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>These investments are part of a broader strategy to help our customers focus on accelerated skills growth and build a <a href="/2023/09/new-integrated-learning-experience-sap-successfactors">future-ready workforce</a>. Recently, we released a redesigned <strong>integrated learning experience</strong> that can deliver an entirely new way for people to experience learning at work. The highly personalized experience can guide the learner to not only accomplish compliance trainings – what they “have to learn” – and organizational goals – what they “need to learn” – but also helps to drive an intrinsic culture of learning around what they “want to learn,” tapping into each individual’s needs, aspirations, interests, or preferences based on their growth profile.</p>
  <p>Furthermore, <strong>the AI-powered</strong> <strong><a href="/2023/10/skills-based-organization-talent-intelligence-hub">talent intelligence hub</a></strong> is now available across all SAP SuccessFactors solutions. It is a framework that helps organizations understand the skills their employees have today, the gaps that exist, and how to close those gaps. With this intelligence, SAP SuccessFactors Learning can continue to deliver even more personalized learning and development recommendations.</p>
  <p>“The level of innovation within the learning systems market continues to accelerate rapidly – specifically around AI and skills,” said David Wilson, founder and CEO of Fosway Group. “As a major vendor in this space, SAP continues to invest significantly in innovating its learning and talent capabilities, reflecting its focus on enhancing the value it delivers to learning buyers as well as its wider HCM audience.”</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d02d983db0796a8aed17039c36d19de9b713748b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d02d983db0796a8aed17039c36d19de9b713748b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1d02d983db0796a8aed17039c36d19de9b713748b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_1d02d983db0796a8aed17039c36d19de9b713748b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="768">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>Source: 2024 Fosway 9-GridTM for Learning Systems. Click to enlarge.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Both multinational and midsize companies leverage <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/corporate-lms.html">SAP SuccessFactors Learning</a>, along with our partner ecosystem, to help drive upskilling and reskilling and create a culture of continuous learning.</p>
  <p><a href="/2023/07/san-pablo-farmacia-employees-brand-ambassadors">San Pablo Farmacia</a>, a Mexico-based pharmacy retail chain, created an intuitive and engaging training experience that employees can consume at their convenience. By integrating the learning solution with other talent management applications, it can design personal training and development plans in line with its growth strategies and the individual needs of the entire workforce. The company delivered certified training to 1,800 employees without the need to transport its people to a training location and take them away from their pharmacy stores.</p>
  <p>Delta is also embracing AI to drive upskilling and personalized development opportunities. “We are incorporating disruptive technologies like our AI-driven skills ontology that automatically incorporates industry trends with embedded intelligence,” said Tim Gregory, managing director of HR Innovation and Workforce Technology at <a href="/2023/10/skills-based-organization-talent-intelligence-hub">Delta</a>. “We can say which skills are most important to Delta Air Lines and the employee can easily combine those with their current capabilities, strengths and styles, and aspirations to create a personal career path. All of the content is based on Delta-specific skills and personalized to each employee’s career goals.”</p>
  <p>Looking ahead, we will continue to deliver more learning-specific enhancements and new AI capabilities throughout 2024 across all SAP SuccessFactors solutions so leaders can hire the best talent and grow their personal skills with individualized plans while building up the compliance and strategic skills needed by the organization.</p>
  <p><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/corporate-lms.html">Learn more about SAP SuccessFactors Learning.</a></p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Vinita Venkatesh is vice president of Product Management for SAP SuccessFactors Learning.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-learning</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sales Performance Management: Empowering Sales Teams for Better Outcomes]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/sap-north-america-sales-performance-management-customer-summit-better-outcomes</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/sap-north-america-sales-performance-management-customer-summit-better-outcomes</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[At the SAP Sales Performance Management Customer Summit, customers shared how to optimize sales compensation for better business results.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_151d6d5f5e440d033f2105cfba96ee66afebd464e.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_151d6d5f5e440d033f2105cfba96ee66afebd464e.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_151d6d5f5e440d033f2105cfba96ee66afebd464e.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Sales Performance Management: Empowering Sales Teams for Better Outcomes" src="./media_151d6d5f5e440d033f2105cfba96ee66afebd464e.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sales-performance-management-empowering-sales-teams-for-better-outcomes">Sales Performance Management: Empowering Sales Teams for Better Outcomes</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>In today’s dynamic business environment, organizations need highly efficient sales teams to generate revenue and stay ahead of the competition. But while advances in AI-powered tools have accelerated the sales process, they have also increased the value of soft skills and the relationship-building acumen that talented salespeople bring to their jobs. That’s why savvy organizations are more committed than ever to keeping their sales teams engaged and productive.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="accelerate-business-outcomes-with-sales-performance-management-products-from-sap">Accelerate business outcomes with sales performance management products from SAP</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/sales-performance-management.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>High-performing sales teams are using <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/sales-performance-management.html">sales performance management</a> solutions from SAP SuccessFactors to manage and optimize sales compensation and incentives – rewarding sales reps for their performance – while streamlining sales processes and using real-time insights to improve operational efficiency and drive revenue.</p>
  <p>“There’s this renewed emphasis on efficiency,” said Rahul Iyer, general manager, Sales Performance Management, SAP SuccessFactors, speaking to SAP customers at the <a href="https://events.sap.com/us/sap-north-america-spm-customer-summit-2024/en/home">SAP North America Sales Performance Management Customer Summit</a>, held February 13-14, 2024, in Dallas, Texas. “Customers want faster, simpler outcomes – and they want to provide a great seller experience, as well. At SAP SuccessFactors, we’ve threaded the intelligence of connected cloud applications throughout the SPM solution portfolio. This allows us to deliver the efficiency, transparency, and rich experience of SAP in a comprehensive platform that covers a full range of end-to-end processes in sales compensation.”</p>
  <h2 id="together-for-success">Together for Success</h2>
  <p>Under the banner “Together we can make it better,” the summit event provided a venue for SAP customers – some of whom came from as far away as South America – to meet one-on-one with experts and gain valuable knowledge from product road maps, demos, and deep dive sessions, as well as learn from one another’s experiences in customer sessions.</p>
  <p>Iyer affirmed SAP’s commitment to deliver the advanced innovations customers need to be competitive: “As a strategic partner to our customers, we have the moral responsibility to help them receive progressively more out of technology innovations, while accelerating with the best-in-class capabilities SAP has to offer. We are simplifying from every angle to make it easy for our customers to adopt, so they can achieve business outcomes faster.”</p>
  <p>Barbara Rubis Linning, SAP SuccessFactors global vice president, Product and Engineering, presented the latest innovations and features across the sales performance management solution set, which includes <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/incentive-compensation-management.html">SAP SuccessFactors Incentive Management</a>, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/territory-and-quota.html">SAP SuccessFactors Territory and Quota</a>, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/agent-lifecycle-mgmt.html">SAP SuccessFactors Agent Lifecycle Management</a>, and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/agent-performance-management.html">SAP SuccessFactors Agent Performance Management</a>. With features like territory planning and incentive compensation, SAP sales performance management solutions enable organizations to optimize their sales performance for better business results. The solutions use advanced features – for tasks such as drive time analysis and mapping to optimize territories – to streamline processes and make workflows easier so that customers realize value faster. The ongoing introduction of the <a href="https://community.sap.com/t5/technology-blogs-by-sap/sap-fiori-evolution-horizon-now-generally-available-in-ui-technologies-and/ba-p/13532969">Horizon</a> visual theme on key administrative pages delivers a fresh, modern user interface (UI) for an elevated user experience.</p>
  <p>“We want our customers to have winning sales teams,” said Linning. “Their success is why we continuously look for new ways to build innovations and relevant features into the portfolio to accelerate business outcomes. SAP is building intelligence that is relevant, responsible, and reliable because we believe it leads to smarter, data-driven decision making and results in better sales performance. Our new intuitive UI helps simplify tasks and puts people at the center of business for improved productivity.”</p>
  <p>SAP SuccessFactors solutions deliver <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/ai-assistant.html">Joule</a>, SAP’s natural language processing AI copilot, to help people be more productive in their jobs using SAP business solutions.</p>
  <p>The integration of sales performance management solutions with <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform.html">SAP Business Technology Platform</a> and <a href="/2023/03/sap-datasphere-power-of-business-data">SAP Datasphere</a> enables seamless access to real-time data and analytics, empowering organizations to make informed decisions and drive sales success.</p>
  <h2 id="winning-with-sales-compensation">Winning with Sales Compensation</h2>
  <p>As the all-important link between an organization’s products and services and its customers, the sales team is a principal driver of bottom-line growth for the whole organization. Correctly incenting sales teams requires the use of proven strategies and solutions to align the pay program with organizational goals, said David Cichelli, revenue growth advisor at <a href="https://www.alexandergroup.com/">The Alexander Group</a>, who presented “Leading the Sales Design Compensation Project.”</p>
  <p>He advised sales compensation leaders adopt an annual review process that includes assessment, strategic alignment, taskforce design, and comprehensive communication phases. “Sales compensation design needs to reflect the consensus of key stakeholders: sales, finance, product management, and HR,” he said. “By following a proven design process, you can develop a strategically aligned, effective, and motivational pay program.”</p>
  <h2 id="supporting-customer-success-for-better-outcomes">Supporting Customer Success for Better Outcomes</h2>
  <p>The summit showcased the SAP ecosystem with sponsorships and informative sessions from <a href="https://spectrumtek.com/">SpectrumTek</a>, <a href="https://canidium.com/">Canidium</a>, <a href="https://www.opensymmetry.com/">OpenSymmetry</a>, <a href="https://www.cahabaconsultinggroup.com/">Cahaba Consulting Group</a>, <a href="https://www.thelcfirm.com/">The LC Firm</a>, and <a href="https://www.aspiredigital.com/">Aspire Digital</a>.</p>
  <p>SAP experts highlighted SAP’s message of ongoing support for customer success: “We’re here for you,” said Tak Kusano, global chief operating officer of SAP SuccessFactors. “SAP has a tight-knit community of sales performance management experts that bring deep domain knowledge to this niche space. That’s why we’re able to work so closely with customers to gain consensus on the road map and product innovations, like AI. We’re passionate about bringing the best of technology to SAP customers.”</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/sales-performance-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Total Workforce Management Evolution: How OG&E and Brightspeed Manage Employees and Contingent Workers]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/oge-and-brightspeed-manage-employees-contingent-workers</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/oge-and-brightspeed-manage-employees-contingent-workers</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[OG&E and Brightspeed highlight the importance of strategic planning and the effective use of technological tools in managing the workforce.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/contingent-workforce-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fieldglass</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>news-tag/total-workforce-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Game-Changing Role of Incentive Compensation Automation in the Retail Industry]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/incentive-compensation-automation-in-retail</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/incentive-compensation-automation-in-retail</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With SAP SuccessFactors Incentive Management, retailers can incorporate key performance indicators into their incentive structure.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10fff8c20499512be48a61b55b1b6ecdb00d8656a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10fff8c20499512be48a61b55b1b6ecdb00d8656a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_10fff8c20499512be48a61b55b1b6ecdb00d8656a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="The Game-Changing Role of Incentive Compensation Automation in the Retail Industry" src="./media_10fff8c20499512be48a61b55b1b6ecdb00d8656a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="the-game-changing-role-of-incentive-compensation-automation-in-the-retail-industry">The Game-Changing Role of Incentive Compensation Automation in the Retail Industry</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>In the dynamic world of retail, staying ahead means adapting to evolving customer expectations and embracing innovative solutions. The era of omnichannel retailing has ushered in demand for seamless, personalized shopping experiences, compelling businesses to think outside the box to support seamless experiences and minimize friction by providing the right product at the right time in the right place. Moreover, recognizing the intricate dance between employee satisfaction and customer experience, businesses are weaving a narrative where a better employee experience becomes the cornerstone for elevating customer delight.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>At the recent <a href="/topics/nrf">NRF event</a>, the world’s largest retail conference, the mantra of “adjust and adapt” echoed through the halls. AI and digital acceleration took the center stage, making innovation the heart of the conversation. Retailers also highlighted a crucial focus on a motivated workforce, emphasizing how an empowered workforce is critical to delivering exceptional customer experiences.</p>
  <p>In a landscape challenged by high turnover rates, retailers showcased their commitment to navigating complexity through strategic investments in their most valuable asset – their people. One of the pivotal elements that drives employee motivation and engagement in the retail industry is incentive compensation, where associates are often paid on commission.</p>
  <p>During NRF, Daniel Jasper from Neiman Marcus shared insights into how incentive compensation automation transformed the company’s commission payment process. With over 40 stores and a complex commission structure, Neiman Marcus faced challenges in managing incentive compensation. Its previous incentive management system was cumbersome and complex, which led to errors, delays, and frustration among sales associates. Implementing <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/sales-performance-management.html#products">the SAP SuccessFactors Incentive Management solution</a> helped streamline the process, providing real-time monitoring of commission calculations. This allowed Neiman Marcus to identify and resolve issues proactively, resulting in improved accuracy and timeliness of commission payments. “Rather than waiting to hear from associates that something is wrong, we can monitor the calculations in real-time and resolve issues in advance,” said Jasper. This shift has been a game-changer for Neiman Marcus, driving better sales and revenue growth.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="empower-sales-teams-with-the-tools-they-need-to-create-effective-sales-experiences">Empower sales teams with the tools they need to create effective sales experiences</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/sales-performance-management.html">Find out how</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP SuccessFactors Incentive Management is one of the sales performance management solutions in the SAP SuccessFactors portfolio, and it offers a sophisticated platform for tailoring incentive programs to suit the unique needs of retail associates. With powerful analytics, embedded intelligence, and built-in workflows, this solution can revolutionize compensation management. Its intelligent design can not only foster trust but also ignite motivation among store associates. Through a user-friendly mobile app, retail customers can enjoy a comprehensive and easily accessible view of both store and individual performance metrics, promoting transparency and a unified understanding of team dynamics and trends. Personalized recommendations, relevant insights, and interactive monitoring help enhance the user experience, while the mobile app helps ensure that store associates can access their incentives anytime, anywhere, from any device.</p>
  <p>The solution’s agility helps facilitate a swift rollout of new and updated compensation plans, offering the flexibility to manage broadly or tailor plans to individual needs. With a steadfast commitment to accuracy and traceability, associates can trust the fairness of calculations, fostering a positive work environment. The effective dating functionalities help further empower organizations, allowing seamless management of associate promotions and transfers.</p>
  <p>“Retail businesses more than ever need the ability to design and manage incentive plans that align with ever-changing organizational goals, with a focus on store-level personalization and granularity that allow for improved accuracy and timeliness of commission payments,” said Rahul Iyer, general manager of Sales Performance Management at SAP. “With SAP SuccessFactors Incentive Management, retailers can incorporate key performance indicators, such as sales per hour and units per sale, into their incentive structure. The mobile app can provide visibility and transparency into individual and store performance, effectively motivating and ensuring optimal performance from their associates.”</p>
  <p>In essence, SAP SuccessFactors Incentive Management emerges as an indispensable tool, helping to empower retail customers to optimize workforce performance and drive sustained success. Displaying key performance indicators and incentives has proven to be a game changer, helping to drive focus on store and individual performance. The result? Associates are more attentive to customers, guiding them through purchasing decisions and enhancing overall satisfaction.</p>
  <p>In the always-changing retail world, success comes down to three things: using better technology, having happy employees, and keeping customers in focus. The story of Neiman Marcus proves that automating incentives can be a game changer. It shows how a motivated and well-connected team can not just boost how things work but also bring in more sales and money.</p>
  <p>To stay ahead in retail, you need to be ready for change and invest in both tech and your team. This is a clear lesson for retailers planning for the future. Learn more about how <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2023/03/509d257a-677e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">sales performance management can simplify the retail industry</a>. To learn more about how sales performance management solutions can support your organization, visit the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/sales-performance-management.html">sales performance management product page on sap.com</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Kevin Coxwell is vice president of GTM for Sales Performance Management at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-sap-news-on-linkedin">Connect with SAP News on LinkedIn</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news">Follow us</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-engagement</category>
            <category>news-tag/nrf</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
            <category>news-tag/sales-performance-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Four-Day Workweek Paradox]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/the-four-day-workweek-paradox</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/the-four-day-workweek-paradox</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Shorten the week, and productivity may go up instead of down. But getting those results takes careful program design.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15b07fc0e7bd5a3b3f19d042af067ca38930006d9.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15b07fc0e7bd5a3b3f19d042af067ca38930006d9.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_15b07fc0e7bd5a3b3f19d042af067ca38930006d9.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="portrait Of Businesswoman In Office Standing By Window" src="./media_15b07fc0e7bd5a3b3f19d042af067ca38930006d9.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1044">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="the-four-day-workweek-paradox">The Four-Day Workweek Paradox</h1>
        <p>Shorten the week, and productivity may go up instead of down. But getting those results takes careful program design.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>By Caitlynn Sendra and Lin Grensing-Pophal</p>
  <p>In the summer of 2019, <a href="https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2019/nov/04/microsoft-japan-four-day-work-week-productivity">Microsoft Japan</a> implemented a pilot project – the Work-Life Choice Challenge – providing its 2,300 employees with the opportunity to work a four-day workweek with Fridays off. The specific changes to the work schedule included giving employees paid leave on Fridays, encouraging shorter meetings (30 minutes or less), and promoting remote communication instead of face-to-face meetings. The pilot project lasted the entire month of August. Despite a reduction in workdays, the company reported a 40% boost in productivity. They were also able to conserve resources, like electricity consumption, which dropped by 23%. Based on the results of the pilot, Microsoft Japan has continued to offer a four-day week.</p>
  <p>That, of course, was before the pandemic knocked over work models, norms, preconceived notions, and expectations. Since then, interest in the idea of a shorter workweek has only gained momentum.</p>
  <p>A <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/03/02/is-a-four-day-work-week-catching-on-in-asia-it-depends-on-the-country.html">global study by nonprofit 4 Day Week Global</a> and researchers from Boston College, University College Dublin, and Cambridge University, has shown that most of the 33 companies and 903 employees who took part in the four-day workweek trials are unlikely to return to a standard five-day workweek. The majority of the firms were in the United States and Ireland, although trials have also taken place in the UK, Japan, Iceland, Spain, and New Zealand. Microsoft Japan claimed productivity rose by just under 40% during their four-day workweek pilot, while a trial in Iceland between 2015 and 2019 saw 2,500 workers participate with well-being increasing in areas such as stress, burnout, health, and work-life balance.</p>
  <p>It may not work for every type of job or industry. On the other hand, some countries – well, <a href="https://www.brusselstimes.com/325240/four-day-working-week-comes-into-effect-who-can-use-it-and-how-to-apply">Belgium</a> and Iceland, so far – may require that most types of companies offer employees the option. Regardless, given today’s burgeoning demand for workers with specialized skills, it pays to explore the potential of a four-day week to attract and keep talent.</p>
  <p>There are several options for structuring this work model to meet your organizational and employee needs. The primary concern organizational leaders express is productivity – ensuring that employees can, and will, accomplish the same (or more), whether they’re working the same hours in fewer days, or fewer hours overall. Some companies also fret over responsiveness to customers, although this often can be addressed with overlapping work schedules. However, there is a wide range of variables to consider and a lot of complexity in implementation.</p>
  <p>Since it’s not a decision to take lightly, this article walks through evidence of the potential benefits and downsides, different ways to structure work requirements and insights into how to increase your chances of success. These range from the seemingly obvious (train your managers!) to some easier to overlook (such as actively encouraging paid time off).</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_184537c8c3ecd543c84d5ccbb7e268d1b04229f8c.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_184537c8c3ecd543c84d5ccbb7e268d1b04229f8c.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_184537c8c3ecd543c84d5ccbb7e268d1b04229f8c.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Two executives having a business conversation sitting in a coffee shop" src="./media_184537c8c3ecd543c84d5ccbb7e268d1b04229f8c.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="240" height="160">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="why-consider-a-four-day-workweek">Why consider a four-day workweek?</h2>
  <p>It’s interesting to note and may come as a surprise, but the five-day workweek really hasn’t been around that long. It was promoted in the 1920s by <a href="https://firmspace.com/theproworker/from-strikes-to-labor-laws-how-the-us-adopted-the-5-day-workweek#:~:text=The%20five%2Dday%2C%2040%2D,no%20changes%20in%20employee%20compensation.">Henry Ford</a>, who felt that giving people more free time – not having them work every day – would help spur the economy. In 1930, <a href="https://www.adeccogroup.com/future-of-work/latest-insights/the-advantages-and-disadvantages-of-the-four-day-work-week/">economist John Maynard</a> Keynes predicted that by 2030 people might only work 15 hours per week. That prediction appears quite off track so far, but the idea of working fewer hours while accomplishing the same (or even better) outcomes has lingered.</p>
  <p>In fact, there are many who believe that “work will expand to fill the time allotted for its completion”– a phenomenon referred to as <a href="https://asana.com/resources/parkinsons-law">Parkinson’s Law</a>. In this view, even in models with fewer total hours worked, employees may accomplish just as much as before, and be happier doing it.</p>
  <p>It’s not a crazy notion. Both research and practical experience with four-day workweek models point to real benefits for organizations, says Lili Tenney, director of outreach and programs at the <a href="https://coloradosph.cuanschutz.edu/research-and-practice/centers-programs/chwe">Center for Health, Work &#x26; Environment at the Colorado School of Public Health</a>, and a renowned expert in workplace productivity. These include employee satisfaction, heightened productivity, and cost savings. Let’s dig into them.</p>
  <h2 id="increased-employee-satisfaction-and-well-being">Increased employee satisfaction and well-being</h2>
  <p>Tenney emphasizes that a four-day workweek can enhance employee satisfaction and overall well-being. Employees may experience reduced stress levels, increased motivation, and a stronger sense of work-life balance. This leads to higher job satisfaction, improved mental health, and decreased burnout rates. Consequently, organizations witness higher employee retention rates and attract top talent.</p>
  <p>A <a href="https://static1.squarespace.com/static/60b956cbe7bf6f2efd86b04e/t/63f3df56276b3e6d7870207e/1676926845047/UK-4-Day-Week-Pilot-Results-Report-2023.pdf">study in the UK</a> found that people who worked the equivalent of four days instead of five “experienced decreased absenteeism (65%) and reduced employee turnover (57%), while employees benefited from improved well-being, including reduced stress (39%) and levels of burnout (71%). These companies also maintained or even increased revenue (by 1.4%), despite the significant reduction in work hours.”</p>
  <h2 id="heightened-productivity">Heightened productivity</h2>
  <p>Contrary to concerns about productivity loss, Tenney highlights the research findings that a condensed workweek can actually <em>boost</em> productivity. Employees can become more focused, driven, and efficient, utilizing their limited time wisely. The compressed schedule encourages individuals to prioritize tasks, eliminate time-wasting activities, and seek innovative solutions to streamline workflows. In addition, the increased downtime allows employees to recharge, resulting in improved concentration and creativity.</p>
  <h2 id="improved-work-life-balance">Improved work-life balance</h2>
  <p>An obvious corollary to a four-day workweek is the extra day off, often creating three-day weekends. This gives employees more time for personal pursuits, family commitments, travel, or leisure activities. This enhanced balance positively affects their mental and physical well-being, fostering higher levels of engagement and satisfaction when they return to work. Employers who prioritize work-life balance experience reduced absenteeism and increased employee loyalty.</p>
  <p>This is especially important for working parents, says Kati Lechner, director of people operations and talent strategies at <a href="https://wonderlic.com/">Wonderlic</a>, a company known for its success with flexible work arrangements. “It eliminates the need for an extra day of childcare when kids aren’t in school,” she notes. In addition, she says, the combination of flexible policies and the four-day workweek “supports employees’ unique needs in the workplace by allowing for better work-life integration for everyone, supporting our commitment to diversity and inclusion.”</p>
  <h2 id="potential-cost-savings">Potential cost savings</h2>
  <p>Tenney notes that there also are potential cost savings associated with a shorter workweek. These include reduced energy consumption, lower utility bills, decreased office supply expenses, and fewer employee-related costs, such as transportation and meals. In addition, the reduced turnover and improved employee satisfaction lead to savings in recruitment and training.</p>
  <p>Research tells us that employees are coming to demand the type of flexibility a four-day workweek can provide. <a href="https://www.mercer.com/en-ca/insights/talent-and-transformation/attracting-and-retaining-talent/four-day-workweek-the-cure-for-burnout/#:~:text=A%20stat%20that%20speaks%20volumes,employers%20to%20tackle%20wage%20inflation.">Mercer research</a>, for instance, indicates that “one in three employees would give up a pay increase this year in return for a fully flexible or compressed workweek. With cost-of-living concerns and an uncertain economic outlook, offering time off could be one way for employers to tackle wage inflation.” Mercer’s 2022–2023 Global Talent Trends Study collected insights from 11,000 executives, HR leaders, and workers across 16 countries in 2022 and 2023.</p>
  <p>While there are certainly still companies that are resistant to a move to a shorter workweek or other flexible scheduling options, they may ultimately be forced to move in this direction, says Lechner. “Flexibility in work arrangements is becoming increasingly important for attracting and retaining talent,” she says. In fact, Wonderlic has received as many as 6,000 applicants for a single job posting, indicating, Lechner believes, the high demand for the type of flexibility the company provides.</p>
  <p>In addition, the United States and other countries are introducing regulations and requirements for organizations to at least consider the four-day workweek option. <a href="https://stateline.org/2023/03/28/a-4-day-workweek-gains-lawmaker-support-in-some-states/">According to <em>Stateline</em></a>, "In the past three years, at least six states – California, Hawaii, Maryland, New York, Pennsylvania, and Washington – have considered bills to mandate, incentivize, or allow the switch to a four-day week.”</p>
  <p>Short weeks aren’t a one-size-fits-all proposition. Organizations can consider a number of approaches in the search forthe right workweek structure for their needs.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1484049ebf7598757dfa2209b8921cc47cef6acc3.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1484049ebf7598757dfa2209b8921cc47cef6acc3.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1484049ebf7598757dfa2209b8921cc47cef6acc3.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="man playing with his little daughter in nature" src="./media_1484049ebf7598757dfa2209b8921cc47cef6acc3.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="employee-experience-management">Employee Experience Management</h3>
        <p>Bridge the employee experience gaps by listening to your people's needs.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/employee-experience-management.html">Learn more</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="different-ways-to-structure-work">Different ways to structure work</h2>
  <p>If a five-day week seems onerous, consider the “996” working hour system common in parts of Asia until quite recently: employees worked from 9 a.m. to 9 p.m., six days a week.</p>
  <p>The Chinese Supreme Court <a href="https://www.npr.org/2021/08/30/1032458104/12-hour-6-day-996-work-schedule-illegal-china-deaths-tech-industry">deemed this practice illegal</a> in 2021. And overall, long workweeks are becoming less common around the globe.</p>
  <p>Even in Asia, CNBC notes, some countries – Singapore, Vietnam, Thailand, the Philippines, and Indonesia – are open to a four-day week. And in Europe, the concept is quite popular. Iceland, in fact, led a large four-day workweek pilot between 2015 and 2019, with very positive results. “As of 2022, workers represented by unions in Iceland – close to 90% of the workforce – have won the right to request a shorter workweek,” <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/04/14/countries-that-are-embracing-or-experimenting-with-a-4-day-workweek.html#:~:text=Iceland,work%2Dlife%20balance%20and%20productivity.">CNBC reports</a>. Iceland isn’t the only country where unions are leading the switch – the UK, Portugal, Spain, and others are <a href="https://www.euronews.com/next/2023/06/21/the-four-day-week-which-countries-have-embraced-it-and-how-s-it-going-so-far">also moving in this direction</a>, or testing through pilots. The United States lags well behind in corporate enthusiasm.</p>
  <p>So how much do employees actually work during these four-day weeks? Programs can take on a number of different variations depending on the organization and its needs. Common forms include:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong><a href="https://www.zavvy.io/blog/how-to-implement-a-4-day-workweek">Condensed workweek</a></strong>: Employees work the same number of hours but across four days instead of five.</li>
    <li><strong><a href="https://www.4dayweek.com/us-ireland-results">Reduced workweeks</a></strong>: Employees work 32 instead of 40 hours a week, with no reduction in pay, and typically the same productivity expectations.</li>
    <li><strong>Reduced output:</strong> Employees have the option to work fewer days and hours — with a corresponding cut in productivity and pay.</li>
    <li><strong><a href="https://www.hcamag.com/us/specialization/benefits/what-are-the-most-popular-ways-to-structure-4-day-workweeks/451948">Staggered schedules</a></strong>: Employees work in one of the structures above, but with different four-day schedules to allow for continuous coverage of key business operations.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>There are many tradeoffs to consider. For example, staggered schedules might mean the office remains open on all weekdays, yielding less energy savings. This might not be the driving factor for choosing one model over another, but it could be important in getting a full, accurate picture of the results.</p>
  <p>Each company will need to determine what works best for them, given their legal requirements, industry, structure, employee, and customer needs. The way this looks in most settings is that the workweek is shortened to 32 hours instead of the traditional 40, while each employee’s workload remains the same. The idea is that without typical workplace distractions and fewer personal stressors (commute times, fewer opportunities for work-life balance, etc.) productivity gains will help to cover those eight hours.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11887c56a7fdeaded8019ce34d547849a192208ea.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11887c56a7fdeaded8019ce34d547849a192208ea.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_11887c56a7fdeaded8019ce34d547849a192208ea.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Four woman sitting around a conference table" src="./media_11887c56a7fdeaded8019ce34d547849a192208ea.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="245" height="160">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="making-it-happen">Making it happen</h2>
  <p>One of the greatest barriers to moving to a four-day workweek is internal resistance. Organizational leaders, and managers in particular, can be resistant to flexibility of work hours; their primary concern is the fear of decreased productivity.</p>
  <p>Just as Microsoft Japan did, starting with a pilot can be a good way to dip your toes into the reality of a four-day workweek while identifying potential barriers and how to get around them. That’s what Wonderlic did when it embarked on its shorter workweek journey, Lechner says. They conducted their pilot in the summer of 2021 and have continued to operate in a four-day workweek model. They’ve experienced an increase in employee engagement and happiness without a significant drop in productivity and found that flexibility helps to attract new candidates to the organization.</p>
  <p>Lechner and other veterans of the shift offer the following strategies effectively implementing a four-day workweek structure.</p>
  <h2 id="pilot-first">Pilot first</h2>
  <p>Mini experiments, or pilots, can help organizations see exactly how a four-day workweek will affect their organizations and their productivity, easing resistance and revealing processes and supporting decisions that can make the idea work better. Every organization is different, and a pilot project, like Microsoft Japan’s, will help uncover unique requirements.</p>
  <h2 id="equip-your-managers-to-keep-their-teams-humming">Equip your managers to keep their teams humming</h2>
  <p>Tackling the many misconceptions about the four-day workweek can be an important first step in getting managers on board. For example, the four-day workweek doesn’t necessarily mean all employees will get Friday or Monday off. But it could mean that companies get the same amount of productivity out of people in fewer hours by making schedules more flexible, giving people more personal and vacation time, making allowances for family duties, and so on. And is particularly important for managers to understand – that they are still in control. Managers often report a sense of being “out of sight, out of mind” when seeing workers less often and feel a loss of control. In truth, of course, that’s not the case. What it may be, though, is a sign that managers aren’t adept at this new type of management and may not be evaluating employee performance based on objective outcomes. They may need training and support to help them feel more confident managing in a condensed work week.</p>
  <p>At Wonderlic, Lechner says, managers implemented different strategies, such as rotating schedules or skeleton crews to address customer support needs on employees’ designated days off. Deliberate planning of meetings and organizational sessions was crucial to optimize time and collaboration, she says.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="the-digital-distractions-problem">The digital distractions problem</h3>
        <p>How managers can avoid decreased productivity, stress, and burnout.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="/resources/addressing-digital-distractions">Get advice</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="ensure-the-right-balance-of-a-focus-on-short--and-long-term-objectives">Ensure the right balance of a focus on short- and long-term objectives</h2>
  <p>There’s an important balance to be struck between productivity and innovation, says Tenney, who refers to this as the “mere urgency effect” – a phenomenon where people focus more on urgent, short-term tasks, neglecting long-term more strategic thinking and innovation. The creative and innovative nature of work is important, Tenney says. In order to nurture that, employees need unstructured, or free time.</p>
  <p>“Focus on productivity measures, but not everything needs to be structured – provide flexibility to allow employees to connect with others,” Tenney advises. One way to do this, she suggests, is to provide employees the flexibility to block time on their calendars to provide them the opportunity to focus on what she calls “deep work.”</p>
  <h2 id="provide-time-management-training-and-resources-for-employees">Provide time management training and resources for employees</h2>
  <p>Time management isn’t a skill that comes naturally to all employees. Companies can benefit from providing time management training and ongoing resources for employees to help them learn about and adopt best practices for being as productive as possible. This might include formal training as well as support groups where employees can share their own best practices with others.</p>
  <h2 id="encourage-pto">Encourage PTO</h2>
  <p>Another must: encouraging employees to take time off and use their paid time off (PTO) to prevent burnout, which is a real risk. “We have to be deliberate about encouraging people to take their time off,” Lechner says. “We’ve seen PTO usage drop dramatically, and it’s important for people to take breaks to be fully present at work.”</p>
  <h2 id="evaluate-learn-and-adjust">Evaluate, learn, and adjust</h2>
  <p>In some cases, Tenney says, companies may try a four-day workweek only to realize it just wasn’t right for them. She cites a company that attempted to implement a four-day workweek but eventually found it challenging: employees ended up working more hours, and the fluctuating demands of the workload caused stress levels to become unpredictable. As a result, the company decided to revert to a five-day workweek with flexible schedules, allowing employees to work fewer than 40 hours per week while still prioritizing productivity focused on performance goals versus hours worked.</p>
  <p>Others have also found that they couldn’t make a four-day workweek work. Lachy Gray, managing director at <a href="https://www.yarno.com.au/">Yarno</a>, for instance, shared his company’s experience in a <a href="https://www.yarno.com.au/blog/4-day-work-week-failure/">post on the company’s website</a> saying: “We wanted it to work because we believe in the principles behind it. But we have to face the facts, that it's not working as we thought it would.” The company is going back to a five-day week, although Gray says, “we’re still committed to flexible working hours on those five days.”</p>
  <p>In the UK’s four-day workweek trial, <a href="https://static1.squarespace.com/static/60b956cbe7bf6f2efd86b04e/t/63f3df56276b3e6d7870207e/1676926845047/UK-4-Day-Week-Pilot-Results-Report-2023.pdf">about 8%</a> of respondents found that the four-day model simply didn’t work for them. <a href="https://www.bbc.com/worklife/article/20230319-four-day-workweek-trial-the-firms-where-it-didnt-work">Reporting for Work: In Progress, Alex Christian says</a>: “Even those firms continuing with reduced hours are navigating new challenges arising from shortened workweeks. Though this reflects a small portion of the trial’s participants, it means the four-day workweek isn’t an automatic solution for all.”</p>
  <h2 id="is-the-four-day-workweek-right-for-your-team">Is the four-day workweek right for your team?</h2>
  <p>Microsoft Japan has never looked back since its successful pilot in 2019, joining <a href="https://tech.co/news/companies-4-day-work-week">several other large companies</a> that have successfully adopted this model. By prioritizing clear communication, flexible scheduling, and effective time management, organizations can navigate the transition to a four-day workweek successfully and reap the rewards this increasingly popular work model provides.</p>
  <p>As with any major undertaking, of course, “the devil is in the details.” In a follow-up article, we will take a closer look into the many details — from labor laws to visas to anti-discrimination regulations — you need to consider to ensure your four-day workweek efforts deliver the best results.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <h4 id="read-more-in-this-series">Read more in this series</h4>
  <div class="collection">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h6 id="best-practice-guide">Best Practice Guide</h6>
        <p><a href="/resources/7-due-diligence-steps-for-the-four-day-workweek">7 Due Diligence Steps for the Four-Day Workweek</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>
        <h6 id="explainer">Explainer</h6>
        <p><a href="/resources/the-four-day-workweek-paradox">The Four-Day Workweek Paradox</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>sidebar</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/what-is</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Eastman Energizes HR Reporting to Deliver One-Stop Insights to Leaders]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/eastman-hr-reporting-deliver-insights-to-leaders</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/eastman-hr-reporting-deliver-insights-to-leaders</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Eastman accelerated HR reporting for improved efficiency and insights using story reports in SAP SuccessFactors People Analytics. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>topic/data-analytics</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-preferred-success</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-employee-central</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-people-analytics</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-recruiting</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[CallidusCloud to SAP: Evolution to Running Better Smarter and Faster]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/calliduscloud-to-sap-evolution</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/calliduscloud-to-sap-evolution</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is excited to help CallidusCloud customers make the strategic move to the SAP SuccessFactors portfolio. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sales-performance-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-hana</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>