<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/product/sap-integrated-business-planning-for-supply-chain/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ericsson Chooses SAP Software to Connect Supply Chains]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/ericsson-chooses-sap-integrated-business-planning-supply-chains</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/ericsson-chooses-sap-integrated-business-planning-supply-chains</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Ericsson chose SAP Integrated Business Planning for Supply Chain to drive operational efficiencies in its global supply chain network.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>product/sap-integrated-business-planning-for-supply-chain</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Chemicals Supplier BYK Harmonized Supply Chain Planning Processes]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/byk-harmonized-supply-chain-planning-processes</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/byk-harmonized-supply-chain-planning-processes</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[BYK, a global supplier of specialty chemicals, has implemented a new supply chain demand planning system using SAP solutions. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/chemicals</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>product/sap-integrated-business-planning-for-supply-chain</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-preferred-success</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
            <category>product/sap-supply-chain-control-tower</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Is Supply Chain Innovation Even Possible in an Era of Tighter Regulation?]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2024/01/is-supply-chain-innovation-possible-era-tighter-regulation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2024/01/is-supply-chain-innovation-possible-era-tighter-regulation</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[When it comes to supply chain regulation, compliance and innovation are not mutually exclusive. Investing in advanced technologies can help.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/executive-blog</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/catena-x</category>
            <category>non-sap-event/wef-davos</category>
            <category>product/sap-integrated-business-planning-for-supply-chain</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Jowat Doubles Productivity with Smarter Maintenance and Strategic Insight into Asset Management]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/jowat-smarter-maintenance-strategic-insight-asset-management</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/jowat-smarter-maintenance-strategic-insight-asset-management</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With SAP solutions, Jowat empowered its technicians to prioritize work more effectively and make smarter decisions about asset investments.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/asset-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-enterprise-support</category>
            <category>product/sap-integrated-business-planning-for-supply-chain</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP and Infosys Introduce New Sustainable and Innovative Industry Cloud Solution]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/sap-and-infosys-introduce-sustainable-industry-cloud-solution</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/sap-and-infosys-introduce-sustainable-industry-cloud-solution</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With the SAP-validated partner use case program, Infosys and SAP created a solution to help companies monitor their carbon footprints.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_164f38f864e0733a6806af629b2d24613241a4b15.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_164f38f864e0733a6806af629b2d24613241a4b15.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_164f38f864e0733a6806af629b2d24613241a4b15.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP and Infosys Introduce New Sustainable and Innovative Industry Cloud Solution" src="./media_164f38f864e0733a6806af629b2d24613241a4b15.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-and-infosys-introduce-new-sustainable-and-innovative-industry-cloud-solution">SAP and Infosys Introduce New Sustainable and Innovative Industry Cloud Solution</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>In today’s fast-paced and dynamic business environment, <a href="/topics/sustainability">sustainability</a> is no longer a buzzword; it’s a critical business priority. Investors and customers seek more sustainable business practices from their solution providers and enterprises are keenly focused on integrating sustainability into their operations. This is no easy lift, and it doesn’t happen overnight. Several challenges need to be addressed, including action planning, effective resource allocation, and prioritization.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>For companies to act sustainably, responsibly, and efficiently, they must harness the power of data-driven decisions and advanced technology to reduce their carbon footprint and create sustainable product portfolios. Enter SAP and its broad ecosystem of industry cloud partners with a shared vision to help businesses become strategic, sustainable, intelligent enterprises.</p>
  <h2 id="hack2build-opens-door-for-innovation-and-sustainability">Hack2Build Opens Door for Innovation and Sustainability</h2>
  <p>The <a href="https://events.sap.com/hack2build/en/home">Hack2Build event from SAP</a>, organized by SAP Co-Innovation Lab, is an initiative designed to harness the creativity and speed of prototyping industry cloud solutions by SAP partners in days as opposed to weeks. At a September 2022 Hack2Build event, SAP partner Infosys presented a solution for organizations to identify, track, predict, and refine carbon emissions during sales and operations planning (S&#x26;OP) and make sustainable decisions. The solution, <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2023/08/7affe1f5-847e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Sustainable S&#x26;OP and Carbon Footprint Management</a>, was built using SAP Integrated Business Planning (SAP IBP) for Supply Chain, SAP S/4HANA, SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP), SAP Integration Suite, and SAP Sustainability Footprint Management.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="industry-cloud-solutions-from-sap-and-partners-can-help-you-find-a-competitive-edge">Industry cloud solutions from SAP and partners can help you find a competitive edge</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/industry-cloud.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="framework-for-tracking-emissions-leverages-the-power-of-saps-industry-cloud">Framework for Tracking Emissions Leverages the Power of SAP’s Industry Cloud</h2>
  <p>Infosys’ carbon footprint solution calculates carbon emissions based on greenhouse gas protocols and global warming potential factors across an organization’s procurement, production, and distribution processes. It helps calculate key information, such as estimates of CO2e emissions per order level, thereby helping to make decisions that can ensure a smaller carbon footprint. The solution also provides an innovative framework to help companies identify, track, predict, and refine their carbon emissions numbers throughout the entire supply chain process.</p>
  <h2 id="sap-validated-partner-use-case-program-offers-momentum-to-service-partner-solution">SAP-Validated Partner Use Case Program Offers Momentum to Service Partner Solution</h2>
  <p>Infosys’ solution is part of the SAP-validated partner use case program. The program was established to give SAP service partners the ability to showcase, position, and promote solutions and spotlight their expertise of SAP Business Technology Platform, leveraging the power of SAP’s vast customer base and industry networks.</p>
  <p>The SAP-validated partner use case program offers service partners the ability to:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Get amplified market reach</strong>: Increased visibility enables service partners to target a broader audience, opening doors to new markets and untapped opportunities. Leveraging SAP’s robust platform, partners can position themselves strategically and expand their global reach.</li>
    <li><strong>Collaborate and co-innovate</strong>: Participating in the SAP-validated partner use case program can foster collaboration with SAP experts, industry leaders, and customers.</li>
    <li><strong>Access a dynamic ecosystem</strong>: Partners can benefit from SAP’s ecosystem, where they can collaborate, exchange knowledge, and share best practices with some of the industry’s best leaders.</li>
    <li><strong>Develop customer-centric solutions</strong>: The program helps put the customer at the core of solution development. Service partners can gain valuable customer insights though interactions facilitated by SAP, leading to better-tailored products and services that can precisely address users’ pain points.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>The program presents opportunities for both customers and service partners to flourish. By achieving certification, service partners can earn credibility, expand market reach, and foster collaborative innovation with industry giants. Its streamlined processes help accelerate time-to-market, providing a significant advantage in today’s fast-paced business landscape.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-information-training-tools-and-resources-you-need">Get the information, training, tools, and resources you need</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://partneredge.sap.com/en/welcome.html?pexpRequestedURL=%2Fen%2Flibrary%2Feducation%2Fpsd%2F2023%2Fmar%2Fe_oe_te_w_rnbo_31837.html">Visit the SAP Partner Portal site</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The program unlocks a door to a dynamic ecosystem where partners can learn, grow, and develop customer-centric solutions that can meet industry demands head-on. For partners aiming to thrive in their respective industries, this program is a game changer. Service partners are encouraged to embrace the power of the SAP-validated partner use case program and transform their business.</p>
  <p>“Infosys is delighted to publish the Infosys Sustainable S&#x26;OP and Carbon Footprint Management Solution through the SAP-validated partner use case program,” said Atul Chorbele, AVP at Infosys. “We are confident that customers across industries will benefit from adopting this solution.”</p>
  <p>Holger Brammer, Global Partner Ecosystem vice president at SAP, praised this partner solution and the development process: “It was impressive to see how fast Infosys developed this solution on SAP BTP and integrated it with SAP S/4HANA, SAP IBP, and SAP Sustainability Footprint Management. I’m quite confident that this solution will resonate very well with customers.”</p>
  <p>To learn how to build industry innovation on SAP BTP and the SAP-validated partner use case program or get more information about <a href="mailto:lucca.sperl@sap.com">validated use cases on the SAP PartnerEdge site</a>, contact <a href="mailto:lucca.sperl@sap.com">Lucca Sperl</a>, industry cloud innovation program lead. To learn more about Infosys’ solution, <a href="https://www.infosys.com/campaigns/documents/sop-carbon-footprint-management.pdf">visit here</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>Vidya Gugnani is senior director and industry cloud ecosystem lead for Strategic Partners, North America at SAP.<br>Nitin Majahan is COE lead for SAP Industrial Manufacturing at Infosys.</p>
        <p>Top image courtesy of SAP employee Karsten Hohage</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-emissions</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-footprint</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-integrated-business-planning-for-supply-chain</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP IBP Wins Best Feature Set, Best Relationship, Best Value for Price from TrustRadius]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/sap-ibp-trustradius-2023-best-feature-set-best-relationship-best-value-for-price</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/sap-ibp-trustradius-2023-best-feature-set-best-relationship-best-value-for-price</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Integrated Business Planning for Supply Chain has been honored with three prestigious Best of 2023 Awards by TrustRadius.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_194c0e322e4ef8811805bf5ed71fd65160a324faf.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_194c0e322e4ef8811805bf5ed71fd65160a324faf.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_194c0e322e4ef8811805bf5ed71fd65160a324faf.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP IBP Wins Best Feature Set, Best Relationship, Best Value for Price from TrustRadius" src="./media_194c0e322e4ef8811805bf5ed71fd65160a324faf.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-ibp-wins-best-feature-set-best-relationship-best-value-for-price-from-trustradius">SAP IBP Wins Best Feature Set, Best Relationship, Best Value for Price from TrustRadius</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>SAP Integrated Business Planning (SAP IBP) for Supply Chain has been honored with three prestigious Best of 2023 Awards by TrustRadius, the trusted decisioning platform for B2B technology buyers, in the areas of:</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <ul>
    <li>Best Feature Set</li>
    <li>Best Relationship</li>
    <li>Best Value for Price</li>
  </ul>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <picture>
          <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b21fb4a340e7e1db1147e59132e4b04d0797af6c.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
          <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b21fb4a340e7e1db1147e59132e4b04d0797af6c.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
          <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1b21fb4a340e7e1db1147e59132e4b04d0797af6c.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
          <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_1b21fb4a340e7e1db1147e59132e4b04d0797af6c.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="624" height="203">
        </picture>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The awards are based on unbiased customer reviews and feedback, and the recognition underscores SAP’s commitment to delivering innovative and best-in-class solutions that empower organizations to thrive in an increasingly digital and dynamic business landscape.</p>
  <h2 id="thank-you-sap-integrated-business-planning-customers">Thank You, SAP Integrated Business Planning Customers</h2>
  <p>We thank our customers around the globe for taking the time for providing feedback and making SAP IBP the success it is today. We are humbled by this recognition and will continue in our mission of delivering intelligent supply chain planning solutions that accelerates your digital journey to the cloud.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="run-a-sustainable-risk-resilient-supply-chain-in-the-face-of-constant-change">Run a sustainable, risk-resilient supply chain in the face of constant change</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/supply-chain-planning.html">Learn how</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>More than 1,000 companies worldwide use SAP IBP to streamline <a href="/topics/supply-chain-management">supply chain</a> and planning processes. Ranging from large multinational corporations to midsize enterprises, these companies span a wide range of industries, including manufacturing, retail, consumer goods, pharmaceuticals, automotive, aerospace, and many others. To learn about how companies have leveraged SAP IBP along with the benefits they have achieved, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/supply-chain-planning.html">explore customer success stories here</a>.</p>
  <p>In providing feedback to the <a href="https://www.trustradius.com/products/sap-integrated-business-planning/reviews">TrustRadius survey on SAP Integrated Business Planning</a>, 100% of respondents reported that they are “happy with the feature set” and that SAP IBP “delivers good value for the price.”</p>
  <p>Here are a sample TrustRadius reviews from our users:</p>
  <p>“SAP has allowed me to see my entire value stream in one quick glance. I am able to see where my products are, what issues it is they are having, and both the delivery stream to/from my shop.”</p>
  <p>– Verified User, General Manager in Manufacturing, Airlines/Aviation Company</p>
  <p>“The integration with the ERP and the pre-built-in models provides great business value. It drives standardization and provides a good framework to grow the business and the process.”</p>
  <p>– Verified User, Manager in Information Technology, Consumer Goods Company</p>
  <p>“One of the most powerful business tools available for best decision making.”</p>
  <p>– TrustRadius Reviewer, Technology Officer, Wow Detailing Studio</p>
  <p>SAP Integrated Business Planning is a cloud-based supply chain planning solution that scales to accommodate business growth and integrates with other SAP and third-party systems. It integrates key aspects of the planning process including demand, supply, inventory, and sales and operations planning.</p>
  <p>Designed to help streamline planning and improve performance, SAP IBP supports data-driven decision-making and simplified collaboration to increase operational efficiency. This is accomplished with help from advanced analytics, artificial intelligence (AI), and powerful optimization algorithms that enable real-time visibility, better forecasting, and faster decision-making across the entire supply chain.</p>
  <p>Some of the key capabilities of SAP IBP include:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Demand management:</strong> SAP IBP integrates historical data, market trends, and advanced predictive analytics to generate more accurate demand forecasts.</li>
    <li><strong>Response and supply planning:</strong> SAP IBP takes capacity constraints, lead times, and inventory levels into account in order to optimize production and distribution plans and more efficiently meet customer demands.</li>
    <li><strong>Inventory management:</strong> SAP IBP helps with maintaining optimal inventory levels by balancing the trade-offs between carrying costs, stockouts, and service levels.</li>
    <li><strong>Sales and operations planning:</strong> SAP IBP provides a unified platform for collaborative planning, allowing different departments to align on strategic goals and operational plans.</li>
    <li><strong>Demand-driven replenishment:</strong> SAP IBP supports DDMRP for strategically positioning inventory buffers in the supply chain to absorb variability and uncertainty.</li>
    <li><strong>Supply chain control tower:</strong> SAP IBP supports the real-time supply chain visibility and enhanced analytics needed to quickly respond to changing market conditions and customer requirements.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>TrustRadius is an independent source for insights and ratings for business software solutions, helping buyers make confident decisions. The platform leverages verified customer reviews and ratings to recognize software providers who consistently deliver exceptional products and experiences to their customers. The organization’s 2023 Top Rated awards distinguish products that have received excellent marks for customer satisfaction. Award criteria are based on customer reviews within the last 12 months, product ratings, and customer sentiment.</p>
  <p>“The 2023 Best of Award for SAP Integrated Business Planning from TrustRadius, a leading B2B software decisioning platform, is a testament to the positive feedback and satisfaction expressed by SAP IBP users,” Megan Headley, vice president of Research at TrustRadius, shared. “The prestigious recognition, carefully evaluated by users and experts alike, highlights SAP IBP’s commitment to excellence and ability to meet the evolving needs of businesses across the globe.”</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>product/sap-integrated-business-planning-for-supply-chain</category>
            <category>news-tag/trustradius</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Supply Chain Issues Keeping CEOs Up at Night]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2023/11/supply-chain-issues-keeping-ceos-up-at-night</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2023/11/supply-chain-issues-keeping-ceos-up-at-night</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Supply chain issues keep executives up at night, but SAP is working to leverage the power of generative AI for supply chain resilience.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17fce40551915dfea41e19d0bfc190fb085838212.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17fce40551915dfea41e19d0bfc190fb085838212.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_17fce40551915dfea41e19d0bfc190fb085838212.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Supply Chain Issues Keeping CEOs Up at Night" src="./media_17fce40551915dfea41e19d0bfc190fb085838212.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="supply-chain-issues-keeping-ceos-up-at-night">Supply Chain Issues Keeping CEOs Up at Night</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Building risk-resilient supply chains is one of the top issues CEOs are discussing on earning calls and in board rooms around the globe. The issue has gone from one priority among many to business critical. And CEOs are no longer just pursuing lower costs, shorter lead times, and higher quality.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Instead, they are recognizing the need to resolve supply chain disruptions in an integrated way, bridging the silos of various functions and going beyond dealing with supply chain disruptions as they occur.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="a-risk-resilient-and-sustainable-supply-chain-is-one-that-is-connected-contextualized-and-collaborative">A risk-resilient and sustainable supply chain is one that is connected, contextualized, and collaborative</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Taking a macro-view is also something governments have begun doing. Just think of the huge investments to “bring supply chains home”; for example, <a href="https://commission.europa.eu/strategy-and-policy/priorities-2019-2024/europe-fit-digital-age/european-chips-act_en">€43 billion in the EU</a> for semiconductors or <a href="https://www.whitehouse.gov/briefing-room/statements-releases/2023/04/17/fact-sheet-biden-harris-administration-announces-new-private-and-public-sector-investments-for-affordable-electric-vehicles/">$100 billion in the U.S.</a> for sustainable energy. At the same time, diversifying supply chains and complying with new regulations keeps increasing their complexity.</p>
  <p>Companies take various approaches to these challenges, such as de-coupling their supply chains by building up costly inventories for critical components. Another option is reshoring or nearshoring, which brings manufacturing and supplier relationships closer to core markets, ideally in countries with similar political and economic systems. But all of these strategies come with downsides, including the cost of operations in globally competitive markets.</p>
  <p>At SAP, our vision is to embrace interconnected supply chains and optimize material flows — sustainably — with digital technologies. We believe in intelligent strategies to reduce supply chain uncertainties for the long-term by helping industries redefine their operations and by creating value chains that are more intelligent, connected, and responsive.</p>
  <h2 id="supply-chain-convergence-increases-agility">Supply Chain Convergence Increases Agility</h2>
  <p>Companies that resolve supply chain disruptions in an integrated manner bridge the silos of various functions such as procurement, logistics, or manufacturing. That’s how they can truly alleviate the impact to their organizations. Supply chain functions need to work in concert and extend into their ecosystem of suppliers. Even the most accurate supply chain plan is meaningless if material suppliers cannot commit to volumes and lead times. Through integrating supply chain planning, such as demand and supply plans with procurement collaboration, manufacturers have a much stronger strategic lever to avoid downstream shortages.</p>
  <p>At SAP, we call this approach <strong>design-to-operate</strong>. Our strategy is to deeply connect all relevant functions in a supply chain along end-to-end value chains and business processes. Going beyond the four walls of your own enterprise, into your ecosystem of suppliers and sub-suppliers — that’s the ultimate way to tackle supply chain challenges. In the case of supply shortages, for example, it is imperative to analyze the impact to the organization.</p>
  <p>With SAP Integrated Business Planning, <a href="https://blogs.sap.com/2022/07/05/how-network-aware-supply-chain-planning-drives-resiliency/">affected production orders can be quickly identified</a>. Impacted customer orders and revenue at risk are visible and informed actions can be taken to mitigate any shortages, for example, by changing production schedules. The SAP Digital Manufacturing system knows immediately about the changed production plan for the next shifts and adjusts labor and resources accordingly. Logistics departments in SAP Extended Warehouse Management orchestrate the new material flow, <a href="https://blogs.sap.com/2023/04/14/sap-digital-manufacturing-and-ewm-integration-using-manage-staging-2.0-app/">moving the right raw materials into production</a>, and asset maintenance activities are re-scheduled to adhere to the new production priorities.</p>
  <p>As a result, supply chain leaders who follow a design-to-operate paradigm are highly agile and can take critical actions quickly to deal with supply chain disruptions.</p>
  <h2 id="saps-industry-business-networks-a-new-paradigm">SAP’s Industry Business Networks: A New Paradigm</h2>
  <p>Entire industries are recognizing the benefits of going beyond the four walls of their own enterprise. Consider a car company investigating faulty engines coming from one of their production lines. Now imagine it can trace the failure not only to a particular batch of components from one supplier but then dig even deeper to identify faulty basic parts from the supplier’s supplier. Instead of having to recall thousands of vehicles, it needs to recall only a few.</p>
  <p>Solving problems this way requires a mindset for radical collaboration as well as technology for efficient, cross-company data exchange. <a href="https://catena-x.net/en/">Catena-X</a> is an open network that enables just that. It guarantees interoperability by defining common standards. The network is not owned by a single business and data providers keep their data sovereignty. For instance, they define for how long and for which purpose their data can be used. On the other hand, consumers can trust that data comes from a reliable source.</p>
  <p>SAP is one of the founding members of Catena-X, together with five other companies. Since 2020, the initiative has grown to <a href="https://catena-x.net/fileadmin/_online_media_/231012_1_CAT_007_List_of_Members_EN.pdf">170 international auto makers, suppliers, and</a> IT companies. Among them are Germany’s biggest car companies as well as many small and medium enterprises. Catena-X may soon become the industry’s standard.</p>
  <p>Naturally, the <a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/automotive/industry-network-automotive.html">SAP Business Network for the automotive industry</a> is ready for Catena-X. It readily connects Catena-X to SAP’s broad portfolio of automotive IT solutions to trace parts, measure carbon emissions and manage demand, capacity and quality. Recently, SAP announced business networks for more industries, including <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-network/industries.html">high tech, industrial manufacturing, consumer products, and life sciences</a>, with more to come.</p>
  <h2 id="generative-ai-adds-new-types-of-intelligence">Generative AI Adds New Types of Intelligence</h2>
  <p>A key tool in solving supply chain complexity challenges is artificial intelligence (AI). Even before the recent groundbreaking advances in large language models (LLMs) and generative AI, our supply chain solutions have been infused with both “traditional” and “advanced” AI.</p>
  <p>For instance, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/integrated-business-planning.html">SAP Integrated Business Planning for Supply Chain</a> creates demand forecasts based on historical demand patterns, but it also leverages advanced machine learning capabilities to improve forecast demand with point-of-sales data and improve planning quality using self-healing master data and lead time predictions. In the future, generative AI will enable completely new types of intelligent capabilities like these:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Facilitating human-machine interaction:</strong> Users will soon be able to interact with their system much more naturally via our new embedded <a href="/2023/09/joule-new-generative-ai-assistant">generative assistant Joule</a>. For example, they will be able to ask which of customer X’s demands for product Y are still unfilled in Central America. Joule will give the answer, intelligently combining data from various systems and domains because it will be embedded throughout the SAP cloud enterprise portfolio.</li>
    <li><strong>Supporting creativity:</strong> Much like a sparring partner, generative AI can help designers, engineers, and product managers create new product ideas in an innovation cycle and iterate them with SAP Enterprise Product Development.</li>
    <li><strong>Transforming unstructured data:</strong> Consider a truck arriving at a warehouse with inbound cargo. The clerk knows what cargo to expect and this is saved in an SAP system. However, what is really on the truck is written on a loading list, often in paper form. Making this data available digitally has been possible for quite a while and is known as optical character recognition (OCR). What’s new is that generative AI tools can now match the unstructured loading list to the structured data already in the system — in a split second.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>Leveraging AI for companies to scale and sustain business operations will no longer be optional. Consider the increasing labor shortage facing manufacturing companies, among others. They will have a shortfall of up to 85 million employees by 2030 — roughly the population of Germany!</p>
  <p>By automating mundane tasks with advanced AI capabilities, we will bridge the human resources gap and enable experts to focus on what really matters: making data-backed business decisions.</p>
  <p>Human and artificial intelligence work hand in hand — it’s a duet, not a duel.</p>
  <p>We already help our customers build risk-resilient supply chains and deeply connect enterprises to run productive, agile and automated operations. Now, by also leveraging the power of generative AI, we will ensure that supply chain resilience doesn’t have to be something that keeps CEOs up at night.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Thomas Saueressig is a member of the Executive Board of SAP SE, SAP Product Engineering.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/blog/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/blog/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/blog/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/blog/article-read-more</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/executive-blog</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/catena-x</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>product/sap-digital-manufacturing</category>
            <category>product/sap-extended-warehouse-management</category>
            <category>product/sap-integrated-business-planning-for-supply-chain</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhancing Customer Experience with Risk-Resilient Supply Chains at BSH Home Appliances Group]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/risk-resilient-supply-chains-at-bsh</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/risk-resilient-supply-chains-at-bsh</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[BSH Home Appliances Group chose SAP Integrated Business Planning for Supply Chain and SAP S/4HANA to coordinate business planning.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/travel-transportation</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-digital-supply-chain</category>
            <category>product/sap-integrated-business-planning-for-supply-chain</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Together Toward a Circular Economy]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2022/06/circular-economy-sap-customers-reduce-food-waste</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2022/06/circular-economy-sap-customers-reduce-food-waste</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Collective action to address food waste and global hunger must take many forms. Read how a number of SAP customers are leading the way.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/executive-blog</category>
            <category>product/sap-integrated-business-planning-for-supply-chain</category>
            <category>product/sap-responsible-design-and-production</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-supply-chain-control-tower</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ducati Accelerates Innovation and Customer Experience with SAP]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/ducati-accelerates-innovation-customer-experience</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/ducati-accelerates-innovation-customer-experience</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Italian motorcycle manufacturer Ducati Motor Holding S.p.A. has chosen RISE with SAP to enable an important business transformation.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-commerce-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-integrated-business-planning-for-supply-chain</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>