<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/product/sap-ariba-buying/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Future of Procurement Is Already a Reality at SAP Spend Connect Live]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/procurement-news-sap-spend-connect-live</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/procurement-news-sap-spend-connect-live</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[At SAP Spend Connect Live, we announced a series of procurement innovations focused on streamlining procurement processes. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>product/sap-ariba-buying</category>
            <category>product/sap-ariba-contracts</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-concur</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fieldglass</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-spend-connect-live</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Unveils New Generative AI Innovations That Boost Productivity and Effectiveness in Spend Management]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/sap-spend-connect-live-generative-ai-innovations-spend-management</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/sap-spend-connect-live-generative-ai-innovations-spend-management</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[From SAP Spend Connect Live in Vienna, SAP has introduced new business AI and UX innovations for spend management and business network.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>product/sap-ariba-category-management</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>product/sap-ariba-buying</category>
            <category>product/sap-ariba-contracts</category>
            <category>product/sap-ariba-sourcing</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-concur</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-spend-connect-live</category>
            <category>product/sap-spend-control-tower</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Future of Buying: Personalization, Predictive Recommendations, and Sustainability Awareness]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/buying-360-capability-personalization-predictive-sustainable-recommendations</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/buying-360-capability-personalization-predictive-sustainable-recommendations</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The buying 360 capability adds new services that help make purchasing more predictive, personalized, and sustainable. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>product/sap-ariba-buying</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Five Lessons Learned from DSM’s Sustainable Procurement Transformation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/five-lessons-learned-dsm-sustainable-procurement-transformation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/five-lessons-learned-dsm-sustainable-procurement-transformation</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Royal DSM utilized SAP Business Network and SAP Ariba solutions to enhance the sustainability of its global indirect procurement. Learn more!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>product/sap-ariba-buying</category>
            <category>product/sap-ariba-contracts</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Companies Continue to Digitalize Spend Management with SAP]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/companies-digitalize-spend-management-with-sap</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/companies-digitalize-spend-management-with-sap</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Ariba and SAP Fieldglass solutions help companies across industries digitalize spend management and external workforce management.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18336490c7900d7c1abeb97d7ba5022908af43cf5.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18336490c7900d7c1abeb97d7ba5022908af43cf5.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_18336490c7900d7c1abeb97d7ba5022908af43cf5.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Companies Continue to Digitalize Spend Management with SAP" src="./media_18336490c7900d7c1abeb97d7ba5022908af43cf5.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="companies-continue-to-digitalize-spend-management-with-sap">Companies Continue to Digitalize Spend Management with SAP</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="achieve-digital-transformation-from-source-to-pay-with-sap-ariba-solutions">Achieve digital transformation from source to pay with SAP Ariba solutions</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.ariba.com/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced that Molson Coors Beverage Co. and the Florida Department of Management Services are among the hundreds of companies across industries and geographies in the second quarter to have chosen <a href="http://www.ariba.com/?campaigncode=CRM-IS20-PRL-OOCWA01">SAP Ariba</a> and <a href="https://www.fieldglass.com/?campaigncode=CRM-IS20-PRL-OOCWF02">SAP Fieldglass</a> solutions to digitalize procurement and external workforce management. Hundreds more renewed licenses and still more went live with the solutions to optimize spend management.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“We have seen significant growth this quarter with companies around the world continuing to prioritize improving their spend management operations,” said John Wookey, president of SAP Intelligent Spend and Business Network. “By modernizing and digitalizing critical business processes across procurement and external workforce management, our customers are gaining visibility and insights that enable them to control costs, reduce risk and drive innovation and growth for their businesses.”</p>
  <p>Highlights from the quarter include:</p>
  <p><strong>Alcon Vision</strong>, the Fort Worth, Texas–based company, is a global leader in eye care, specializing in surgical medical devices and nonsurgical vision care products. Alcon selected SAP Ariba solutions for sourcing and procurement for direct and indirect materials. The company also selected the Qualtrics XM for Suppliers solution to help build stronger and more collaborative relationships with suppliers. With a new and improved intuitive source-to-pay experience, Alcon aims to foster simplicity, speed and user-friendly buying services with increased data transparency and compliance.</p>
  <p>Refrigeration and air conditioning technology manufacturer <strong>BITZER SE</strong> has implemented the SAP Ariba Buying solution with guided buying capability to help streamline and digitalize its procurement operations. With the SAP Ariba solution, BITZER, based in Sindelfingen, Germany, aims to drive a more efficient, paperless, transparent process from sourcing to payment as it expands globally.</p>
  <p>The <strong>Florida Department of Management Services (DMS)</strong> selected SAP Ariba solutions for sourcing, contracts, buying and invoicing, and commerce automation to modernize its statewide procurement system with a cloud-based solution. DMS plans to standardize and automate procurement processes across the State of Florida, increase spend visibility and control, and enhance savings statewide.</p>
  <p>Aligned with its innovation and sustainability strategy, <strong>Grupo Financiero Banorte, S.A.B. de C.V.,</strong> one of the largest financial holdings companies in Mexico, continues its procurement transformation with the renewal of SAP Ariba solutions. By further digitalizing its procurement processes and strengthening its supply lifecycle management automation, Banorte will help improve the experience of more than 21,000 suppliers while enhancing process efficiency and spend compliance.</p>
  <p><strong>Molson Coors</strong> made a strategic investment in SAP Ariba solutions to help modernize its global procurement operations, building on its implementation of the SAP Ariba Contracts solution and adding the SAP Ariba Buying and Invoicing solution with commerce automation capabilities. With the new solutions integrated with its multiple ERP infrastructure, the company, headquartered in Golden, Colorado, and Montreal, Canada, intends to standardize on best practices from source to pay, improve efficiency in supplier relationship management and minimize risk.</p>
  <p><strong>Promigas SA ESP</strong>, a leading Colombian provider of natural gas, has selected SAP Ariba solutions for digital procurement as it continued its transformation journey with SAP. Building on its existing transportation management system based on SAP S/4HANA, Promigas will adopt the cloud-based SAP Ariba solutions to help standardize and automate its procurement processes, increase purchasing efficiencies and reduce costs and risks.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-fieldglass-rework-how-work-gets-done">SAP Fieldglass: Rework how work gets done</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.fieldglass.com/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><strong>Roca Sanitario SA</strong>, a global leader in bathroom equipment, selected SAP Ariba solutions for strategic sourcing, buying, commerce automation and supply chain collaboration. The Spanish company will adopt the digital <a href="https://www.fieldglass.com/solutions/services-procurement">procurement solutions</a> to help improve, standardize and automate spend management processes across the organization. The company expects to increase visibility into spend and supplier performance to optimize costs and operational efficiencies.</p>
  <p>For more information, visit the <a href="/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP on Twitter at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>About SAP</strong></p>
  <p>SAP’s strategy is to help every business run as an intelligent enterprise. As a market leader in enterprise application software, we help companies of all sizes and in all industries run at their best: 77% of the world’s transaction revenue touches an SAP system. Our machine learning, Internet of Things (IoT), and advanced analytics technologies help turn customers’ businesses into intelligent enterprises. SAP helps give people and organizations deep business insight and fosters collaboration that helps them stay ahead of their competition. We simplify technology for companies so they can consume our software the way they want – without disruption. Our end-to-end suite of applications and services enables business and public customers across 25 industries globally to operate profitably, adapt continuously, and make a difference. With a global network of customers, partners, employees, and thought leaders, SAP helps the world run better and improve people’s lives. For more information, visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/">www.sap.com</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Note to editors:</strong><br>To preview and download broadcast-standard stock footage and press photos digitally, please visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/photos">www.sap.com/photos</a>. On this platform, you can find high resolution material for your media channels. To view video stories on diverse topics, visit <a href="http://www.sap-tv.com">www.sap-tv.com</a>. From this site, you can embed videos into your own Web pages, share video via email links, and subscribe to RSS feeds from SAP TV.</p>
  <p><strong>For customers interested in learning more about SAP products:</strong><br>Global Customer Center: +49 180 534-34-24<br>United States Only: 1 (800) 872-1SAP (1-800-872-1727)</p>
  <p><strong>For more information, press only:</strong> Kelly Sheldon Murray, +1 (978) 708-6821, <a href="mailto:kelly.murray@sap.com">kelly.murray@sap.com</a><u>,</u> ET<br>Geraldine Lim, +1 (415) 418-0945, <a href="mailto:geraldine.lim@sap.com">geraldine.lim@sap.com</a>, PT<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>Any statements contained in this document that are not historical facts are forward-looking statements as defined in the U.S. Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995. Words such as “anticipate,” “believe,” “estimate,” “expect,” “forecast,” “intend,” “may,” “plan,” “project,” “predict,” “should” and “will” and similar expressions as they relate to SAP are intended to identify such forward-looking statements. SAP undertakes no obligation to publicly update or revise any forward-looking statements. All forward-looking statements are subject to various risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results to differ materially from expectations. The factors that could affect SAP’s future financial results are discussed more fully in SAP’s filings with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (“SEC”), including SAP’s most recent Annual Report on Form 20-F filed with the SEC. Readers are cautioned not to place undue reliance on these forward-looking statements, which speak only as of their dates.<br>© 2021 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="http://www.sap.com/corporate-en/legal/copyright/index.epx#trademark">http://www.sap.com/corporate-en/legal/copyright/index.epx#trademark</a> for additional trademark information and notices.<br>Please consider our <a href="https://www.sap.com/corporate/en/legal/privacy.html">privacy policy</a>. If you received this press release in your e-mail and you wish to unsubscribe to our mailing list please contact <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a> and write Unsubscribe in the subject line.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-news</category>
            <category>news-tag/digitalization</category>
            <category>news-tag/external-workforce-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-spend</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>product/sap-ariba-buying</category>
            <category>product/sap-ariba-contracts</category>
            <category>topic/spend-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[BITZER Optimizes Global Procurement Operations with SAP Ariba Solutions]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/05/bitzer-optimizes-global-procurement-operations-sap-ariba</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/05/bitzer-optimizes-global-procurement-operations-sap-ariba</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[BITZER has implemented SAP Ariba Buying with guided buying capability to help streamline and digitalize its procurement operations.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18c15341d8dc69e50c6f77d68b195a1533cda2e7a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18c15341d8dc69e50c6f77d68b195a1533cda2e7a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_18c15341d8dc69e50c6f77d68b195a1533cda2e7a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="BITZER Optimizes Global Procurement Operations with SAP Ariba Solutions" src="./media_18c15341d8dc69e50c6f77d68b195a1533cda2e7a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="bitzer-optimizes-global-procurement-operations-with-sap-ariba-solutions">BITZER Optimizes Global Procurement Operations with SAP Ariba Solutions</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="increase-procurement-visibility-and-control-with-operational-flexibility-repeatable-cost-savings-and-compliant-processes">Increase procurement visibility and control with operational flexibility, repeatable cost savings, and compliant processes</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/e-procurement/procurement.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced that refrigeration and air conditioning technology manufacturer BITZER has implemented the <a href="https://www.ariba.com/solutions/solutions-overview/procurement/guided-buying">SAP Ariba Buying solution with guided buying capability</a> to help streamline and digitalize its procurement operations.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>With the SAP Ariba solution, BITZER, based in Sindelfingen, Germany, aims to drive a more efficient, paperless, transparent process from sourcing to payment as it executes on its global expansion plans.</p>
  <p>“To overcome challenges and thrive in today’s business environment, visibility, resiliency and agility in our procurement operations are critical,” said Christian Stenzel, BITZER director of organization and IT. “Until now, our employees have procured indirect materials through manual processes. By standardizing on a digitalized procurement process, we are increasing efficiency and transparency across our operation to deliver value for our business.”</p>
  <p>The company has implemented SAP Ariba solutions to help centralize its procurement operations on a single cloud-based platform, and with help from consulting firm apsolut GmbH, it can continue its digital transformation journey.</p>
  <p>For BITZER, SAP Ariba solutions, integrated with SAP S/4HANA, help to drive a more efficient procurement process and tighter collaboration with suppliers. The guided buying capability in the SAP Ariba solution will help BITZER reduce maverick spending, provide an intuitive purchasing experience and drive more consistent compliance with purchasing policies such as budget limits, minimum bids and preferred suppliers.</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="http://news.sap.com/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP on Twitter at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>About SAP</strong></p>
  <p>SAP’s strategy is to help every business run as an intelligent enterprise. As a market leader in enterprise application software, we help companies of all sizes and in all industries run at their best: 77% of the world’s transaction revenue touches an SAP system. Our machine learning, Internet of Things (IoT) and advanced analytics technologies help turn customers’ businesses into intelligent enterprises. SAP helps give people and organizations deep business insight and fosters collaboration that helps them stay ahead of their competition. We simplify technology for companies so they can consume our software the way they want — without disruption. Our end-to-end suite of applications and services enables business and public customers across 25 industries globally to operate profitably, adapt continuously and make a difference. With a global network of customers, partners, employees and thought leaders, SAP helps the world run better and improve people’s lives. For more information, visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/">www.sap.com</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Note to editors:</strong><br>To preview and download broadcast-standard stock footage and press photos digitally, please visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/photos">www.sap.com/photos</a>. On this platform, you can find high resolution material for your media channels. To view video stories on diverse topics, visit <a href="http://www.sap-tv.com">www.sap-tv.com</a>. From this site, you can embed videos into your own Web pages, share video via email links, and subscribe to RSS feeds from SAP TV.</p>
  <p><strong>For customers interested in learning more about SAP products:</strong><br>Global Customer Center: +49 180 534-34-24<br>United States Only: 1 (800) 872-1SAP (1-800-872-1727)</p>
  <p><strong>For more information, press only:</strong><br>Kelly Sheldon Murray, +1 (978) 708-6821, <a href="mailto:kelly.murray@sap.com">kelly.murray@sap.com</a><u>,</u> ET<br>Geraldine Lim, +1 (415) 418-0945, <a href="mailto:geraldine.lim@sap.com">geraldine.lim@sap.com</a>, PT<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>Any statements contained in this document that are not historical facts are forward-looking statements as defined in the U.S. Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995. Words such as “anticipate,” “believe,” “estimate,” “expect,” “forecast,” “intend,” “may,” “plan,” “project,” “predict,” “should” and “will” and similar expressions as they relate to SAP are intended to identify such forward-looking statements. SAP undertakes no obligation to publicly update or revise any forward-looking statements. All forward-looking statements are subject to various risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results to differ materially from expectations. The factors that could affect SAP’s future financial results are discussed more fully in SAP’s filings with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (“SEC”), including SAP’s most recent Annual Report on Form 20-F filed with the SEC. Readers are cautioned not to place undue reliance on these forward-looking statements, which speak only as of their dates.<br>© 2021 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="http://www.sap.com/corporate-en/legal/copyright/index.epx#trademark">http://www.sap.com/corporate-en/legal/copyright/index.epx#trademark</a> for additional trademark information and notices.<br>Please consider our <a href="https://www.sap.com/corporate/en/legal/privacy.html">privacy policy</a>. If you received this press release in your e-mail and you wish to unsubscribe to our mailing list please contact <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a> and write Unsubscribe in the subject line.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-news</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>product/sap-ariba-buying</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>