<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/google-cloud/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hunkemöller Finds Perfect Fit with RISE with SAP]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/hunkemoeller-perfect-fit-rise-with-sap</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/hunkemoeller-perfect-fit-rise-with-sap</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Hunkemöller has tapped RISE with SAP to move to the cloud and offer customers personalized experiences while keeping up with strong demand.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1babc3b4bba211bb8b678216b0fff7e19a9d7ad3b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1babc3b4bba211bb8b678216b0fff7e19a9d7ad3b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1babc3b4bba211bb8b678216b0fff7e19a9d7ad3b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Hunkemöller Finds Perfect Fit with RISE with SAP" src="./media_1babc3b4bba211bb8b678216b0fff7e19a9d7ad3b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="hunkemöller-finds-perfect-fit-with-rise-with-sap">Hunkemöller Finds Perfect Fit with RISE with SAP</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced that Hunkemöller International B.V., Europe’s fastest-growing lingerie brand, has moved to the cloud, leveraging the RISE with SAP solution to offer customers personalized experiences and to keep up with strong demand.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>With more than 850 retail stores and 15 online stores across 23 countries, Hunkemöller needed a technology infrastructure that could scale and keep up with the brand’s growth. Moving from an on-premise system to the SAP S/4HANA Cloud Private Edition solution with Google Cloud marks the first milestone in Hunkemöller’s digital transformation journey to become a data-driven company.</p>
  <p>Hunkemöller has an omnichannel sales strategy, selling through its own shops and through wholesale and international franchises. Strong wholesale activities were one of the reasons the company looked to move to the cloud. Hunkemöller wanted a technology infrastructure that could offer flexibility, personalized insights into customers’ shopping behaviors and innovation to position itself for further growth.</p>
  <p>With SAP S/4HANA Cloud Private Edition, Hunkemöller is eyeing its next step in its digital transformation journey as it embarks on the implementation of the SAP S/4HANA solution for fashion and vertical business, a version of SAP S/4HANA optimized for the fashion industry. The solution will allow the company to manage its business, from design to wholesale and retail, all on one platform. This will enable Hunkemöller to deliver collections faster on its channels, optimize inventory and cost as well as increase margins.</p>
  <p>“About 75% of our customers are already a member of Hunkemöller,” said Gordon Smit, global IT director, Hunkemöller. “How great would it be if we could offer them an even more personalized experience, for example, by predicting when a customer wants to make a repeat purchase and being able to send the right offer at the right time? Thanks to our current efforts with RISE with SAP, we are ready for that next phase. This is going to be a game changer for our customer experience.”</p>
  <p>Achim Schneider, global head of industry business unit retail and wholesale distribution, SAP, said: “Having worked closely over the past few months and migrating from on-premise to cloud in 48 hours is testament to the strong collaboration that our teams have had. With RISE with SAP now implemented, Hunkemöller is ready to continue building on the strong growth momentum they’ve had, and I’m excited to see them setting new standards in the lingerie market.”</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="http://news.sap.com/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Media Contact:</strong><br>Lesa Plingen, +49 622-776-9000, <a href="mailto:lesa.plingen@sap.com">lesa.plingen@sap.com</a>, CET<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>This document contains forward-looking statements, which are predictions, projections, or other statements about future events. These statements are based on current expectations, forecasts, and assumptions that are subject to risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results and outcomes to materially differ. Additional information regarding these risks and uncertainties may be found in our filings with the Securities and Exchange Commission, including but not limited to the risk factors section of SAP’s 2022 Annual Report on Form 20-F.<br>© 2024 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>news-tag/google-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP and Google Cloud Enhance Open Data Cloud With New Generative AI Solutions for Enterprises]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/sap-google-cloud-partnership-open-data-cloud-new-generative-ai-solutions-for-enterprises</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/sap-google-cloud-partnership-open-data-cloud-new-generative-ai-solutions-for-enterprises</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The expanded SAP and Google Cloud partnership will launch new generative AI-powered industry solutions supporting improved sustainability.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>industry/automotive</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/google-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
            <category>product/sap-datasphere</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP and Google Cloud Expand Partnership to Build the Future of Open Data and AI for Enterprises]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/sap-google-cloud-expanded-partnership-open-data-ai-enterprises</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/sap-google-cloud-expanded-partnership-open-data-ai-enterprises</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP and Google Cloud are introducing an open data offering designed to simplify data landscapes and unleash the power of business data.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/google-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/machine-learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-datasphere</category>
            <category>product/sap-hana-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Google Cloud and SAP Expand Partnership to Enable Native Integration Between Google Workspace and SAP S/4HANA Cloud]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/google-cloud-and-sap-native-integration-google-workspace-sap-s4hana-cloud</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/google-cloud-and-sap-native-integration-google-workspace-sap-s4hana-cloud</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Google Cloud and SAP have expanded their relationship, unveiling new integrations between Google Workspace and SAP S/4HANA Cloud.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/google-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Google Cloud and SAP Partner to Accelerate Business Transformations in the Cloud]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/google-cloud-and-sap-accelerate-business-transformations-cloud</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/google-cloud-and-sap-accelerate-business-transformations-cloud</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In an expanded strategic partnership, Google Cloud and SAP will help customers migrate critical business systems to the cloud.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1dd983520693b24a89fdbb1e66a291d87c8496233.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1dd983520693b24a89fdbb1e66a291d87c8496233.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1dd983520693b24a89fdbb1e66a291d87c8496233.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Google Cloud and SAP Partner to Accelerate Business Transformations in the Cloud" src="./media_1dd983520693b24a89fdbb1e66a291d87c8496233.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="google-cloud-and-sap-partner-to-accelerate-business-transformations-in-the-cloud">Google Cloud and SAP Partner to Accelerate Business Transformations in the Cloud</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-the-sap-and-google-cloud-partnership">Learn more about the SAP and Google Cloud partnership</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://sap.com/googlecloud">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong><em>SUNNYVALE, Calif., and WALLDORF</em></strong> — Google Cloud and <a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/defense-security.html">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced an expanded strategic partnership to help customers execute business transformations, migrate critical business systems to the cloud and augment existing business systems with Google Cloud capabilities in artificial intelligence (AI) and machine learning (ML).</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Under this expanded partnership, Google Cloud will be a strategic cloud partner for the RISE with SAP offering. The two companies will partner to accelerate customers’ cloud migrations and business process migrations. In addition, customers can benefit from the planned global availability of multiple SAP services and products on Google Cloud’s reliable, scalable cloud infrastructure and high-speed network, including the SAP Analytics Cloud and SAP Data Warehouse Cloud solutions within SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP).</p>
  <p>“Google Cloud and SAP share a commitment to supporting customer success and growth. We’re delighted to partner with SAP to accelerate business’ digital transformations with SAP on Google Cloud and with next-generation cloud capabilities,” said Rob Enslin, president at Google Cloud. “Through support for RISE with SAP and in-depth integrations between SAP and Google Cloud, this new partnership will enable customers to seamlessly bring their most critical business systems and applications to a future-proof, secure and low-latency environment and to run them sustainably, on the industry’s cleanest cloud.”</p>
  <p>“RISE with SAP has been enthusiastically adopted by customers who want to accelerate their journey toward becoming an intelligent enterprise. We are now expanding our partnership with Google Cloud to further customer success,” said Thomas Saueressig, member of the Executive Board of SAP SE and responsible for SAP Product Engineering. “Offering integration between SAP solutions, SAP BTP and Google Cloud infrastructure and capabilities in artificial intelligence, machine learning and analytics gives customers the choice they desire as well as the innovative portfolio they seek to transform their businesses in the cloud.”</p>
  <p>SAP and Google Cloud drove successful joint customer adoption throughout 2021, with mutual customers such as <a href="/2021/07/energizer-holdings-finance-transformation">Energizer</a>, <a href="https://cloud.google.com/press-releases/2021/0614/msc-industrial-google-cloud">MSC Industrial Supply Co.</a>, the AES Corporation and others selecting RISE with SAP on Google Cloud.</p>
  <p><strong>About Google Cloud</strong></p>
  <p>Google Cloud accelerates organizations’ ability to digitally transform their business with the best infrastructure, platform, industry solutions and expertise. We deliver enterprise-grade cloud solutions that leverage Google’s cutting-edge technology to help companies operate more efficiently and adapt to changing needs, giving customers a foundation for the future. Customers in more than 200 countries and territories turn to Google Cloud as their trusted partner to solve their most critical business problems.</p>
  <p><strong>About SAP</strong></p>
  <p>SAP’s strategy is to help every business run as an intelligent enterprise. As a market leader in enterprise application software, we help companies of all sizes and in all industries run at their best: 77% of the world’s transaction revenue touches an SAP system. Our machine learning, Internet of Things (IoT), and advanced analytics technologies help turn customers’ businesses into intelligent enterprises. SAP helps give people and organizations deep business insight and fosters collaboration that helps them stay ahead of their competition. We simplify technology for companies so they can consume our software the way they want – without disruption. Our end-to-end suite of applications and services enables business and public customers across 25 industries globally to operate profitably, adapt continuously, and make a difference. With a global network of customers, partners, employees, and thought leaders, SAP helps the world run better and improve people’s lives. For more information, visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/">www.sap.com</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Note to editors:</strong><br>To preview and download broadcast-standard stock footage and press photos digitally, please visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/photos">www.sap.com/photos</a>. On this platform, you can find high resolution material for your media channels. To view video stories on diverse topics, visit <a href="http://www.sap-tv.com">www.sap-tv.com</a>. From this site, you can embed videos into your own Web pages, share video via email links, and subscribe to RSS feeds from SAP TV.</p>
  <p><strong>For customers interested in learning more about SAP products:</strong><br>Global Customer Center: +49 180 534-34-24<br>United States Only: 1 (800) 872-1SAP (1-800-872-1727)</p>
  <p><strong>For more information, press only:</strong><br>Stacy Ries, +1 (484) 619-0411, <a href="mailto:stacy.ries@sap.com">stacy.ries@sap.com</a>, ET<br><a href="mailto:SAP%20Press%20Room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>Any statements contained in this document that are not historical facts are forward-looking statements as defined in the U.S. Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995. Words such as “anticipate,” “believe,” “estimate,” “expect,” “forecast,” “intend,” “may,” “plan,” “project,” “predict,” “should” and “will” and similar expressions as they relate to SAP are intended to identify such forward-looking statements. SAP undertakes no obligation to publicly update or revise any forward-looking statements. All forward-looking statements are subject to various risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results to differ materially from expectations. The factors that could affect SAP’s future financial results are discussed more fully in SAP’s filings with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (“SEC”), including SAP’s most recent Annual Report on Form 20-F filed with the SEC. Readers are cautioned not to place undue reliance on these forward-looking statements, which speak only as of their dates.<br>© 2021 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.<br>Please consider our <a href="https://www.sap.com/corporate/en/legal/privacy.html">privacy policy</a>. If you received this press release in your e-mail and you wish to unsubscribe to our mailing list please contact <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a> and write Unsubscribe in the subject line.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/google-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>