<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/sap-award/hasso-plattner-founders-awards/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Celebrating the Winners of the Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award 2023]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/celebrating-hasso-plattner-founders-award-winners-2023</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/celebrating-hasso-plattner-founders-award-winners-2023</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP announced the 2023 winners of the Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award, the company’s most prestigious employee recognition.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_13403df4d72b3f7d91e84c8c6f66e21dcbf1a8636.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_13403df4d72b3f7d91e84c8c6f66e21dcbf1a8636.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_13403df4d72b3f7d91e84c8c6f66e21dcbf1a8636.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Celebrating the Winners of the Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award 2023" src="./media_13403df4d72b3f7d91e84c8c6f66e21dcbf1a8636.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="celebrating-the-winners-of-the-hasso-plattner-founders-award-2023">Celebrating the Winners of the Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award 2023</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Last week, to a virtual audience of nearly 50,000 employees, the Executive Board of SAP SE announced the 2023 winners of the Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award, the company’s most prestigious employee recognition.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Three teams were selected for outstanding and innovative projects in the categories Go-to-Market, Operational Excellence, and Products and Technology.</p>
  <p>In 2023, 115 nominations involved more than 750 employees from 35 countries. Eight teams consisting of 81 employees from around the world made it to the final round.</p>
  <p>In honor of the three winning teams, SAP will make donations to three charities selected by the team members. The €30,000 total donation – €10,000 per team – will be split between <a href="https://bettershelter.org/">Better Shelter</a>, <a href="https://wck.org/">World Central Kitchen</a>, and <a href="https://www.embraceglobal.org/">Embrace Global</a>.</p>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_134b71501074e5b151cb81e7d9d054b44ff8f3a67.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_134b71501074e5b151cb81e7d9d054b44ff8f3a67.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_134b71501074e5b151cb81e7d9d054b44ff8f3a67.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Meet the 2023 Hasso Plattner Founders&#x27; Award Winners" src="./media_134b71501074e5b151cb81e7d9d054b44ff8f3a67.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://youtu.be/qzsiBITdf8Y">Meet the 2023 Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award Winners</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="go-to-market-winner">Go-to-Market Winner</h3>
        <h2 id="reimagined-rise-with-sap-business-case-with-sap-signavio-and-sap-value-lifecycle-manager-integration">Reimagined RISE with SAP Business Case with SAP Signavio and SAP Value Lifecycle Manager Integration</h2>
        <p>When shifting to a cloud-first approach, it can be a challenge to pitch the cloud to customers due to the comprehensiveness of the solution spanning across the entire value chain of an enterprise.</p>
        <p>To apply a more streamlined and dependable method for crafting compelling value propositions, the Value Advisory team at SAP implemented the SAP Signavio portfolio of cloud-based business process management solutions within their practice to demonstrate value to customers through data-driven insights.</p>
        <p>The team created a system where business metrics from <a href="https://vlm.cfapps.eu10.hana.ondemand.com/home">SAP Value Lifecycle Manager</a> and process performance data from <a href="https://www.signavio.com/">SAP Signavio solutions</a> were merged and applied to business KPIs to identify cases of suboptimal performance. This allows customers to more easily see the connection between business outcomes and the process capabilities, supported by data.</p>
        <p>The approach offers a robust and repeatable performance diagnostic that can be used to identify, clarify, verify, and amplify value throughout the customer value journey, helping customers better understand the value of the cloud and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/rise.html">RISE with SAP</a>. The innovation helps build customer trust and intimacy while also helping our business operate at scale. To date, this process-driven value management has impacted more than 190 customers.</p>
        <p>“Our future focus involves enhancing usability and capabilities to comprehensively cover the customer value journey,” Nitin Singh, team leader and Value Advisory principal, says. “We extend our sincere gratitude to our leaders for fostering a culture of innovation, our colleagues for experimenting and navigating challenges with us, and prior colleagues whose work paved the way for this journey. We genuinely stand on the shoulders of giants.”</p>
        <h3 id="operational-excellence-winner">Operational Excellence Winner</h3>
        <h2 id="plutus-rate-optimization-and-management">Plutus: Rate Optimization and Management</h2>
        <p>Cloud services are a critical part of SAP’s recent evolution, with the company dedicating extensive time and resources to seamlessly integrate all essential services into the cloud. This effort aims to enhance customer experiences – and Plutus serves as the cornerstone of these endeavors.</p>
        <p>Plutus, which leverages <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform.html">SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP)</a>, is a one-stop solution for major hyperscalers. It’s crafted to empower lines of business by providing smarter and more efficient advice for optimizing cloud services. Plutus can centralize the management of cost optimization and intelligently navigate users through cloud expenses, providing top-notch recommendations and comprehensive end-to-end management. It caters to users’ needs from guidance to execution, helping to ensure cost savings every step of the way.</p>
        <p>The Plutus team used cutting-edge technologies to create a 24/7, fully integrated, user-centric cloud service hub and a smooth user interface platform that can operate across various channels. Plutus provides simplified financial operations processes by offering an intuitive interface across all platforms, working to eliminate pricing disparities and provide reliable cost-saving solutions. These efforts strongly emphasize SAP’s commitment to advancing global digital sustainability through innovative enterprise solutions.</p>
        <p>The solution uses machine learning to provide smart recommendations. The team also plans to integrate a versatile digital chatbot based on generative AI to help ensure seamless and comprehensive user support in the future.</p>
        <p>Plutus allows for a new approach to SAP’s cloud cost optimization strategy, unlocking new avenues for significant cost savings and margin improvements. To date, Plutus has generated over US$920 million in net savings for SAP, with projections reaching $1 billion in Q1 2024. It has also achieved and maintained remarkable, best-in-industry cloud utilization and coverage rates – exceeding 97% and 90%, respectively.</p>
        <p>“Winning the Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award reflects our dedication to teamwork and innovation,” Donghua Chen, Plutus team lead, says. “Our journey to this point has required a lot of hard work. But as we celebrate this achievement, we remain committed to continually analyzing cloud usage to maximize savings for SAP through rate optimization.”</p>
        <h3 id="products--technology-winner">Products &#x26; Technology Winner</h3>
        <h2 id="cap-and-capgpt--sap-cloud-application-programming-model-and-generative-ai">CAP and capGPT – SAP Cloud Application Programming Model and Generative AI</h2>
        <p>The SAP Cloud Application Programming Model (CAP) was started in 2018 as a project to address the lack of guidance for developers building apps on what is now SAP BTP. At first, developers could choose from a huge number of technologies, which made integration with the platform services a relatively high effort.</p>
        <p>As a development framework, CAP automatically solves about 80% of the problems backend developers face – such as multitenancy, expandability, or business features such as localization and translatability. But thanks to CAP’s domain-driven approach, it is no longer necessary to always change the coding in each of those cases. And for special use cases that CAP doesn’t cover, the coding can be easily added to build in this functionality. To help safeguard customers’ investments, CAP offers the possibility to interchange components, such as runtime or the database, without changing the actual implementation.</p>
        <p>CAP, as a centerpiece of Golden Path and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/developer-tools.html">SAP Build Code</a>, is now an integral part of the consumption experience of SAP BTP. Today, thousands of internal and external developers use CAP to build business applications on SAP BTP, driving higher developer productivity and easier SAP BTP service adoption.</p>
        <p>“This award is a great testament to the hard work and dedication of the whole CAP unit and a recognition of the impact we have both internally as well as for our customers and partners,” Ole Lilienthal, team lead, says.</p>
        <p>To make prototyping even easier, in spring 2023, SAP software architect David Kunz applied ChatGPT’s large language model to writing code for business apps.</p>
        <p>capGPT, as the new functionality is called, allows users to write in natural language what they want their app prototype to be able to do. In as little as 30 seconds, they can receive all the code – which previously had to be written by hand – and access the prototype to test it. This can not only save experienced developers an amazing amount of time, but can also enable non-developers to create prototypes of the apps they need. capGPT can also generate user interfaces in addition to backend applications. It will soon be available to customers through integration into SAP Build Code as part of AI-development assistant Joule.</p>
        <p>“Seeing capGPT go from an idea to a Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award winner within a year is a true testament that everything is possible at SAP,” Kunz says. “I feel very proud and I’m energized to continue to push the limits of what generative AI can enable.”</p>
        <p>Photo courtesy of SAP employee Fateh Kassab</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-sap-news-on-linkedin">Connect with SAP News on LinkedIn</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news">Follow us to stay in touch</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>sap-award/hasso-plattner-founders-awards</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[2023 Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award Finalists: Products and Technology]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/2023-hasso-plattner-founders-award-finalists-products-and-technology</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/2023-hasso-plattner-founders-award-finalists-products-and-technology</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Here are the three finalists for the 2023 Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award in the Products and Technology category. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>sap-award/hasso-plattner-founders-awards</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[2023 Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award Finalist: SAP Ariba Category Management]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/videos/2023-hasso-plattner-founders-award-finalist-sap-ariba-category-management</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/videos/2023-hasso-plattner-founders-award-finalist-sap-ariba-category-management</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Ariba Category Management is one of the finalists for the 2023 Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award in the Products & Technology category!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/video</category>
            <category>sap-award/hasso-plattner-founders-awards</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[2023 Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award Finalist: The SAP Cloud Application Programming Model]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/videos/2023-hasso-plattner-founders-award-finalist-the-sap-cloud-application-programming-model</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/videos/2023-hasso-plattner-founders-award-finalist-the-sap-cloud-application-programming-model</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The SAP Cloud Application Programming Model is one of the finalists for the 2023 Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award in the Products & Technology category!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/video</category>
            <category>sap-award/hasso-plattner-founders-awards</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[2023 Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award Finalist: capGPT, Create Business Apps with Generative AI]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/videos/2023-hasso-plattner-founders-award-finalist-capgpt-create-business-apps-with-generative-ai</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/videos/2023-hasso-plattner-founders-award-finalist-capgpt-create-business-apps-with-generative-ai</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[capGPT is a Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award 2023 finalist in the Products & Technology category!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/video</category>
            <category>sap-award/hasso-plattner-founders-awards</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[2023 Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award Finalists: Operational Excellence]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/2023-hasso-plattner-founders-award-finalists-operational-excellence</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/2023-hasso-plattner-founders-award-finalists-operational-excellence</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Here are the three finalists for the 2023 Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award in the Operational Excellence category. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>sap-award/hasso-plattner-founders-awards</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[2023 Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award Finalist: Service and Support Data Lake]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/videos/2023-hasso-plattner-founders-award-finalist-service-and-support-data-lake</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/videos/2023-hasso-plattner-founders-award-finalist-service-and-support-data-lake</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The Service & Support Data Lake team is one of the finalists for the 2023 Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award in the Operational Excellence category!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/video</category>
            <category>sap-award/hasso-plattner-founders-awards</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[2023 Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award Finalist: Customer Data Hub]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/videos/2023-hasso-plattner-founders-award-finalist-customer-data-hub</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/videos/2023-hasso-plattner-founders-award-finalist-customer-data-hub</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Customer Data Hub is a 2023 finalist for the Hasso Plattner Founder’s Award in the Operational Excellence category!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/video</category>
            <category>sap-award/hasso-plattner-founders-awards</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[2023 Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award Finalist: Plutus Rate Optimization & Management]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/videos/2023-hasso-plattner-founders-award-finalist-plutus-rate-optimization-management</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/videos/2023-hasso-plattner-founders-award-finalist-plutus-rate-optimization-management</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Plutus is a Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award 2023 finalist in the Operational Excellence category!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1200ba03a85bd4d38d495de53e38e1bec02927a74.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1200ba03a85bd4d38d495de53e38e1bec02927a74.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1200ba03a85bd4d38d495de53e38e1bec02927a74.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Plutus – Rate Optimization &#x26; Management" src="./media_1200ba03a85bd4d38d495de53e38e1bec02927a74.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="hasso-plattner-founders-award-finalist-plutus-rate-optimization--management">2023 Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award Finalist: Plutus Rate Optimization &#x26; Management</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1200ba03a85bd4d38d495de53e38e1bec02927a74.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1200ba03a85bd4d38d495de53e38e1bec02927a74.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1200ba03a85bd4d38d495de53e38e1bec02927a74.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Plutus – Rate Optimization &#x26; Management" src="./media_1200ba03a85bd4d38d495de53e38e1bec02927a74.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EX3TS0g6dd8">Plutus – Rate Optimization &#x26; Management</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Plutus is a Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award 2023 finalist in the Operational Excellence category.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Meet the team and learn how they centralize cost optimization.</p>
  <p><a href="/2023/12/2023-hasso-plattner-founders-award-finalists-operational-excellence">Learn more about the Operational Excellence category finalists.</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/video</category>
            <category>sap-award/hasso-plattner-founders-awards</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[2023 Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award Finalists: Go to Market]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/2023-hasso-plattner-founders-award-finalists-go-to-market</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/2023-hasso-plattner-founders-award-finalists-go-to-market</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Here are the three finalists for the 2023 Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award in the Go to Market category. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a842b22def0330aaaa0008d877b0f3d80ae308db.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a842b22def0330aaaa0008d877b0f3d80ae308db.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1a842b22def0330aaaa0008d877b0f3d80ae308db.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="2023 Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award Finalists: Go to Market" src="./media_1a842b22def0330aaaa0008d877b0f3d80ae308db.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="hasso-plattner-founders-award-finalists-go-to-market">2023 Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award Finalists: Go to Market</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Nine teams are vying for the highest employee recognition at SAP: the Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award. The award is organized around three categories, each reflecting a different type of breakthrough thinking, considering the various ways in which innovation drives SAP’s success.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Here, we kick it off with the 2023 <strong>Go to Market</strong> finalists.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="the-hasso-plattner-founders-award-is-the-highest-employee-recognition-at-sap-awarded-annually-by-the-ceo-to-an-individual-or-a-team">The Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award is the highest employee recognition at SAP, awarded annually by the CEO to an individual or a team.</h3>
        <p><em><a href="/2023/04/2022-hasso-plattner-founders-award-winners">Read about last year’s winners</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="transforming-learning-in-the-sap-ecosystem">Transforming Learning in the SAP Ecosystem</h2>
  <p>Learning within the SAP ecosystem can be a daunting task. For both customers and SAP professionals, it can be hard to keep up with the landscape of ever-evolving innovations and advancing technologies. Constant learning has become somewhat of a standard with the transition to the cloud, which has resulted in a greater requirement for skilled talent. Yet the team behind the SAP Learning site noticed an unfortunate trend. “Most SAP professionals are not engaging in SAP Learning and certification activities,” says team leader Jan Meyer, global head of SAP Learning Systems. “Many customers feared a skills shortage impacting their move to SAP S/4HANA.” However, the SAP Learning team also determined that when customers and partners engaged in learning activities, there were tremendous positive effects in their technical skills and overall work satisfaction.</p>
  <p>The next steps were therefore clear for the team. As team member Marina Noble, head of Learning Systems Product and Solution Management, states, “These challenges and opportunities motivated us to significantly reduce learning, experiential, and commercial barriers and to create opportunities through learning and development for everyone.” Their realization led to the creation of <a href="https://learning.sap.com/">learning.sap.com</a>. In doing so, they garnered support from leaders across SAP, including Customer Success, Partner Ecosystem Success, Intelligent Enterprise Group, and SAP Learning. The goal was to tear down as many barriers to entry as possible by simplifying and consolidating information into one all-encompassing learning destination.</p>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1da48d40dba059a32f6c259b1f46b71a0452b5e2b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1da48d40dba059a32f6c259b1f46b71a0452b5e2b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1da48d40dba059a32f6c259b1f46b71a0452b5e2b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Learning Site and Learning Business Transformation" src="./media_1da48d40dba059a32f6c259b1f46b71a0452b5e2b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://youtu.be/9tiZOL-5GtY">SAP Learning Site and Learning Business Transformation</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Within the site, the team focused on simplifying discovery and access for all users. They eliminated the need for registration, simplified the complexity of the learning process by consolidating multiple learning destinations, and increased optimization for search engines and digital learning. They also made a wealth of learning content available for free. Timo Schuette, team member and global head of SAP Product Learning CoE, explains how, “Today, 191 learning journeys, many leading to SAP certification, are available in this new experience on SAP Learning in front of the paywall.” The results of this decision have already bore fruit, with 2023 showcasing a 250% year-over-year growth in users and a record 1.7 million active learners. On the other side of the paywall, the team created a premium learning experience that uses key methods to help maximize learning impact. Premium users can gain access to hands-on practice systems, expert-led sessions, role-based certification, and advanced learning analytics. Additionally, the premium learning experience has been substantially reduced in cost, allowing more partners and customers to reap the benefits.</p>
  <h2 id="finalist-fast-facts">Finalist Fast Facts</h2>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Submission Title:</strong> SAP Learning Site and Learning Business Transformation</li>
    <li><strong>Team:</strong> Marina Noble, Tine Vandenbreeden, Sabine Benz, Amy Sellers, Riz Khan, Paul Maguire, Manuel Rodriguez, Timo Schuette, Dave LeFevre, Jan Meyer</li>
    <li><strong>Number of Employees:</strong> 10</li>
    <li><strong>Achievement:</strong> A completely new, world-class learning experience on learning.sap.com, designed for building and sustaining SAP product knowledge and deep skills at scale, with free and self-paced learning content in front of the paywall and the most compelling premium learning value proposition in our industry behind the paywall</li>
    <li><strong>Impact:</strong> This initiative will help bridge the skills gap in our ecosystem; add value to every phase of the customer value journey, leading to accelerated and more sustainable customer success; generate incremental cloud revenue for SAP; and provide development and career opportunities for all in SAP’s ecosystem.</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="a-new-and-improved-ai-customer-support-experience">A New and Improved AI Customer Support Experience</h2>
  <p>The team behind the new <a href="https://support.sap.com/en/my-support/product-support.html?anchorId=section">“get support”</a> application on SAP for Me began with a blank slate. Instead of taking the solutions from SAP ONE Support Launchpad and applying them to a new application, they knew that the needs of customers using SAP for Me were different. For instance, the get support app would house the customer service requirements of many more employees using a multitude of SAP products. The case creation process would therefore have to properly support Digital Core &#x26; Platform and People &#x26; Operations, as well as SAP Signavio, SAP Fieldglass, and SAP Ariba solutions. Additionally, due to the influx in customer volume, it became a necessity to increase the customer self-service rate while making sure customers could still connect with the right experts to solve their issues.</p>
  <p>The team found their solution to these challenges in the implementation of AI. Built alongside the Artificial Intelligence Technologies team in the Customer Support &#x26; Innovation organization, they utilized the innovative technology to help reduce customer effort and improve the accuracy of responses. One of the key improvements AI has facilitated within the get support app is helping customers correctly qualify their problems through the channel recommender. As explained by John Bowley, team leader and product manager of Support Applications in SAP for Me, “Based on data analysis, an AI service derives the most suitable support channel to solve an issue, whether that is SAP Community or Expert Chat.”</p>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1fe9c7a72f56d02f5d34ca0d5ff7f21fc9bbd95a4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1fe9c7a72f56d02f5d34ca0d5ff7f21fc9bbd95a4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1fe9c7a72f56d02f5d34ca0d5ff7f21fc9bbd95a4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="AI-Powered Customer Support Experience" src="./media_1fe9c7a72f56d02f5d34ca0d5ff7f21fc9bbd95a4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IQrrqu5yIvc">AI-Powered Customer Support Experience</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The team also used AI to help improve the self-service features of the app. While customers are providing information and getting support, an AI service will run alongside and present relevant knowledge articles to the customer. These articles will be based on customer input and will happen in parallel with the customer receiving support, helping to expedite the whole process.</p>
  <p>The new and improved get support app has already proven itself with positive outcomes. There is now a significant increase in the percentage of customers that start the case creation process within the app but don’t fully create a support case (64.5%, up from 32% in the previous application). This means that these customers began searching for help in the app and found a solution during the process without needing to create a case. Additionally, the app helps bolster the operational efficiency of the SAP support organization with its improvements in routing customers to the right support teams.</p>
  <h2 id="finalist-fast-facts-1">Finalist Fast Facts</h2>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Submission Title:</strong> Introducing a Groundbreaking AI-Powered Customer Support Experience</li>
    <li><strong>Team:</strong> Katrin Bauer, Rosemary Gaine, John Bowley, Mike Trott, Peter Kappelmann, Amanda Gong, Silvia Niklass, Yuan Wang, Felicia Shafiq, Biyu Zhao</li>
    <li><strong>Number of Employees:</strong> core team of 10</li>
    <li><strong>Achievement:</strong> The new get support application on SAP for Me helps guide customers to solve technical product issues in real time or reach SAP experts with relevant information through an AI-enabled framework.</li>
    <li><strong>Impact:</strong> The application is used about 280,000 times every month, resulting in around 110,000 interactions created with our application (cases, expert chats, Schedule an Expert sessions).</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="reimagining-sales-engagements-with-sap-signavio">Reimagining Sales Engagements with SAP Signavio</h2>
  <p>The Value Advisory team collaborates with customers to help link their business strategies and experiences to their desired outcomes. But in the process of shifting to a cloud-first approach, the team faced a dilemma: it became apparent that their sales engagement strategy required modernization. An increase in the volume of deals within the cloud space required a faster, more efficient, and more consistent sales engagement approach that aligns with the specific needs of the customer. And pitching the cloud to customers came with its own unique crop of difficulties. “Justifying the value of cloud [to customers] is challenging due to the comprehensiveness of the solution spanning across the entire value chain of an enterprise,” says Nitin Singh, team leader and Value Advisory principal. The team knew that a data-driven sales perspective was the key to a more streamlined and dependable method for crafting compelling value propositions.</p>
  <p>To aid them in this endeavor, the team implemented the <a href="https://www.signavio.com/">SAP Signavio</a> portfolio of cloud-based business process management solutions within their practice to demonstrate value to customers through data-driven insights. As Singh explains, “This new approach involved merging business metrics from <a href="https://vlm.cfapps.eu10.hana.ondemand.com/home">SAP Value Lifecycle Manager</a> with process performance data from SAP Signavio solutions. This integration allowed our customers to clearly see the connection between business outcomes and the process capabilities supported by data.”</p>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_123b9508fe3c316c83b90b32ba0161155403d8806.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_123b9508fe3c316c83b90b32ba0161155403d8806.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_123b9508fe3c316c83b90b32ba0161155403d8806.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Signavio &#x26; SAP Value Lifecycle Manager Integration" src="./media_123b9508fe3c316c83b90b32ba0161155403d8806.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://youtu.be/0un89ACerJI">SAP Signavio &#x26; SAP Value Lifecycle Manager Integration</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Previously, business cases relied on benchmarking a customer’s performance KPIs against competitors in specific functions, like finance and asset management, demonstrating problematic areas within the business. SAP Signavio solutions, on the other hand, rely on analyzing performance through metrics such as work order automation and backlogs, which in turn identify specific pain points. The team combined these two approaches – business centric and process centric – to create a system where data produced by SAP Signavio solutions was applied to business’ KPIs to help identify cases of suboptimal performance.</p>
  <p>So far, this new approach has impacted 170 customers. The approach offers a highly repeatable performance diagnostic that can be utilized across the SAP sales landscape. “It can be used to identify, clarify, verify, and amplify value throughout the customer value journey,” says Singh. With the merging of SAP Signavio and Value Advisory, the team even wound up creating a new category: process-driven value management. Customer feedback regarding the innovation has already proven to be incredibly positive.</p>
  <h2 id="finalist-fast-facts-2">Finalist Fast Facts</h2>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Submission Title:</strong> Reimagined RISE with SAP Business Case with SAP Signavio and Value Lifecycle Manager Integration</li>
    <li><strong>Team:</strong> Nitin Singh, Devesh Thakur, Axel Hecke, Gerry McCool, Jonathon Ngo, Vikas Gupta, Jasjeet Singh, Hartosh Singh Bugra, Abhishek Dhawan, Christian Oehler</li>
    <li><strong>Number of employees:</strong> 10 (North America Value Advisory, global Value Advisory, SAP Signavio customer transformation)</li>
    <li><strong>Achievement:</strong> The team innovated a new approach to integrate business and process data to help analyze customer maturity and embed that into customer engagements, which in turn helps articulate the value of the cloud and RISE with SAP to customers.</li>
    <li><strong>Impact:</strong> The ability for SAP teams to provide a linkage between process performance indicators and key performance indicators in a streamlined manner to provide a more robust business value case for over 100 customer transformations</li>
  </ul>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Top photo courtesy of SAP employee Denise Moll</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>sap-award/hasso-plattner-founders-awards</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[2023 Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award Finalist: SAP Learning Site and Learning Business Transformation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/videos/sap-learning-site-and-learning-business-transformation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/videos/sap-learning-site-and-learning-business-transformation</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Learning Site and Learning Business Transformation is a Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award 2023 finalist in the Go to Market category!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1da48d40dba059a32f6c259b1f46b71a0452b5e2b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1da48d40dba059a32f6c259b1f46b71a0452b5e2b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1da48d40dba059a32f6c259b1f46b71a0452b5e2b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Learning Site and Learning Business Transformation" src="./media_1da48d40dba059a32f6c259b1f46b71a0452b5e2b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="hasso-plattner-founders-award-finalist-sap-learning-site-and-learning-business-transformation">2023 Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award Finalist: SAP Learning Site and Learning Business Transformation</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1da48d40dba059a32f6c259b1f46b71a0452b5e2b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1da48d40dba059a32f6c259b1f46b71a0452b5e2b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1da48d40dba059a32f6c259b1f46b71a0452b5e2b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Learning Site and Learning Business Transformation" src="./media_1da48d40dba059a32f6c259b1f46b71a0452b5e2b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9tiZOL-5GtY">SAP Learning Site and Learning Business Transformation</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>SAP Learning Site and Learning Business Transformation is a Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award 2023 finalist in the Go to Market category.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Meet the team and find out how their innovation designed a new learning experience.</p>
  <p><a href="/2023/12/2023-hasso-plattner-founders-award-finalists-go-to-market">Learn more about the Go to Market category finalists.</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/video</category>
            <category>sap-award/hasso-plattner-founders-awards</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[2023 Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award Finalist: SAP Signavio & SAP Value Lifecycle Manager Integration]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/videos/sap-signavio-sap-value-lifecycle-manager-integration</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/videos/sap-signavio-sap-value-lifecycle-manager-integration</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The SAP Signavio & SAP Value Lifecycle Manager Integration team is a Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award 2023 finalist in the Go to Market category!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/video</category>
            <category>sap-award/hasso-plattner-founders-awards</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[2023 Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award Finalist: AI-Powered Customer Support Experience]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/videos/ai-powered-customer-support-experience</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/videos/ai-powered-customer-support-experience</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The AI-Powered Customer Support Experience team is a Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award 2023 finalist in the Go to Market category!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/video</category>
            <category>sap-award/hasso-plattner-founders-awards</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Celebrating the Winners of the 2022 Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/2022-hasso-plattner-founders-award-winners</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/2022-hasso-plattner-founders-award-winners</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Congratulations to the three teams selected as 2022 Hasso Plattner Founders' Award winners! Read to learn more about the innovative projects.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>sap-award/hasso-plattner-founders-awards</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[2022 Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award Finalists: Products and Technology]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/2022-products-and-technology-finalists-hasso-plattner-founders-award</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/2022-products-and-technology-finalists-hasso-plattner-founders-award</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Meet the 2022 Products and Technology finalists for the Hasso Plattner Founders' Award, SAP's highest employee recognition.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>sap-award/hasso-plattner-founders-awards</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[2022 Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award Finalists: Operational Excellence]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/2022-operational-exellence-finalists-hasso-plattner-founders-award</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/2022-operational-exellence-finalists-hasso-plattner-founders-award</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Meet the 2022 Operational Excellence finalists for the Hasso Plattner Founders' Award, SAP's highest employee recognition.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>sap-award/hasso-plattner-founders-awards</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[2022 Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award Finalists: Go to Market]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/2022-go-to-market-finalists-hasso-plattner-founders-award</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/2022-go-to-market-finalists-hasso-plattner-founders-award</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Meet the 2022 Go to Market finalists for the Hasso Plattner Founders' Award, SAP's highest employee recognition.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>sap-award/hasso-plattner-founders-awards</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Celebrating the Winners of the 2021 Hasso Plattner Founders' Award]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/02/2021-hasso-plattner-founders-award-winners</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/02/2021-hasso-plattner-founders-award-winners</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Meet the 2021 Hasso Plattner Founders' Award winners: Support Assistant, Customer Health Score, and SAP Information Collaboration Hub for Life Sciences.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15d0fd22a994b277404768c0eda29f726d6465458.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15d0fd22a994b277404768c0eda29f726d6465458.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_15d0fd22a994b277404768c0eda29f726d6465458.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Celebrating the Winners of the 2021 Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award" src="./media_15d0fd22a994b277404768c0eda29f726d6465458.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="celebrating-the-winners-of-the-2021-hasso-plattner-founders-award">Celebrating the Winners of the 2021 Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Last week, to a virtual audience of nearly 50,000 employees, SAP CEO Christian Klein announced the winners of the <a href="/topics/hasso-plattner-founders-award">Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award</a>, the company’s most prestigious employee recognition.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Three teams were selected for outstanding and innovative projects in the categories Go-To-Market, Operational Excellence, and Products and Technology.</p>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11915182f4f45d066f0692dd219a2a5186c5eb303.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11915182f4f45d066f0692dd219a2a5186c5eb303.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_11915182f4f45d066f0692dd219a2a5186c5eb303.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="The Winners of 2021 Hasso Plattner Founders&#x27; Award" src="./media_11915182f4f45d066f0692dd219a2a5186c5eb303.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://youtu.be/GLLlFmBDNew">The Winners of 2021 Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In 2021, 196 nominations involved more than 1,300 employees from 42 countries. Nine teams consisting of 49 employees from around the world made it to the final round. The three winning teams chose the charity organizations <a href="https://www.wfp.org/">World Food Programme</a> and <a href="https://www.tfaconsulting.com/">Tech for All</a>, to which SAP will donate €10,000 on behalf of each team — €30,000 total.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong>Go-To-Market Winner</strong></p>
        <h2 id="support-assistant-delighting-customers-by-solving-issues-faster">Support Assistant: Delighting Customers by Solving Issues Faster</h2>
        <p>To stay No. 1 in customer satisfaction, SAP continues to look for new ways to create positive customer experiences by providing fast reactions and effective solutions to their customers seeking support.</p>
        <p>The <strong>Support Assistant</strong> is a cloud-based application that uses automation and machine learning to connect customers directly to solutions and further reduce the time needed to resolve customer support cases — without the need for a support engineer.</p>
        <p>Customers are guided through a conversational user interface that helps them easily access knowledge repositories and act on solutions quickly and on their own. If the support of a human engineer is needed, the previous conversation thread is aggregated into a comprehensive case description that can be shared with the human.</p>
        <p>With more than 65,000 requests in 2021 via SAP Support Portal, the Support Assistant shows impressive results. Tens of thousands fewer support cases required help from a human support engineer thanks to the automated assistant.</p>
        <p>Winning team member Jonathan Wiens says, “While still a little bit in shock, I can say it is an absolutely amazing and incredibly proud moment. I have always believed in all the people that have contributed to the Support Assistant and today was a validation of the ideas and hard work that everyone put in to make our vision a reality. We will go forward now, bolstered with the confidence of this win, to further evolve the Support Assistant and execute on our plans to integrate it as a central piece of SAP’s support workflow.”</p>
        <p><strong>Operational Excellence Winner</strong></p>
        <h2 id="cloud-customer-health-score-based-on-machine-learning">Cloud Customer Health Score Based on Machine Learning</h2>
        <table>
          <thead>
            <tr>
              <th colspan="2">Promo</th>
            </tr>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td>
                <h3 id="learn-about-what-life-looks-like-at-sap">Learn about what life looks like at SAP</h3>
              </td>
              <td><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/careers/who-we-are/life.html">Learn more</a></strong></td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
        <p><strong>Customer Health Score</strong> specifies a customer’s renewal risk and helps account teams create a positive customer experience and improve customer relationships.</p>
        <p>The solution relies on machine learning for real-time insights to predict the renewal risk for 94% of nearly 68,000 cloud customers and use these findings to alert account teams at an early stage.</p>
        <p>The Customer Health Score is used both regionally and globally across 11 cloud lines of business and already supports almost all cloud solutions from SAP. The prediction quality is over 80% and the team is confident they can increase it with the help of additional data, such as external financial metrics.</p>
        <p>“Many SAP colleagues gave us their best effort, time, and talents,” <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/angelareichert/">Angela Reichert</a> from the winning team says. “The diverse skill sets represented across the team were our winning strategy. Where one pushes, the other balances. We are all equal and we contribute as one team. There is plenty of work ahead in 2022 for Customer Health Score to become even more valuable and relevant to predicting cloud renewal health at SAP.”</p>
        <p><strong>Products and Technology Winner</strong></p>
        <h2 id="sap-information-collaboration-hub-for-life-sciences">SAP Information Collaboration Hub for Life Sciences</h2>
        <p>The issue of drug counterfeiting has experienced a dramatic rise in recent years, particularly in developing nations. It is estimated that currently more than 50% of the drugs in Africa are counterfeit.</p>
        <p><strong>SAP Information Collaboration Hub for Life Sciences</strong> is an industry network based on software-as-a-service (SaaS) that helps SAP customers in the pharmaceutical industry share information on their products with supply chain partners and government agencies to enable traceability and verification of individual product packs.</p>
        <p>With over 1,000 live trading partners, including eight of the world’s largest pharmaceutical companies and most <a href="/covid-19">COVID-19</a> vaccine manufactures, the hub currently hosts 2.2 billion product packs in the blockchain for verification in the U.S. market. It manages tens of thousands of messages every day reported to governments around the world to help prevent counterfeit products being introduced into the legitimate supply chain.</p>
        <p>“This award is a milestone in the long journey that started with a customer meeting in 2015 and that yielded a solution essential for our customers’ business while helping make the pharmaceutical supply chain safer,” winning team member <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/onuernberg/">Oliver Nuernberg</a> says. “I am grateful for the passionate team that made this work.”</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>sap-award/hasso-plattner-founders-awards</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Winners of the 2021 Hasso Plattner Founders' Award]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/videos/winners-of-the-2021-hasso-plattner-founders-award</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/videos/winners-of-the-2021-hasso-plattner-founders-award</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The winners of the 2021 Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award have been announced! Last year, 196 nominations involved over 1,300 employees from 42 countries. Nine teams...]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11915182f4f45d066f0692dd219a2a5186c5eb303.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11915182f4f45d066f0692dd219a2a5186c5eb303.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_11915182f4f45d066f0692dd219a2a5186c5eb303.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="The Winners of 2021 Hasso Plattner Founders&#x27; Award" src="./media_11915182f4f45d066f0692dd219a2a5186c5eb303.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="winners-of-the-2021-hasso-plattner-founders-award">Winners of the 2021 Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11915182f4f45d066f0692dd219a2a5186c5eb303.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11915182f4f45d066f0692dd219a2a5186c5eb303.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_11915182f4f45d066f0692dd219a2a5186c5eb303.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="The Winners of 2021 Hasso Plattner Founders&#x27; Award" src="./media_11915182f4f45d066f0692dd219a2a5186c5eb303.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://youtu.be/GLLlFmBDNew">The Winners of 2021 Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>The <a href="/2022/02/2021-hasso-plattner-founders-award-winners">winners of the 2021 Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award</a> have been announced!</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Last year, 196 nominations involved over 1,300 employees from 42 countries. Nine teams consisting of 49 employees from all around the world made it to the final round. The three teams were selected for outstanding and innovative projects in the categories Go-To-Market, Operational Excellence, and Products and Technology.</p>
  <p>Explore the <a href="https://youtube.com/playlist?list=PLRgxiZBuQ4PYjWeOa19kP8c75Ch-vDol_">Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award playlist</a>.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/video</category>
            <category>sap-award/hasso-plattner-founders-awards</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[2021 Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award Finalists: Products and Technology]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/products-and-technology-finalists-hasso-plattner-founders-award-2021</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/products-and-technology-finalists-hasso-plattner-founders-award-2021</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Get to know the three Products and Technology finalists for the 2021 Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award, SAP's highest employee recognition.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_129285b67f76b890ac19d839e260195f38133f292.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_129285b67f76b890ac19d839e260195f38133f292.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_129285b67f76b890ac19d839e260195f38133f292.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="2021 Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award Finalists: Products and Technology" src="./media_129285b67f76b890ac19d839e260195f38133f292.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="hasso-plattner-founders-award-finalists-products-and-technology">2021 Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award Finalists: Products and Technology</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Nine teams across three categories are vying for this year’s Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award. Each category reflects a different type of breakthrough thinking, considering the various ways in which innovation drives SAP’s success.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Here, meet the finalists in the <strong>Products and Technology</strong> category.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>The Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award is the highest<br>employee recognition at SAP, awarded annually by the CEO<br>to an individual or a team.</p>
        <h2 id="finalist-greentoken-by-sap">Finalist: GreenToken by SAP</h2>
        <table>
          <thead>
            <tr>
              <th colspan="2">Promo</th>
            </tr>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td>
                <h3 id="learn-about-what-life-looks-like-at-sap">Learn about what life looks like at SAP</h3>
              </td>
              <td><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/careers/who-we-are/life.html">Learn more</a></strong></td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
        <p>Eighty percent of the world’s palm oil originates from Indonesia and Malaysia. While some of it is being sustainably sourced in sustainable fair-trade plantations and small holdings, much is also being harvested on recently deforested land. How can you tell one from the other?</p>
        <table>
          <thead>
            <tr>
              <th>Embed</th>
            </tr>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td>
                <p>
                  <picture>
                    <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_105dd24f6a7a30ed482a11a642c59bcd55b199697.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
                    <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_105dd24f6a7a30ed482a11a642c59bcd55b199697.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
                    <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_105dd24f6a7a30ed482a11a642c59bcd55b199697.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
                    <img loading="lazy" alt="GreenToken" src="./media_105dd24f6a7a30ed482a11a642c59bcd55b199697.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
                  </picture>
                </p>
                <p><a href="https://youtu.be/Dz2VDEBDAx8">GreenToken</a></p>
              </td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
        <p><em>Video produced by David Aguirre and Rana Hamzakadi</em></p>
        <p>The GreenToken by SAP solution was designed to address this issue by providing a new level of transparency into complex raw material supply chains.</p>
        <p>“In 2019 a group of SAP palm oil customers approached us with this very problem – they wanted a robust solution to maintain facts across the value chain from smallholder to end customer,” says GreenToken Co-Founder James Veale. “Traditional batch-based inventory systems with their simple rules don’t truly reflect the exact makeup of a raw material inventory, which may be a mix of sustainable and non-sustainable sources. At scale, we would be dealing with millions of batches.”</p>
        <p>GreenToken instead uses a digital twin token to represent a fixed and usually small amount of the raw material. Records are kept on a blockchain ledger, and as the material moves along the supply chain GreenToken passes the equivalent number of tokens that represent the volume of material moved, from one supply chain actor’s wallet to another. This creates a tracing history — an immutable chain of custody that adds complete supply chain transparency and makes the data trustworthy.</p>
        <p><strong>Transforming the World Economy</strong></p>
        <p>GreenToken’s elegant yet powerful design has found applications in many industries. The tokens can carry information on any kind of raw materials to help answer a variety of questions: “Are these food crops sustainably sourced? Has this cobalt been mined free of child labor? Is this plastic recycled with a high percentage coming from molecular recycling of plastic waste?”</p>
        <p>With over 77% of the world’s manufactured goods passing through an SAP system, GreenToken is receiving huge interest from SAP customers under increasing pressure from both legislation and their own customer base to prove that their raw material sourcing, processing, and supply chain practices are the best that they can be.</p>
        <p>“GreenToken is SAP’s answer to that,” says Nitin Jain, GreenToken co-founder. “We have found a truly innovative use for tokens on a blockchain ledger that gives transparency to these formerly opaque raw material supply chains. GreenToken’s purpose is to help the world transform to a sustainable and circular economy — and our innovation has made it available in the cloud using simple, frictionless browser-based interfaces.”</p>
        <p><strong>Finalist Fast Facts</strong></p>
        <ul>
          <li><strong>Submission Title</strong>: GreenToken by SAP</li>
          <li><strong>Team:</strong> Nitin Jain in Canada and James Veale in Australia, co-founders, with a global team of 18, including full-time employees and fellows spread across Asia-Pacific Japan, Europe, and North America regions</li>
          <li><strong>Number of employees:</strong> 20</li>
          <li><strong>Achievement:</strong> Developed an elegant yet powerful method to add complete supply chain transparency to previously opaque raw material supply chains using digital twin tokens on a blockchain ledger. The solution works for any raw material supply chain. The team is currently deploying the system in the U.S. and Europe to prove that plastic has a high degree of circular recycled content.</li>
          <li><strong>Impact:</strong> GreenToken allows SAP customers to not only measure and make claims on their current sustainable, ethical, and circular sourcing practices, but also use their procurement spending power to promote good supply chains over bad.</li>
        </ul>
        <h2 id="finalist-ecosilient">Finalist: Ecosilient</h2>
        <p>While optimizing resources and capacities is not exactly a new business challenge, B2B circular sharing platform Ecosilient aims to commodify demand, supply, and services, connecting organizations in a community to generate value more efficiently and sustainably with special focus on existing resources and capacities.</p>
        <table>
          <thead>
            <tr>
              <th>Embed</th>
            </tr>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td>
                <p>
                  <picture>
                    <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11211402536f520f8427a0ee83c63d86205e69ead.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
                    <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11211402536f520f8427a0ee83c63d86205e69ead.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
                    <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_11211402536f520f8427a0ee83c63d86205e69ead.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
                    <img loading="lazy" alt="Ecosilient" src="./media_11211402536f520f8427a0ee83c63d86205e69ead.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
                  </picture>
                </p>
                <p><a href="https://youtu.be/CMowD2YOGDY">Ecosilient</a></p>
              </td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
        <p><em>Video produced by David Aguirre and Rana Hamzakadi</em></p>
        <p>Ecosilient helps businesses leverage resources such as obsolete assets, surplus inventory, waste, and other byproducts into a circular economy. It creates a community layer based on enterprise resource planning (ERP) to enable this growing demand for businesses, stakeholders, and investors to make more responsible decisions that drive meaningful impact on critical issues.</p>
        <p>Ecosilient Founder Avital Ben-Natan says the team’s mission is to “decouple economic growth from natural extraction and corrosive business practices. It’s about creating a trust platform to discover and facilitate collaboration opportunities around shared values.”</p>
        <p>The goal is no less than to address interlinked problems like the climate crisis, social inequities, or broken supply chains. Ecosilient serves as a framework for evolving SAP’s core technologies, data, and its global ecosystem into an engine for a sustainable economy.</p>
        <p>Users will be able to work with SAP software as they are accustomed — sourcing materials, signing contracts, tracing their shipping, and managing their inventories. “But with Ecosilient,” Ben-Natan says, “there is this additional layer in our software that users can trust will guide them to make responsible choices — to do more and better with less.”</p>
        <p><strong>Leading the Sustainable Economy</strong></p>
        <p>Fostered within the SAP Intrapreneurs program, the idea of Ecosilient resonated with many people at SAP from the start and attracted like-minded employees willing to engage in their spare time. “Even though few of us have ever been in the same room, we’ve all become very close while building Ecosilient over the last one and a half years.”</p>
        <p>Ben-Natan says names the impact of climate change as his team’s motivation. “As parents, we feel responsible for the future of our kids and our communities. We have to answer the challenges that we face as a species, but also as a planet and as an economy, and find an appropriate response.”</p>
        <p>The team considers its solution as a natural evolution of what SAP stands for: to create order in chaos, to create opportunities and collaboration, to create a fair, responsible, and ultimately more efficient economy.</p>
        <p>But Ecosilient is also a way for SAP to innovate its own infrastructure and the way it operates as a company, as Ben-Natan stresses: “It’s about creating a fundamental direction for SAP to lead in the sustainable economy.”</p>
        <p><strong>Finalist Fast Facts</strong></p>
        <ul>
          <li><strong>Submission Title</strong>: Ecosilient, the B2B Circular Sharing Platform</li>
          <li><strong>Team:</strong> Avital Ben Natan, Umesh Shekar</li>
          <li><strong>Number of employees:</strong> More than 20, with engineers, designers, innovation specialists, and mentors that have contributed to the business model, design thinking, demo, MVP, and customer engagement, and with special thanks to New Ventures and Technologies, Services IMM, and SAP Experience Garage for platforming.</li>
          <li><strong>Achievement:</strong> Leveraged market research and data analysis to identify target industries and organizations for freight pooling; implemented a WIP MVP and a demo for a sustainable shipping network; started customer engagement and GTM with companies like Unilever, Bechtle, Steelcase, Cargill, and others.</li>
          <li><strong>Impact:</strong> Ecosilient helps companies increase resource efficiency while promoting a sustainable economy by engaging the ecosystem to create shared value.</li>
        </ul>
        <h2 id="finalist-sap-information-collaboration-hub-for-life-sciences">Finalist: SAP Information Collaboration Hub for Life Sciences</h2>
        <p>In recent years, the world has seen the issue of drug counterfeiting increase dramatically. In Africa alone, over 120,000 people die each year because they are being treated with fake malaria medication. It is estimated that currently over 50% of the drugs in Africa are counterfeit.</p>
        <table>
          <thead>
            <tr>
              <th>Embed</th>
            </tr>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td>
                <p>
                  <picture>
                    <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f7faef3f1072158912848af92b3b7caad8242c3c.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
                    <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f7faef3f1072158912848af92b3b7caad8242c3c.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
                    <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1f7faef3f1072158912848af92b3b7caad8242c3c.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
                    <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Information Collaboration Hub for Life Sciences" src="./media_1f7faef3f1072158912848af92b3b7caad8242c3c.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
                  </picture>
                </p>
                <p><a href="https://youtu.be/izPHfZP4CLE">SAP Information Collaboration Hub for Life Sciences</a></p>
              </td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
        <p><em>Video produced by David Aguirre and Rana Hamzakadi</em></p>
        <p>Enter SAP Information Collaboration Hub for Life Sciences: this industry network based on software-as-a-service (SaaS) helps SAP pharmaceutical customers share information on their pharmaceutical products with supply chain partners and government agencies to enable traceability and verification of individual product packs in these markets.</p>
        <p>“It was really a joint effort with plenty of input from SAP customers that inspired the info hub,” says Oliver Nuernberg, chief product owner, SAP Life Sciences. “They pointed out the need for a global network that would minimize the effort by connecting once while sharing data with many participants.”</p>
        <p>Running on SAP Business Technology Platform, the information hub leverages the platform’s integration services to exchange messages, SAP Blockchain Business Services to make data available for verification, and portal services. In 2021, new innovative capabilities enabling the automation of onboarding processes and self-onboarding of trading partners were delivered to enable customers to efficiently onboard hundreds of partners in parallel for new markets.</p>
        <p>The largest eight pharmaceutical manufacturers, and 14 of the top 20, are already using SAP Information Collaboration Hub for Life Sciences, including most of the COVID-19 vaccines manufacturers.</p>
        <p>Next, we plan to offer SAP Information Collaboration Hub for Life Sciences together with SAP Advanced Track and Trace for Pharmaceuticals to enable aid workers from organizations such as the Red Cross and Doctors Without Borders to verify, for example, COVID-19 vaccines that they receive on the spot to low- to middle-income countries.</p>
        <p>Initially, the team was made up of just a handful of SAP employees working out of Germany and Ireland. Today, there are more than 50 team members from the Customer Innovation &#x26; Maintenance organization, mainly located in India, who develop and operate the solution as well as help onboard customers and their business partners.</p>
        <p>Amba Bisht, senior developer for Engineering in Customer Innovation &#x26; Maintenance, says: “What’s so rewarding about working on this project is how it really brings the spirit of SAP — to make the world run better — to life, because by increasing security in the pharmaceutical supply chain and preventing counterfeit medication from reaching patients, SAP Information Collaboration Hub for Life Sciences may ultimately save lives.”</p>
        <p><strong>Finalist Fast Facts</strong></p>
        <ul>
          <li><strong>Submission Title</strong>: SAP Information Collaboration Hub for Life Sciences, Saving Lives One Serial Number at a Time</li>
          <li><strong>Team:</strong> Oliver Nuernberg, Martin Janssen, Dennis Keilbach, Vincent Varain, Sandeep Kumar Dikshit, Shashank Goyal, Amba Bisht, Anil Kumar Suresh, Geetha Ranjani G M, Athul Umesh</li>
          <li><strong>Number of employees:</strong> More than 50</li>
          <li><strong>Achievement</strong>: Global network with the eight largest pharmaceutical companies and 14 of the top 20, most COVID-19 vaccine manufactures, over 1,000 live trading partners. The hub currently hosts 2.2 billion product packs in the blockchain for verification in the U.S. market, manages tens of thousands of messages reported to government agencies, such as those in the EU, Russia, Brazil, and other markets, every day, all to prevent counterfeit products being introduced into the legitimate supply chain.</li>
          <li><strong>Impact:</strong> Increase patient safety by authenticating pharmaceutical products, thus avoiding counterfeit drugs reaching patients; increase sustainability by reducing drug wastage.</li>
        </ul>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>sap-award/hasso-plattner-founders-awards</category>
            <category>product/sap-green-token</category>
            <category>product/sap-information-collaboration-hub-for-life-sciences</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[2021 Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award Finalists: Operational Excellence]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/operational-excellence-finalists-hasso-plattner-founders-award-2021</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/operational-excellence-finalists-hasso-plattner-founders-award-2021</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Get to know the three Operational Excellence finalists for the 2021 Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award, SAP's highest employee recognition.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_156abd619041804682268f89108a7aaab035ebf4d.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_156abd619041804682268f89108a7aaab035ebf4d.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_156abd619041804682268f89108a7aaab035ebf4d.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="2021 Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award Finalists: Operational Excellence" src="./media_156abd619041804682268f89108a7aaab035ebf4d.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="hasso-plattner-founders-award-finalists-operational-excellence">2021 Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award Finalists: Operational Excellence</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Nine teams across three categories are vying for this year’s Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award. Each category reflects a different type of breakthrough thinking, considering the various ways in which innovation drives SAP’s success.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Here, meet the finalists in the <strong>Operational Excellence</strong> category.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>The Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award is the highest<br>employee recognition at SAP, awarded annually by the CEO<br>to an individual or a team.</p>
        <h2 id="finalist-competitive-advantage-for-sales">Finalist: Competitive Advantage for Sales</h2>
        <table>
          <thead>
            <tr>
              <th colspan="2">Promo</th>
            </tr>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td>
                <h3 id="learn-about-what-life-looks-like-at-sap">Learn about what life looks like at SAP</h3>
              </td>
              <td><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/careers/who-we-are/life.html">Learn more</a></strong></td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
        <p>An integrated knowledge of customers, markets, and competition can be the decisive factor for a sales team in closing a deal. The challenge is that although sales-relevant data is available, it is often spread across different tools and platforms. Sales employees may lack the time and expertise needed to analyze and interpret the data. This represents a missed opportunity for sales and a gap that needed to be closed.</p>
        <p>The three-member <strong>Data-Driven Selling</strong> team — Pilar Navarro, Rajesh Parthasarathy, and Benjamin Baumann — accepted this challenge. The team is passionate about fundamentally improving sales decisions by using data-driven insights aligned with the sales journey and personalized to every phase of the sales cycle.</p>
        <table>
          <thead>
            <tr>
              <th>Embed</th>
            </tr>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td>
                <p>
                  <picture>
                    <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11853a8e93d48c756b201a975884b02febb3dd62e.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
                    <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11853a8e93d48c756b201a975884b02febb3dd62e.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
                    <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_11853a8e93d48c756b201a975884b02febb3dd62e.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
                    <img loading="lazy" alt="Data Driven Selling" src="./media_11853a8e93d48c756b201a975884b02febb3dd62e.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
                  </picture>
                </p>
                <p><a href="https://youtu.be/GieIFLuH1g4">Data Driven Selling</a></p>
              </td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
        <p><em>Video produced by Rana Hamzakadi and David Aguirre</em></p>
        <p>Starting in 2019, the team members delivered various ad-hoc and standard reports for demand generation and sales teams with the aim of identifying new sales opportunities. In the following year, the report was enhanced with additional data points, such as pipeline, profiling, adoption, market forecast, and competition, and was mapped to the different phases of the sales cycle, from planning to execution.</p>
        <p>In 2021, the team formally translated all the different needs from the field into the Data-Driven Selling dashboard for account, territory, and executive views.</p>
        <p><strong>The Right Data at the Right Time</strong></p>
        <p>“Our dashboard integrates sales data from more than 10 different sources into one holistic view that enables teams to analyze and interpret the data,” says Navarro. “Sales teams can make faster, better-informed decisions as to where they should concentrate their efforts.”</p>
        <p>As a result, the solution can help both sales planning and execution teams generate and accelerate new deals, giving them a significant competitive advantage. Better informed employees are a threefold win: for the sales teams, for customers, and for SAP.</p>
        <p>“Data-Driven Selling has already generated tremendous interest and has been well accepted in our EMEA South region and in the various market units,” Navarro shares. “The concept is so powerful that it could be used outside of SAP, too, and even offered as a solution.”</p>
        <p><strong>Finalist Fast Facts</strong></p>
        <ul>
          <li><strong>Submission Title</strong>: Data-Driven Selling</li>
          <li><strong>Team</strong>: Pilar Navarro, Rajesh Parthasarathy, Benjamin Baumann</li>
          <li><strong>Number of employees</strong>: Three, with many internal contributors and supporters</li>
          <li><strong>Achievement</strong>: Provide the sales team with the right data at the right time to make the right decisions on where to focus their efforts. Some of the key proven impacts realized are incremental pipeline, progress in existing opportunities and pipeline conversion to revenue.</li>
          <li><strong>Impact</strong>: SAP sales teams can use the Data-Driven Selling dashboard to improve demand management, opportunity acceleration, and deal closure.</li>
        </ul>
        <h2 id="finalist-the-future-of-engineering">Finalist: The Future of Engineering</h2>
        <p>Integration is at the center of SAP’s business strategy. More than 15,000 customers use SAP Integration Suite to execute business-critical processes in 30 data centers, supporting 10 billion transactions monthly – and the numbers keep rising.</p>
        <p>While customers expect solutions to run trouble-free, SAP teams are continuously challenged by the steadily growing number of customers and systems. More than 50,000 monthly software deployments on these systems across different environments, such as those of the leading infrastructure providers, add many additional sources of error to the equation. Many of the incidents are caused by factors that developers cannot anticipate. In the worst case, this leads to interruptions for customers and ties up developer time to resolve the issues.</p>
        <table>
          <thead>
            <tr>
              <th>Embed</th>
            </tr>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td>
                <p>
                  <picture>
                    <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17e39a1f51dac8c3d034cc2e6809188aab7e1478f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
                    <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17e39a1f51dac8c3d034cc2e6809188aab7e1478f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
                    <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_17e39a1f51dac8c3d034cc2e6809188aab7e1478f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
                    <img loading="lazy" alt="Data Driven Engineering" src="./media_17e39a1f51dac8c3d034cc2e6809188aab7e1478f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
                  </picture>
                </p>
                <p><a href="https://youtu.be/lnFgaY00QqU">Data Driven Engineering</a></p>
              </td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
        <p><em>Video produced by Rana Hamzakadi and David Aguirre</em></p>
        <p>That is why the <strong>Data-Driven Engineering</strong> team, led by Bhagyesh Hede, believed that developer teams needed an intelligent, data-driven methodology to achieve uninterrupted, functional, and focused software deployment at a high level of quality. Their goal was to proactively predict and prevent outages for customers. It quickly became clear that they were not only building a bridge between development and operations, but also had to establish permanent, close cooperation between these two areas – which also benefits customers. With this inspiration, the 10-person team worked on their project tirelessly until they were able to present the initial results of their work.</p>
        <p><strong>Dashboards Support Developers</strong></p>
        <p>Data-Driven Engineering methodology outlines capturing key metrics in multiple dashboards tailored to individual scrum teams. These dashboards provide information about the most important KPIs for the functions, as well as insights into how the software is working in the actual productive environment. The metrics give teams an overview of the most significant configuration changes and their impacts, and pre-defined thresholds trigger alerts when passed. The dashboards also provide insights for the planning of peak loads and help the development and operation teams develop robust, scalable software for diverse environments.</p>
        <p>“Data-Driven Engineering enables us to meet our customers’ expectations by shortening recovery times, reducing the number of incidents, and deploying new features faster,” explains Hede. “Since the development teams have better insights into both development and productive environments, we can identify error patterns at an early stage that could have a major impact if not corrected. We’ve been able to avoid many customer incidents as a result. The solution will help us achieve our cloud availability service level agreements of close to 100%.”</p>
        <p><strong>Finalist Fast Facts</strong></p>
        <ul>
          <li><strong>Submission Title:</strong> Data-Driven Engineering</li>
          <li><strong>Team:</strong> Bhagyesh Hede, Ashwinkumar Vijayakumar, Himanshu Mahajan, Tarun Ramakrishna Elankath, Karthikeyan R, Mrutyunjay Padmasali Sidda, Nitin Verma, Sapreen Ahuja, Prajwal Gonsalves, Sandhya Nambrath</li>
          <li><strong>Number of employees</strong>: 10</li>
          <li><strong>Achievement:</strong> Conceptualized and contextualized the Data-Driven Engineering methodology in the organization using state-of-the-art monitoring and Big Data technology within the Cloud Integration unit. The methodology centers on customer satisfaction and helps make SAP engineers’ work more efficient.</li>
          <li><strong>Impact:</strong> Data-Driven Engineering supports fulfilling the business expectations of customers, such as improved time to recovery, lower incidents, and delivering new features at speed. As the development teams have greater insights into production, early visibility of the failure patterns is available, which could cascade to greater impact.</li>
        </ul>
        <h2 id="finalist-healthy-accounts--satisfied-customers">Finalist: Healthy Accounts = Satisfied Customers</h2>
        <p>Sales employees know it is better – and easier – to keep customers than to attract new ones. But the grand prize is when current customers regularly renew their contracts and buy additional solutions. Customer Health Score specifies a customer’s renewal risk and helps account teams create better customer relationships.</p>
        <table>
          <thead>
            <tr>
              <th>Embed</th>
            </tr>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td>
                <p>
                  <picture>
                    <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1088f4e50cc002597618f4ea14d9c44b54d4178ac.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
                    <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1088f4e50cc002597618f4ea14d9c44b54d4178ac.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
                    <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1088f4e50cc002597618f4ea14d9c44b54d4178ac.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
                    <img loading="lazy" alt="Cloud Health Score" src="./media_1088f4e50cc002597618f4ea14d9c44b54d4178ac.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
                  </picture>
                </p>
                <p><a href="https://youtu.be/VxU05U61p5A">Cloud Health Score</a></p>
              </td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
        <p><em>Video produced by Rana Hamzakadi and David Aguirre</em></p>
        <p>Under Angela Reichert, the 10-person team began work in late 2019 to predict the renewal risk in cloud accounts and use these findings to alert account teams at an early stage. The goal is to improve the health score and thus minimize the renewal risk. The team is comprised primarily of colleagues from North America and Germany who otherwise work on different teams. “We want to achieve 10% more customers with healthy and neutral cloud health scores,” says Reichert.</p>
        <p><strong>Machine Learning for Real-Time Insights</strong></p>
        <p>The team relied on machine learning to create a powerful solution and is convinced that the data, combined with real-time insights into accounts, is extremely powerful when predicting renewal risk. Sixty-five percent of SAP cloud customers are digital customers that are not assigned a customer team. In some cases, the automated check of the customer status is the only information available.</p>
        <p>The Customer Health Score model is already forecasting the renewal risk for 94% of nearly 68,000 cloud customers. The score is used both regionally and globally and already supports almost all cloud solutions from SAP. The prediction quality is over 80% and the team is confident they can increase it with the help of additional data, such as external financial metrics.</p>
        <p>When asked about the project’s impact on the company, Reichert explains, “In addition to the improved health index and higher visibility of critical accounts, our approach delivers one thing above all else: a positive customer experience and thus a better customer relationship.”</p>
        <p><strong>Finalist Fast Facts</strong></p>
        <ul>
          <li><strong>Submission Title</strong>: Intelligent Visibility into Cloud Customer Health with Predictive Score</li>
          <li><strong>Team</strong>: Cloud Health Score core project team, including Global Post Sales Process Office, Customer Engagement &#x26; Experience, and Intelligent Data and Analytics, Franchise for Customer Success</li>
          <li><strong>Number of employees</strong>: 10</li>
          <li><strong>Achievement</strong>: Machine prediction of customer health, identifying risk to renewal, using over 90 data points, validated at 80% accuracy</li>
          <li><strong>Impact</strong>: Ninety-four percent cloud annual contract value with intelligent predictive score (€7.1 billion revenue), global coverage, across 11 cloud lines of business, 65,000 cloud accounts and growing</li>
        </ul>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>sap-award/hasso-plattner-founders-awards</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[2021 Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award Finalists: Go-to-Market]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/go-to-market-finalists-hasso-plattner-founders-award</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/go-to-market-finalists-hasso-plattner-founders-award</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Get to know the three Go-to-Market finalists for the 2021 Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award, SAP's highest employee recognition.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16c9e69f266d0eab95ad4dd00eb4ad4702d37389c.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16c9e69f266d0eab95ad4dd00eb4ad4702d37389c.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_16c9e69f266d0eab95ad4dd00eb4ad4702d37389c.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="2021 Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award Finalists: Go-to-Market" src="./media_16c9e69f266d0eab95ad4dd00eb4ad4702d37389c.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="hasso-plattner-founders-award-finalists-go-to-market">2021 Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award Finalists: Go-to-Market</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Nine teams across three categories are vying for this year’s Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award. Each category reflects a different type of breakthrough thinking, considering the various ways in which innovation drives SAP’s success.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Here, meet the finalists in the <strong>Go-to-Market</strong> category.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>The Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award is the highest<br>employee recognition at SAP, awarded annually by the CEO<br>to an individual or a team.</p>
        <h2 id="finalist-business-operation-self-healing">Finalist: Business Operation Self-Healing</h2>
        <table>
          <thead>
            <tr>
              <th colspan="2">Promo</th>
            </tr>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td>
                <h3 id="learn-about-what-life-looks-like-at-sap">Learn about what life looks like at SAP</h3>
              </td>
              <td><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/careers/who-we-are.html">Learn more</a></strong></td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
        <p>“A world where AI is an integral part of day-to-day business operations, where we learn from every interaction and data point to improve business systems.” This is the vision of Glenn Svensson and his team. And with implementing their innovation – Business Operation Self-Healing (BOSH) – they want to take a step toward realizing this vision.</p>
        <table>
          <thead>
            <tr>
              <th>Embed</th>
            </tr>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td>
                <p>
                  <picture>
                    <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14514f9f441dcd479c26c429c54764bd4d431be9e.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
                    <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14514f9f441dcd479c26c429c54764bd4d431be9e.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
                    <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_14514f9f441dcd479c26c429c54764bd4d431be9e.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
                    <img loading="lazy" alt="Business Operation Self-Healing Service" src="./media_14514f9f441dcd479c26c429c54764bd4d431be9e.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
                  </picture>
                </p>
                <p><a href="https://youtu.be/KJ9cOd_neXc">Business Operation Self-Healing Service</a></p>
              </td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
        <p><em>Video produced by Rana Hamzakadi and David Aguirre</em></p>
        <p>It all started as a research project for the SAP Executive Board, exploring the broader context of artificial intelligence (AI) in businesses. In the process, the team quickly discovered they could “do way more with AI than anticipated,” Svensson remembers. As business operations become more complex, automated solutions are crucial to supporting the best customer experiences.</p>
        <p>According to the team, their digital innovation can identify and fix issues, address performance variations, and restore outages without human intervention, which is time-consuming and prone to error. At the same time, it is helping business users, service desks, and IT professionals work more efficiently. “Gone are the days of submitting a help desk ticket and waiting for a member of the IT team to intervene when a system incident occurs,” Svensson says.</p>
        <p>BOSH is an automation engine build on AI that is capable of understanding human-machine interactions and has contextual awareness. Based on these capabilities, BOSH can resolve customers’ operational issues all by itself. With BOSH, high-volume complex issues can be solved in minutes – even seconds – rather than hours.</p>
        <p>Built on SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP), it combines a broad set of services. “We have some amazing platform services in SAP BTP,” Svensson says. “We took these and elevated them into something inventive and unique that brings tremendous value to our customers.”</p>
        <p>The team built more than 80 high-value, ready-to-use resolutions addressing common customer issues. BOSH also has more than 500 conversational skills, allowing faster and better routing of issues to the right department, leading to faster resolutions and the best possible customer experience.</p>
        <p>This customer-first approach is the fundamental motivation for the whole team: “We originated in the Customer Success organization, so our background was solidly in the customer-facing side of the company,” Svensson says.</p>
        <p><strong>Transformational Moment in User Experience</strong></p>
        <p>Svensson and his team are confident that BOSH will drive the adoption of AI in day-to-day business and offer a huge impact on customers. “We have observed that self-healing services settle issues in a fraction of the time and improve the user experience dramatically,” he says.</p>
        <p>With their innovation, the finalist team wants to bring hyperautomation closer to customers and demonstrate that AI can play a secure and transparent role in their businesses.</p>
        <p><strong>Finalist Fast Facts</strong></p>
        <ul>
          <li><strong>Submission Title:</strong> Business Operations Self-Healing Service (BOSH)</li>
          <li><strong>Team:</strong> Glenn Svensson, Andy Lawrence, Mark Cooling, Eoghan Murphy</li>
          <li><strong>Number of Employees:</strong> More than 40 with core team, other colleagues, fellows, delivery colleagues, and interns</li>
          <li><strong>Achievement:</strong> BOSH has gone live at HPE, SAP, and other large blue-chip companies around the world. It offers over 80 ready-to-use resolutions and more than 500 conversational skills.</li>
          <li><strong>Impact:</strong> As market makers in the hyperautomation space, BOSH demonstrates to customers that AI can safely and transparently take a role in their organizations. The solution covers sales, HR, procurement, and IT, and crosses lines of business. BOSH is leading the acceptance of AI in day-to-day business in a human-centric approach. All this can be delivered in less than four weeks to customers.</li>
        </ul>
        <h2 id="finalist-successline">Finalist: SuccessLine</h2>
        <p>How can SAP bring teams from the Customer Success organization together to better support customers’ moves to software-as-a-service offerings and accelerate their value realization in the cloud? Questions like these drove the Industries and Customer Advisory (ICA) team to develop SuccessLine, a tool that brings proven best practices to Customer Success organization teams worldwide.</p>
        <table>
          <thead>
            <tr>
              <th>Embed</th>
            </tr>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td>
                <p>
                  <picture>
                    <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ac9b037266b4e5135ed7d672acb00d85c2dd8140.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
                    <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ac9b037266b4e5135ed7d672acb00d85c2dd8140.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
                    <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1ac9b037266b4e5135ed7d672acb00d85c2dd8140.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
                    <img loading="lazy" alt="ICA SuccessLine" src="./media_1ac9b037266b4e5135ed7d672acb00d85c2dd8140.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
                  </picture>
                </p>
                <p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4SsJDDE609Y">ICA SuccessLine</a></p>
              </td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
        <p><em>Video produced by Rana Hamzakadi and David Aguirre</em></p>
        <p>SuccessLine is a tool that helps teams plan, collaborate, and execute complex customer engagements. With their innovation, the finalist team delivers a solution that can drive customer engagements with a cloud-first mindset.</p>
        <p>SuccessLine guides teams through the entire customer journey. For each step, it links to the most up-to-date go-to-market best practices, including the latest SAP innovations, such as SAP solutions for sustainability offerings, and puts them into a customer context. For each recommended activity, SucccessLine proposes references, best-in-class examples, and contacts to help teams position the right value to the customer.</p>
        <p>“For example, the global RISE with SAP template guides the teams to the digital discovery assessment process to effectively position RISE with SAP,” explains Jeff Tanner, global director from the Industries and Customer Advisory team at SAP. At the same time, the tool enables teams around the world to join forces and collaborate visually with one another.</p>
        <p><strong>Creating Alignment, Transparency, Simplicity</strong></p>
        <p>Throughout the process, the entire customer journey can be shared with colleagues from the Customer Engagement &#x26; Experience organization as well as partner teams, helping to facilitate a smoother handover and full transparency of the customer engagement.</p>
        <p>“There is no other solution available to our Customer Success teams that can create the alignment, transparency, and simplicity that SuccessLine delivers,” Tanner says.</p>
        <p>SuccessLine was initially developed and tested as a prototype in the EMEA North region. Following a successful global pilot in 65% of SAP regions, SuccessLine is planned to be rolled out worldwide in 2022 and for availability to more than 5,000 field employees in the first quarter of 2022.</p>
        <p>For Tanner, the current global reach will benefit Customer Success teams everywhere. However, he stresses that the impact of SuccessLine will be measured not only by its adoption, but also by how it helps the field transform customer discussions. He is confident that SuccessLine has the potential to reshape the way field teams collaborate, help them deliver value to SAP customers, and ultimately accelerate both SAP’s and its customers’ transitions to the cloud.</p>
        <p>“One of the most important jobs we have is helping our customers move to the cloud. SuccessLine empowers teams to position the latest cloud solutions and enables our customers’ reinvention in the cloud,” Tanner says.</p>
        <p><strong>Finalist Fast Facts</strong></p>
        <ul>
          <li><strong>Submission Title</strong>: SuccessLine by Industries and Customer Advisory</li>
          <li><strong>Team:</strong> Geff Gilligan, Richard Abbiss, Ummar Rasheed, Ilda Freitas, Mieke de Rooij, Thomas Scaysbrook, Henry Himanen, Ken Crovetti, Jeff Tanner, Phil Davies</li>
          <li><strong>Number of Employees:</strong> 10</li>
          <li><strong>Achievement:</strong> An innovative, best practice delivery and collaboration platform to drive customer value realization</li>
          <li><strong>Impact:</strong> Available soon to more than 5,000 field employees in the Customer Success organization, SuccessLine will transform customer discussions – measured by improved customer NPS, cloud adoption, and renewal rates.</li>
        </ul>
        <h2 id="finalist-support-assistant">Finalist: Support Assistant</h2>
        <p>Fast reactions and providing solutions are key when it comes to creating positive customer experiences. To prevent customer support cases from piling up in the queue and longer wait times, Jonathan Wiens and his team set a goal of connecting customers directly to solutions to further reduce the time needed to resolve customer support cases. An idea was born: a tool that enables customers to find their solutions easily without the need for a support engineer to walk them through it.</p>
        <table>
          <thead>
            <tr>
              <th>Embed</th>
            </tr>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td>
                <p>
                  <picture>
                    <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_108e263567bd0303fb502c313c57f9e9af185e44a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
                    <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_108e263567bd0303fb502c313c57f9e9af185e44a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
                    <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_108e263567bd0303fb502c313c57f9e9af185e44a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
                    <img loading="lazy" alt="Support Assistant" src="./media_108e263567bd0303fb502c313c57f9e9af185e44a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
                  </picture>
                </p>
                <p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HSe3F0TkGXc">Support Assistant</a></p>
              </td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
        <p><em>Video produced by Rana Hamzakadi and David Aguirre</em></p>
        <p>The team introduced Support Assistant, a cloud-based application that uses automation and machine learning to maximize customer satisfaction and minimize time-consuming manual work. With this innovation, customer teams are better able to handle an increasing number of support cases with the same amount of resources while supporting high customer satisfaction throughout the process.</p>
        <p>Wiens, lead developer, explains: “The Support Assistant takes our most valuable asset — the expertly combined knowledge of our engineers — and makes recommendations in a single tool for all customers to easily interrogate and resolve their issues.”</p>
        <p><strong>Guiding Customers from Problem to Solution Automatically</strong></p>
        <p>To narrow down their problem area when reporting an issue, customers are guided through a conversational user interface where the Support Assistant automates the most common and repeatable questions. Wiens explains that with each response the customer provides, Support Assistant uses machine learning to recommend expert content such as SAP Knowledge Base Articles, SAP Notes, SAP Community posts, or wikis. By presenting customers with possible solutions before they even need to connect with a human, the case submission process is simplified and the Support Assistant guides them from problem description to solution automatically.</p>
        <p>“The Support Assistant enables our customers to access knowledge repositories with ease, so they are empowered to act on solutions quickly and on their own,” Wiens summarizes.</p>
        <p>If the support of an engineer is needed, the previous conversation thread is aggregated into a comprehensive case description that can be shared with the human engineer. As a result, follow-up questions by the support provider can be minimized, leading to a reduced customer effort. This way, both customers and engineers can rely on the Support Assistant to increase the speed with which support organizations can react to them.</p>
        <p>The results speak for themselves: the Support Assistant is used daily, with more than 100,000 visitors on SAP Support Portal per day. Wiens shares that the Support Assistant was used 65,000 times in 2021, leading to tens of thousands fewer support cases requiring help from a human support engineer.</p>
        <p>Wiens and his team are confident in the benefits of Support Assistant: “It is more vital than ever before to ensure we are No. 1 in customer satisfaction, especially when our customers consider cloud solutions. Support Assistant is helping us get there.”</p>
        <p><strong>Finalist Fast Facts</strong></p>
        <ul>
          <li><strong>Submission Title</strong>: Support Assistant: Delighting Customers by Solving Issues Faster</li>
          <li><strong>Team:</strong> James Chaplin, Lisa Lewis, Vincent Judge, Mike Griffiths, Sean MacNiven, Peter Rigo, Jonathan Wiens, Marcel Pinheiro, Christine Osborn, Lucas Viana</li>
          <li><strong>Number of employees:</strong> 10</li>
          <li><strong>Achievement:</strong> A team of product support engineers came together to design, build, and release an innovative customer-facing solution that guides customers to resolve their own product issues through interactively asking product- and problem-specific questions and matching them to the perfect solution.</li>
          <li><strong>Impact:</strong> With more than 100,000 visitors to SAP Support Portal every day, the Support Assistant reaches customers on a daily basis, as it is now available for 90% of all customer cases raised (excluding SAP Ariba, SAP Fieldglass, and SAP Concur). In 2021, SAP customers have used Support Assistant 65,000 times to find their solution, which means fewer cases in the support queue that require help from a support engineer. Happier customers renew their maintenance and continue paying their subscription, helping drive revenue for SAP.</li>
        </ul>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>sap-award/hasso-plattner-founders-awards</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Three Teams Take Home the 2020 Hasso Plattner Founders‘ Award]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/2020-hasso-plattner-founders-award-winners</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/2020-hasso-plattner-founders-award-winners</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Three teams were named 2020 Hasso Plattner Founders' Award winners, selected for outstanding, innovative projects. Learn more about them now.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ffcb0538e54e4c2303408650bb3cf38a54397e96.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ffcb0538e54e4c2303408650bb3cf38a54397e96.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1ffcb0538e54e4c2303408650bb3cf38a54397e96.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Three Teams Take Home the 2020 Hasso Plattner Founders‘ Award" src="./media_1ffcb0538e54e4c2303408650bb3cf38a54397e96.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="three-teams-take-home-the-2020-hasso-plattner-founders-award">Three Teams Take Home the 2020 Hasso Plattner Founders‘ Award</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>For the first time in the award’s history, SAP CEO Christian Klein last week announced three winners of the Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award, the company’s most prestigious employee recognition.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The three teams were selected for outstanding and innovative projects in the new categories <a href="/2020/12/customer-success-finalists-hasso-plattner-founders-award">Customer Success</a>, <a href="/2020/11/operational-excellence-finalists-hasso-plattner-founders-award">Operational Excellence</a>, and <a href="/2020/12/products-and-technology-finalists-hasso-plattner-founders-award">Products and Technology</a>.</p>
  <p>In 2020, more than 200 nominations involved over 1,400 employees from 37 countries. Eight teams consisting of 51 employees from all over the world made it to the final round, and the winning teams have chosen charity organizations to which SAP will donate €10,000: <a href="https://www.pih.org/">Partners in Health</a> and <a href="https://www.barefootcollege.org/">Barefoot College</a>.</p>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_100d9697f424135ea130adb6fb9996a98cd8feb93.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_100d9697f424135ea130adb6fb9996a98cd8feb93.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_100d9697f424135ea130adb6fb9996a98cd8feb93.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="The Winners of 2020 Hasso Plattner Founders&#x27; Award" src="./media_100d9697f424135ea130adb6fb9996a98cd8feb93.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://youtu.be/8-bVY00nxeY">The Winners of 2020 Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="intelligent-case-routing-making-the-machine-understand-the-issue">Intelligent Case Routing: Making the Machine Understand the Issue</h2>
  <p>The <strong>Customer Success</strong> category winner set out with the challenge to simplify the support triage and routing process within SAP Concur software. As tickets get older and remain unanswered, customer satisfaction score drastically drops.</p>
  <p>“With over 200,000 support tickets created per year in SAP Concur alone, we understood that any improvement on the overall process would be multiplied and have a significant impact on our key customer support and experience metrics,” Frantisek Zdvoran explained. “We found that combining a deep understanding of the customer support world, processes, and challenges with the right teams behind SAP’s machine learning services would provide real, business value-driven results.”</p>
  <p>Working on Intelligent Case Routing as a side project over the course of three years, Zdvoran and his team of Justin Lew, Alena Bartunkova, Lukas Tancer, and Radovan Murin built and implemented a machine learning solution that cuts down the manual effort using text recognition to examine past tickets.</p>
  <p>Intelligent Case Routing assigns the cases to specialists faster and more accurately. The goal was to eliminate the labor-intensive, repetitive, and slow ticketing process. “We didn’t want to add complexity, but to remove it,” Zdvoran said. “Support cases run through our application have a six percent higher customer experience score, 16% faster time to close, 11% higher first contact resolution metric, and have a 8.4% lower change of hands number.”</p>
  <p>On winning the award, Lew said: “We are beyond grateful and honored to have been selected as a winner and cannot give enough thanks to everyone that has helped and been supportive of us. We are so proud of how our diverse team has been able to marshal SAP’s intelligent enterprise and combine that with our customer-first approach to deliver an application that helps enhance our customer and employee experience.”</p>
  <h2 id="monitor-of-monitors-holistic-picture-of-cloud-health">Monitor of Monitors: Holistic Picture of Cloud Health</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-what-life-looks-like-at-sap">Learn more about what life looks like at SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/careers/who-we-are.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The winning team in the <strong>Operational Excellence</strong> category successfully tackled the challenge of creating a single source of information on the condition of SAP’s cloud. The Monitor of Monitors brings all monitoring tools into a cohesive and consistent view that shows the complete picture of SAP’s cloud health.</p>
  <p>Information that was previously siloed in disconnected monitoring tools, is now accessible and transparent in single service window. Monitor of Monitors not only enables SAP teams to detect, determine, and resolve problems and risks in the cloud much faster, it also allows operations and support teams across SAP to work faster and more collaboratively toward a common goal.</p>
  <p>“Recognize faster, react faster, respond faster, fix faster,” Anthony Sanchez said, summing up what Monitor of Monitors enables SAP support teams to do to improve the lives of their customers. “Monitor of Monitors isn’t a niche; it has value for everyone in SAP. It integrates well with any technology or tool a team is using to manage the cloud health and alert management. It simply opens an exchange of information that is centralized and transparent.”</p>
  <p>After the announcement that Monitor of Monitors had won the award, he added: “Today is one of the proudest days of my professional career. There are no words to capture the enormity of the pride I feel toward the team and the support we received from every corner. This was a true one SAP effort. We are all excited and motivated for the future of SAP, and the contributions we can continue to make.“</p>
  <p>Team members also include Vittalraya Shenoy Adige, Gabor Kaszonyi, József Kertész, Birk Bohne, Marcus Mrozowski, Gregory Melasecca-Jr, Yu Chen, Alexander Julian Danek, and Daniel Koller.</p>
  <h2 id="sap-hana-data-anonymization-inventing-a-new-market">SAP HANA Data Anonymization: Inventing a New Market</h2>
  <p>The winner in the category <strong>Products and Technology</strong> took on a particularly complex topic that is the subject of frequent legal and governmental changes. With SAP HANA Data Anonymization, the team developed a cross-industry solution for the anonymization of personal data that can be applied to a variety of use cases.</p>
  <p>“Data privacy constraints have been road blockers to a number of use cases,” Stephan Kessler shared. “SAP HANA data anonymization strives to make privacy guarantees available throughout an entire organization, while integrating seamlessly into business applications.”</p>
  <p>To achieve this, SAP HANA data anonymization is implemented at the database level, following the SAP HANA code “push-down” paradigm, leading to a tight integration of data and privacy mechanisms.</p>
  <p>“As data privacy becomes a priority on business agendas, we are the first to offer this sort of anonymization features in the database core system,” Kessler explained. “The solution thus permits SAP to satisfy an urgent need of customers and society.”</p>
  <p>On winning the award, the team said: “We are humbled and very honored to have received the Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award. SAP HANA data anonymization solves the challenge of combining privacy and innovation for internal and external stakeholders. We now have momentum to accelerate development and customer adoption to further improve our product, while helping customers, research, and society to demonstrate digital responsibility.”</p>
  <p>Team members include Kristin Ulrich, Matthias Menz, Brian Raver, Kai Morich, Kaweh Amoi-Taleghani, and Kessler.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>sap-award/hasso-plattner-founders-awards</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Winners of the 2020 Hasso Plattner Founders' Award]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/videos/winners-of-the-2020-hasso-plattner-founders-award</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/videos/winners-of-the-2020-hasso-plattner-founders-award</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[For the first time in the history of the Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award, SAP CEO Christian Klein announced not just one but three winners of...]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_100d9697f424135ea130adb6fb9996a98cd8feb93.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_100d9697f424135ea130adb6fb9996a98cd8feb93.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_100d9697f424135ea130adb6fb9996a98cd8feb93.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="The Winners of 2020 Hasso Plattner Founders&#x27; Award" src="./media_100d9697f424135ea130adb6fb9996a98cd8feb93.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="winners-of-the-2020-hasso-plattner-founders-award">Winners of the 2020 Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_100d9697f424135ea130adb6fb9996a98cd8feb93.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_100d9697f424135ea130adb6fb9996a98cd8feb93.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_100d9697f424135ea130adb6fb9996a98cd8feb93.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="The Winners of 2020 Hasso Plattner Founders&#x27; Award" src="./media_100d9697f424135ea130adb6fb9996a98cd8feb93.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://youtu.be/8-bVY00nxeY">The Winners of 2020 Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>For the first time in the history of the Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award, SAP CEO Christian Klein announced not just one but <em>three</em> winners of the prestigious reward.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The winning teams were selected for their outstanding and innovative projects in the categories Customer Success, Operational Excellence, and Products and Technology. Meet the winners.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/video</category>
            <category>sap-award/hasso-plattner-founders-awards</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Meet Intelligent Case Routing]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/videos/hpfa-intelligent-case-routing</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/videos/hpfa-intelligent-case-routing</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Intelligent Case Routing is a Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award 2020 finalist for the category Customer Success. Zdvoran, Frantisek, Support Manager & Case Routing Guru of...]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1408698335bd24699b2e1a522ade96e180f1553fc.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1408698335bd24699b2e1a522ade96e180f1553fc.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1408698335bd24699b2e1a522ade96e180f1553fc.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Intelligent Case Routing" src="./media_1408698335bd24699b2e1a522ade96e180f1553fc.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="meet-intelligent-case-routing">Meet Intelligent Case Routing</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1408698335bd24699b2e1a522ade96e180f1553fc.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1408698335bd24699b2e1a522ade96e180f1553fc.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1408698335bd24699b2e1a522ade96e180f1553fc.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Intelligent Case Routing" src="./media_1408698335bd24699b2e1a522ade96e180f1553fc.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://youtu.be/bLRArjGHv4I">Intelligent Case Routing</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Intelligent Case Routing is a Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award <a href="/2020/12/customer-success-finalists-hasso-plattner-founders-award">2020 finalist for the category Customer Success</a>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Zdvoran, Frantisek, Support Manager &#x26; Case Routing Guru of ‘Intelligent Case Routing’ shares how their innovation tackles the challenge of simplifying the complex, time-consuming and manual support triage and case routing process.</p>
  <p>Read the SAP News story:<a href="https://www.youtube.com/redirect?redir_token=QUFFLUhqbVJlNTNpYi00emVQZ0dYVjNGUkFLUUhYYU9DZ3xBQ3Jtc0treVA3UEhFOGR0YVJpenl2aVlSbW85TWFoQUtpM3FPX3E4cnhKTldCMU5RSmU0dTY4UzUtYVRxVnBtcVByWk9kVHFZcFZZWDVSV2pTSk9aNzRGblFjSU42T0ZkMnlqLWJvSmRGZzZOYlZMYVdRSjVjcw%3D%3D&#x26;q=https%3A%2F%2Fnews.sap.com%2F%3Fp%3D181105&#x26;v=bLRArjGHv4I&#x26;event=video_description">https://news.sap.com/?p=181105</a></p>
  <p><em>*Some scenes in this video were captured before the pandemic.</em></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/video</category>
            <category>sap-award/hasso-plattner-founders-awards</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Meet the Intelligent Enterprise Showroom]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/videos/hpfa-intelligent-enterprise-showroom</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/videos/hpfa-intelligent-enterprise-showroom</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The Intelligent Enterprise Showroom is a Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award 2020 finalist for the category Customer Success. Dr. Oliver Gutzeit shares insights about the Intelligent...]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/video</category>
            <category>sap-award/hasso-plattner-founders-awards</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Meet Monitor of Monitors]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/videos/hpfa-monitor-of-monitors</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/videos/hpfa-monitor-of-monitors</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Monitor of Monitors is the Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award 2020 finalist for the category Operational Excellence. Anthony Sanchez, concept leader and evangelist, shares insights...]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18130aac0c2f04f446cc8d0488772cbc3a3830c58.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18130aac0c2f04f446cc8d0488772cbc3a3830c58.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_18130aac0c2f04f446cc8d0488772cbc3a3830c58.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="The Monitor of Monitors" src="./media_18130aac0c2f04f446cc8d0488772cbc3a3830c58.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="meet-monitor-of-monitors">Meet Monitor of Monitors</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18130aac0c2f04f446cc8d0488772cbc3a3830c58.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18130aac0c2f04f446cc8d0488772cbc3a3830c58.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_18130aac0c2f04f446cc8d0488772cbc3a3830c58.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="The Monitor of Monitors" src="./media_18130aac0c2f04f446cc8d0488772cbc3a3830c58.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://youtu.be/vzNve58UgGA">The Monitor of Monitors</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Monitor of Monitors is the Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award <a href="/2020/11/operational-excellence-finalists-hasso-plattner-founders-award">2020 finalist for the category Operational Excellence</a>.</p>
  <p>Anthony Sanchez, concept leader and evangelist, shares insights into the innovation and the challenges they tackle. Meet the smart team behind the innovation and find out how it enables an exchange of centralized and transparent information.</p>
  <p><em>*Some scenes in this video were captured before the pandemic.</em></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/video</category>
            <category>sap-award/hasso-plattner-founders-awards</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nicolas Neumann Wins SAP Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award 2019]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/videos/nicolas-neumann-wins-sap-hasso-plattner-founders-award-2019</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/videos/nicolas-neumann-wins-sap-hasso-plattner-founders-award-2019</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[For the first time, SAP’s most prestigious employee award has been taken home by a single person. Award-winner Nicolas Neumann has created a tool that...]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>content-type/video</category>
            <category>sap-award/hasso-plattner-founders-awards</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Leveling the Playing Field for Entrepreneurs]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/videos/leveling-the-playing-field-for-entrepreneurs</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/videos/leveling-the-playing-field-for-entrepreneurs</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP.iO No Boundaries is an initiative designed to provide venture capital and acceleration support to underrepresented entrepreneurs in the business software industry – and it...]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1dcf1219791ba35f5f45b546afc2a367839dd0446.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1dcf1219791ba35f5f45b546afc2a367839dd0446.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1dcf1219791ba35f5f45b546afc2a367839dd0446.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Leveling the Playing Field for Entrepreneurs" src="./media_1dcf1219791ba35f5f45b546afc2a367839dd0446.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="leveling-the-playing-field-for-entrepreneurs">Leveling the Playing Field for Entrepreneurs</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1dcf1219791ba35f5f45b546afc2a367839dd0446.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1dcf1219791ba35f5f45b546afc2a367839dd0446.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1dcf1219791ba35f5f45b546afc2a367839dd0446.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Leveling the Playing Field for Entrepreneurs" src="./media_1dcf1219791ba35f5f45b546afc2a367839dd0446.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bTvstj6W6Hc">Leveling the Playing Field for Entrepreneurs</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>SAP.iO No Boundaries is an initiative designed to provide venture capital and acceleration support to underrepresented entrepreneurs in the business software industry – and it is the first of its kind.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The initiative supports groups of B2B software entrepreneurs like women, who have historically received disproportionately less support than other groups. The startups receive tailored mentorship, workshops in pricing, sales, marketing, or design, access to SAP executives and customers and exposure to SAP technologies, including APIs. The team is closely collaborating with internal and external stakeholders, ensuring growth that is focused on value instead of volume. SAP.iO No Boundaries is one of eight finalists of the Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award 2019.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/video</category>
            <category>news-tag/entrepreneurship</category>
            <category>sap-award/hasso-plattner-founders-awards</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-io</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Digital Aged Care: Live Longer Healthier And Happier Lives]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/videos/digital-aged-care-live-longer-healthier-and-happier-lives</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/videos/digital-aged-care-live-longer-healthier-and-happier-lives</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A group of SAP employees across five board areas has come up with a solution that enables senior citizens to live healthier and more autonomous...]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/video</category>
            <category>sap-award/hasso-plattner-founders-awards</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>