<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/product/sap-ariba-contracts/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Future of Procurement Is Already a Reality at SAP Spend Connect Live]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/procurement-news-sap-spend-connect-live</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/procurement-news-sap-spend-connect-live</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[At SAP Spend Connect Live, we announced a series of procurement innovations focused on streamlining procurement processes. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>product/sap-ariba-buying</category>
            <category>product/sap-ariba-contracts</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-concur</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fieldglass</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-spend-connect-live</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Unveils New Generative AI Innovations That Boost Productivity and Effectiveness in Spend Management]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/sap-spend-connect-live-generative-ai-innovations-spend-management</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/sap-spend-connect-live-generative-ai-innovations-spend-management</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[From SAP Spend Connect Live in Vienna, SAP has introduced new business AI and UX innovations for spend management and business network.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>product/sap-ariba-category-management</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>product/sap-ariba-buying</category>
            <category>product/sap-ariba-contracts</category>
            <category>product/sap-ariba-sourcing</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-concur</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-spend-connect-live</category>
            <category>product/sap-spend-control-tower</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Five Lessons Learned from DSM’s Sustainable Procurement Transformation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/five-lessons-learned-dsm-sustainable-procurement-transformation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/five-lessons-learned-dsm-sustainable-procurement-transformation</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Royal DSM utilized SAP Business Network and SAP Ariba solutions to enhance the sustainability of its global indirect procurement. Learn more!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>product/sap-ariba-buying</category>
            <category>product/sap-ariba-contracts</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Companies Continue to Digitalize Spend Management with SAP]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/companies-digitalize-spend-management-with-sap</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/companies-digitalize-spend-management-with-sap</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Ariba and SAP Fieldglass solutions help companies across industries digitalize spend management and external workforce management.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18336490c7900d7c1abeb97d7ba5022908af43cf5.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18336490c7900d7c1abeb97d7ba5022908af43cf5.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_18336490c7900d7c1abeb97d7ba5022908af43cf5.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Companies Continue to Digitalize Spend Management with SAP" src="./media_18336490c7900d7c1abeb97d7ba5022908af43cf5.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="companies-continue-to-digitalize-spend-management-with-sap">Companies Continue to Digitalize Spend Management with SAP</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="achieve-digital-transformation-from-source-to-pay-with-sap-ariba-solutions">Achieve digital transformation from source to pay with SAP Ariba solutions</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.ariba.com/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced that Molson Coors Beverage Co. and the Florida Department of Management Services are among the hundreds of companies across industries and geographies in the second quarter to have chosen <a href="http://www.ariba.com/?campaigncode=CRM-IS20-PRL-OOCWA01">SAP Ariba</a> and <a href="https://www.fieldglass.com/?campaigncode=CRM-IS20-PRL-OOCWF02">SAP Fieldglass</a> solutions to digitalize procurement and external workforce management. Hundreds more renewed licenses and still more went live with the solutions to optimize spend management.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“We have seen significant growth this quarter with companies around the world continuing to prioritize improving their spend management operations,” said John Wookey, president of SAP Intelligent Spend and Business Network. “By modernizing and digitalizing critical business processes across procurement and external workforce management, our customers are gaining visibility and insights that enable them to control costs, reduce risk and drive innovation and growth for their businesses.”</p>
  <p>Highlights from the quarter include:</p>
  <p><strong>Alcon Vision</strong>, the Fort Worth, Texas–based company, is a global leader in eye care, specializing in surgical medical devices and nonsurgical vision care products. Alcon selected SAP Ariba solutions for sourcing and procurement for direct and indirect materials. The company also selected the Qualtrics XM for Suppliers solution to help build stronger and more collaborative relationships with suppliers. With a new and improved intuitive source-to-pay experience, Alcon aims to foster simplicity, speed and user-friendly buying services with increased data transparency and compliance.</p>
  <p>Refrigeration and air conditioning technology manufacturer <strong>BITZER SE</strong> has implemented the SAP Ariba Buying solution with guided buying capability to help streamline and digitalize its procurement operations. With the SAP Ariba solution, BITZER, based in Sindelfingen, Germany, aims to drive a more efficient, paperless, transparent process from sourcing to payment as it expands globally.</p>
  <p>The <strong>Florida Department of Management Services (DMS)</strong> selected SAP Ariba solutions for sourcing, contracts, buying and invoicing, and commerce automation to modernize its statewide procurement system with a cloud-based solution. DMS plans to standardize and automate procurement processes across the State of Florida, increase spend visibility and control, and enhance savings statewide.</p>
  <p>Aligned with its innovation and sustainability strategy, <strong>Grupo Financiero Banorte, S.A.B. de C.V.,</strong> one of the largest financial holdings companies in Mexico, continues its procurement transformation with the renewal of SAP Ariba solutions. By further digitalizing its procurement processes and strengthening its supply lifecycle management automation, Banorte will help improve the experience of more than 21,000 suppliers while enhancing process efficiency and spend compliance.</p>
  <p><strong>Molson Coors</strong> made a strategic investment in SAP Ariba solutions to help modernize its global procurement operations, building on its implementation of the SAP Ariba Contracts solution and adding the SAP Ariba Buying and Invoicing solution with commerce automation capabilities. With the new solutions integrated with its multiple ERP infrastructure, the company, headquartered in Golden, Colorado, and Montreal, Canada, intends to standardize on best practices from source to pay, improve efficiency in supplier relationship management and minimize risk.</p>
  <p><strong>Promigas SA ESP</strong>, a leading Colombian provider of natural gas, has selected SAP Ariba solutions for digital procurement as it continued its transformation journey with SAP. Building on its existing transportation management system based on SAP S/4HANA, Promigas will adopt the cloud-based SAP Ariba solutions to help standardize and automate its procurement processes, increase purchasing efficiencies and reduce costs and risks.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-fieldglass-rework-how-work-gets-done">SAP Fieldglass: Rework how work gets done</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.fieldglass.com/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><strong>Roca Sanitario SA</strong>, a global leader in bathroom equipment, selected SAP Ariba solutions for strategic sourcing, buying, commerce automation and supply chain collaboration. The Spanish company will adopt the digital <a href="https://www.fieldglass.com/solutions/services-procurement">procurement solutions</a> to help improve, standardize and automate spend management processes across the organization. The company expects to increase visibility into spend and supplier performance to optimize costs and operational efficiencies.</p>
  <p>For more information, visit the <a href="/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP on Twitter at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>About SAP</strong></p>
  <p>SAP’s strategy is to help every business run as an intelligent enterprise. As a market leader in enterprise application software, we help companies of all sizes and in all industries run at their best: 77% of the world’s transaction revenue touches an SAP system. Our machine learning, Internet of Things (IoT), and advanced analytics technologies help turn customers’ businesses into intelligent enterprises. SAP helps give people and organizations deep business insight and fosters collaboration that helps them stay ahead of their competition. We simplify technology for companies so they can consume our software the way they want – without disruption. Our end-to-end suite of applications and services enables business and public customers across 25 industries globally to operate profitably, adapt continuously, and make a difference. With a global network of customers, partners, employees, and thought leaders, SAP helps the world run better and improve people’s lives. For more information, visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/">www.sap.com</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Note to editors:</strong><br>To preview and download broadcast-standard stock footage and press photos digitally, please visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/photos">www.sap.com/photos</a>. On this platform, you can find high resolution material for your media channels. To view video stories on diverse topics, visit <a href="http://www.sap-tv.com">www.sap-tv.com</a>. From this site, you can embed videos into your own Web pages, share video via email links, and subscribe to RSS feeds from SAP TV.</p>
  <p><strong>For customers interested in learning more about SAP products:</strong><br>Global Customer Center: +49 180 534-34-24<br>United States Only: 1 (800) 872-1SAP (1-800-872-1727)</p>
  <p><strong>For more information, press only:</strong> Kelly Sheldon Murray, +1 (978) 708-6821, <a href="mailto:kelly.murray@sap.com">kelly.murray@sap.com</a><u>,</u> ET<br>Geraldine Lim, +1 (415) 418-0945, <a href="mailto:geraldine.lim@sap.com">geraldine.lim@sap.com</a>, PT<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>Any statements contained in this document that are not historical facts are forward-looking statements as defined in the U.S. Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995. Words such as “anticipate,” “believe,” “estimate,” “expect,” “forecast,” “intend,” “may,” “plan,” “project,” “predict,” “should” and “will” and similar expressions as they relate to SAP are intended to identify such forward-looking statements. SAP undertakes no obligation to publicly update or revise any forward-looking statements. All forward-looking statements are subject to various risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results to differ materially from expectations. The factors that could affect SAP’s future financial results are discussed more fully in SAP’s filings with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (“SEC”), including SAP’s most recent Annual Report on Form 20-F filed with the SEC. Readers are cautioned not to place undue reliance on these forward-looking statements, which speak only as of their dates.<br>© 2021 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="http://www.sap.com/corporate-en/legal/copyright/index.epx#trademark">http://www.sap.com/corporate-en/legal/copyright/index.epx#trademark</a> for additional trademark information and notices.<br>Please consider our <a href="https://www.sap.com/corporate/en/legal/privacy.html">privacy policy</a>. If you received this press release in your e-mail and you wish to unsubscribe to our mailing list please contact <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a> and write Unsubscribe in the subject line.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-news</category>
            <category>news-tag/digitalization</category>
            <category>news-tag/external-workforce-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-spend</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>product/sap-ariba-buying</category>
            <category>product/sap-ariba-contracts</category>
            <category>topic/spend-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Procurement Becomes a Strategic Business Function at SuKarne]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/sukarne-procurement-strategic-business-function</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/sukarne-procurement-strategic-business-function</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Before adopting SAP Ariba solutions, SuKarne turned its procurement into a strategic business function. Learn how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e6b2f420c8e5c7895b43507194fd74b5e36094b6.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e6b2f420c8e5c7895b43507194fd74b5e36094b6.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1e6b2f420c8e5c7895b43507194fd74b5e36094b6.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Procurement Becomes a Strategic Business Function at SuKarne" src="./media_1e6b2f420c8e5c7895b43507194fd74b5e36094b6.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="procurement-becomes-a-strategic-business-function-at-sukarne">Procurement Becomes a Strategic Business Function at SuKarne</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Discovering opportunities for a business to improve processes and operations does not have to be an exhausting adventure. Sometimes challenges can be seen in broad daylight. That was the case for SuKarne, a <a href="https://www.sukarne.com/">Grupo Viz company based in Mexico</a>, thanks to innovation and technology adoption.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="increase-procurement-visibility-and-control-with-operational-flexibility-repeatable-cost-savings-and-compliant-processes">Increase procurement visibility and control with operational flexibility, repeatable cost savings, and compliant processes</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/e-procurement/procurement.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="world-class-and-northern-roots">World Class and Northern Roots</h2>
  <p>With corporate headquarters in Culiacán, Sinaloa, in northern Mexico, SuKarne is one of the four organizations established by <a href="http://www.grupoviz.mx/">Grupo Viz</a>. What emerged 52 years ago as a family initiative is now the third-largest beef fattener in the world and the fifth-largest beef supplier in North America.</p>
  <p>The company’s success has been sustained by an infrastructure consisting of five comprehensive livestock units, four in Mexican territory and one in Nicaragua; seven processing plants, with an installed capacity of 2 million head of cattle per year; 10 distribution centers across Mexico, the U.S., and Central America and 400 distribution routes; more than 220 livestock purchase and conditioning centers; and more than 300 owned stores. In addition, since its facilities have the necessary international sanitary and industrial certifications, SuKarne is a big exporter — its products are available in six countries on four continents. In fact, it is estimated that SuKarne is responsible for 70% of the meat exports of the Mexican economy.</p>
  <p>SuKarne today has 13,000 direct workers, collaborates with more than 100,000 agricultural and livestock suppliers, and serves more than 80,000 customers, such as supermarket chains, although most are micro-businesses like small butchers and restaurants.</p>
  <p>The numbers speak for themselves: the Mexican economy has a true powerhouse in the global market for animal protein.</p>
  <h2 id="first-steps-goodbye-to-paper-based-billing">First Steps: Goodbye to Paper-Based Billing</h2>
  <p>Before adopting SAP Ariba solutions, SuKarne’s Procurement department would not have surprised anyone from an innovation perspective. In fact, as in many organizations, it was a highly traditional corporate area serving a registry of more than 5,000 suppliers, 2,000 of them active, not including suppliers of livestock and raw materials for livestock feed, which are served by another area of ​​the corporation.</p>
  <p>In these circumstances, recalls SuKarne Chief Procurement Officer Gonzalo Padilla, the work was bureaucratic, prone to human errors, and without real business value. “Between 60 and 70% of the team’s time was spent on managing invoices: reviewing them, ensuring that none had been misplaced, and taking them in-person to a colleague’s desk in the Accounts Payable area. All this, despite the fact that electronic invoicing had been implemented in Mexico for a while,” Padilla shares.</p>
  <p>Common mistakes, derived from human execution, were not unusual in this environment: lost or misplaced invoices, which delayed payments and ignited the anger of suppliers; processes interrupted by the modification of a process or corporate policy, and even by the vacations of a person involved in the process; and long sessions at Accounts Payable desks to review and reconcile issues, which tended to cause friction between departments.</p>
  <p>“The Procurement area concentrated on management tasks that did not add business value; we dedicated ourselves to seeking payments and not seeking negotiations,” says Padilla.</p>
  <p>Aware of its challenges and taking advantage of a reorganization that brought Padilla’s team into the Finance department, the Procurement team set out on an innovation journey with the implementation of the <a href="https://www.ariba.com/solutions/solutions-overview/strategic-sourcing">SAP Ariba Strategic Sourcing</a> solutions, part of SAP’s Intelligent Spend Management concept.</p>
  <p>Initially, thanks to <a href="https://www.ariba.com/solutions/solutions-overview/strategic-sourcing/contract-management-software">SAP Ariba Contracts</a>, the billing processes were digitalized and automated, reducing the administrative and transactional burdens of the team while also reducing human errors and non-essential interactions with the Accounts Receivable area. In this way, the Procurement department was able to focus more on generating value for the business, including conducting strategic negotiations for the company.</p>
  <p>SuKarne’s suppliers were resistant to the new model at first. “They did not see the benefits, perhaps because we were in the initial process of discovering and understanding them, and therefore the process of supplier adoption was slower,” recalls Padilla. “Once the advantages were evident, a communication campaign was implemented that was very important since it showed the benefits: invoices from suppliers would not be parked on a desk and the payments would come out on time.”</p>
  <h2 id="extending-the-power-of-innovation">Extending the Power of Innovation</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="manage-all-categories-of-spend-with-the-markets-leading-cloud-solutions-and-worlds-largest-business-network">Manage all categories of spend with the market's leading cloud solutions and world's largest business network</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/e-procurement.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Billing was not the only area of improvement. SuKarne also began a digital transformation project encompassing the entire organization, which implied defining and rethinking processes, creating operation manuals, documenting transactions in the various areas, and establishing continuous improvement policies, among other tasks that are essential in these types of innovative initiatives.</p>
  <p>Within this framework, Padilla’s team, taking advantage of the end-to-end source-to-pay solutions – SAP Ariba Strategic Sourcing and <a href="https://www.ariba.com/solutions/solutions-overview/procurement/procure-to-pay">SAP Ariba Buying and Invoicing</a> – expanded its digital procurement capabilities. After an internal analysis of the different tasks and goals of the Procurement area, multiple opportunities were detected to boost productivity to new levels:</p>
  <p><strong>Self-purchase catalogs</strong></p>
  <p>Taking advantage of the functions of <a href="https://www.ariba.com/solutions/solutions-overview/procurement/catalog">SAP Ariba Catalog</a>, self-purchase catalogs were created for items in which Padilla’s department uses prenegotiated contracts. At SuKarne, this tool is already being used for purchases of stationery, general services, materials, and some aspects of marketing. Catalogs are very easy to use, implement, and manage so the company has full visibility and control of transactions. Quality remains high since the catalogs include images of the product, price, characteristics, etc. In addition, the company was able to adapt this resource to its branding, so the catalogs today are known as the “Compras SK” portals.</p>
  <p><strong>Contract generation process</strong></p>
  <p>Before the implementation of SAP Ariba Contracts, when a contract was generated, Legal had to go through an internally developed tool, which provided very basic functionality and did not offer any certainty in terms of time. Now, with SAP Ariba Contracts, from the moment a supplier registers in the SuKarne system, the provider can find all the legal and commercial information they need on the platform. In addition to speeding up activity, this allows for timely monitoring of contracts and easy reviews.</p>
  <p><strong>Audits</strong></p>
  <p>Being part of the agri-food industry, SuKarne is constantly audited by authorities, industrial organizations, institutions, and even clients. An important part of these reviews focuses on suppliers — how they are evaluated, what criteria are used to qualify them, what policies and action plans do they have, etc. SuKarne found a solution in the <a href="https://www.ariba.com/solutions/solutions-overview/supplier-management">SAP Ariba Supplier Management</a> portfolio with <a href="https://www.ariba.com/solutions/solutions-overview/supplier-management/supplier-lifecycle-management">SAP Ariba Supplier Lifecycle and Performance</a> and <a href="https://www.ariba.com/solutions/solutions-overview/supplier-management/supplier-risk">SAP Ariba Supplier Risk</a>. In the past, when an audit was submitted, the company had to put in place a plan to address that specific item. Today, the evaluation of suppliers is carried out all the time, through very friendly, digital tools. When an audit is submitted, SuKarne now has real-time information accessible immediately.</p>
  <p>In order to achieve these advances, a decisive factor, according to Padilla, was the support of the SAP team. “Through seminars and constant support, the team not only explained the capabilities of the solutions to us, but also guided us in the task of adapting existing processes to the platform, how to get more out of the innovation we were adopting,” he says.</p>
  <h2 id="challenge-overcome-the-year-of-the-pandemic">Challenge Overcome: The Year of the Pandemic</h2>
  <p>From Culiacán, SuKarne’s Procurement department continues to explore – and discover – the benefits of investing in innovation. With the guided sourcing and guided buying capabilities within the SAP Ariba solution suite, the company hopes to improve other procurement and sourcing processes and increase the efficiency of Procurement interactions with other corporate divisions.</p>
  <p>These future projects will be led by a totally transformed department – a Procurement team with the capacity to provide value to the business in a new and strategic way. The solutions implemented help ensure SuKarne has complete visibility and robust analytical functions via <a href="https://www.ariba.com/solutions/solutions-overview/strategic-sourcing/spend-analysis">SAP Ariba Spend Analysis</a>.</p>
  <p>“The platform allows us to see how the organization’s spending moves; which categories grow the most; which supplier, especially if it is a strategic one, are we ceasing to serve,” comments Padilla. The data obtained is specified in reports, which are sent to SuKarne’s central corporate information system supporting decision-making in the organization.</p>
  <p>In 2020, the year in which the global economy was severely affected by the <a href="/covid-19">pandemic</a>, SuKarne managed to protect its supply chain, which, in turn, safeguarded its business operations.</p>
  <p>“Through the platform, we detected that there were suppliers and categories that were falling. Thanks to the information, we discovered that they were companies facing financial difficulties due to the health crisis, which is why our purchase orders were declining,” Padilla points out. “With regard to strategic suppliers, this allowed us to detect risks to the operation and, in some cases, to think of ways to support them.” And in that sense, another benefit cannot be ignored: technology adoption in an unfavorable economic environment can help to guarantee punctual payments.</p>
  <p>With the support of its Procurement area, 2020 was difficult, but not catastrophic, and SuKarne succeeded in this new context. Beyond operational continuity, the power of technology had a positive impact on suppliers, who could have been most affected by the pandemic.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-spend</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>product/sap-ariba-buying-and-invoicing</category>
            <category>product/sap-ariba-contracts</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>