<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/social-entrepreneurship/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP CSR's eBook Celebrates a Year of Global Impact]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/sap-csr-ebook-celebrates-global-impact</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/sap-csr-ebook-celebrates-global-impact</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The impact of SAP CSR in 2023 is a testament to the power of collective action and shared vision. Read to find out how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1aa60aead41f035043e44cbfe1f53c8c65e859485.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1aa60aead41f035043e44cbfe1f53c8c65e859485.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1aa60aead41f035043e44cbfe1f53c8c65e859485.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP CSR’s eBook Celebrates a Year of Global Impact" src="./media_1aa60aead41f035043e44cbfe1f53c8c65e859485.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-csrs-ebook-celebrates-a-year-of-global-impact">SAP CSR’s eBook Celebrates a Year of Global Impact</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Reflecting on the past year, one event stands out vividly in my memory: the Social Enterprises World Forum (SEWF) in Amsterdam, the Netherlands. For those unfamiliar, imagine a global assembly where more than 1,500 entrepreneurs from 82 countries dedicated to societal and environmental missions come together. These enterprises prioritize people and the planet, reinvesting their profits to advance their respective causes. Witnessing the energy and innovation in Amsterdam was a powerful reminder of why SAP has emphasized social entrepreneurship for the second consecutive year.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>It makes me proud to think about the 676 SAP colleagues who, in 2023, participated in our pro bono consulting programs, offering their expertise to these visionary social entrepreneurs. As in previous years, this collaboration has proven mutually beneficial, with 74% of our employees reporting a positive, lasting impact on their careers. Furthermore, 96% of the supported organizations and 77% of their beneficiaries have seen significant improvements. These numbers speak volumes about the shared value of our engagement.</p>
  <p>But the 2023 SEWF wasn’t just a personal highlight; it marked the beginning of another significant milestone. We announced our investment in the <strong>Social Enterprise People and Planet First Verification</strong> with Good Market and SEWF. This initiative aims to set a global standard for recognizing organizations prioritizing social and environmental impacts. Social enterprises can now also identify themselves on SAP Business Network, the world’s largest B2B commerce platform. This breakthrough can make it easier for these businesses to explore new business-to-business opportunities while also helping SAP customers achieve their goals of being more environmentally and socially responsible. Saying it’s a win-win situation is a bit cliché, but in this case it’s actually true.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-is-powering-equitable-access-to-economic-opportunity-education-and-employment-and-the-circular-economy">SAP is powering equitable access to economic opportunity, education and employment, and the circular economy</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/our-values/csr.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Working with SEWF shows how much we believe in working together and driving towards collective impact. I’ve said it before and I’ll say it again: we can’t do this by ourselves. Working with others is the key to driving the kind of systemic change our world needs. This idea is a big part of what we stand for at SAP, and is at the heart of our corporate social responsibility (<a href="/topics/csr">CSR</a>) strategy.</p>
  <p>This idea of working together really comes to life in our collaboration with <strong>UNICEF and Generation Unlimited</strong>. In 2023 – the fourth year of our partnership – we set out to make a real difference by not just developing the skills of young people but also finding jobs in the SAP ecosystem. Launching the SAP Educate to Employ program is a big step in that direction. Helping 25 young people get jobs with SAP in each of our pilot countries – Nigeria, Kenya, South Africa, and the Philippines – might not sound like a lot, but it’s a huge deal for each of those young people. For them, it’s a gateway to a sustainable livelihood, offering them not just gainful employment but a chance to build a career, achieve financial stability, and make meaningful contributions to their communities and the broader world. It’s about unlocking their potential and enabling them to participate in the digital and green economy. By the end of the year, we saw amazing results. While more than 2,500 had already passed the aptitude test, over 1,000 young people in Africa finished our “Boost Your Career with SAP Skills” course and more than 500 got through the first big part of their training.</p>
  <p>But, what’s a year recap without some high-level numbers? Let’s dive into some impressive <strong>numbers from 2023</strong>. More than 20,000 of our SAP colleagues volunteered over 140,000 hours. Our initiatives reached over 2.8 million young people – almost half girls – and supported over 41,000 teachers. Our partner network reached 1 billion people in over 140 countries. These stats are just the tip of the iceberg, showing our big reach and impact together with our partners.</p>
  <p>Building on this, our signature partnerships with Africa Code Week, Meet and Code, and Latin Code Week have always been at the heart of our achievements. As we handed over these initiatives in 2023, we took a moment to reflect and evaluate Africa Code Week and Latin Code Week outcomes more deeply. For instance, by empowering 14.6 million participants with the education, knowledge, and ICT skills needed to participate in the digital future, <strong>Africa Code Week</strong> has increased the likelihood that beneficiaries will realize higher earnings during their working lives. Common Good Marketplace estimates that Africa Code Week catalyzed up to US$1 billion in social value for program participants between 2015 and 2022 based on future increased income.</p>
  <p>As we close the chapter on 2023 and look ahead, the journey we’ve embarked upon at SAP CSR is a testament to the power of collective action and shared vision. The stories, numbers, and outcomes shared in our eBook reflect our commitment to making a meaningful difference. <a href="https://d.dam.sap.com/a/Gnggenc/SAP%20CSR%20in%20Review%202023.pdf?rc=10">Read the full eBook.</a></p>
  <p>Thank you to everyone who has been a part of this journey. Your passion, dedication, and commitment are what drive us forward.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Alexandra van der Ploeg is global head of Corporate Social Responsibility at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="follow-sap-news-on-linkedin-to-stay-up-to-date">Follow SAP News on LinkedIn to stay up-to-date</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news">Connect with us</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>non-sap-event/africa-code week</category>
            <category>news-tag/csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/generation-unlimited</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/social-entrepreneurship</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fostering Refugee Inclusion: Lessons Learned from Social Entrepreneurs]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/supporting-refugees-sap-csr</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/supporting-refugees-sap-csr</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[When it comes to supporting refugees, social entrepreneurs are among those who can play a vital role in fostering inclusion.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ea9a5a56c75ee44ca639d30f89e1d7b48c0ac813.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ea9a5a56c75ee44ca639d30f89e1d7b48c0ac813.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1ea9a5a56c75ee44ca639d30f89e1d7b48c0ac813.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Fostering Refugee Inclusion: Lessons Learned from Social Entrepreneurs" src="./media_1ea9a5a56c75ee44ca639d30f89e1d7b48c0ac813.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="fostering-refugee-inclusion-lessons-learned-from-social-entrepreneurs">Fostering Refugee Inclusion: Lessons Learned from Social Entrepreneurs</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>SAP recently marked two significant events: World Refugee Day on June 20 and the United Nations (UN) Micro-, Small, and Medium-Sized Enterprise Day on June 27.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>To underscore the vital role of partnerships in creating a global environment where refugees are fully integrated and valued members of society, we hosted a webinar, “Hope, Inclusion, Action: Building Opportunity for Refugees.” (<a href="https://broadcast.sap.com/replay/230628NSQ_sapcsr">Watch a replay here</a>.) Joining me were two remarkable social entrepreneurs, Innocent Tshilombo, co-founder of <a href="https://kakumaventures.com/">Kakuma Ventures</a>, and Mozamel Aman, co-founder and CEO of <a href="https://startsteps.org/en">StartSteps</a> and founder of <a href="https://www.startupistan.org/">Startupistan</a>.</p>
  <p>In 2022, the number of forcibly displaced people for the first time exceeded <a href="https://www.unhcr.org/refugee-statistics/">100 million</a> due to war, violence, and persecution. Unfortunately, this number is expected to rise even further given the current global challenges, such as conflicts, political tensions, and climate change.</p>
  <p>These social entrepreneurs are among many who are playing a role in supporting refugees to integrate into their new environment by finding meaningful work and education opportunities. After an hour with Tshilombo and Aman, I felt privileged to hear their personal narratives and gain valuable insights into navigating challenges with authenticity and vulnerability.</p>
  <p>To provide some context: Tshilombo, an entrepreneur and humanitarian professional, has spearheaded educational, business, and humanitarian initiatives in the Kakuma refugee camp in Kenya. As the co-founder of Kakuma Ventures, a renowned social enterprise, Tshilombo aims to enhance the well-being of refugees and host communities by leveraging digital services and opportunities through energy and internet access for education, trades, and employment. Meanwhile, Aman is deeply passionate about the intersection of technology, entrepreneurship, and social impact. Through his involvement in various startup organizations, Aman has developed a unique perspective on problem-solving. He firmly believes that privilege comes with great responsibility, forming the foundation of sustainable social ventures.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-csr-at-sap">Learn more about CSR at SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/our-values/csr.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="the-transformative-power-of-social-entrepreneurship">The Transformative Power of Social Entrepreneurship</h2>
  <p>Despite operating in challenging environments with limited resources, these founders did not seek traditional employment for stability and security. Instead, they cultivated their own skills and forged ahead, building their social businesses in the face of adversity while remaining driven.</p>
  <p>The Kakuma Camp hosts approximately 200,000 refugees, and Germany, where Aman operates, is home to around <a href="https://www.unhcr.org/refugee-statistics/">2 million refugees</a>. One might assume that scaling their ventures should be a top priority from the get-go. However, both entrepreneurs emphasized the significance of starting small and witnessing the impact created. By demonstrating success, they gradually gained access to additional resources, facilitating further growth.</p>
  <p>This reminded me of a powerful notion: systemic change doesn’t necessarily require focusing on the big picture; it can begin by positively impacting one individual at a time. Through this approach, social enterprises have the opportunity to learn, adapt, and secure the resources needed to expand their efforts over time.</p>
  <h2 id="partnerships-are-crucial-to-overcoming-challenges">Partnerships Are Crucial to Overcoming Challenges</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-more-stories-and-coverage-about-csr-efforts-at-sap">Read more stories and coverage about CSR efforts at SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/topics/sap-csr">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Many corporations have strict criteria and predefined standards that often hinder the inclusion of individuals from diverse backgrounds. However, more companies have started to recognize the potential in these individuals and consider them as potential employees. This realization has led to the development of tailored programs in collaboration with companies. However, there is a challenge in Germany, for example, where many open positions exist. Still, the skills companies require are often too specific or need to be adequately addressed in generic training programs. It is, therefore, essential to work with employers and partners to design and develop programs that meet their specific needs.</p>
  <p>These entrepreneurs have managed to navigate this barrier by forging strategic alliances and fostering a mindset shift among potential hiring partners. By showcasing the skills and potential of their participants, they have successfully broken down these barriers and opened doors to new opportunities.</p>
  <h2 id="sustainability-and-scalability-make-the-world-run-better">Sustainability and Scalability Make the World Run Better</h2>
  <p>Both Tshilombo and Aman’s experiences highlight the importance of sustainability and scalability in social enterprises. While charitable and nonprofit organizations undoubtedly play a crucial role, integrating a business model offers long-term viability. Social enterprises create a continuous cycle of positive impact by generating profits and reinvesting them into sustainable projects. This approach supports self-sufficiency and allows for scalability, replication, and the ability to address specific community needs effectively.</p>
  <p>At SAP, we are dedicated to accelerating social enterprises and take great pride in providing continuous pro bono consulting support to organizations like these. The recent discussion held in commemoration of World Refugee Day and SME Day underscores a powerful message: when we work together, we have the ability to create a transformative ecosystem that empowers purpose-driven enterprises and positively impacts the lives of individuals in need.</p>
  <p>Recognizing the importance of creating economic opportunities and education for refugees and migrants, SAP has established robust partnerships that began several years ago. One notable program is <a href="https://digitalskillsfortoday.org/">Digital Skills for Today</a> in the Middle East, which aims to equip young refugees with the necessary skills to pursue employment opportunities in the IT sector. Additionally, SAP collaborates with the <a href="https://www.uopeople.edu/">University of the People</a>, offering free scholarships to refugees seeking bachelor’s and master’s degrees. The nonprofit tuition-free American accredited online university has an impressive enrollment of more than 120,000 students from 200 countries, including 16,500 refugees.</p>
  <p>If you are a social enterprise in need of our support or an experienced professional who can offer skilled expertise, join us on the <a href="https://movingworlds.org/transform">TRANSFORM Support Hub</a>.</p>
  <p>Together, we can create change and be changed.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Alexandra van der Ploeg is head of <a href="/topics/sap-csr">Corporate Social Responsibility at SAP</a>.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/social-entrepreneurship</category>
            <category>non-sap-event/world-refugee-day</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[What You Didn’t Know You Needed to Know About Entrepreneurship]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/01/what-you-need-to-know-entrepreneurship</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/01/what-you-need-to-know-entrepreneurship</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP's Cindy Fagen spoke with Anastasia Kiku of Reusables about her startup experience and expertise in entrepreneurship. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/entrepreneurship</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-canada</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-labs-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-io</category>
            <category>news-tag/social-entrepreneurship</category>
            <category>news-tag/startups</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[To the Young People Who Move Us Forward]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/international-youth-day-young-people-move-us-forward</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/international-youth-day-young-people-move-us-forward</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[On International Youth Day, SAP thanks the future of business who are shaping the business of future. Learn more about our gratitude.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_105fe4b2ea2df77b44006256013330a86b5c479a0.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_105fe4b2ea2df77b44006256013330a86b5c479a0.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_105fe4b2ea2df77b44006256013330a86b5c479a0.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="To the Young People Who Move Us Forward" src="./media_105fe4b2ea2df77b44006256013330a86b5c479a0.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="to-the-young-people-who-move-us-forward">To the Young People Who Move Us Forward</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>To young people worldwide, on International Youth Day, I offer my gratitude to you on behalf of our 103,000 colleagues at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>To the doers, the dreamers, and those like <a href="https://vimeo.com/446987417">Teevyah</a> and <a href="https://vimeo.com/431802348">Veenadhari</a> who are <a href="https://www.un.org/en/observances/youth-day">transforming food systems</a>, we honor you. To all The Possibilists who dare businesses to do things differently, we hear you. We see you. You are not just the future of business; you are shaping the business of future!</p>
  <p>For every Greta, Malala, or Simone making global headlines, there are thousands of young changemakers like you, <a href="/2021/08/african-refugee-camps-youth-inspire-change">Avina</a>, <a href="/2021/07/possibilists-study-youth-lead-post-pandemic-world">Ryan</a>, and <a href="/2021/08/the-world-within-us-passion-travel-purpose">Anina</a>, who are making a world of difference in communities and countries alike. The successes and struggles documented in <a href="https://thepossibilists.org/">The Possibilists</a>, a recent report by an alliance of 16 of the world’s leading youth social innovation networks, is a reminder to all of us that you can’t be stopped. And if we can unite business, government, and the social sector around your work, we will succeed in accelerating (your) solutions to the world’s most challenging problems.</p>
  <p>While traditional business has much to learn from social innovators, we also have a lot to offer you.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="in-a-post-pandemic-world-youth-take-center-stage-and-lead">In a Post-Pandemic World, Youth Take Center Stage and Lead</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/07/possibilists-study-youth-lead-post-pandemic-world">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="accessing-networks-build-bridges-not-silos">1. Accessing Networks: Build Bridges, Not Silos</h2>
  <p>Many of the solutions the world needs already exist, but gaining access to the right people and organizations to share those solutions with is not as easy. More than 94% of Possibilists shared that they lack the personal or business access needed to move their organization forward. And yet, combined with financial and mental hardships, they forge on with their work because they are intrinsically motivated to do the right thing for the world. So how can corporations create space for leaders like you to bring game changing ideas to the table? It might be easier than you think.</p>
  <p>In 2020, SAP formally launched “Youth To The Table” in partnership with <a href="https://www.wearefamilyfoundation.org/">We Are Family Foundation</a>, giving skilled experts like Riddhima Yadav, a young climate and sustainability finance expert, a seat at c-suite level decision making tables at SAP. Riddhima joined SAP’s External Sustainability Advisory Council this year, joining the ranks of tenured sustainability leaders. Together, the council members provide formal outside-in guidance on SAP’s sustainability journey. Like many of The Possibilists, Riddhima formed her first organization as a teenager. Although still “early” in her career, she is an outstanding representative for both her field of expertise and her generation.</p>
  <p>A program like Youth To The Table should not only exist within one company, and perhaps we can help change that. I challenge you to approach the business leaders and companies operating in your field of interest or expertise. Reach out to their sustainability or corporate social responsibility leaders on social media as a place to start. If that doesn’t work, connect with intermediaries like <a href="https://changemakerxchange.org/">ChangemakerXChange</a> or We Are Family Foundation, which have formal youth-to-corporate programs. This is an opportunity for all of us if we focus more on building bridges, and a little less on our erecting own silos.</p>
  <h2 id="accelerating-business-keep-the-promise">2. Accelerating Business: Keep the Promise</h2>
  <p>Once you know who is (or could be) in your extended network, be sure you know how you can partner with them. During the <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Vx5O0ECmr2g">presentation of The Possibilists results</a>, we heard innovators request support like, “We need help. We’re looking for an expert who can help us do the work.” Rest assured, there is help out there.</p>
  <p>Helping businesses run better is what we do, but SAP is not alone in that work when it comes to supporting the work of social entrepreneurs. Unilever, EY, and Ikea are a few awesome corporations that come to mind. We all have programs that will provide you with skilled business experts or financial support, usually in partnership with social sector organizations like <a href="https://movingworlds.org/organization">MovingWorlds</a>, <a href="https://acumen.org/covid-19-response/">Acumen</a>, <a href="https://www.pyxeraglobal.org/">PYXERA Global</a>, and <a href="https://www.yunussb.com/">Yunus Social Business</a>. We are constantly innovating together through initiatives like the <a href="https://www.weforum.org/covid-alliance-for-social-entrepreneurs">COVID Response Alliance for Social Entrepreneurs</a> to help improve the way we connect you with valuable resources.</p>
  <p>So you’re probably asking yourself, “Why would companies share their resources with you?” It’s a win-win for us, too. As employees connect with topics that matter to them, they also flex their leadership skills, build empathy and cross-cultural understanding, and gain exposure to ‘what’s next’ from leaders like you.</p>
  <p>If you are looking for skilled support, know that you don’t have to go it alone. SAP and MovingWorlds are inviting social innovators ages 18 to 30 to <a href="https://movingworlds.org/partner/sap/acceleration-collective-organizations">join the Acceleration Collective</a>, a new pro bono consulting experience launching in September. Beyond pro bono consulting, the Acceleration Collective includes access to certified business coaching, and bridges access to other SAP partners’ service offerings like <a href="https://acumenacademy.org/">Acumen Academy</a>. Unilever and EY, with the support of the COVID Response Alliance, are also offering resources through their market-leading program <a href="https://www.transform.global/resources/">TRANSFORM</a>.</p>
  <p>Keeping the promise to organizations of all kinds is just another day at the office for many of us. Do your research to see who is willing to help. (Hint: we are!) If you are not sure where to begin, join Social Shifters and SAP at <a href="https://sewfonline.com/events/2021-events/youth-forum/">Social Enterprise World Forum’s Youth Forum on September 27</a>.</p>
  <h2 id="recognizing-your-value-tell-it-like-it-is">3. Recognizing Your Value: Tell It Like It is</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-more-sap4good-stories">Read more SAP4Good stories</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/topics/sap4good">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>It is true that with age comes wisdom, but age is not synonymous with the value you bring forward as a leader. Innovation starts with all of us! Last year, I was working on a speaker series, and I approached a young social entrepreneur to speak at the event on SAP’s behalf. Her response was one you should take note of. “I’d gladly speak to your audience, but preparing and speaking for you comes at an opportunity cost for my organization. Will you compensate me for my time?” I was momentarily speechless. She further explained to me, “The moderator is likely getting paid, along with the caterer and the venue. They are all providing a service to you, and so am I.” This young person was respectfully challenging my originally unpaid request. She was right to do so — and you are too!</p>
  <p>My ask was not one of ill intention, rather ignorance, though it’s still no excuse. Throughout a decade working in marketing for SAP, I often asked business leaders to speak on our company’s behalf. The difference? They were all being paid by their organization for their time. Young innovators can be exploited and showcased on both virtual and physical stages globally, but you can change that.</p>
  <p>If you are being asked for something, know your worth and how to leverage it. Be bold and ask for the support you need in return. It may not always be financial compensation, rather it might be access to people or networks or could also include personal skill-building or revenue generation opportunities for your organization.</p>
  <p>Lastly, I want to revisit a topic I touched on briefly above. The Possibilists shared that many of you sacrifice your mental and financial well-being in the pursuit of a better world. While I’m grateful for your efforts, I’m also here to remind you that you will never be able to successfully deliver on your goals if you don’t also prioritize your own well-being. Breathe, find a coach, join a peer support group, pay yourself: whatever it is, invest in your own well-being. You are worth it!</p>
  <h2 id="so-what">So What?</h2>
  <p>Am I asking you to start your own youth movement within the corporate world? No. Am I trying to do that? Perhaps. Do I expect that every organization has the same support structure as SAP to embrace young leaders like you? Probably not. But I hope I’m giving you the courage to connect, learn, and lead with people and organizations like mine.</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Reach out and connect with those who can help you. I promise there are more of us who want to help!</li>
    <li>Learn from the experts and teach them a few things along the way. We don’t know it all, I assure you.</li>
    <li>Speak up! Keep leading the way doing exactly what you are doing. You are creating the change we all need to see in the world, and I can’t wait to see more of you in board rooms around the world.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>Thank you for all that you do to keep moving us forward. We owe you one.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Jennifer Beason is global program director of Social Entrepreneurship for Corporate Social Responsibility at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/redefining-youth</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
            <category>news-tag/social-entrepreneurship</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>