<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/sap-preferred-success/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Expanded SAP Preferred Success Services Fast-Track the Value of Cloud ERP]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/expanded-sap-preferred-success-services-fast-track-cloud-erp</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/expanded-sap-preferred-success-services-fast-track-cloud-erp</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The SAP Preferred Success service for RISE with SAP, premium can deliver more guidance and insight to help optimize cloud ERP. Find out how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a9061bfb24965c3c00629fea26b76b50e8d33ff1.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a9061bfb24965c3c00629fea26b76b50e8d33ff1.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1a9061bfb24965c3c00629fea26b76b50e8d33ff1.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Expanded SAP Preferred Success Services Fast-Track the Value of Cloud ERP" src="./media_1a9061bfb24965c3c00629fea26b76b50e8d33ff1.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="expanded-sap-preferred-success-services-fast-track-the-value-of-cloud-erp">Expanded SAP Preferred Success Services Fast-Track the Value of Cloud ERP</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Navigating disruption and uncertainty is always daunting, especially in economies and industries that evolve at different speeds. The influences of <a href="/topics/ai">AI</a>, post-globalization trends, regulatory changes, constrained capital, and other factors are impacting every region and industry, albeit at different rates and levels of severity.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>By using any of a variety of <a href="https://www.sap.com/services-support/service-offerings/preferred-success.html">SAP Preferred Success</a> services when implementing and adopting SAP S/4HANA Cloud, customers can strategically and effectively handle each change. Their efforts include 44% improved user experiences, 40% faster incident resolution, 38% better enablement and upskilling, and 38% faster time to value from their technology investments, according to a <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2023/05/18fe9a13-717e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Forrester Consulting analysis</a>.</p>
  <p>And now, with the latest offering for SAP Preferred Success, customers are going beyond navigating turbulence. They can also maximize opportunities, reduce risks, and understand how dynamic economic and market forces impact their long-term success.</p>
  <h2 id="introducing-sap-preferred-success-for-rise-with-sap-premium">Introducing SAP Preferred Success for RISE with SAP, premium</h2>
  <p>The SAP Preferred Success service for RISE with SAP, premium can deliver more guidance and insight to help accelerate and optimize the value of the cloud ERP journey, in addition to the foundational services of SAP Preferred Success.</p>
  <p>With personalized services designed to meet unique business needs proactively, customers can realize benefits, including:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Improved productivity</strong> with access to SAP knowledge and best practices</li>
    <li><strong>Accelerated ROI</strong> with tailored guidance and expert support to organize SAP solutions faster and more efficiently</li>
    <li><strong>Fewer risks</strong> by following best practice recommendations that minimize system disruptions and help ensure smooth operations</li>
    <li><strong>Better alignment</strong> by matching SAP solutions with organization goals, capitalizing on the features and innovations of every release</li>
    <li><strong>Higher efficiency</strong> by consistently fine-tuning and providing personalized recommendations aligned with specific business value drivers</li>
  </ul>
  <p>For customers such as <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/customer-stories/kyocera.html">Kyocera Document Solutions Australia</a> (Kyocera), SAP Preferred Success helps create a solid foundation for modernizing business operations. “Using SAP Preferred Success enabled us to accelerate the business acceptance of change and drive a continuous improvement landscape. It has provided an avenue to reevaluate our processes and create a more efficient business,” states Rohan Higgins, chief financial officer of Kyocera Document Solutions.</p>
  <p>As a result of the quality and caliber of the SAP expertise and active engagement, Kyocera has successfully moved 100% of its ERP processes to the cloud, leading to zero manual touchpoints across its forecasting processes. Other customers have realized additional benefits, such as more efficient business processes, smaller database sizes, infrastructure simplification, and reduction of cost centers.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="a-personalized-proactive-partnership-for-the-lifetime-of-your-cloud-solution">A personalized, proactive partnership for the lifetime of your cloud solution</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/services-support/service-offerings/preferred-success.html">Read more on SAP Preferred Success</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP Preferred Success for RISE with SAP, premium can provide additional elements for modernizing business operations, including:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>A dedicated, named enterprise adoption expert</strong> with a strong technical and functional background, who can provide expertise and help orchestrate how-to conversations supporting the build of outcome-focused plans</li>
    <li><strong>Assistance and guidance based on recommended best practices</strong> to help increase the customer’s understanding of its business processes and how the solution is being used</li>
    <li><strong>Ongoing innovation and transformation</strong> through continuous review of the customer’s calendar and plans – including the adoption of entitlements, such as business AI, sustainability, intelligent technologies exploration, and process management</li>
    <li><strong>Clean core guidance and quality checks</strong> for each project phase to help ensure the customer can leverage existing and future innovations within RISE with SAP</li>
  </ul>
  <p>With a dedicated focus on sustainability exploration, SAP Preferred Success for RISE with SAP, premium helps ensure that businesses can embrace a more sustainable future while driving growth and success in the digital age. By leveraging the comprehensive suite of tools and resources provided by SAP and orchestrated by an enterprise adoption expert, organizations can navigate their sustainability initiatives with confidence and precision.</p>
  <p>SAP Preferred Success for RISE with SAP, premium also offers a unique avenue for harnessing the transformative power of AI with cloud ERP. Through a tailored approach, customers are guided by seasoned enterprise adoption experts facilitating a comprehensive exploration of business AI. Customers are then empowered to innovate, automate, and optimize their business processes using the cutting-edge AI capabilities seamlessly integrated into the SAP ecosystem.</p>
  <p>Access to such a wealth of products, tools, and frameworks gives invaluable insights on configuring and customizing AI solutions to suit unique needs. By leveraging built-in AI capabilities from SAP, customers are not only equipped to streamline operations but also to drive innovation and achieve sustained growth in today’s dynamic business landscape.</p>
  <h2 id="accelerating-competitive-outcomes-from-cloud-erp">Accelerating Competitive Outcomes from Cloud ERP</h2>
  <p>As businesses continue to compete in an ever-evolving landscape, the need for innovative solutions that drive growth and efficiency has never been more critical. And SAP Preferred Success for RISE with SAP, premium is ready to help, offering the functional and technical guidance, personalized services, and ongoing support necessary to realize the full potential of the cloud.</p>
  <p>As demonstrated by success stories worldwide, including that of Kyocera, SAP Preferred Success for RISE with SAP, premium is helping customers not only adapt to change but also seize new opportunities for growth. This service is not just a solution; it’s a strategic partnership that can empower organizations to thrive in an ever-evolving world.</p>
  <p>Ready to amplify the impact of your cloud ERP transformation? <a href="https://sap.com/preferred-success">Visit us online</a> or contact your local SAP representative to learn more about SAP Preferred Success for RISE with SAP, premium.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Mine Ecevit is cloud ERP lead for Cloudified Services Sales and Go to Market at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-preferred-success</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Chemicals Supplier BYK Harmonized Supply Chain Planning Processes]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/byk-harmonized-supply-chain-planning-processes</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/byk-harmonized-supply-chain-planning-processes</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[BYK, a global supplier of specialty chemicals, has implemented a new supply chain demand planning system using SAP solutions. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/chemicals</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>product/sap-integrated-business-planning-for-supply-chain</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-preferred-success</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
            <category>product/sap-supply-chain-control-tower</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Expanded Partnership Turns Transactions into Lasting Connections]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/expanded-sap-preferred-success-sales-services-lasting-connections</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/expanded-sap-preferred-success-sales-services-lasting-connections</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Preferred Success for SAP Sales Cloud and SAP Service Cloud, expanded edition, helps businesses create personalized customer experiences.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-preferred-success</category>
            <category>product/sap-sales-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-service-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Clear Path to Digital Supply Chain Excellence with SAP Preferred Success]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/digital-supply-chain-excellence-with-sap-preferred-success</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/digital-supply-chain-excellence-with-sap-preferred-success</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Preferred Success can be a guiding light for businesses keen on transforming to digital supply chain operations.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-supply-chain</category>
            <category>news-tag/digitalization</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-preferred-success</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How to Boost Your Cloud Adoption]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/how-to-boost-your-cloud-adoption</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/how-to-boost-your-cloud-adoption</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Preferred Success and SAP Learning Hub can provide the training essential for unlocking the full business value of the cloud.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>product/sap-learning-hub</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-preferred-success</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Eastman Energizes HR Reporting to Deliver One-Stop Insights to Leaders]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/eastman-hr-reporting-deliver-insights-to-leaders</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/eastman-hr-reporting-deliver-insights-to-leaders</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Eastman accelerated HR reporting for improved efficiency and insights using story reports in SAP SuccessFactors People Analytics. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>topic/data-analytics</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-preferred-success</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-employee-central</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-people-analytics</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-recruiting</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Preferred Success: Kicking Off a New Era of Business Transformation for 2024 and Beyond]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/sap-preferred-success-new-era-business-transformation-2024-beyond</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/sap-preferred-success-new-era-business-transformation-2024-beyond</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is kicking off new era of business transformation for SAP Preferred Success for 2024 and beyond. Learn more about what's to come.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a1919dd764234934a6eee0f64eeedbf266e76eaf.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a1919dd764234934a6eee0f64eeedbf266e76eaf.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1a1919dd764234934a6eee0f64eeedbf266e76eaf.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Preferred Success: Kicking Off a New Era of Business Transformation for 2024 and Beyond" src="./media_1a1919dd764234934a6eee0f64eeedbf266e76eaf.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-preferred-success-kicking-off-a-new-era-of-business-transformation-for-2024-and-beyond">SAP Preferred Success: Kicking Off a New Era of Business Transformation for 2024 and Beyond</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>The past few years have been marked by a profound shift in the concept of “business transformation.” From recent AI advancements to cloud-centric innovations, the boundaries between adapting to change and shaping conditions that radically impact people’s lives for the better are blurring – driving ongoing growth and prosperity.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Many SAP customers are at the forefront of this new era of business transformation, relying on the guidance and expertise offered through <a href="https://www.sap.com/services-support/service-offerings/preferred-success.html">SAP Preferred Success</a>. They are mapping out new strategies and developing unique solutions that not only scale up their digital capabilities but also accelerate growth in more relevant, responsible, and self-differentiating ways.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-preferred-success-a-personalized-proactive-partnership-for-the-lifetime-of-your-cloud-solution-by-sap">SAP Preferred Success: A personalized, proactive partnership for the lifetime of your cloud solution by SAP</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/services-support/service-offerings/preferred-success.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Here is my overview of some of these game-changing transformation successes.</p>
  <h2 id="supporting-citizens-with-integrated-solutions">Supporting Citizens with Integrated Solutions</h2>
  <p><a href="https://www.sap.com/asset/dynamic/2022/12/101267bd-537e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">The City of Hamburg</a> leveraged the intuitive self-service capabilities of <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform.html">SAP Business Technology Platform</a> to build on its advanced IT infrastructure to support a digitalized aid-application process – from initial requests, validity checks, and objection handling to payment.</p>
  <p>The new aid platform was developed in a hybrid landscape as a side-by-side extension, which enabled a speedy implementation of only three weeks. SAP Preferred Success and SAP Innovation Services offerings were employed for expertise in architecture design and project implementation and management. The city also gained assistance from external partners Dataport and D-Labs to coordinate the back-end integration – running the solution, providing technical support, and building the portal user experience, respectively.</p>
  <p>Backing more than 1 million registered cultural events, the platform has the flexibility and scalability to change with the government authority’s technical footprint as needs evolve. AI-based decision support makes the process manageable for a limited workforce. Furthermore, live reporting gives essential, real-time information, such as requested budget amounts and application status, to state authorities and the federal government.</p>
  <p>On the social side, the real-time distribution of financial aid allows Hamburg’s cultural industry to thrive, enabling events to occur with reduced capacities and elevating confidence in event planning. Overall, the project’s success is serving as a best-practice model for helping people in need in other sectors or situations in the future quickly and reliably.</p>
  <h2 id="expanding-global-reach-through-a-unified-platform">Expanding Global Reach Through a Unified Platform</h2>
  <p><a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2023/07/ee2a3fca-817e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Lenovo Group</a> built a unified end-to-end digital platform to increase global data transparency. This initiative affected five business regions worldwide that involve various people, modules, and business chains. The international technology company applied best-practice guidance and deployment planning methods from customer success experts to create an intelligent innovation culture for the enterprise.</p>
  <p>Through the SAP Preferred Success plan for <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/spend-management.html">SAP Ariba solutions</a>, Lenovo received exclusive and ongoing access to subject-matter specialists, which proved invaluable when resolving technical issues, addressing functionality concerns, and driving user adoption. Moreover, the company has benefited from frequent workshops to review available features and functionality, develop product adoption strategies, and introduce technical enhancements catering to its globalization goals.</p>
  <p>This approach, anchored in a digital mindset, positioned Lenovo on a forward trajectory, enabling it to navigate complex regional compliance and business convergence processes effectively. In return, Lenovo is taking significant steps toward enhancing its operational efficiency and transparency. For example, developing a customized statement system known as the “Progress Cockpit” offers critical business data visibility and traceability, empowering Lenovo to make data-driven decisions more effectively.</p>
  <h2 id="delivering-quality-products-by-amplifying-the-impact-of-cloud-erp">Delivering Quality Products by Amplifying the Impact of Cloud ERP</h2>
  <p><a href="https://www.sap.com/asset/dynamic/2022/12/7623b1c0-577e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Grupo La Moderna</a> has experienced a smooth and rapid implementation of <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/s4hana.html">SAP S/4HANA Cloud, public edition</a> in its Services and Cookies divisions. The deployment helped simplify the food producer’s IT infrastructure and significantly reduced its database size. In addition, best practice-based processes supported by the software enable employees to work faster and more productively, and ready access to expertise allows incidents to be handled quickly and efficiently.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="its-time-for-cloud-native-erp">It’s time for cloud-native ERP</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/s4hana.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>To minimize implementation risk, experts from SAP Preferred Success carried out success checks at each stage of the project, identifying and addressing issues before they become major problems. Doing so provided the confidence that all necessary preparations were in place for a smooth go live.</p>
  <p>According to Hermilo Peña, CIO of Corporativo La Moderna, “With the services, tools, and direct access to experts provided by the teams from SAP Preferred Success and SAP Services and Support, we were able to effectively prepare for the deployment and develop a master plan for our journey with SAP S/4HANA Cloud, public edition.”</p>
  <p>La Moderna continues to receive guidance in unlocking the potential of SAP S/4HANA Cloud, public edition. For each new release, the company received recommendations tailored to its specific requirements that show how the new features can be best adopted and used.</p>
  <h2 id="pouring-personalization-into-digital-channels">Pouring Personalization into Digital Channels</h2>
  <p>With the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm/commerce-cloud.html">SAP Commerce Cloud</a> solution and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm/customer-identity.html">customer data solutions from SAP</a> as the foundation for its e-commerce Web site, <a href="https://www.sap.com/asset/dynamic/2023/07/7619fdf0-807e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Breakthru Beverage</a> now offers a consumer-like shopping experience for B2B customers. The initiative transformed how Breakthru’s sales team connects with and assists its customers, cementing relationships and leading to US$8.4 million in incremental purchases from existing accounts following the launch.</p>
  <p>A complete and personalized success plan from SAP Preferred Success empowered Breakthru to harness the comprehensive functionality of the cloud-based commerce solutions. The company received in-depth recommendations for solution deployments and gained access to a designated customer success partner. Plus, constant communication in the form of technical calls, road map discussions, and continuous delivery of success checks and best-practice sessions helped optimize its solution investment’s value.</p>
  <p>As a result of its transformation, Breakthru has more insights into how and when its customers want to be served. Elsewhere, sales reps have always-on access, supporting real-time selling on the go. Most orders are delivered within 24 hours, while pricing on Breakthru Now is in sync with the pricing sales reps offer. And in terms of efficiency, the company saved 6,000 sales-rep hours following the launch.</p>
  <h2 id="elevating-the-employee-experience-with-the-cloud">Elevating the Employee Experience with the Cloud</h2>
  <p>To strengthen its employee relationships, <a href="https://www.sap.com/asset/dynamic/2023/04/7a53dae4-6c7e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Purolator Inc.</a> transformed its business, HR, and employee experience technology in the cloud. Canada’s largest courier, freight, and logistics company recognized the importance of modernizing its existing on-premise ERP and core HR software. This led to a clear decision to move to <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/s4hana-private-edition.html">SAP S/4HANA Cloud, private edition</a> and the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/employee-central-hris.html">SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central</a> solution.</p>
  <p>Throughout the cloud migration journey, Purolator relied on SAP Preferred Success to gain access to SAP expert resources – from planning to implementation. This partnership assisted in the company’s integration of existing SAP SuccessFactors solutions with the private edition of SAP S/4HANA Cloud, enhancing the employee experience with self-services and supporting core business operations such as finance.</p>
  <p>Doug Patzelt, HCM lead for the future ERP transformation project at Purolator, explains, “There have been numerous cases when we’ve called on SAP Preferred Success services, and they’ve been critical to the project. Our regular meetings with the team keep us on top of new releases and help with issue resolution.”</p>
  <p>After implementing the cloud solutions, Purolator brought together the company’s HR, IT, and finance teams to establish a new software foundation that works as one integrated system across operations in Canada and the U.S. Employees have access to better HR self-service tools, reporting capabilities, and data analytics – all as part of a harmonized experience that requires less dependence on internal IT resources. More impressively, the company has a newfound ability to quickly grant or revoke access when employees are hired or leave the business.</p>
  <h2 id="easing-an-agile-future-ready-transition-to-the-cloud">Easing an Agile, Future-Ready Transition to the Cloud</h2>
  <p><a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2023/09/e4b5fcd3-8e7e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Hitachi High-Tech America Inc.</a> envisioned a reshaping of its operations to form an ideal management model. But instead of improving its current state, the high tech manufacturer invested in <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/s4hana.html">SAP S/4HANA Cloud, public edition</a> to create future-ready business operations with a bold step toward becoming an intelligent enterprise.</p>
  <p>Working with SAP Preferred Success, Hitachi was able to not only successfully implement the solution but also obtain tailored release updates. It also received advice on new features, such as mobile apps for the SAP Extended Warehouse Management application.</p>
  <p>To this day, the services provide on-demand, tailored enablement on functional or product updates and solution-specific learning opportunities, including access to the edition of SAP Learning Hub for SAP Preferred Success. They support the go-live of critical functionality, give advanced notice of deprecated items (such as warehouse management APIs), and offer extensive access to expert resources to address questions and provide crucial knowledge. Plus, Hitachi has a close relationship with an internal SAP advocate who escalates issues, helps resolve critical items, and connects with a development team from SAP to clearly communicate needs.</p>
  <p>“We have been very pleased with the quality and caliber of the team of experts for SAP Preferred Success,” says Randal Miller, general manager of the IT division at Hitachi. “They actively engaged with our needs and took ownership to resolve issues. We greatly appreciate their guidance and continued support as we move forward from our on-premise ERP system mindset toward leveraging the capabilities of SAP S/4HANA Cloud, public edition.”</p>
  <h2 id="raising-the-bar-in-2024-and-beyond">Raising the Bar in 2024 and Beyond</h2>
  <p>Reflecting on these initiatives and many more achieved by organizations using cloud solutions from SAP in partnership with SAP Preferred Success, it is no wonder transformations now go beyond incremental improvements and the adoption of breakthrough technologies. They have the required guidance to prioritize their growth and operational efficiency while improving resiliency, embracing integration, driving personalization, and eliminating technology debt.</p>
  <p>Looking ahead to 2024 and beyond, we anticipate that our customers will have the choice to gain additional advantages from the expanded edition of SAP Preferred Success, such as:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Prescriptive solution reviews that aid more-effective decision-making</li>
    <li>Feature adoption assistance for building and operating resilient solutions</li>
    <li>Extended expert access and enhanced services to maximize the use of cloud investments</li>
  </ul>
  <p>With such a strategic, expertise-led, and cloud-centric approach, our customers will continue to be well-prepared to explore new business opportunities and tackle any challenges that come their way.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Andreia Bessa is global program lead for SAP Preferred Success at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="looking-to-fast-track-and-extend-the-value-of-your-business-transformation-efforts-sap-preferred-success-can-help">Looking to fast-track and extend the value of your business transformation efforts? SAP Preferred Success can help.</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/services-support/service-offerings/preferred-success.html">Learn how</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-preferred-success</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How an Expanded Partnership Amplifies the Value of SAP Business Technology Platform]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/sap-preferred-success-amplifies-value-of-sap-btp</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/sap-preferred-success-amplifies-value-of-sap-btp</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Preferred Success for SAP BTP, expanded edition helps businesses achieve agility and resilience through hands-on guidance. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-preferred-success</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The NHL Continues Evolving with Fast-Paced Innovation and Skillful Teamwork]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/nhl-continues-evolving-sap-preferred-success</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/nhl-continues-evolving-sap-preferred-success</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[By working with SAP Preferred Success, the NHL has a smooth rollout and adoption experience across its club coaching staff. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/database-and-data-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/nhl</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-analytics</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-hana-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-preferred-success</category>
            <category>industry/sports-entertainment</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Preferred Success: Driving Lasting Value from SAP S/4HANA Cloud, Private Edition]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/sap-preferred-success-sap-s-4hana-cloud-private-edition</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/sap-preferred-success-sap-s-4hana-cloud-private-edition</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Preferred Success helps deliver the foundation and ongoing operations needed to optimize SAP S/4HANA Cloud, private edition. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-preferred-success</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Changing the World of Work for Good with Expanded Partnership]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/changing-world-of-work-sap-preferred-success-expanded-edition</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/changing-world-of-work-sap-preferred-success-expanded-edition</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Unleash the full potential of you HR investment and shape the future of work with SAP Preferred Success for HXM solutions, expanded edition.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_197a4d2385b4320de35038be252b5c395708fb3dd.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_197a4d2385b4320de35038be252b5c395708fb3dd.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_197a4d2385b4320de35038be252b5c395708fb3dd.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Changing the World of Work for Good with Expanded Partnership" src="./media_197a4d2385b4320de35038be252b5c395708fb3dd.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="changing-the-world-of-work-for-good-with-expanded-partnership">Changing the World of Work for Good with Expanded Partnership</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>The natural order of work is drastically changing as new realities disrupt and suspend workplace traditions, models, and assumptions. For example, jobs are no longer exclusively tied to neatly defined processes or a single business function. Even decision-making is more democratized, regardless of role and experience, as work continues to occur primarily outside the four walls of the workplace.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>According to a <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2022/12/3020508e-527e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.rc.html">report</a> from The Josh Bersin Company, today’s dynamic workplace environments require a <a href="/topics/human-resources">human capital management</a> (HCM) system that is “ready to use, productive from day one, welcoming to change, and easily adapted to.” The diversity and comprehensiveness of features incorporated into cloud-based <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/hxm-suite.html">human experience management (HXM) solutions from SAP</a> fall into this category, setting the foundation for building impactful, next-generation HCM and HXM solutions.</p>
  <p>Now, you can get the specialized resources and enhanced services necessary to unleash the full potential of your HXM solution investment. Using the SAP Preferred Success service for HXM solutions from SAP, expanded edition, you can optimize the value of SAP SuccessFactors solutions by benefiting from a closer partnership for workplace transformation.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="the-future-of-work-beyond-flex-work">The Future of Work Beyond Flex Work</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2023/07/future-of-work-beyond-flex-work">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="a-close-partnership-for-workplace-transformation">A Close Partnership for Workplace Transformation</h2>
  <p>From planning to go-live and active operation of an SAP SuccessFactors solution, your business can realize significant value from SAP Preferred Success for HXM solutions from SAP, expanded edition. The edition can not only protect your workforce and organizational data and HR applications but can also set the foundation for a long-term partnership that drives continuous knowledge transfer, technical upskilling, and increased awareness of relevant software updates.</p>
  <p>Building on the existing SAP Preferred Success service for HXM solutions from SAP, the edition helps accelerate business transformation success. It can provide extended access to subject-matter experts in cloud adoption, a set of prescriptive reviews of business needs and applications that support daily operations, and assistance with feature adoption. More importantly, you can develop and operate resilient solutions, maximize the value of your cloud investment, and make effective decisions that support business goals.</p>
  <p>Let’s start with <strong>extended access to functional technical resources</strong>. Your HR organization and stakeholders can engage with experts offering the technical and functional guidance you need to understand existing business processes, assess and maximize product usage, and accelerate outcomes. Throughout this service engagement, you can closely collaborate and align future updates, landscape changes, and service delivery and follow-up with a technical and functional resource. The expert can also help orchestrate how-to conversations, review your calendar and plans, and document your landscape.</p>
  <p>Then, with <strong>proactive monitoring</strong>, you can work with an SAP technical resource to oversee the five most critical managed jobs for your business. You and an SAP delivery specialist can create a standard operating procedure for each job, which is used to determine what needs to be done and which actions should be taken if a failure arises.</p>
  <p>Next, an annual <strong>solution stabilization review</strong> of all live modules of your HXM solution investment is conducted. This experience allows you to schedule services required to be completed for each live module and validates usage compared to best practices to identify gaps or improvement opportunities. Moreover, you can gain recommendations for continuous improvement activities and increased adoption over time.</p>
  <p>And last but not least, <strong>new feature activation</strong> is available to help plan, discover, explore, test, enable, and measure the impact of new functionality. Subject-matter experts can kick off the activation process by mapping your success plan as part of an inclusion list and recommending features that best meet your needs. Then, with the help of an SAP delivery specialist, you can activate your chosen feature in a nonproductive landscape, define a testing strategy that contains a base-level unit evaluation, and start testing in a productive environment. During regular touch points, you and your customer success partner can review the usage of the feature and its impact on your business success plan.</p>
  <h2 id="driving-continuous-value-in-the-workplace">Driving Continuous Value in the Workplace</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="fast-track-the-value-of-your-cloud-investment-with-sap-preferred-success">Fast track the value of your cloud investment with SAP Preferred Success</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/services-support/service-offerings/preferred-success.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The ever-evolving and continuously improving nature of the cloud is shaping a future where employees of all roles and seniorities are consistently engaged, empowered, and motivated. And with the prescriptive guidance and personalized assistance of SAP Preferred Success for HXM solutions from SAP, expanded edition, you can bring that vision to life with less risk, greater flexibility, and better transparency.</p>
  <p>Ready to amplify the impact of your work experience? <a href="https://sap.com/preferred-success">Visit us online</a> or contact your local SAP representative to learn more about SAP Preferred Success for HXM solutions from SAP, expanded edition.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Sébastien Brun is global director of Customer Success at SAP.</em><br><em>Marcel Bitter is global director of Customer Success at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-preferred-success</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reimagining the Always-On Marketplace Calls for Expanded Partnership]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/sap-preferred-success-sap-commerce-cloud-always-on-marketplace</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/sap-preferred-success-sap-commerce-cloud-always-on-marketplace</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The expanded edition of SAP Preferred Success for SAP Commerce Cloud allows customers to create an agile, composable commerce system.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>product/sap-commerce-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-preferred-success</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Preferred Success: Where the Benefits of Cloud Adoption Outweigh the Costs]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/sap-preferred-success-benefits-cloud-adoption-outweigh-costs</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/sap-preferred-success-benefits-cloud-adoption-outweigh-costs</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A Forrester study show that SAP Preferred Success allows customers to gain an advantage from their cloud investment. Read to find out how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/forrester</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-preferred-success</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Procurement’s Impact Rises with the Expanded Edition of SAP Preferred Success]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/procurement-sap-preferred-success-expanded-edition</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/procurement-sap-preferred-success-expanded-edition</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Preferred Success for SAP Ariba solutions, expanded edition, empowers procurement leaders to rethink the status quo. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/cloud-success-services</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-preferred-success</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Reimagined Services and Support Portfolio and a New Era of Value Creation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/04/reimagined-services-and-support-portfolio</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/04/reimagined-services-and-support-portfolio</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is reimagining, simplifying, and sharpening its services and support portfolio by pivoting to focus heavily on adoption and consumption.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/cloud-success-services</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-journeys</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-enterprise-support</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-maxattention</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-preferred-success</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Reimagines Services and Support Portfolio for Success in the Cloud]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/04/simplified-services-and-support-portfolio-for-the-cloud</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/04/simplified-services-and-support-portfolio-for-the-cloud</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP's new simplified services and support portfolio is built for the cloud and designed to help customers achieve lasting success.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-journeys</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-enterprise-support</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-maxattention</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-preferred-success</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Innovation Challenge: How to Make the Extraordinary Happen]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/innovation-challenge-make-extraordinary-happen</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/innovation-challenge-make-extraordinary-happen</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Innovation is immensely powerful when driving transformative change. SAP Innovation Awards celebrate those that've taken this lesson to heart.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_178431ff0f2c3efa5a2c191ea2f1455f4a21ff21a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_178431ff0f2c3efa5a2c191ea2f1455f4a21ff21a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_178431ff0f2c3efa5a2c191ea2f1455f4a21ff21a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="The Innovation Challenge: How to Make the Extraordinary Happen" src="./media_178431ff0f2c3efa5a2c191ea2f1455f4a21ff21a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="the-innovation-challenge-how-to-make-the-extraordinary-happen">The Innovation Challenge: How to Make the Extraordinary Happen</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>One of the most important lessons of the last two years has been the power of innovation when driving genuinely transformative change. With SAP Innovation Awards, we celebrate individuals and organizations that have taken this lesson to heart with a mix of ingenuity, SAP technology, and the support of knowledgeable experts.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Innovations are always top of mind for companies – especially SAP customers. But you won’t find them musing future-minded technology trends such as quantum computing, neural interfaces, or nanotechnology. Instead, they are accomplishing extraordinary feats and delivering meaningful outcomes with existing technology and expertise.</p>
  <p>Certainly, every business has a story of exceptional innovation to tell. And I am proud to share those of our customers – some of which were recognized by <a href="https://www.sap.com/idea-place/sap-innovation-awards.html">SAP Innovation Awards</a> in 2021 for making the world better with assistance from SAP Services and Support offerings.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-sap-innovation-awards">Learn more about SAP Innovation Awards</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/idea-place/sap-innovation-awards.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="enhancing-scale-and-performance-for-heavy-data-workloads">Enhancing Scale and Performance for Heavy Data Workloads</h2>
  <p>When under pressure to meet regulatory requirements, deliver higher margins, and improve customer experiences, companies must improve how they manage increasing volumes of data. But all too often, the limitation of an on-premise landscape does not allow the flexibility, agility, speed, and cost-effectiveness to meet that challenge.</p>
  <p>For one of the SAP Innovation Award winners, the answer was found in a proof of concept created through a joint effort between SAP and Google Cloud. <a href="https://www.sap.com/idea-place/sap-innovation-awards/submission-details-2021.html?idea_id=2376">PayPal Holdings</a> (PayPal), which adopted Google Cloud as its core IT partner, chose a combination of Google Cloud and SAP S/4HANA for financial products subledger on a 96 TB scale-out configuration of SAP HANA. The innovation leveraged Google Cloud’s expertise in building scalable, distributed systems and SAP’s relentless focus on delivering mission-critical business process automation.</p>
  <p>Bringing the best of SAP and Google Cloud engineering together, PayPal can benefit from groundbreaking capabilities with higher performance, lower costs, and more flexibility. The technology platform company now runs one of the world’s largest scale-out clusters of SAP HANA. And in return, it accelerated query runtime by 40 times through parallelization, reduced its memory footprint by 78% with dynamic data-tiering techniques, and experienced 24 weeks of continuous operations with zero downtime.</p>
  <h2 id="achieving-health-goals-through-process-standardization">Achieving Health Goals Through Process Standardization</h2>
  <p>During <a href="/covid-19">the COVID-19 pandemic</a>, businesses were concerned with maintaining operational continuity and keeping pace with demand while ensuring a safe and healthy environment for their workforce. However, as one of our award finalists discovered, a complex IT infrastructure involving multiple disparate enterprise resource planning (ERP) systems prevented the ability to run as quickly as possible.</p>
  <p>The European division of <a href="https://www.sap.com/idea-place/sap-innovation-awards/submission-details-2021.html?idea_id=2471">American Air Filter Company</a> addressed this issue by deploying cloud-based solutions to standardize processes and support localization requirements for different countries. With <a href="https://www.sap.com/services/support-plans/preferred-success-cloud.html">SAP Preferred Success</a>, <a href="https://www.sap.com/services/implementation/implementation-pkg.html">SAP Value Assurance</a>, and SAP development experts, the division consolidated 13 ERP systems into a single instance of SAP S/4HANA Cloud and gained the agility to achieve meaningful change.</p>
  <p>American Air Filter Company harmonized processes and gained a single view of the truth, providing more transparent and streamlined operations across all business areas. Additionally, its simplified IT infrastructure costs less to maintain and enables the business to take advantage of intelligent technologies to innovate new offerings.</p>
  <h2 id="setting-new-standards-with-embedded-analytics">Setting New Standards with Embedded Analytics</h2>
  <p>Every organization reaches a point where homegrown, mainframe-based business information systems must be replaced to enhance decision-making and enable higher standards for data governance, quality, and security. But the first step is not necessarily ripping out the legacy technology and implementing a completely new architecture, which in most cases can become too operationally disruptive and costly.</p>
  <p>For 2021 finalist <a href="https://www.sap.com/idea-place/sap-innovation-awards/submission-details-2021.html?idea_id=2036">Pennsylvania State University</a> (Penn State), expert guidance from SAP Enterprise Support services was needed to help upskill its IT team and pave the way for cutting-edge embedded analytics. The university worked with <a href="https://support.sap.com/en/offerings-programs/enterprise-support/enterprise-support-advisory-council.html">SAP Enterprise Support Advisory Council</a> to build a strong foundation in analytics, including through remote, recorded individual and group webinars, to support its digital transformation journey.</p>
  <p>Penn State relied on the <a href="https://support.sap.com/en/offerings-programs/enterprise-support/enterprise-support-academy/value-maps.html">SAP Enterprise Support value maps</a> for SAP Analytics solutions to help close any digital skills gaps. The organization engaged with experts, posting questions in value map forums and arranging collaborative sessions with peers. Plus, it used the <a href="https://cal.sap.com/">SAP Cloud Appliance Library</a> tool to help demonstrate and trial innovative data analytics and reporting tools, conduct scoping and sandboxing exercises, and create a proof of concept.</p>
  <p>Relating training material to workflows and real project scenarios enabled Penn State’s employees to apply knowledge more readily and apply feedback as they adopted SAP S/4HANA embedded analytics. And with access to experts who truly understand its challenges, Penn State’s administration staff now has the necessary skills to adapt and run embedded analytics, which will influence how it runs the university.</p>
  <h2 id="transforming-for-agility-speed-and-success">Transforming for Agility, Speed, and Success</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="discover-how-sap-can-help-enable-your-outcome-driven-business-imperatives">Discover how SAP can help enable your outcome-driven business imperatives</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/services/premium-engagement.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>During any significant organizational change such as a merger, acquisition, or spin-off, most companies find that their legacy landscape is too complex, lacking in technical depth, redundant, or costly to maintain. Another finalist, <a href="https://www.sap.com/idea-place/sap-innovation-awards/submission-details-2021.html?idea_id=2145">Hewlett Packard Enterprise</a> (HPE), is no stranger to this challenge.</p>
  <p>When HPE’s parent company, the Hewlett-Packard Company, spun off in 2015, the business needed to simplify applications and processes enterprise-wide to fulfill the world’s growing need for cloud services and intelligent technology. HPE implemented a wide variety of solutions and services to create a solid foundation for the business and enhance IT with powerful next-generation technologies. The <a href="https://www.sap.com/services/premium-engagement/maxattention.html?sort=latest_desc">SAP MaxAttention</a> program provided the guidance necessary to help validate, plan, execute, and test the design of its infrastructure.</p>
  <p>As a result of its efforts with SAP, HPE reduced recommitments to orders after removing the legacy processes that had resulted in rescheduled jobs. The company improved on-time delivery by focusing on its partners and helping them improve their shipping performance. Today, 99.5% of HPE’s customer orders are delivered on time, up from 90% in the past.</p>
  <h2 id="trailblazing-the-future-with-innovation">Trailblazing the Future with Innovation</h2>
  <p>All these stories are exceptional examples of how SAP customers are shaping their innovation effort to trailblaze a future of ongoing productivity and growth. And I am proud that my experts, who support SAP Services and Support offerings, are playing a key role in our customers’ success.</p>
  <p>Throughout the year, I hear our customers express their gratitude to my team of experts for helping them realize their potential as intelligent enterprises. Recently, I read a quote from SAP Innovation Award finalist <a href="https://www.sap.com/idea-place/sap-innovation-awards/submission-details-2021.html?idea_id=2118">Delivery Hero</a> that I think best sums up the best of what we offer.</p>
  <p>“Thanks to guidance from SAP Services and Support and the Intelligent Enterprise Institute, we better understand the dependency of customer experience on our delivery processes,” said Sebastian McClintock, global director of Customer Experience at Delivery Hero. “Leveraging SAP S/4HANA, Experience Management solutions from SAP and Qualtrics, and machine learning models, we now know how to improve data flows and best use our data to meet customers’ needs.”</p>
  <h2 id="do-you-have-a-story-to-tell">Do You Have a Story to Tell?</h2>
  <p>Such change is hard work, and extraordinary results deserve to be told. That’s why we host SAP Innovation Awards every year. It allows us to celebrate organizations that are improving business processes, providing faster and more effective customer service, making a difference for current and future employees, and more.</p>
  <p>And we invite all of you – especially if you selected services and support from SAP as your partner or co-partner – to submit a nomination. The call for nominations to <a href="https://www.sap.com/idea-place/sap-innovation-awards.html">SAP Innovation Awards 2022</a> is open now, but only for a few more months. Share your story with us!</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Oliver Huschke is vice president and global head of Marketing and Communications for Services and Support at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-enterprise-support</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-hana</category>
            <category>sap-award/sap-innovation-awards</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-maxattention</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-preferred-success</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Digital Transformation: The Importance of New Technology and the Human Factor]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/digital-transformation-importance-of-technology-and-the-human-factor</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/digital-transformation-importance-of-technology-and-the-human-factor</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Services and Support can give the necessary digital transformation guidance to gain the full potential of SAP BTP. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f9c6f0bfcccf6e95cda70514e753925ce62dba7d.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f9c6f0bfcccf6e95cda70514e753925ce62dba7d.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1f9c6f0bfcccf6e95cda70514e753925ce62dba7d.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Digital Transformation: The Importance of New Technology and the Human Factor" src="./media_1f9c6f0bfcccf6e95cda70514e753925ce62dba7d.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="digital-transformation-the-importance-of-new-technology-and-the-human-factor">Digital Transformation: The Importance of New Technology and the Human Factor</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>From the simplest to the most complex projects, SAP Business Technology Platform is a critical piece of the larger digital transformation puzzle – empowering organizations to deliver human experiences that are integrated, data-driven, and extensible.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The more sophisticated technology becomes, the greater the struggle to adopt new business models and establish internal policies and processes to support them. Yet, the barrier is not the technology – it’s how people experience those models.</p>
  <p>One of the ways you can focus on the human factor of digital transformation is by implementing <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">SAP Business Technology Platform</a> (SAP BTP). The platform features a comprehensive selection of solutions and functionalities that are cloud native or can be used for on-premise or hybrid environments and architectures. It includes database and data management solutions, analytics advancements, application development and integration capabilities, and intelligent technologies.</p>
  <p>By integrating your choice of functionalities across SAP solutions and processes on a single platform, you can obtain the critical insights and tools you need to amplify the value of those investments. But many organizations are gaining even more value when leveraging SAP Services and Support offerings that emphasize enablement, integration, optimization, and operational change.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="gain-the-full-potential-of-sap-btp-with-sap-services-and-support">Gain the full potential of SAP BTP with SAP Services and Support</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://youtu.be/6wFzZpf7pwY">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="connecting-digital-change-to-the-human-experience">Connecting Digital Change to the Human Experience</h2>
  <p>It seems that SAP customers know a secret to meaningful change that most businesses do not. According to a newly released <a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/dg/btp-technology-services-study/index.html">IDC Vendor Spotlight</a>, “The Benefits of Services and Support for Complex Technology Adoption,” surveyed CIOs and business managers indicated that they are too focused on their processes and organizational structure to take full advantage of new technology solutions and platforms. As a result, they cannot quantify business value adequately, nor scale and innovate with the IT architecture effectively.</p>
  <p>Many organizations worldwide are using SAP BTP to help address operational- and talent-related challenges in digital transformation initiatives. You can innovate a wide variety of new business scenarios and strengthen existing ones with technology providers and partners that provide ongoing services and support with a portfolio of integrated applications and services.</p>
  <p>But with the help of SAP Services and Support, you can safeguard a key part of your future success – how your customers and employees experience change. Every day, our service experts and I see how an outside perspective from vendor-driven services can help an organization gain the full value of increasingly complex technology. Such support brings much more than deep, industry-specific expertise and proprietary solutions and methodologies. It’s a much-needed answer to addressing unique people-related challenges quickly and effectively when they occur.</p>
  <p>For example, the <a href="https://www.sap.com/services/premium-engagement.html">premium engagements services</a> from SAP, with tailored business scenarios enabled by SAP BTP, offer detailed road maps for specific business objectives. The <a href="https://www.sap.com/services/support-plans/preferred-success-cloud.html">SAP Preferred Success</a> offering provides recommendations for optimizing cloud solutions from SAP. Our step-by-step, quick-start <a href="https://www.sap.com/services/advisory-development/business-transformation.html">SAP Advisory Services</a> help ensure technical and functional cloud readiness to adopt new industry and business scenarios and accelerate deployment and delivery. Meanwhile, our <a href="https://www.sap.com/services/advisory-development/education-consulting.html">training and adoption options</a> provide the continuous learning, hands-on practice, and skill validation you need to use the platform confidently.</p>
  <p>Combining SAP BTP and SAP Services and Support helps unlock human-centered solution design that empathizes with real-world challenges of customers and employees. This collaboration allows you to identify significant use cases, create relevant and engaging user experiences, and develop value-added services. In fact, one of our customers – <a href="/2021/09/kakao-work-b2b-domain-sap-btp">Kakao Enterprise</a> – verified 68 cross-industry use cases to expand its consumer-grade mobile app’s functionality to improve user flow and overall performance quality for a business-to-business market.</p>
  <h2 id="building-up-transformations-that-last">Building Up Transformations That Last</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="download-the-idc-infographic">Download the IDC infographic</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/11/b4e04e3b-037e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Without question, your organization has profound opportunities to advance your digital transformation, especially when leveraging our technologies and the expertise of our global ecosystem of partners. But that does not mean that the internal challenges encountered along the way are becoming any less critical to resolve.</p>
  <p>SAP BTP and SAP Services and Support provide the tools and expertise that help you and your partners overcome technical and nontechnical barriers that get in the way of realizing a future as an intelligent enterprise. And as you continue to refine, innovate, and expand business scenarios and digital capabilities, we help you, as our customer, become well-positioned to deliver ongoing value to your business and the people that support you.</p>
  <p>Find out how vendor-provided services and support can help your business manage a complicated digital transformation more effectively, with minimal disruption and long-term success. Read the IDC Vendor Spotlight, sponsored by SAP, “<a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/dg/btp-technology-services-study/index.html">The Benefits of Services and Support for Complex Technology Adoption</a>.”</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Augusta Spinelli is interim services president and head of Services Intelligent Delivery Group at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-advisory-services</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-preferred-success</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Surrounded by Change, Businesses Transform on Their Terms with SAP Preferred Success]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/businesses-transform-on-their-terms-sap-preferred-success</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/businesses-transform-on-their-terms-sap-preferred-success</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Businesses can use the guidance of SAP Preferred Success to optimize the value of their efforts in a private cloud – on their terms.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c20156fbee80bc911a01ba8070589a7af2a244ce.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c20156fbee80bc911a01ba8070589a7af2a244ce.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1c20156fbee80bc911a01ba8070589a7af2a244ce.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Surrounded by Change, Businesses Transform on Their Terms with SAP Preferred Success" src="./media_1c20156fbee80bc911a01ba8070589a7af2a244ce.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="surrounded-by-change-businesses-transform-on-their-terms-with-sap-preferred-success">Surrounded by Change, Businesses Transform on Their Terms with SAP Preferred Success</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>People are well aware of the power of technology to drive meaningful change. They feel it in their gut that digital leadership is critical, even to the point where their IT and business strategies are one and the same. This understanding is evident whenever business leaders say they want to use data and analytics more strategically.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>But that digital urgency is only a small part of the larger business transformation equation. Businesses must also objectively identify risks and see where potential disruption is beginning to emerge. Their future stability – let alone success – depends on this ability to guide highly strategic decisions every day.</p>
  <p>That’s why SAP customers rely on the <a href="https://www.sap.com/preferred-success">SAP Preferred Success</a> offering to help actively disrupt their sectors. They are the ones connecting processes across systems and ecosystems to improve their customer experience and streamline operations. And now that can go even further by being able to invent new approaches continuously and implement them rapidly with the latest enterprise resource planning (ERP) technology in a private cloud environment, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/s4hana-erp/technical-information/private-cloud.html">SAP S/4HANA Cloud, private edition</a>.</p>
  <h2 id="know-the-right-way-to-evolve-at-the-right-speed">Know the Right Way to Evolve at the Right Speed</h2>
  <p>When moving from an on-premise, legacy ERP system to intelligent ERP software in the cloud, business leaders usually consider a public cloud environment managed by a third-party provider and shared with multiple organizations. The functionality of modern ERP software is highly standardized and can be upgraded frequently with new capabilities as the business demands, with little or no effort from the company’s IT team.</p>
  <p>While the use of a public cloud is widely popular, some businesses prefer the flexibility of a private cloud to be more hands-on with their deployment of SAP S/4HANA Cloud. In this case, they may already have a digital landscape with a global reach, multiple integrations, custom processes, and unique data. And leveraging cloud-based services that are hosted within their own private servers offers the control desired to transform on their terms and at their pace.</p>
  <p>Available through <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/rise.html">RISE with SAP</a>, SAP S/4HANA Cloud, private edition can deliver on that promise with SAP Preferred Success. Our experts can bring together the technologies, services, and support that our customers need to transform their business in a way that works best for them – regardless of their digital maturity and ultimate vision. In return, our customers can drive continuous innovation through predictable upgrade cycles that can deliver measurable value, a clear view of current and future solution capabilities and innovations, and rapid adoption of new business models.</p>
  <p>While the involvement of SAP Preferred Success can be a crucial factor in the successful deployment of SAP S/4HANA Cloud, private edition, the offering can also provide an economic boost to a company’s bottom line. A <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/07/aed54c54-ee7d-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Total Economic Impact™ study</a> conducted by Forrester Consulting and commissioned by SAP, reported that a composite SAP customer realized 380% ROI over three years, 17% shorter implementation time, 30% higher efficiency, and 40% faster incident resolution.</p>
  <h2 id="keep-a-strong-focus-on-continuous-value">Keep a Strong Focus on Continuous Value</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-resources-you-need-to-be-successful-in-the-cloud">Get the resources you need to be successful in the cloud</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/preferred-success">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The insight-driven, prescriptive recommendations generated by SAP Preferred Success can empower companies to actively understand how they can best benefit from SAP S/4HANA Cloud, private edition, answering key questions such as:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Why choose a cloud ERP subscription over an on-premise, legacy ERP?</li>
    <li>Which functionalities provide the capabilities the business needs right now?</li>
    <li>Will planned future capabilities address future demand, regulations, and growth?</li>
    <li>How should the business consume and optimize the cloud solution to position itself for future success?</li>
  </ul>
  <p>This line of questioning is facilitated through a series of interactions and guidance that include:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Success checks:</strong> Maintain peace of mind throughout the deployment and adoption experience by mapping a success plan and adapting it to achieve a desirable ROI with best practices.</li>
    <li><strong>Targeted training programs:</strong> Empower key users and administrators with knowledge on relevant topics and best practices.</li>
    <li><strong>In-depth release guidance:</strong> Plan for relevant feature adoption to reach desired business outcomes and tailor release timing and processes based on expected business outcomes.</li>
    <li><strong>Designated expertise:</strong> Drive the cloud strategy and derive superb value from our cloud solutions with the assistance of SAP experts.</li>
    <li><strong>Advanced support and enhanced service levels:</strong> Receive faster initial incident response times and resolution targets for non-defect issues.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>From initial setup to continuous innovation and operational excellence, the services provided through SAP Preferred Success are designed to help optimize the value of each stage of the overall business transformation journey.</p>
  <p>Our customers can create an upskilled, knowledgeable team with continuous learning and resources, streamline comprehensive solutions to leverage best practices and capabilities, and provide positive user experiences that gain the confidence of employees and stakeholders. Plus, they can become a disruptive market leader with faster adoption of the latest innovations.</p>
  <h2 id="accelerate-winning-outcomes-with-insight-driven-services">Accelerate Winning Outcomes with Insight-Driven Services</h2>
  <p>Businesses are surrounded by transformation drivers – from economic and environmental changes to technology disruption, rising competition, and new market behaviors. However, that doesn’t mean that digital investments must be inspired by a desire to appear cutting-edge. Instead, businesses should think about harnessing innovation and disruption to transform themselves and remain relevant to customers.</p>
  <p>That’s the beauty of SAP Preferred Success when implementing SAP S/4HANA Cloud, private edition. Businesses can redefine their digital transformation proactively with a 360-degree view of the technology landscape, processes, customer demand, and future needs. But more importantly, all of this can be accomplished with an unwavering eye on broader challenges that impact their operations and how their people use advanced data and analytics to address them.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="subscribe-to-the-innovation-and-transformation-newsletter">Subscribe to the Innovation and Transformation newsletter</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/nl/sap-innovation-and-transformation-newsletter/index.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="ready-to-achieve-innovation-and-cloud-value-by-converting-existing-systems-to-an-intelligent-erp-system-in-a-private-cloud-learn-more-about-sap-preferred-success">Ready to achieve innovation and cloud value by converting existing systems to an intelligent ERP system in a private cloud? <a href="https://www.sap.com/services/support-plans/preferred-success-cloud.html">Learn more about SAP Preferred Success.</a></h3>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Arun P is global director and product manager of SAP Preferred Success – SAP S/4HANA Cloud at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-preferred-success</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Custom Guidance: The Secret to High-Value Transformation in the Cloud]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/custom-guidance-cloud-transformation-sap-preferred-success</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/custom-guidance-cloud-transformation-sap-preferred-success</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A Forrester study revealed the business benefits in the cloud that are enabled by SAP Preferred Success. Read about the highlights.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1fe50fe3db75fc6d5437a22dc37e75d23a81dacf4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1fe50fe3db75fc6d5437a22dc37e75d23a81dacf4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1fe50fe3db75fc6d5437a22dc37e75d23a81dacf4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Custom Guidance: The Secret to High-Value Transformation in the Cloud" src="./media_1fe50fe3db75fc6d5437a22dc37e75d23a81dacf4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="custom-guidance-the-secret-to-high-value-transformation-in-the-cloud">Custom Guidance: The Secret to High-Value Transformation in the Cloud</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Cloud technology may drive fast and agile change, but technical unknowns and strategic misdirection can lessen the impact of any degree of success. So how can businesses get on the right path to high-value transformation? The answer is proactive, ongoing, and personalized guidance, according to a study conducted by Forrester Consulting.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>When looking to the cloud to improve operational efficiencies, reduce costs, and meet customer demand with flexibility and speed, companies throw open the doors to a world of opportunities. But first, they need to become familiar with the landscape and available resources, discover capabilities that can benefit them most, and know how to scale the technology to fuel long-term, sustainable growth.</p>
  <p>Unfortunately, most internal IT organizations are too lean to manage it all. They do not have the time and budget needed to scrutinize road map strategies for the cloud and concentrate on continuous improvement after an initial implementation.</p>
  <p>The Forrester Consulting study commissioned by SAP, “<a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/07/aed54c54-ee7d-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">The Total Economic Impact™ of SAP Preferred Success</a>,” presents a solution to this common dilemma. In its assessment of the <a href="https://www.sap.com/services/support-plans/preferred-success-cloud.html">SAP Preferred Success</a> offering, the third-party global market research company revealed that access to success resources and customized guidance can yield a 380% ROI in cloud technology investments over three years.</p>
  <h2 id="fostering-adoption-and-optimization-for-long-term-growth">Fostering Adoption and Optimization for Long-Term Growth</h2>
  <p>To evaluate the potential economic impact of continuous cloud services, Forrester surveyed four companies actively using SAP Preferred Success. The participants’ experiences were then aggregated to create a single composite organization to determine the offering’s total economic impact (TEI).</p>
  <p>In this TEI study, Forrester emphasized how SAP Preferred Success helps SAP customers adopt, consume, and operate cloud solutions with greater ease, speed, and strategic value. Over a three-year period, this kind of guidance was shown to impact how businesses can quickly transform to meet the needs of a dynamic marketplace in four fundamental ways.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-preferred-success-prescriptive-guidance-for-a-world-of-uncertainty">SAP Preferred Success: Prescriptive Guidance for a World of Uncertainty</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2020/04/sap-preferred-success-prescriptive-guidance">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="shrink-implementation-time-by-two-months">1. Shrink Implementation Time by Two Months</h3>
  <p>With the assistance of customer success managers (CSMs), in-depth training materials, and support tools, surveyed businesses cited that their implementations and updates were completed faster and with lower risk. The more familiar they became with the cloud landscape and best-practice methodologies, the more confident their organizations were in supporting a cloud-based IT model. For example, deployment impediments and bugs were detected and addressed proactively, cloud investments were safeguarded, and technologies and capabilities that provide relevant benefits were chosen quickly without the fear of missing opportunities.</p>
  <h3 id="accelerate-time-to-value-with-faster-releases">2. Accelerate Time to Value with Faster Releases</h3>
  <p>The exercise of researching answers to new questions can delay planning by approximately 30%, pushing out the delivery of the solution and realization of its value. Businesses that leverage SAP Preferred Success during planning, deployment, and release preparation can add two more months of additional benefits each year after the initial implementation. Furthermore, those gains can be achieved without disrupting the everyday work experiences of internal teams.</p>
  <h3 id="facilitate-innovation-with-collaboration-and-insight">3. Facilitate Innovation with Collaboration and Insight</h3>
  <p>Interviewed organizations mentioned their interactions with customer communities and access to in-depth training materials through regular strategic reviews and ongoing informal exchanges with CSMs. They viewed this experience as a turning point in their ability to focus on their business priorities and identify opportunities to improve processes and implement new enhancements. Plus, based on Forrester’s calculation, gains in process optimization could raise productivity by, on average, 30% when the time saved is reinvested in constructive work.</p>
  <h3 id="resolve-incidents-faster-and-more-productively">4. Resolve Incidents Faster and More Productively</h3>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-resources-you-need-to-be-successful-in-the-cloud">Get the resources you need to be successful in the cloud</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/services/support-plans/preferred-success-cloud.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>With access to a dedicated CSM from SAP Preferred Success as a point of contact, interviewees from this TEI study reported resolving issues more quickly. Incidents that they raised were prioritized in SAP’s system to meet enhanced service-level agreements, supported by the CSM acting as their advocate, and connected to relevant experts to expedite resolution. This support reduced priority one and priority two incidents by half in the third year after the initial implementation while accelerating priority two incident resolution times by at least 40% and reducing effort by 30%.</p>
  <h2 id="creating-a-low-risk-flexible-foundation-for-transformation">Creating a Low-Risk, Flexible Foundation for Transformation</h2>
  <p>SAP Preferred Success is a premium add-on to SAP Enterprise Support, cloud editions. In an earlier <a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/dg/tei-on-sap-enterprise-support/index.html">TEI study covering the SAP Enterprise Support offering</a>, Forrester revealed that surveyed businesses felt they were well-equipped to move from on-premise solutions to the cloud smoothly. The offering’s prescriptive guidance enabled organizations to implement cloud solutions from SAP and find new ways to safeguard processes, optimize operations, and unlock innovations through continuous enhancements.</p>
  <p>But as Forrester emphasized in this TEI study on SAP Preferred Success, businesses that are unfamiliar with cloud solutions may want personalized assistance and advice on how to adopt, consume, and operate the technology. This is where an add-on, particularly SAP Preferred Success, can be helpful.</p>
  <p>SAP Preferred Success supports a combination of outcomes that can be critical for companies looking to transition and evolve with cloud technology. But more importantly, those advantages create an environment that empowers organizations to transform at their pace and toward their vision with less risk and greater flexibility.</p>
  <p>How can SAP Preferred Success help amplify your potential in the cloud? Find out by reading the full economic impact study by Forrester, “<a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/07/aed54c54-ee7d-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">The Total Economic Impact™ of SAP Preferred Success</a>.”</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Lisa Spangler is global vice president and chief product owner for SAP Preferred Success at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/forrester</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-enterprise-support</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-preferred-success</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Viega Future-Proofs Its Workforce with SAP SuccessFactors]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/viega-workforce-sap-successfactors</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/viega-workforce-sap-successfactors</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Viega tapped SAP SuccessFactors solutions to provide the environment and technology its employees need to be successful.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-preferred-success</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[RHI Magnesita Heats Up HR Transformation with SAP SuccessFactors Solutions]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/rhi-magnesita-hr-transformation-sap-successfactors</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/rhi-magnesita-hr-transformation-sap-successfactors</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[RHI Magnesita implemented SAP SuccessFactors to deliver the employee experience, support its workplace culture and transform HR processes.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-preferred-success</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-employee-central</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-recruiting</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Agile and Intelligent ERP Is a Myth No More with SAP Preferred Success]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/sap-preferred-success-sap-s4hana-cloud-agile-intelligent-erp</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/sap-preferred-success-sap-s4hana-cloud-agile-intelligent-erp</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With SAP Preferred Success and SAP S/4HANA Cloud, customers can can map their transition to the cloud. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1381148cc7bc7bd04a2ac63a702d499a37236c656.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1381148cc7bc7bd04a2ac63a702d499a37236c656.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1381148cc7bc7bd04a2ac63a702d499a37236c656.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Agile and Intelligent ERP Is a Myth No More with SAP Preferred Success" src="./media_1381148cc7bc7bd04a2ac63a702d499a37236c656.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="agile-and-intelligent-erp-is-a-myth-no-more-with-sap-preferred-success">Agile and Intelligent ERP Is a Myth No More with SAP Preferred Success</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>An enterprise resource planning (ERP) system that possesses the agility and intelligence to move a business forward provides distinct characteristics, ranging from realizing emerging opportunities faster to mitigating risk in real time and predicting future needs accurately. For hundreds of SAP customers, such a profound shift is best achieved with insight-driven, prescriptive, and personalized guidance.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Thinking about the technical and business challenges that executives face every day, two conclusions come to mind. First and foremost, ERP systems are fundamental platforms for digital transformation. And secondly, modernizing the technology to meet the demands of today’s fast-paced, ever-evolving market dynamics is a time-consuming, complex, and sustaining commitment.</p>
  <p>When companies are prepared to move their legacy processes to our intelligent ERP, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/s4hana-erp.html">SAP S/4HANA Cloud</a>, a wide variety of challenges inevitably arise. All organizations may not share the same goals. Shifting from a fully flexible model to one rooted in standardization may lead to confusion about the ability to adapt and modify the technology as needed. Complex discussions on integration, extensibility, data migration and management, regulatory compliance, and the cloud provider’s role may fall to the wayside among some business leaders.</p>
  <p>The <a href="https://www.sap.com/services/support-plans/preferred-success-cloud.html">SAP Preferred Success</a> offering enables our customers to productively overcome these challenges with targeted recommendations for optimizing and maximizing the value of their investment in SAP S/4HANA Cloud. The offering helps customers fully adopt the cloud mindset necessary for deployment and rapidly plan ongoing adoption of capabilities that bring specific value to their line-of-business priorities and align with their overall business goals.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-more-about-services-from-sap">Read more about services from SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/support.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="trusted-guide-to-agility-and-intelligence">Trusted Guide to Agility and Intelligence</h2>
  <p>By aligning expectations for SAP S/4HANA Cloud with desired business outcomes early in the life cycle, our customers can map their transition to the cloud and understand the importance of standardization with some adaptation of existing processes.</p>
  <p>But this standardization should also be liberating. This foundational concept simplifies support for operational processes and focuses the implementation on the capabilities and functions that truly differentiate our customers from their competitors. The initial phase of SAP Preferred Success allows our customers to fully understand how the modern ERP model fills existing gaps and continues to scale at the same pace that organizational change happens.</p>
  <p>More importantly, our customers can further build out their digital strategy by considering new capabilities and tools available that they didn’t know existed. For example, live virtual events and expert-led sessions give insight into a range of intelligent technologies embedded in SAP S/4HANA Cloud, including robotic process automation (RPA), machine learning, predictive analytics, and artificial intelligence (AI). This targeted content uncovers the connection between what SAP S/4HANA Cloud provides and what can be achieved as their ultimate vision.</p>
  <p>Although these experiences with SAP Preferred Success are early in the overall implementation of SAP S/4HANA Cloud, the information provided can be an eye-opener that impacts the entire digital transformation journey for years to come. Executives are better prepared to lead their workforce through every change along the path to go-live while knowing how to minimize costs and risk and focusing on value.</p>
  <p>Unlike some offerings, SAP Preferred Success stays engaged with SAP customers throughout the life of their deployment of SAP S/4HANA Cloud. Dedicated customer success managers help steer organizations through quarterly updates, determining which new capabilities are needed to further their digital strategy and address unique business needs. They recommend the capabilities that customers should consider enhancing or adopting and assist in the creation and completion of a minimally disruptive plan to implement relevant innovations. Adoption planning sessions are offered to dive into these new ideas, weigh their viability, and choose the best options to deliver a better technology or process experience.</p>
  <h2 id="continuous-support-for-scaled-digital-transformation">Continuous Support for Scaled Digital Transformation</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-to-know-sap-preferred-success">Get to know SAP Preferred Success</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/services/support-plans/preferred-success-cloud.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Many businesses are digitally transforming themselves with impressive speed. However, speed alone is not the key to a successful digital transformation. What’s needed is an agile and intelligent foundation that unlocks their true potential – whether navigating economic uncertainty, exploring new business models, ramping up toward a recovery, or paving the way to growth.</p>
  <p>While change doesn’t come without risks, SAP Preferred Success helps prepare SAP customers to navigate them all – with the agility and intelligence of SAP S/4HANA Cloud.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>For more real-life insights on SAP Preferred Success, read the rest of the series, “<a href="/topics/sap-preferred-success-cloud-series">Heading to the Cloud with SAP Preferred Success</a>” and discover how your entire company can accelerate cloud adoption and business outcomes with insight-driven, prescriptive, and personalized guidance and support.</p>
        <p><em>Chris Lewis is global director and product manager for SAP Preferred Success, SAP S/4HANA Cloud at SAP.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="subscribe-to-the-innovation-and-transformation-newsletter">Subscribe to the Innovation and Transformation Newsletter</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/nl/sap-innovation-and-transformation-newsletter/index.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-erp</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-preferred-success</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-preferred-success-cloud-series</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Preferred Success: Leading Organizations to the Future of Cloud Computing]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/sap-preferred-success-and-cloud-computing</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/sap-preferred-success-and-cloud-computing</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Together SAP Preferred Success and cloud computing are helping SAP customers are map and navigate unique paths to the cloud.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-preferred-success</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-preferred-success-cloud-series</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Preferred Success Reveals the Cloud’s Influence on Customer Experience]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/01/sap-preferred-success-and-customer-experience</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/01/sap-preferred-success-and-customer-experience</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With SAP Preferred Success and customer experience solutions, insight-driven, prescriptive, and personalized support is available.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16b1df8be771b3179df47340b63cf8aba4868fe6c.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16b1df8be771b3179df47340b63cf8aba4868fe6c.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_16b1df8be771b3179df47340b63cf8aba4868fe6c.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Preferred Success Reveals the Cloud’s Influence on Customer Experience" src="./media_16b1df8be771b3179df47340b63cf8aba4868fe6c.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-preferred-success-reveals-the-clouds-influence-on-customer-experience">SAP Preferred Success Reveals the Cloud’s Influence on Customer Experience</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>It’s no secret that “experience” is the new focus for many organizations – whether it is the experience of their customers or their own employees. Businesses now need to be conscious of experience more than ever.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Customers’ expectations evolve rapidly in today’s digital world, which only increases the pressure for businesses to meet them. So how do businesses provide a superior omnichannel experience for their customers now while remaining poised to adapt to the customer of the future? The answer is cloud. Investing in cloud solutions and technologies can help give businesses that competitive advantage they need.</p>
  <p>As the margin of error for businesses slims and customers increasingly prefer digital channels for their shopping experience, businesses need to use this competitive advantage to connect with their customers on multiple levels. They need to demonstrate their value as a trusted supplier, relevant brand, and committed partner. Maintaining this reputation is no easy feat given the endless number of options customers have at their fingertips and how quickly a poor experience can send a customer running to a competitor.</p>
  <p>To maintain the relationships with their customers, businesses need to understand them at a holistic level. They need to have deep insights into the behaviors and desired experiences of their customers to proactively create and engage opportunities and react quickly to challenges. For many SAP customers, cloud technology connects those customer data points and sets the foundation for more intelligent data capture, processing, and analysis. Before the pandemic, <a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/cx/b2b-value-chains-gch14/index.html?url_id=ctabutton-gl-FCEE-platforms-will-rule-in-B2B-experience-economy-blogpost">46% of B2B companies</a> were already planning to employ cloud-based technologies for 61% to 100% of their digital commerce solutions. And now, B2C businesses are following the same path to engage customers with restrictive in-person policies.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-to-know-sap-preferred-success">Get to know SAP Preferred Success</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/services/support-plans/preferred-success-cloud.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="taking-the-customer-experience-to-the-cloud--with-confidence">Taking the Customer Experience to the Cloud – with Confidence</h2>
  <p>When moving from an on-premise environment to a cloud landscape, most organizations quickly realize that the experience is unlike anything they’ve seen before. Challenges exist for both the business and IT teams. Organizations must adapt to a mindset of standardization over customization, more frequent releases containing new innovations designed to improve their business, and foundationally new products that they lack knowledge and experience administering.</p>
  <p>The <a href="https://www.sap.com/services/support-plans/preferred-success-cloud.html">SAP Preferred Success</a> offering can help organizations overcome those challenges to help ensure a successful transition to the cloud and adoption of optimal business processes, leading to better user experience. The offering orchestrates a success plan including a comprehensive portfolio of exclusive resources to optimize the consumption of cloud solutions and technology from SAP.</p>
  <p>The underlying goal of SAP Preferred Success is to help customers leverage cloud solutions the right way for their business. We work with our customers to help ensure their cloud investments play an integral role in helping them reach their desired and expected business outcomes.</p>
  <p>Through an extensive community of users, business peers, and product experts, customers receive guidance on the latest functions. A dedicated customer success manager (CSM) acts as the partner for success for customers. The CSM helps ensure milestones and goals are being met through close collaboration with customer teams and by orchestrating the necessary resources for success.</p>
  <p>Each phase and milestone – such as an implementation or a new release – is supported by SAP Preferred Success. Customers’ goals and key initiatives are integrated into the approach to help ensure the delivery of the expected outcomes and the overall digital transformation strategy.</p>
  <h2 id="driving-continuous-value-that-resonates">Driving Continuous Value that Resonates</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-more-about-services-and-support-from-sap">Read more about services and support from SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/support.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Without question, today’s competitive landscape is full of challenges primarily centered around the experience of customers. But don’t forget that a slew of new opportunities is emerging and quickly becoming a point of differentiation in a rapidly evolving digital marketplace.</p>
  <p>It’s a juggling act to handle all this change. Beyond just implementing new technology, businesses need to commit to a fundamental and permanent shift in their digital strategies, processes, and mindsets to serve customers better. And with SAP Preferred Success by their side, they have the insight-driven, prescriptive, and personalized support they need to build the right customer experience.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>Get more real-life insights on SAP Preferred Success through the series, <a href="/topics/sap-preferred-success-cloud-series">Heading to the Cloud with SAP Preferred Success</a>, and learn how your entire company can accelerate cloud adoption and business outcomes with insight-driven, prescriptive, and personalized guidance and support.</p>
        <table>
          <thead>
            <tr>
              <th>Quote</th>
            </tr>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td>Stay in the conversation by following SAP Services and Support on <a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/sapsupportinfo">YouTube</a>, <a href="https://twitter.com/SAPDigitalSvcs">Twitter</a>, <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/138840">LinkedIn</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/SAPDigitalBusinessServices">Facebook</a>.</td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
              <td>Timothy Curcio is global director of SAP Customer Experience solutions for SAP Preferred Success, Customer Engagement and Experience, at SAP.</td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="subscribe-to-the-innovation-and-transformation-newsletter">Subscribe to the Innovation and Transformation Newsletter</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/nl/sap-innovation-and-transformation-newsletter/index.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-preferred-success</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-preferred-success-cloud-series</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Preferred Success Opens the Door to Talent Businesses Need Now]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/01/sap-preferred-success-and-sap-fieldglass-talent-businesses-need</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/01/sap-preferred-success-and-sap-fieldglass-talent-businesses-need</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Preferred Success and SAP Fieldglass solutions can help organizations capitalize on a well-managed, dynamic, flexible external workforce.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f1525d4b569e23fd8bb241e9c0ce8b91aaa49e83.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f1525d4b569e23fd8bb241e9c0ce8b91aaa49e83.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1f1525d4b569e23fd8bb241e9c0ce8b91aaa49e83.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Preferred Success Opens the Door to Talent Businesses Need Now" src="./media_1f1525d4b569e23fd8bb241e9c0ce8b91aaa49e83.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-preferred-success-opens-the-door-to-talent-businesses-need-now">SAP Preferred Success Opens the Door to Talent Businesses Need Now</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>The workforce you need today isn’t the same as it was yesterday – and it will undoubtedly be different tomorrow. To <a href="https://insights.sap.com/importance-upskilling/">stay competitive</a>, organizations are capitalizing on a well-managed, dynamic, and flexible external workforce. And SAP Preferred Success can help reveal yours with the visibility and insight of SAP Fieldglass solutions.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>While navigating an economy that is reshaping customer demand, business models, and industries in unpredictable ways, executives are just as concerned about their company’s recovery readiness. Just days before the onset of the <a href="/covid-19">pandemic</a>, <a href="https://www.economist.com/business/2020/03/24/the-coronavirus-crisis-thrusts-corporate-hr-chiefs-into-the-spotlight">The Economist</a> revealed that four-fifths of CEOs worried about skill gaps, up from half in 2012.</p>
  <p>As the marketplace continues to evolve, concern over skill shortages is intensifying. In response, businesses are relying more on contingent talent, comprising 42 percent of the average workforce spend according to <a href="https://www.fieldglass.com/resources/research/contingent-workforce-insights-2019/download">Oxford Economics</a>. Sometimes, we even hear organizational managers say that their company couldn’t conduct business as usual without the support of independent contractors, freelancers, temporary staff, and service providers.</p>
  <p>Despite the importance of external workers, most CEOs and senior leaders do not have fast, easy access to information on them. This reality is not as uncommon as you may think. In fact, this lack of visibility that limits compliance, governance, cost control, and resource optimization prompts many companies to implement <a href="https://www.fieldglass.com/">SAP Fieldglass</a> solutions. And with the assistance of the <a href="https://www.sap.com/services/support-plans/preferred-success-cloud.html">SAP Preferred Success</a> offering, our customers are aligning their workforce practices with business needs in real time.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-to-know-sap-preferred-success">Get to know SAP Preferred Success</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/services/support-plans/preferred-success-cloud.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="uncovering-workforce-value-outside-the-payroll">Uncovering Workforce Value Outside the Payroll</h2>
  <p>Every business wants the best talent – on the payroll or not – that can help see them through times of disruption, uncertainty, and prosperity. They need knowledgeable people who can get the job done efficiently, timely, and with an edge that further differentiates the brand. And most importantly, executives expect high-quality outcomes at a fair price and the ability to quickly identify talent that could be a valuable candidate for an open role or leadership position.</p>
  <p>Bringing these expectations to life requires a system of checks and balances when managing workers hired outside the payroll. This capability involves workflow automation that serves as a single point for compliance auditing, assignment administration, communication, and delivery of work items. External workforce information should also be integrated seamlessly with modern enterprise resource planning (ERP) software to trigger invoicing and payment; cost analysis; and HR processes such as onboarding, badging, security checks, technology access, and laptop distribution.</p>
  <p>Our customers find that SAP Fieldglass solutions are well-suited to support such a digital transformation. But to optimize their adoption of the vendor management system, they often want insight-driven, prescriptive, and personalized support to determine <a href="https://www.fieldglass.com/solutions/contingent-workforce-management">contingent workforce</a> goals that complement their business strategies and address talent management disparities.</p>
  <p>SAP Preferred Success gives the guidance that our customers seek. With a comprehensive portfolio of exclusive success plans and support expertise, organizations can identify opportunities for cost savings, process automation, and adoption of business networks to allow qualified contingent workers to bid against each other. Tailored functional learning, change management, and enhanced support capabilities are also offered to help implement new solutions, establish new processes and refine existing ones, and foster business-wide adoption.</p>
  <p>Perhaps as its most critical advantage, SAP Preferred Success offers continuous support throughout our customers’ transformation journey. We give organizations the freedom to fully understand emerging trends and consider how they relate to their business needs, workforce capabilities, and digital strategies. These developments may include recently passed labor regulations, rising demand for new skills, evolving market forces, and shifts in business direction.</p>
  <p>Semiannually, SAP Fieldglass solutions are updated to fulfill the changing landscape of external workforce management. However, we also understand that our customers must also strategically choose capabilities based on current requirements and scale the technology as the contingent workforce fluctuates. Access to the latest release notes, solutions road maps, and real-life best practices allows our customers to make informed decisions that meet their unique needs.</p>
  <h2 id="bringing-to-life-a-connected-ecosystem-of-the-right-talent">Bringing to Life a Connected Ecosystem of the Right Talent</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-more-about-services-and-support-from-sap">Read more about services and support from SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/support.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>For many of our customers, the experience of evolving their external talent management with SAP Preferred Success brings a new perspective on the value of independent contractors, freelancers, temporary staff, and service providers.</p>
  <p>Every workshop, design-thinking session, update release, and process change allows them to make connections between business goals, defined success metrics, and the role of external employees. This level of visibility enables them to look beyond the day-to-day minutia to think about their entire workforce on and off the payroll – opening the door to the talent they need.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>Get more real-life insights on SAP Preferred Success through the series, <a href="/topics/sap-preferred-success-cloud-series">Heading to the Cloud with SAP Preferred Success</a>, and learn how your entire company can accelerate cloud adoption and business outcomes with insight-driven, prescriptive, and personalized guidance and support.</p>
        <table>
          <thead>
            <tr>
              <th>Quote</th>
            </tr>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td>Stay in the conversation by following SAP Services and Support on <a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/sapsupportinfo">YouTube</a>, <a href="https://twitter.com/SAPDigitalSvcs">Twitter</a>, <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/138840">LinkedIn</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/SAPDigitalBusinessServices">Facebook</a>.</td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
              <td>John Wagner, Jr., is global practice lead for SAP Preferred Success, Intelligent Spend Management, at SAP. Nick Geiger is director of Customer Adoption, Americas, for SAP Fieldglass.</td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="subscribe-to-the-innovation-and-transformation-newsletter">Subscribe to the Innovation and Transformation Newsletter</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/nl/sap-innovation-and-transformation-newsletter/index.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-spend</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-preferred-success</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-preferred-success-cloud-series</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>