<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/digital-skills-gap/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Powering the AI Revolution with New Learning, Certifications, and Simplified Access to Talent]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/powering-ai-revolution-learning-certifications-talent</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/powering-ai-revolution-learning-certifications-talent</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Bring out your best with new learning opportunities, role-based SAP Certifications, and simplified access to talent. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_158ee9e4c4293f1933f13d07a2fb3eddc96c821de.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_158ee9e4c4293f1933f13d07a2fb3eddc96c821de.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_158ee9e4c4293f1933f13d07a2fb3eddc96c821de.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Powering the AI Revolution with New Learning, Certifications, and Simplified Access to Talent" src="./media_158ee9e4c4293f1933f13d07a2fb3eddc96c821de.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="powering-the-ai-revolution-with-new-learning-certifications-and-simplified-access-to-talent">Powering the AI Revolution with New Learning, Certifications, and Simplified Access to Talent</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Artificial intelligence (AI) is currently forcing the technology industry to undergo <a href="">a paradigm shift</a>, further accelerating the upheaval in business and society. We see AI embedded in tools we have been using for years, and we see software finding its way into every aspect of competition today. Against this background, it comes as no surprise that <a href="https://www2.deloitte.com/us/en/pages/consulting/articles/state-of-ai-2022.html">94% of business leaders see AI as critical to success over the next five years</a>. However, many report the lack of resources and talent to drive competitiveness with these new tools.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="taking-business-to-the-next-level-in-the-era-of-ai">Taking Business to the Next Level in the Era of AI</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/events/sapphire/news-guide.html">Read the news guide</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>To make it easier to develop relevant skills and secure business success in such a volatile environment, <a href="/2022/11/sap-coursera-partnership-digital-skills-underrepresented-groups">we embarked on a journey to upskill millions of people worldwide</a> in search of opportunity. After launching a digital skills initiative for those underserved in tech, forging new partnerships, offering the first role-based certifications to help meet real-life business needs, and making future-focused learning resources available to all, we are now taking our efforts to an even higher level – with more free, self-paced learning and engagement opportunities, new solution demos to experience the latest innovations in SAP Business AI, cloud ERP, and SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP), among others, a full portfolio of role-based certifications and a new certification model, as well as an extended digital skills initiative.</p>
  <h2 id="more-than-250-free-online-courses-now-available-for-all">More Than 250 Free Online Courses Now Available for All</h2>
  <p>From global talent shortages and changing job profiles to the digitalization of entire economies, many organizations see the gaps between skill supply and demand grow wider and wider while searching for ways to adapt to a business landscape where advancements like AI, machine learning, and a new era of Big Data come into play. In this ever-changing atmosphere, tens of thousands of organizations have <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company.html">deployed SAP solutions</a> to support them on their path to bring out their best, leading to skyrocketing demand for SAP talent.</p>
  <p>To help meet the increasing demand, we recently launched more than 50 new free, self-paced learning journeys – many of them touching on AI features embedded in our software – bringing the total number of digital courses on the <a href="https://learning.sap.com/?url_id=text-sapnewscenter-prdteng-Sapphire">SAP Learning site</a> to more than 250. By allowing everyone with an Internet connection to quickly learn a new skill for free, keep up with the latest innovations, and prepare for an in-demand SAP Certification, more professionals can advance in the competitive technology labor market, while customers can draw on a deeper bench of skills to accelerate digital transformation.</p>
  <h2 id="launching-role-based-certifications-for-all-key-roles">Launching Role-Based Certifications for All Key Roles</h2>
  <p>As organizations need to be more adaptive and dynamic, traditional university degrees become less important and skills-based hiring is on the rise when trying to fill positions. In fact, recent reports show that up to <a href="https://www.hiringlab.org/2024/02/27/educational-requirements-job-postings/">52% of job postings</a> in the U.S. in the beginning of the year did not state an educational requirement. Instead, role-based certifications and practical experience have become more determining factors for career paths and hiring.</p>
  <p>Recognizing the advantages role-based certifications can offer both individuals and organizations, we have further enhanced our certification program to better align with real-life business needs, now offering role-based certification for all key roles, including consultants, analysts, and architects. These role-based certifications come with a clear career path for individuals. Together with a <a href="https://learning.sap.com/get-certified?url_id=text-sapnewscenter-prdteng-Sapphire">new model to get and stay certified</a> with continuous assessments, this is our way to help ensure skill sets are sharp, focused on core competencies, and more sustainable and valid for longer periods of time.</p>
  <p>With these enhancements, we believe we have now taken an important next step to support professionals and organizations in the SAP ecosystem to bring out their best with ongoing and up-to-date knowledge of the latest skills, helping to maximize the ROI of SAP software, shorten deployment times, lower costs, speed innovation, and increase employee retention and satisfaction.</p>
  <h2 id="simplified-access-to-pre-trained-sap-talent">Simplified Access to Pre-Trained SAP Talent</h2>
  <p>However, we recognize that many people considered underrepresented in tech still do not have access to future-focused educational resources and with it, fulfilling careers. Launched in late 2022, <a href="https://learning.sap.com/digital-skills?url_id=text-sapnewscenter-prdteng-Sapphire">SAP’s digital skills initiative</a> was intended to equip 10,000 people from underrepresented and underserved groups for a career in the tech industry with free, self-paced learning resources and a free certification exam attempt to obtain an in-demand SAP Certification to show their expertise. Ever since its launch, the initiative has grown – and contributed to <a href="https://community.sap.com/t5/learner-stories/bg-p/learner-stories">amazing success stories</a>.</p>
  <p>Hearing that SAP professionals like <a href="https://community.sap.com/t5/sap-learning-blog-posts/breaking-barriers-and-fighting-sexism-lin-s-journey-from-a-salesgirl-to-an/ba-p/13588835">Lin Fan, a Chinese immigrant to Germany</a>, could overcome gender bias because of our digital skills initiative, makes me proud. “[The digital skills initiative and SAP Certification] indeed opened new doors and helped me get noticed by recruiters,” Fan said. “I got several interviews from major SAP consulting firms shortly after handing in my application. In the interviews, I highlighted what I learned and expressed my confidence in accepting challenges for rolling out SAP S/4HANA. In the end, I got an offer and gladly started a junior role at a consulting firm that actively implements SAP S/4HANA projects.”</p>
  <p>While Fan’s path is inspiring, she is not the only one who turned their life around with the help of SAP. Given the expectation-exceeding demand of now more than 14,500 candidates, we are overwhelmed by the positive uptake of the initiative. One of our recent graduates, <a href="https://community.sap.com/t5/learner-stories/breaking-down-barriers-hear-from-chelcie-scott-how-she-broke-into-tech-with/ba-p/13710541">Chelcie Scott, agreed to tell her story</a> on camera and shared how intimidating the tech industry appeared to the single mother at first. Thanks to her willpower and commitment, plus a little help from the digital skills initiative, she recently got certified and hired by an SAP partner. And as organizations are still struggling to find skilled employees, we have decided to extend SAP’s digital skills initiative, bringing candidates and organizations together. With simplified access to SAP-trained talent, we are helping customers and partners to recruit talent and expand their workforce faster while also allowing for greater diversity and innovation.</p>
  <p>At SAP, we recognize the challenges and opportunities that lie ahead for customers, partners, and individual learners within and outside of the SAP ecosystem. With these enhancements, we have taken the next step to help organizations equip their existing workforce with the right tools and resources to future-proof their skill set while also paving career growth for those who do not have a seat at the table yet but can bring a fresh set of perspectives to it.</p>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1bf4a81f181aead9f58c4d25e211885b7fc5988cc.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1bf4a81f181aead9f58c4d25e211885b7fc5988cc.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1bf4a81f181aead9f58c4d25e211885b7fc5988cc.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Break Down Barriers With the Help of SAP’s Digital Skills Initiative" src="./media_1bf4a81f181aead9f58c4d25e211885b7fc5988cc.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pEsE7dicrc4&#x26;feature=youtu.be">Break Down Barriers With the Help of SAP’s Digital Skills Initiative</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Andre Bechtold is SVP and head of Solution &#x26; Innovation Experience at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-sapphire-in-2024-innovations-to-bring-out-the-best-in-your-business">SAP Sapphire in 2024: Innovations to bring out the best in your business</h3>
        <p><em><a href="/topics/sap-sapphire">Get the latest news and coverage</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills-gap</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Accelerate Your Skills Transformation with the New Integrated Learning Experience for SAP SuccessFactors]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/new-integrated-learning-experience-sap-successfactors</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/new-integrated-learning-experience-sap-successfactors</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The integrated learning experience for SAP SuccessFactors helps to address skills gaps and considers employees' whole self in skills growth.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills-gap</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning-management-system</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-learning</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Communicating the True Value of Learning and Development in 2023]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/communicating-value-of-learning-development-2023</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/communicating-value-of-learning-development-2023</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Leaders need to be strategic in providing learning opportunities. Learn why and how leaders and employees can benefit from the investment.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c348ed4ab53e7860823ae46dfe75ba57f60e11e8.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c348ed4ab53e7860823ae46dfe75ba57f60e11e8.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1c348ed4ab53e7860823ae46dfe75ba57f60e11e8.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Communicating the True Value of Learning and Development in 2023" src="./media_1c348ed4ab53e7860823ae46dfe75ba57f60e11e8.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="communicating-the-true-value-of-learning-and-development-in-2023">Communicating the True Value of Learning and Development in 2023</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>As we move quickly into the second quarter of 2023, leaders and workers alike are facing increasing pressure resulting from the current tumultuous economic period. In a business environment where every budget line is being questioned, IT leaders must maintain a strategic lens when providing <a href="/topics/training">learning</a> opportunities for their teams. They must be able to clearly articulate the value of technical training and development opportunities – or risk losing them.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In the midst of this uncertainty, keeping IT workers abreast of innovative technologies and the skills to implement them is a balancing act. To stay at the forefront of industry change, learning must be considered more than a priority – it needs to be a core pillar of every organization. IT upskilling is key in today’s landscape to drive employee satisfaction and organizational success. Here are three of the top reasons to invest in learning and development opportunities and how the benefits can be articulated to leadership to ensure they consider learning a top priority, too.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-digital-skills-you-need-with-sap-learning">Get the digital skills you need with SAP Learning</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://learning.sap.com/digital-skills?url_id=text-sapnewscenter-prdteng-DigitalSkills">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="invest-in-your-employees--and-they-just-might-stick-around">Invest in Your Employees – and They Just Might Stick Around</h2>
  <p>While layoffs seem to be dominating the headlines, employees are quitting their jobs at <a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2023/02/13/business/employee-retention-quitting-companies.html">three times</a> the rate of layoffs. Retaining strong talent remains a competitive pursuit, and organizations are feeling the impacts of this challenge. Now, <a href="http://workplaceintelligence.com/upskilling-study/">64% to 66% of employees</a> would consider leaving their current role because there aren’t enough opportunities for skill development or career advancement. The truth is that adequate training directly impacts retention. An important factor in how employees evaluate their organization is based on the opportunities they’re provided to learn the skills that will catapult them towards reaching their goals. Learning and development opportunities can equip employees with essential leadership skills that can elevate their current position and pave the way for internal advancement.</p>
  <p>By offering learning programs, and therefore showing the workforce that leaders are invested in their growth, executive teams will realize a multitude of benefits. Individuals will feel valued and excited by new challenges and upskilling opportunities, making them more likely to be happy with their current role. Beyond this, they’ll build a workforce that is equipped with the latest knowledge to drive meaningful outcomes for the organization.</p>
  <h2 id="fostering-creativity-innovation-and-curiosity">Fostering Creativity, Innovation, and Curiosity</h2>
  <p>The tech industry is evolving – fast. From generative artificial intelligence (AI) and machine learning to immersive-reality technologies, digital transformation has raised the bar on the skills required of teams today. Inspiring employees to lead innovative strategies can feel daunting when the workforce is not properly equipped with the latest knowledge to take on new initiatives. When employees do not feel prepared, they are less likely to be enthusiastic about taking on new responsibilities or raise their hand to lead a project that is outside of their comfort zone. In fact, <a href="https://www.gartner.com/en/publications/emerging-technology-roadmap-for-large-enterprisesB">64% of IT professionals</a> think the skills shortage is the biggest barrier to the adoption of game-changing technologies.</p>
  <p>To combat this hesitation and encourage workers to tackle new challenges, leaders must recognize that learning and development opportunities enable IT teams to feel prepared and excited to move forward on adopting new workplace technologies. This ultimately increases efficiency and allows more time and space for innovation and creativity.</p>
  <p>Steve Lucas, SAP S/4HANA Cloud application consultant at Sapphire Systems, has seen how learning, for instance with <a href="https://learning.sap.com/?url_id=text-sapnewscenter-prdteng">self-paced SAP Learning Journeys on the SAP Learning site</a>, can drive innovation firsthand. “Earning an SAP Certiﬁcation is important to not just my future but the future of my company. It ensures we’ll both meet our goals and remain at the forefront of SAP’s latest innovations,” he said.</p>
  <h2 id="tackling-the-persistent-skills-gap-challenge">Tackling the Persistent Skills Gap Challenge</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="explore-sap-learning-journeys-and-product-pages">Explore SAP Learning Journeys and product pages</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://learning.sap.com/?url_id=text-sapnewscenter-prdteng">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The skills gap remains top-of-mind for leaders across industries as technical roles continue to evolve and competition for top talent remains high. Due to the speed of innovation, over <a href="https://www.gartner.com/en/newsroom/press-releases/2021-02-03-gartner-hr-research-finds-fifty-eight-percent-of-the-workforce-will-need-new-skill-sets-to-do-their-jobs-successfully">58% of the workforce will need new skill sets</a> to do their jobs successfully in the coming years.</p>
  <p>While some employees may be able to make time outside of work hours for learning and development, many have competing personal priorities – meaning encouraging employees to seek upskilling opportunities outside of their nine-to-five may set them on a path of frustration and burnout. Instead, bring training programs directly to them and build a few uninterrupted hours into their workday so that employees can devote themselves to learning without navigating demanding tasks at the same time. This simple solution can mitigate burnout and ensure everyone is receiving the information they need to be successful in their roles – now and in the future.</p>
  <p>For example, learning programs like <a href="https://learning.sap.com/learning-journey/discover-the-foundations-of-sap-commerce-cloud-and-sap-s-4hana-cloud-integration?url_id=text-sapnewscenter-prdteng">SAP S/4HANA</a> or <a href="https://learning.sap.com/learning-journey/utilize-sap-build-for-low-code-no-code-applications-and-automations-for-citizen-developers?url_id=text-sapnewscenter-prdteng">low-code/no-code</a> basics can quickly and efficiently equip employees with the skills they need by educating them on the latest platforms and technology necessary to keep up with digital transformation efforts. These programs can also level the playing field among teams, increasing workers’ value and purpose within their current role.</p>
  <h2 id="the-return-on-learning-and-development-priceless">The Return on Learning and Development? Priceless.</h2>
  <p>While it’s true that that investing in learning and development is a commitment – both in budget and in resources – the benefits far outweigh the drawbacks. It’s easy to deprioritize learning when the time and money that goes into upskilling can seem like an optional expense, but in today’s workplace culture, it is essential. Companies who invest in learning and development opportunities will reap the benefits almost immediately and will equip their teams for a future of innovation, creativity, and equitable opportunities for growth, ultimately leading to higher retention, empowered employees, and a more secure workforce.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Jan Meyer is head of Learning Systems at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills-gap</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Women Can Be the Key to Solving the Global Skills Gap in Tech]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/01/women-key-to-global-digital-skills-gap-in-tech</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/01/women-key-to-global-digital-skills-gap-in-tech</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The global lack of digitally skilled workers is increasing in the tech industry. Learn about SAP's initiative and how women are key.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/coursera</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills-gap</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-certification</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-community</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Advancing Digital Skills When Needed Most]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/advancing-digital-skills-when-needed-most-sap-young-professionals-program</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/advancing-digital-skills-when-needed-most-sap-young-professionals-program</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[During COVID-19, the SAP Young Professionals program went virtual, attracting recent graduates who might not have been able to attend in-person.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills-gap</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>