<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/climate-21/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sustainable Business Playbook: Stop Just Collecting Data and Start Acting On It]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/sustainable-business-stop-collecting-data-start-acting</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/sustainable-business-stop-collecting-data-start-acting</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[To deliver on net-zero commitments, corporate and public sector leaders are capturing and acting on decision relevant data. Read to learn how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-emissions</category>
            <category>news-tag/climate-21</category>
            <category>news-tag/climate-action</category>
            <category>non-sap-event/cop26</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Sustainability Control Tower: A Commanding Business View]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/sap-sustainability-control-tower-business-view</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/sap-sustainability-control-tower-business-view</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The new SAP Sustainability Control Tower solution helps companies monitor and control financial, sustainability, and governance indicators.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_178ac8cffe9c3f119cbea667aae6c42edcad8f7aa.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_178ac8cffe9c3f119cbea667aae6c42edcad8f7aa.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_178ac8cffe9c3f119cbea667aae6c42edcad8f7aa.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Sustainability Control Tower: A Commanding Business View" src="./media_178ac8cffe9c3f119cbea667aae6c42edcad8f7aa.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-sustainability-control-tower-a-commanding-business-view">SAP Sustainability Control Tower: A Commanding Business View</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>SAP unveiled the new SAP Sustainability Control Tower solution today, designed to help enterprises monitor operational performance and steer their business according to a combination of traditional- and sustainability-related performance indicators.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The cloud-based solution’s dashboard provides executives a commanding view of business operations and enables faster decision-making in response to events that, if unrecognized, would imperil company objectives.</p>
  <p>“The release of SAP Sustainability Control Tower represents another key milestone on our mission to establish the ‘green line’ alongside the top and bottom lines as key dimensions of performance,” says Gunther Rothermel, head of SAP S/4HANA Sustainability Management. “Based on the power of SAP Business Technology Platform, the solution provides the necessary agility and flexibility to quickly adapt to evolving and changing requirements without having to write code.”</p>
  <p><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/sustainability-control-tower.html">SAP Sustainability Control Tower</a> enables companies to transform into intelligent and sustainable enterprises based on financial as well as environmental, social, and governance (ESG) indicators, allowing them to fully assess global impact both within their operations and across their business networks.</p>
  <p>“The very first thing companies need to do on their path of becoming sustainable enterprises is to understand their environmental footprint based on facts and figures,” says Jan Gilg, president of SAP S/4HANA, SAP. “Using these insights, SAP Sustainability Control Tower combines a company’s critical ESG metrics into one aggregated view, helping leaders take informed decisions to shape a better, sustainable future.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="our-planet-cannot-afford-fragmented-reporting">Our Planet Cannot Afford Fragmented Reporting</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="the-push-to-become-more-sustainable-and-socially-responsible">The Push to Become More Sustainable and Socially Responsible</h2>
  <p>A number of drivers – ecological, economic, and societal – are currently motivating businesses and entire industries to make their operations more sustainable. Companies have taken notice, for example, that investors, shareholders, regulators, and consumers increasingly demand responsibly derived products and services with a smaller environmental footprint.​</p>
  <p>In a <a href="https://www.stern.nyu.edu/experience-stern/about/departments-centers-initiatives/centers-of-research/center-sustainable-business/research/research-initiatives/csb-sustainable-market-share-index#:~:text=Our%20findings%20include%3A,products%20not%20marketed%20as%20sustainable.">study of consumer purchasing from 2015 to 2019</a>, the share of sustainability-marketed products grew more than seven times faster than other products, delivering 54.7% of CPG market growth. According to The World Bank, <a href="https://carbonpricingdashboard.worldbank.org/">65 carbon pricing initiatives</a> have already been implemented worldwide. A <a href="https://www2.deloitte.com/global/en/pages/about-deloitte/articles/millennialsurvey.html">Deloitte survey from 2021</a> confirmed that younger generations want to work for companies with a purpose beyond profit.</p>
  <p>Most recently, the ambitious goals discussed at the <a href="https://ukcop26.org/">UN Climate Change Conference</a> (COP26) in Glasgow made it clear that businesses are under growing pressure to accelerate their sustainability efforts in conformance with regulations and that ESG-related KPIs have become part of the “license to operate.”</p>
  <p>In a <a href="https://insights.sap.com/environmental-sustainability-affects-competitiveness/">2021 SAP Insights global survey</a> of business professionals who are knowledgeable about their organization’s sustainability goals, actions, and reporting methods, 17% of respondents believe environmental issues are already materially affecting their companies’ finances and operations.</p>
  <p>But, as with every new venture, there are challenges. Early adopters seeking a complete picture of their ESG impact struggle with many reporting frameworks and standards. This hinders their ability to produce consistent and comparable investor-focused disclosures, creating a negative impact on global business. The International Federation of Accountants <a href="https://internationalbanker.com/finance/global-regulatory-fragmentation-an-impediment-to-economic-growth/">reported in 2018</a> that fragmented financial reporting systems cost the global economy US$780 billion per year.</p>
  <h2 id="embedding-sustainability-into-business-processes">Embedding Sustainability into Business Processes</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="accelerating-a-new-era-of-sustainability-management">Accelerating a New Era of Sustainability Management</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/12/sap-sustainability-control-tower-new-era-sustainability-management">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP Sustainability Control Tower addresses fragmented financial reporting head-on by giving companies tools to extend their top- and bottom-line optimizations to the “green line,” based on sustainability KPIs. Using a data-driven approach, businesses can now embed sustainability throughout their business and gain actionable insights across the value chain to enable the transition to low-carbon business processes.</p>
  <p>“The insights from combined data provide a continuous view on a company’s performance that manual processes based on spreadsheets cannot match,” says Rothermel. “Simplified steering, reporting, and performance management meet the requirements of a growing number of legal obligations as well as the emerging sustainability standards.”</p>
  <p>Users can drill down into strategic areas within the company and across a business network to make informed decision-making based on financial and pre-financial (ESG) indicators. An optimization can then be made between costs and greenhouse gas emissions. For example, a company’s chief financial officer could quantify the total impact of a business activity on the environment and society and manage trade-offs based on a comparable monetary currency.</p>
  <p>SAP Sustainability Control Tower uses the World Economic Forum’s <a href="https://www.weforum.org/stakeholdercapitalism">Stakeholder Capitalism Metrics</a> as a foundation. These can be applied by companies to align reporting on performance against ESG indicators and include non-financial disclosures centered around four pillars: people, planet, prosperity, and principles of governance. The Stakeholder Capitalism Metrics promote alignment among ESG frameworks and create data points that are comparable between companies, regardless of industry or region.</p>
  <h2 id="co-innovating-with-customers-and-partners">Co-Innovating with Customers and Partners</h2>
  <p>As part of its co-innovation model, SAP has worked closely with numerous customers and partners to test SAP Sustainability Control Tower during development to ensure it meets market requirements and is focused on users’ needs. Customer feedback is continually used to improve the product and adapt the road map to customer priorities. Partnerships with BCG, Deloitte, EY, and PwC will help reinforce SAP’s strong value proposition to its customers on ESG reporting and climate compliance.</p>
  <p>SAP has long been committed to fully integrating sustainability into its strategy and business model, and <a href="/2021/12/sap-achieves-top-scores-dow-jones-sustainability-index-and-cdp-carbon-disclosure-project">recently achieved top scores</a> as an ESG leader by the Carbon Disclosure Project (CDP) and Dow Jones Sustainability Indices (DJSI). It is only natural, therefore, for the company to apply SAP Sustainability Control Tower in its own operations.</p>
  <p>“At SAP, we believe in managing business success holistically and have been reporting on our financial, social, and environmental performance in one <a href="http://www.sapintegratedreport.com/">integrated report</a> since 2012,” says Daniel Schmid, SAP’s chief sustainability officer. “We are excited about being an early adopter of SAP Sustainability Control Tower, which will help us further simplify and automate our reporting processes by enabling us to integrate financial and pre-financial data on an ongoing basis. Based on the insights derived from the combined data we can manage and steer the company performance while minimizing manual processes.”</p>
  <p>SAP Sustainability Control Tower is one of numerous sustainability solutions SAP released in 2021. In November, the company introduced <a href="/2021/11/sap-responsible-design-and-production-accelerate-circular-economy">SAP Responsible Design and Production</a>, a solution for designing products sustainably and transitioning to a circular economy. With <a href="/2021/09/sap-product-footprint-management-redesign-sustainability">SAP Product Footprint Management</a>, introduced in September, companies can gain visibility into carbon footprint data throughout a product’s supply chain, enabling intelligent supply chain decisions that improve sustainability KPIs. This product-related carbon footprint data – collected during production, material sourcing, and transport – can be used by other solutions, such as <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/integrated-business-planning.html">SAP Integrated Business Planning for Supply Chain</a>.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/climate-21</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Integrating Climate Action End to End]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/integrating-climate-action-end-to-end</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/integrating-climate-action-end-to-end</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn how SAP is tackling climate action by embedding sustainability into its portfolio and across its purpose, strategy, and operations.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10563aea73452ab4df96f0b3c9ac9b08a7bf73965.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10563aea73452ab4df96f0b3c9ac9b08a7bf73965.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_10563aea73452ab4df96f0b3c9ac9b08a7bf73965.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Integrating Climate Action End to End" src="./media_10563aea73452ab4df96f0b3c9ac9b08a7bf73965.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="integrating-climate-action-end-to-end">Integrating Climate Action End to End</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>The climate emergency has reached a new peak. To help accelerate the transformation toward a low-carbon, circular future, SAP is embedding sustainability end to end in its portfolio, as well as across its purpose, vision, strategy, and business operations.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Climate change is widespread, rapid, and intensifying, with some trends now irreversible, according to the recent <a href="https://www.ipcc.ch/report/ar6/wg1/">6th Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change (IPCC) report</a>.</p>
  <p>The science is clear: unless immediate, fast, and large-scale action is taken to reduce emissions, the average global temperature is likely to reach, or cross, the 1.5° C warming threshold within 20 years. The alarming results are already with us, ranging from droughts and heat waves to wildfires and devastating flooding worldwide.</p>
  <p>While much hope is focused on a green recovery, the window of opportunity is closing fast. The latest report from the International Energy Agency (IEA) predicts that energy-related <a href="https://www.iea.org/reports/global-energy-review-2021/co2-emissions">carbon emissions are on course to surge again by 1.5 billion tons in 2021</a>, an increase of nearly 5% year-over-year and the second-largest in history, taking us back to pre-COVID-19 peak levels.</p>
  <p>The urgency to dramatically change course and accelerate decarbonization has never been higher. But only when businesses are moving beyond their siloed approaches, commitments, and climate pledges to fully embrace sustainability and embed these ambitions in an integrated way will we be able to drive the systemic change needed.</p>
  <p>It is a journey toward embedding sustainability across everything we do.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="register-today-for-the-upcoming-sap-sustainability-day">Register today for the upcoming SAP Sustainability Day</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://events.sap.com/sap-sustainability-summit/en/home">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="moving-away-from-add-on-to-core">Moving Away From Add-On to Core</h2>
  <p>Companies need to avoid thinking of sustainability as only an add-on to their strategies and operations. They need to integrate it across the business. Rather than defining a separate sustainability strategy, it is crucial to <a href="https://insights.sap.com/environmental-sustainability-affects-competitiveness/">set a corporate business strategy that is sustainable</a>.</p>
  <p>A first step toward SAP realizing this was linking sustainability to our purpose of helping the world run better and improving people’s lives. The objective: create positive economic, environmental, and social impact within <a href="https://stockholmresilience.org/research/planetary-boundaries.html">planetary boundaries</a> with special focus on climate action, circular economy, social responsibility, and holistic steering and reporting.</p>
  <p>This is reflected not only in the updated SAP vision to “reinvent how the world runs as a network of intelligent, sustainable enterprises,” but also in the executive compensation that rewards Executive Board members for customer loyalty, employee commitment, and SAP’s carbon impact, along with financial performance.</p>
  <h2 id="enabling-climate-action-through-technology">Enabling Climate Action Through Technology</h2>
  <p>The IPCC report has once again highlighted that harnessing the innovation power of enterprises has to be at the center of fighting climate change. For SAP, this means using digitalization to contribute to the United Nations Sustainable Development Goals (UN SDGs), <a href="https://www.sap.com/dmc/exp/2021-04-74301-unglobalgoals/Climate_Action">including #13, Climate Action</a>.</p>
  <p>In collaboration with customers and partners, SAP is working to optimize material, financial, and energy flows throughout end-to-end business processes in order to address planetary and social challenges. For example, <a href="/2020/06/climate-21-track-greenhouse-gas-emissions">the company’s multi-year Climate 21 program</a> helps build analytical and transactional capabilities into enterprise applications that can help SAP customers understand and minimize the greenhouse gas footprint of their products and operations along their value chains.</p>
  <p>During the <a href="https://events.sap.com/sap-sustainability-summit/en/home">SAP Sustainability Summit</a> in April, <a href="/2021/06/sapphire-now-sustainability-management-by-sap">sustainability management by SAP</a> was introduced, providing an expanded portfolio of sustainability-specific solutions, including <a href="/2021/09/sap-product-footprint-management-launch">SAP Product Footprint Management</a>, which has been available since September 2021. There is more to come with the releases of the <a href="https://blogs.sap.com/2021/05/21/helping-business-thrive-in-a-circular-economy/">SAP Responsible Design and Production</a> and SAP Sustainability Control Tower solutions in the next months, as will be shown during <a href="https://events.sap.com/sap-sustainability-summit/en/home">SAP Sustainability Day October 28</a></p>
  <p><a href="https://sap.io/">SAP.iO</a> Foundries locations Berlin and Munich are fostering startup innovation by setting up the <a href="/2021/03/sapio-sustainable-future-cohort-accenture">Sustainable Future program</a> together with Accenture. The equity-free program is designed to propel digital transformation in four target areas: carbon tracking and trading, resource efficiency, climate risk tracking and mitigation, and circular economy.</p>
  <h2 id="setting-ambitious-targets">Setting Ambitious Targets</h2>
  <p>In addition to harnessing innovation, the climate emergency calls for bold targets for decarbonization. By mid-2021, countries representing around 65% of global carbon dioxide emissions and more than 70% of the world economy have made ambitious commitments to carbon neutrality. The U.S, the European Union, Japan, the Republic of Korea, and others — in total 126 countries — have pledged carbon neutrality by 2050; China says it will do so before 2060.</p>
  <p>The private sector also needs to step up. More than 1,900 companies, including SAP in 2017, have set emissions reduction targets grounded in climate science through the <a href="https://sciencebasedtargets.org/about-the-science-based-targets-initiative/">Science Based Targets initiative</a>.</p>
  <p>In 2019, SAP raised its commitment and adopted a <a href="/2019/07/sap-emissions-reduction-targets">1.5° C science-based emissions reduction targets</a> aligned with a net-zero future. However, the journey started much earlier; back in 2009, SAP set the first goal of reducing its global carbon emissions to the year-2000 level by 2020. <a href="/2018/03/sap-integrated-report-2020-targets-met-early">This target was met at the end of 2017</a>, even though SAP grew more than fourfold over the period.</p>
  <p>The next milestone is 2023, when SAP aims to be <a href="/2021/03/sap-carbon-neutrality-goal-2023">carbon neutral in its own operations</a> – two years earlier than previously envisaged. This includes all direct (Scope 1), indirect (Scope 2), and selected categories of value chain (Scope 3) carbon emissions, such as business flights, employee commuting, paper consumption, and external data centers (co-locations and hyperscalers).</p>
  <h2 id="monitoring-and-reporting">Monitoring and Reporting</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="chasing-zero-the-future-can-be-greener-cleaner-and-more-equal">Chasing Zero: The future can be greener, cleaner, and more equal</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/purpose-and-sustainability.html#chasing-zero">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>It is essential to measure and monitor progress on the path toward achieving these targets. For example, SAP has increasingly embraced holistic steering and reporting because connecting financial and pre-financial performance leads to better management decisions and business success.</p>
  <p>SAP’s sustainability and annual reports were merged into the <a href="http://www.sapintegratedreport.com">SAP Integrated Report</a> in 2012. Since then, both material and immaterial value creation have been at the center of the company’s reporting and have been placed on an equal footing. Besides key financial information, environmental progress, workforce information, and social investments have been made transparent. In addition, an internal sustainability dashboard allows employees to explore the key sustainability key performance indicators (KPIs), such as women in management and carbon emissions by their country, location, and line of business, with updates every quarter.</p>
  <p>Our reporting shows that in 2020, SAP was able to overachieve by 43% on its target for net carbon emissions in 2020, generating 135 kilotons instead of the anticipated 238 kilotons. This trend continued in the first half of 2021, during which SAP’s carbon emissions totaled 45 kilotons compared to 90 kilotons in the first half of 2020 (-37%).</p>
  <p>The low emissions level is a consequence of the ongoing <a href="/covid-19">COVID-19</a> pandemic, as well as the introduction of <a href="/2021/06/pledge-to-flex-future-of-work-at-sap">Pledge to Flex</a>, which enables a more flexible mix of remote and onsite work. SAP believes this trend will continue and has just announced in its <a href="https://www.sap.com/docs/download/investors/2021/sap-2021-half-year-report.pdf">2021 half-year report</a> that it has lowered its 2021 carbon emissions outlook from 145 kilotons to a range of 90-110 kilotons.</p>
  <h2 id="taking-action-measures-of-implementation">Taking Action: Measures of Implementation</h2>
  <p>To become <a href="/2017/05/sap-to-go-carbon-neutral-by-2025">carbon neutral in its own operations by 202</a>3, SAP is following a three-pillar approach: <strong>avoid</strong>, <strong>reduce</strong>, <strong>compensate</strong>.</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Avoid:</strong> Whenever possible, SAP aims to avoid the creation of greenhouse gases. This is a top priority, supported by, for example, using virtual telecommunication instead of business flights.</li>
    <li><strong>Reduce:</strong> If greenhouse gas emissions cannot be avoided, SAP aims to drive efficiency and reduce all types of emissions; for example, building efficiency, data center operations, carpooling and car sharing, and e-mobility.</li>
    <li><strong>Compensate:</strong> SAP has extended its compensation models for travel. For business flights, it has introduced an internal carbon price to offset related carbon emissions. If greenhouse gas emissions cannot be eliminated altogether, SAP aims to reduce them through innovations in the areas of building efficiency, data center operations, carpooling, and car sharing, as well as e-mobility. For example, SAP has powered its own data centers and facilities with 100% renewable electricity since 2014, implemented an environmental management system with ISO 14001 certification in more than 30 countries and ISO 50001 at headquarters, adopting green IT initiatives in order to foster sustainable IT equipment usage and promoting tools such as <a href="https://www.ecosia.org/">Ecosia</a> as a default search engine.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>In 2020, SAP implemented additional energy and climate measures within its operations, ranging from opening a new office with energy-efficient design in Australia and implementing more efficient data center technology in Germany to introducing a bike fleet at SAP Hungary as well as a flexible mobility budget in Germany and installation of photovoltaic systems in Austria.</p>
  <p>For emissions that cannot yet be reduced or avoided, SAP thirdly invests in high-quality carbon credits. For example, <a href="/2020/08/sap-lcf-investment-livelihoods-carbon-funds">SAP has been a long-term investor of the Livelihoods Carbon Funds (LCF) since 2012</a>. SAP has also donated funds to restore ecosystems and improve people’s lives. In support of the UN Decade on Ecosystem Restoration 2021-2030, SAP recently joined the 1t.org corporate alliance, which aims to conserve, restore, and grow trees worldwide, with a <a href="/2021/07/enhancing-sustainability-people-technology-21-million-trees">pledge to plant 21 million trees by the end of 2025</a>.</p>
  <p>I am proud that SAP’s efforts to combat climate change and to strengthen its transparent reporting are <a href="/2021/01/corporate-knights-cdp-sap-top-esg-ratings">externally recognized</a>. The non-profit organization CDP included SAP on its <a href="https://www.cdp.net/en/companies/companies-scores?cid=9205306762&#x26;adgpid=95799580520&#x26;itemid=&#x26;targid=kwd-870315494871&#x26;mt=b&#x26;loc=9041983&#x26;ntwk=g&#x26;dev=c&#x26;dmod=&#x26;adp=&#x26;gclid=EAIaIQobChMIxpSS4e_Z7gIVjLh3Ch2xkAciEAAYASAAEgLpJPD_BwE">A List 2020</a>, thereby granting us the top rating for leading in environmental transparency and action.</p>
  <h2 id="partnering">Partnering</h2>
  <p>SAP recognizes that strong partnerships are an invaluable asset in tackling climate change. This is why we became a founding member of the European Green Digital Coalition and joined the World Economic Forum Stakeholder Capitalism Coalition and CEO Climate Leaders as well as the World Business Council for Sustainable Development (WBCSD), complementing our previous engagements with the UN Global Compact, the We Mean Business Coalition, the Value Balancing Alliance, the Ellen MacArthur Foundation, and many more.</p>
  <p>In addition, we signed the <a href="https://eur01.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.wemeanbusinesscoalition.org%2Fg20-2021%2F&#x26;data=04%7C01%7Cpreeti.srivastav%40eu.asahibeer.com%7C6b7d2eeaddaf447c6e2e08d97822af12%7C7ef011f8898a4d0182329087b2c2abaf%7C0%7C0%7C637672913526232765%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJWIjoiMC4wLjAwMDAiLCJQIjoiV2luMzIiLCJBTiI6Ik1haWwiLCJXVCI6Mn0%3D%7C3000&#x26;sdata=jX%2BiZ7Ipm3Wm9sXEgD6AbZ%2BWKk%2B4sePJIfTDXi7qNEI%3D&#x26;reserved=0">business letter to the G20</a> calling for greater climate ambition and we launched <a href="/topics/chasing-zero">Chasing Zero</a>, a new initiative that will feature executive thought leadership, best practices, and insights into a sustainability-related transformation of SAP and its global ecosystem to achieve zero emissions, zero waste, and zero inequality. The transition to a circular economy remains central to our vision for a world of zero waste and plastic free oceans by 2030. Consequently, we support stronger circular economy policies, such as the Worldwide Fund for Nature’s OneSource Coalition and the Ellen MacArthur Foundation’s Extended Producer Responsibility endorsement.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Daniel Schmid is chief sustainability officer of SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/climate-21</category>
            <category>product/sap-product-footprint-management</category>
            <category>product/sap-responsible-design-and-production</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
            <category>news-tag/un-sdgs</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Navigating Climate Change with Supply Chain]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/climate-change-and-supply-chain</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/climate-change-and-supply-chain</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[When it comes to climate change and supply chain, the private sector is waking up. Learn how SAP software supports sustainability efforts.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/climate-21</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Decarbonization Depends on the Data]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/06/decarbonization-depends-on-data</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/06/decarbonization-depends-on-data</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn how digitalization, data transparency, and collaborative action are key to meeting decarbonization targets in the automotive industry.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10d619ba9f35d98eba2a2b782fbc8fb3ca9f169de.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10d619ba9f35d98eba2a2b782fbc8fb3ca9f169de.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_10d619ba9f35d98eba2a2b782fbc8fb3ca9f169de.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Decarbonization Depends on the Data" src="./media_10d619ba9f35d98eba2a2b782fbc8fb3ca9f169de.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="decarbonization-depends-on-the-data">Decarbonization Depends on the Data</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>The race to zero carbon emissions among car manufacturers <a href="http://www.automobilsport.com/cars-tuning--37,222545,Way-to-Zero-Volkswagen-presents-roadmap-for-climate-neutral-mobility,news.htm">is in full swing</a>. Earlier this month, the world’s largest producer, Volkswagen Group (VW), indicated it would <a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/volkswagen-electric-emissions/insight-how-low-can-you-go-volkswagen-throws-down-the-emissions-gauntlet-idUSL1N2ML25I">support more ambitious CO2 emissions targets</a>, catching European rivals off guard and putting them under pressure to follow suit.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>But the race to “net zero” for the automobile industry is still in the first lap, and the route promises to be long and arduous. Greenhouse gas emissions from the industry account for more than 9% of global emissions – equaling those of the entire European Union. To achieve their individual sustainability targets, companies are dependent on each other for reliable and verifiable data.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="is-your-company-chasing-zero-learn-more">Is your company Chasing Zero? Learn more.</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="http://sap.com/ChasingZero">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="decarbonization-is-all-about-the-data">Decarbonization Is All About the Data</h2>
  <p>Becoming carbon neutral requires managing the carbon footprint of individual products in the supply chain, and to achieve this companies need transparency into the carbon footprints of their upstream suppliers – referred to as <a href="https://ghgprotocol.org/sites/default/files/standards_supporting/FAQ.pdf">scope 3 emissions</a>. The problem is that only 21% of business executives are satisfied with the quality of their environmental data, <a href="/2021/04/sustainability-study-from-sap-actions-challenges">according to a global research study from SAP</a>.</p>
  <p>But more accurate carbon footprint data is on the way. “Until now, companies have been using averages to calculate carbon footprint at a product level because there’s been a lack of accurate, granular emissions data and no consistent methodology,” said John Revess, director Net Zero Transformation at the World Business Council for Sustainable Development (WBCSD). “To remain a part of global supply chains, it will be necessary for companies to accurately calculate the carbon footprint of their products based on measured values,” predicted Revess. As a member of WBCSD, SAP and other companies are defining a <a href="https://www.wbcsd.org/Programs/Climate-and-Energy/Climate/SOS-1.5/Resources/Value-Chain-Carbon-Transparency-Pathfinder-Enabling-decarbonization-through-Scope-3-emissions-transparency">Value Chain Carbon Transparency Pathfinder</a> for the exchange of carbon emissions data.</p>
  <p>“To meet our decarbonization goals, we depend on credible data from our suppliers on the carbon footprints of the components we build our vehicles with,” said Ralf Pfitzner, global head of Sustainability at Volkswagen, at the <a href="https://events.sap.com/sap-sustainability-summit/en/home">SAP Sustainability Summit</a>.</p>
  <p>The two-day online meeting focused on how companies are applying new technologies to reduce their environmental footprint and manage limited resources. “We decided to join SAP in the co-innovation of a digital carbon tracking tool and database, and this is really exciting because there is obviously a demand,” said Pfitzner.</p>
  <p>Volkswagen and SAP are working together toward decarbonization in other ways. In 2020, their CEOs Herbert Diess and Christian Klein joined the <a href="https://www.volkswagenag.com/en/news/2021/03/European-CEO-Alliance-advocates-for-ambitious-climate-strategy.html#:~:text=The%20CEO%20Alliance%20considers%20itself,chain%20and%20rapid%20build%2Dup">CEO Alliance for Europe’s Recovery, Reform, and Resilience</a>. The Alliance’s 10 European business leaders have committed 100 billion to decarbonizing their companies and products and are calling for far-reaching climate protection measures.</p>
  <h2 id="massive-investments-necessary-in-electrification-and-digitalization">Massive Investments Necessary in Electrification and Digitalization</h2>
  <p>VW is <a href="https://www.volkswagen-newsroom.com/en/press-releases/volkswagen-group-raises-investments-in-future-technologies-to-eur-73-billion-6607">investing a hefty €73 billion</a> to help put its decarbonization challenges in the rear-view mirror. The underlying reasons for <a href="/2021/04/sustainability-study-from-sap-actions-challenges">companies’ investments in environmental issues</a> varies, spanning industry regulations (29%) to society’s approval of their organization (27%) and strengthening company reputation (26%). Uncertainty as to how to embed sustainability into business processes and IT systems is seen as the greatest barrier to implementing plans for action, <a href="/2021/04/sustainability-study-from-sap-actions-challenges">one study concludes</a>.</p>
  <p>Despite the challenges, VW’s Pfitzner is optimistic about achieving the company’s decarbonization targets. VW’s head of sustainability expects digitalization to play a major role in this transformation. “Beyond green electricity, there are plenty of opportunities where digitalization will help us reduce our carbon footprint, for example by hooking the manufacturing data into the cloud and having more efficient programming of robots,” he said.</p>
  <p>Pfitzner reiterated <a href="https://www.volkswagenag.com/en/news/stories/2019/12/what-volkswagen-is-doing-for-the-environment.html">VW’s 2050 goal of carbon neutrality</a> along the entire lifecycle of its cars, emphasizing the need for intermediate milestones. “The coming decades will be essential for the transformation of transport and the car industry. By 2030, we intend to reduce the lifecycle carbon footprint of our passenger car portfolio by 30% compared to 2018,” said Pfitzner.</p>
  <h2 id="no-carbon-neutrality-in-isolation">No Carbon Neutrality in Isolation</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sustainability-actions-still-challenging-to-implement-according-to-new-study-from-sap">Sustainability Actions Still Challenging to Implement, According to New Study from SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/04/sustainability-study-from-sap-actions-challenges">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Although nearly two-thirds of the global economy is covered by net zero targets, achieving them will require systems thinking and collaborative action among businesses of a type and scale that has never been done before, <a href="https://www2.deloitte.com/uk/en/pages/press-releases/articles/deloitte-announces-senior-partner-appointments-in-climate-change-and-transport.html">said Hannah Routh</a>, partner, Deloitte UK. “The proof will be in the implementation,” she predicted.</p>
  <p>“No business or country can become net zero in isolation,” said Routh. “Whether you are looking at energy supply, transportation, infrastructure, government, or communities, they all need to act in a coordinated way.”</p>
  <p>One of the biggest challenges for companies, says Routh, is embedding climate transformation into their business strategies and decision-making processes. This requires data transparency, she emphasizes, noting that there is no shortage of data, but the quality and usability of the data must be ensured.</p>
  <p>Nicolas Peter, BMW’s chief financial officer, agrees. “Digitalization helps in a significant way to increase data quality, and, from an auditor’s perspective, data quality is key in order to perform his responsibility in the audit process,” he said at SAP’s Sustainability Summit. Peter left no doubts that BMW is counting on new technologies to help it <a href="https://www.wemeanbusinesscoalition.org/blog/bmw-joins-growing-list-of-automakers-committed-to-bold-climate-action/">achieve its climate targets</a>: “The trend to sustainability has to be accompanied by digitalization. There is no alternative,” said Peter.</p>
  <h2 id="digitalization-supports-decarbonization">Digitalization Supports Decarbonization</h2>
  <p>“CEOs need transparency into their supply chains,” said Thomas Saueressig, head of Product Engineering and member of the Executive Board of SAP SE. “Through its strategic initiative <a href="https://community.sap.com/topics/sustainability/climate21">Climate 21</a>, SAP is launching new solutions that help customers reduce their emissions and manage their carbon footprint.”</p>
  <p>A new integrated set of solutions announced at the SAP Sustainability Summit includes SAP Product Footprint Management, which treats greenhouse gases like a ‘currency’ in the value chain. “Our sustainability management solutions enable companies not only to optimize their production facilities according to top line and bottom line, but also according to greenhouse gas emissions,” said Saueressig. As part of several joint sustainability initiatives with Accenture, <a href="/2021/04/sap-and-accenture-sustainability-better-business">SAP and Accenture are working</a> to develop new SAP solutions that address sustainability and enhance existing core technologies.</p>
  <h2 id="the-need-for-speed">The Need for Speed</h2>
  <p>Setting data quality issues aside, the most important factor for transforming businesses to net-zero is speed, said Deloitte’s Routh. “I think the world can master this, but my concern is whether it can do it quickly enough. The businesses that are going to succeed are the ones that understand and embrace the urgency.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/automotive</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-emissions</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-footprint</category>
            <category>news-tag/chasing-zero</category>
            <category>news-tag/climate-21</category>
            <category>news-tag/climate-change</category>
            <category>news-tag/economics</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sustainability Management by SAP: Enabling Tomorrow Starts Today]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/06/sapphire-now-sustainability-management-by-sap</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/06/sapphire-now-sustainability-management-by-sap</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Sustainability management by SAP supports organizations on the journey to becoming sustainable enterprises. Read the news from SAPPHIRE NOW.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/circular-economy</category>
            <category>news-tag/climate-21</category>
            <category>product/sap-product-footprint-management</category>
            <category>product/sap-responsible-design-and-production</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
            <category>news-tag/un-sdgs</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP and Accenture Join Forces to Help Enterprises Become More Sustainable]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/sap-accenture-more-sustainable-enterprises</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/sap-accenture-more-sustainable-enterprises</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In support of more sustainable enterprises, Accenture and SAP are expanding their partnership to help companies unlock new value and grow.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_111fc2de51a7c6d48aca6568d9f8dd292604349ae.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_111fc2de51a7c6d48aca6568d9f8dd292604349ae.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_111fc2de51a7c6d48aca6568d9f8dd292604349ae.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP and Accenture Join Forces to Help Enterprises Become More Sustainable" src="./media_111fc2de51a7c6d48aca6568d9f8dd292604349ae.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-and-accenture-join-forces-to-help-enterprises-become-more-sustainable">SAP and Accenture Join Forces to Help Enterprises Become More Sustainable</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><em>Where there’s a will, there’s a way</em>. This proverb dating back to the 1600s could not be more appropriate today as enterprises around the world grapple with the biggest business challenge of our lifetimes: creating a sustainable future.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Unsurprisingly, many companies are daunted by the seemingly insurmountable challenges, so SAP and Accenture are taking action to help them.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="catch-up-on-the-virtual-sap-sustainability-summit">Catch up on the virtual SAP Sustainability Summit</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://events.sap.com/sap-sustainability-summit/en/home">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="the-right-time">The Right Time</h2>
  <p>By now, we all know we must radically change the way businesses run, our impact on the environment, and the inequalities in society. That’s the only way to ensure a lifestyle that allows us to meet our current needs without compromising the ability of future generations to meet theirs.</p>
  <p>The signs are everywhere. Consumers are increasingly aware about the negative environmental impact of products and services, such as fast fashion, single-use plastics, food waste, and excessive packaging. They are demanding accountability and responsible business models from their favorite brands. Governments are increasing regulations around carbon emissions and waste management and are demanding manufacturers to take responsibility for their impact on the environment.</p>
  <p>Enterprises are under pressure from investors to include their environmental, societal, and governance (ESG) factors in their financial performance reports. And finally, employees are increasingly vocal about the environmental policies and actions of their employers. Businesses know they need to act, but few are rising to the challenge.</p>
  <p>A study by Accenture found while the United Nations (UN) Global Compact’s Sustainable Development Goal (SDG) program has challenged companies to enhance their commitment to the UN SDGs, only 25% have set goals aligned to societal or environmental needs. Although CEOs acknowledge the universal call-to-action to achieve a better and more sustainable future for all, less than 50% have implemented sustainability into their operations.</p>
  <h2 id="the-challenge">The Challenge</h2>
  <p>As a survey of business drivers and actions to improve the environment at planetary scale conducted by SAP Insights revealed there are numerous barriers. Almost 7,500 CEOs and other business leaders from 16 industries around the globe participated in the survey. The top three reasons they cited for not moving ahead were lack of clarity on how to embed sustainability in business processes and IT systems, lack of clarity on how potential actions would align with strategy, and difficulty proving return on investment. Other factors include lack of funding, lack of expertise, or lack of support from senior management.</p>
  <p>The challenges are daunting, which is why solving sustainability issues is not something individual corporations or governments can do alone. The way ahead involves <a href="https://insights.sap.com/government-business-civil-society-fast-track-circularity/">cooperation and collaboration</a>. In this decade of delivery, partnerships are crucial.</p>
  <h2 id="a-will-and-a-way">A Will and a Way</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-the-news-accenture-and-sap-extend-partnership-to-help-companies-lead-in-the-circular-economy">Read the news: Accenture and SAP Extend Partnership to Help Companies Lead in the Circular Economy</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/04/accenture-sap-partnership-accelerate-sustainability">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Accenture and SAP, for example, <a href="/2021/04/accenture-sap-partnership-accelerate-sustainability">have just announced they are expanding their long-term engagement</a> to help companies embed sustainability across the full spectrum of their business operations. This will help unlock new value and realize long-term growth.</p>
  <p>By combining SAP technology with Accenture’s <a href="http://www.accenture.com/sustainabilityservices">Sustainability Services</a>, the partners plan to jointly create new solutions that can empower companies to accelerate their progress on decarbonizing their supply chains and capture their share of the projected $4.5 trillion economic growth that the <a href="https://www.palgrave.com/us/book/9781349959679">circular economy could bring</a>.</p>
  <p>Together, Accenture and SAP will develop the new SAP Responsible Production and Design solution, which will help companies consume fewer resources and build sustainability within the design process. It will also enable companies to apply analytics to the operational, asset, and process data collected across the value chain. Such an integrated view will help them determine clear sustainability goals and metrics across business processes.</p>
  <p>As a result, companies will be able to reduce the costs of compliance and extended producer responsibility (EPR) regulation by designing and producing products with <a href="https://insights.sap.com/circularity-creates-value-from-waste/">more recycled content and less waste</a>.</p>
  <p>Accenture also supports SAP’s <a href="https://community.sap.com/topics/climate21">Climate 21</a> initiative, which allows companies in any industry to use analytics to measure and minimize carbon dioxide (CO<sub>2</sub>) emissions and lower the carbon footprint across the product life cycle. Adding sustainability metrics across the supply chain provides an integrated view of environmental savings and helps optimize operations.</p>
  <p>This type of co-innovation could help solve some of the barriers cited in the SAP Insights survey. Embedding sustainability in business processes and IT systems and measuring return on investment (ROI) gives enterprises a better understanding of how to fund their sustainability efforts. With time and success companies can gain expertise, set aside funds, and engage senior leadership to support their sustainability journey.</p>
  <h2 id="call-to-action">Call to Action</h2>
  <p>The Accenture study identifies three things leaders anywhere in any industry can do to start implementing and scaling plans of action to address climate change, social inequalities, and resource availability.</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Raise ambition and impact:</strong> Leaders must drive change in their own organizations, and through the disruption of market systems.</li>
    <li><strong>Change collaboration:</strong> Key players must connect in new ways because meaningful transformation is not a solo sport.</li>
    <li><strong>Redefine responsible leadership:</strong> Leaders must embrace their role as change agents to champion the sustainability agenda.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>To learn more about the SAP and Accenture partnership for a sustainable future, join the virtual <a href="https://events.sap.com/sap-sustainability-summit/en/home">SAP Sustainability Summit</a>, taking place April 28-29. The event will focus on how companies are reducing their environmental footprints and managing limited resources productively while steering and reporting their businesses holistically.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Follow me on Twitter: <a href="https://twitter.com/magyarj">@magyarj</a></em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/accenture</category>
            <category>news-tag/circular-economy</category>
            <category>news-tag/climate-21</category>
            <category>news-tag/climate-change</category>
            <category>news-tag/un-sdgs</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Joins World Business Council for Sustainable Development to Innovate in Global Decarbonization Effort]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/sap-joins-wbcsd-global-decarbonization</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/sap-joins-wbcsd-global-decarbonization</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP has joined the World Business Council for Sustainable Development (WBCSD) as innovation partner. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_12e52ba8efa72574cf8018a601d2f5c6afab9e93a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_12e52ba8efa72574cf8018a601d2f5c6afab9e93a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_12e52ba8efa72574cf8018a601d2f5c6afab9e93a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Joins World Business Council for Sustainable Development to Innovate in Global Decarbonization Effort" src="./media_12e52ba8efa72574cf8018a601d2f5c6afab9e93a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-joins-world-business-council-for-sustainable-development-to-innovate-in-global-decarbonization-effort">SAP Joins World Business Council for Sustainable Development to Innovate in Global Decarbonization Effort</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="catch-up-on-the-virtual-sap-sustainability-summit">Catch up on the virtual SAP Sustainability Summit</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://events.sap.com/sap-sustainability-summit/en/home">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced it has joined the <a href="http://www.wbcsd.org">World Business Council for Sustainable Development (WBCSD)</a> as an innovation partner in <a href="https://www.wbcsd.org/Programs/Climate-and-Energy/Climate/SOS-1.5/News/WBCSD-launches-new-Pathfinder-to-enable-Scope-3-emissions-transparency-and-accelerate-decarbonization">WBCSD’s Value Chain Carbon Transparency Pathfinder</a>.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The initiative is dedicated to enhancing transparency in corporate carbon emissions with the objective to ultimately decarbonize supply chains. The announcement was made at the <a href="https://events.sap.com/sap-sustainability-summit/en/home">SAP Sustainability Summit</a> virtual event.</p>
  <p>The membership accelerates SAP’s momentum in sustainability leadership and innovation. Last year, SAP announced <a href="/2020/06/sapphire-now-innovations-supply-chain-industry-sustainability">the Climate 21 program</a> to help companies understand, minimize and disclose the full carbon footprints of their products and services.</p>
  <p>“We are supporting businesses of all sizes and industries in determining the carbon footprint across their operations and supply chains down to the individual product level by embedding the corresponding capabilities into our core enterprise software systems,” said Christian Klein, CEO and member of the Executive Board of SAP SE. “By partnering with WBCSD and other forward-thinking companies, we will jointly find new ways to collect and share product carbon footprint data with their customers and consumers, which will give them a real competitive advantage while accelerating global decarbonization efforts.”</p>
  <p>WBCSD is a global, CEO-led organization dedicated to accelerating the transition to a sustainable world. At the core of the network are its six work programs, including climate, energy and circular economy, which focus on helping realize the Sustainable Development Goals (SDGs) set by the United Nations General Assembly in 2015. WBCSD invites businesses, standards-setting bodies, technology experts and other decarbonization initiatives to join the Carbon Transparency Pathfinder in helping develop an effective model to help decarbonize industry through data transparency.</p>
  <p>“We’re glad to be counting on SAP’s support, drive and expertise across our programs and projects – especially in the Carbon Transparency Pathfinder, which is a perfect initiative for SAP because their software and data management solutions are used by many of the world’s largest companies to run complex supply chain and manufacturing operations,” said Peter Bakker, president and CEO, WBCSD. “We look forward to innovating with SAP and other members to make real, tangible progress on sustainable development and climate action for a more sustainable world in line with the recently released <a href="http://www.timetotransform.biz">Vision 2050</a>.”</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP on Twitter at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <p>Visit <a href="http://www.wbcsd.org">WBCSD</a>. Follow WBCSD on <a href="https://twitter.com/wbcsd">Twitter</a> and <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/wbcsd">LinkedIn</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>About WBCSD</strong></p>
  <p>WBCSD is a global, CEO-led organization of over 200 leading businesses working together to accelerate the transition to a sustainable world. We help make our member companies more successful and sustainable by focusing on the maximum positive impact for shareholders, the environment and societies. Their member companies come from all business sectors and all major economies, representing a combined revenue of more than USD $8.5 trillion and 19 million employees. Their global network of almost 70 national business councils gives our members unparalleled reach across the globe. Since 1995, WBCSD has been uniquely positioned to work with member companies along and across value chains to deliver impactful business solutions to the most challenging sustainability issues. The organization is a leading voice of business for sustainability, united by a vision of a world where more than 9 billion people are all living well, within planetary boundaries, by 2050. <a href="http://www.wbcsd.org">www.wbcsd.org</a></p>
  <p><strong>About SAP</strong></p>
  <p>SAP’s strategy is to help every business run as an intelligent enterprise. As a market leader in enterprise application software, we help companies of all sizes and in all industries run at their best: 77% of the world’s transaction revenue touches an SAP system. Our machine learning, Internet of Things (IoT), and advanced analytics technologies help turn customers’ businesses into intelligent enterprises. SAP helps give people and organizations deep business insight and fosters collaboration that helps them stay ahead of their competition. We simplify technology for companies so they can consume our software the way they want – without disruption. Our end-to-end suite of applications and services enables business and public customers across 25 industries globally to operate profitably, adapt continuously, and make a difference. With a global network of customers, partners, employees, and thought leaders, SAP helps the world run better and improve people’s lives. For more information, visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/">www.sap.com</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Note to editors:</strong><br>To preview and download broadcast-standard stock footage and press photos digitally, please visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/photos">www.sap.com/photos</a>. On this platform, you can find high resolution material for your media channels. To view video stories on diverse topics, visit <a href="http://www.sap-tv.com">www.sap-tv.com</a>. From this site, you can embed videos into your own Web pages, share video via email links, and subscribe to RSS feeds from SAP TV.</p>
  <p><strong>For customers interested in learning more about SAP products:</strong><br>Global Customer Center: +49 180 534-34-24<br>United States Only: 1 (800) 872-1SAP (1-800-872-1727)</p>
  <p><strong>For more information, press only:</strong><br>Bettina Wunderle, +49 7544 970 538, <a href="mailto:bettina.wunderle@sap.com">bettina.wunderle@sap.com</a>, CET<br>Stacy Ries, +1 (484) 619-0411, <a href="mailto:stacy.ries@sap.com">stacy.ries@sap.com</a>, ET<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>Any statements contained in this document that are not historical facts are forward-looking statements as defined in the U.S. Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995. Words such as “anticipate,” “believe,” “estimate,” “expect,” “forecast,” “intend,” “may,” “plan,” “project,” “predict,” “should” and “will” and similar expressions as they relate to SAP are intended to identify such forward-looking statements. SAP undertakes no obligation to publicly update or revise any forward-looking statements. All forward-looking statements are subject to various risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results to differ materially from expectations. The factors that could affect SAP’s future financial results are discussed more fully in SAP’s filings with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (“SEC”), including SAP’s most recent Annual Report on Form 20-F filed with the SEC. Readers are cautioned not to place undue reliance on these forward-looking statements, which speak only as of their dates.<br>© 2021 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.<br>Please consider our <a href="https://www.sap.com/corporate/en/legal/privacy.html">privacy policy</a>. If you received this press release in your e-mail and you wish to unsubscribe to our mailing list please contact <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a> and write Unsubscribe in the subject line.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/climate-21</category>
            <category>news-tag/un-sdgs</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Accenture and SAP Extend Partnership to Help Companies Accelerate Sustainability Transformation, Drive New Sources of Value and Lead in the Circular Economy]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/accenture-sap-partnership-accelerate-sustainability</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/accenture-sap-partnership-accelerate-sustainability</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[To accelerate sustainability, SAP and Accenture are expanding their decades-long partnership to help companies to unlock new value.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/accenture</category>
            <category>news-tag/circular-economy</category>
            <category>news-tag/climate-21</category>
            <category>news-tag/un-sdgs</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SMEs: Small CO2 Footprint, Big Climate Impact]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/carbon-footprint-of-smes-impact</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/carbon-footprint-of-smes-impact</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Pressure is on to manage the carbon footprint of SMEs, as large companies pass their carbon-neutral goals requirements on.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16dca4aab592023620ed62a1dddbb0779c36d48b4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16dca4aab592023620ed62a1dddbb0779c36d48b4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_16dca4aab592023620ed62a1dddbb0779c36d48b4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SMEs: Small CO2 Footprint, Big Climate Impact" src="./media_16dca4aab592023620ed62a1dddbb0779c36d48b4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="smes-small-co2-footprint-big-climate-impact">SMEs: Small CO2 Footprint, Big Climate Impact</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>More than 90% of the world’s businesses are small and midsize enterprises (SMEs), and their combined CO<sub>2</sub> footprint, while not easily calculated, exceeds that of large enterprises.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The challenge this presents is huge, but so are the rewards. In Europe alone, <a href="https://www.oecd-ilibrary.org/environment/smes-key-drivers-of-green-and-inclusive-growth_8a51fc0c-en">SMEs contribute up to 70% of industrial pollution</a>.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="explore-how-sap-is-working-to-make-sustainability-profitable-and-profitability-sustainable">Explore how SAP is working to make sustainability profitable and profitability sustainable</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/purpose-and-sustainability.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="change-in-the-air">Change in the Air</h2>
  <p>SMEs have <a href="https://www.oecd.org/greengrowth/GGSD_2018_SME%20Issue%20Paper_WEB.pdf">traditionally experienced less environmental scrutiny and regulation</a> compared with large corporations. But change is in the air. Pressure to act is <a href="https://hbr.org/2021/03/what-bidens-sustainability-agenda-means-for-business">is mounting on SMEs</a> as large companies pass their requirements on to suppliers.</p>
  <p>BMW is a case in point. In July 2020, the German auto group <a href="https://www.press.bmwgroup.com/global/article/detail/T0312166EN/no-premium-without-responsibility-bmw-group-makes-sustainability-and-efficient-resource-management">announced CO<sub>2</sub> targets for its supply chain</a> of well over 10,000 suppliers, with the goal of reducing emissions per vehicle produced by at least one-third. The company uses carbon footprint as a criterion for awarding contracts for everything from materials and components to production equipment and tools. “Our aim is to ensure the most sustainable supply chain in the entire industry,” says Oliver Zipse, chairman of the Board of Management at BMW.</p>
  <p>BMW’s German competitor Mercedes-Benz announced that more than 75% of its suppliers are committed to supplying CO₂-neutral parts to help it achieve its 2039 ambition of CO₂ neutrality.</p>
  <p>Other examples of large enterprises that are working with their suppliers to reduce carbon footprint include <a href="https://www.tetrapak.com/sustainability/environmental-impact/suppliers">Tetra Pak</a> and <a href="https://www.basf.com/global/en/who-we-are/sustainability/we-produce-safely-and-efficiently/energy-and-climate-protection/corporate-carbon-footprint.html">BASF</a>. Nearly half of CEOs at large companies are targeting sustainability in their business operations, according to the <a href="https://www.unglobalcompact.org/library/5716">2019 UN Global Compact Progress Report</a>.</p>
  <p>But it is not only the supply chain leaders that are adding climate action to their corporate policies. Increasingly investors, shareholders, consumers, and employees are looking to business to adopt ambitious climate-related targets. Countries, cities, states, and provinces are also adding to the pressure. Over <a href="https://carbonpricingdashboard.worldbank.org/">60 carbon-pricing initiatives have already been implemented</a> or are planned worldwide. National and international regulations may soon require <a href="https://www.environdec.com/about-us/the-international-epd-system-about-the-system">environmental impact information</a> to be provided on product labels and descriptions.</p>
  <h2 id="open-questions-without-adequate-answers">Open Questions Without Adequate Answers</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="information-sheet-manage-your-green-line-with-sap-business-ecology-management">Information sheet: Manage your green line with SAP Business Ecology Management</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2020/11/421f493b-ba7d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Matthias Weigold is familiar with the complex world in which SMEs currently find themselves. The director of the Institute for Production Management, Technology, and Machine Tools (PTW) at the Technical University Darmstadt is partnering with German manufacturers to test scenarios for energy efficiency and flexibility in manufacturing processes based on the availability of renewable energy sources.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1630186fe657cd9b593134d4b9c04f76ee6c49d2d.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1630186fe657cd9b593134d4b9c04f76ee6c49d2d.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1630186fe657cd9b593134d4b9c04f76ee6c49d2d.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Headshot: Matthias Weigold" src="./media_1630186fe657cd9b593134d4b9c04f76ee6c49d2d.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="850" height="800">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p><em>Image courtesy of PTW</em></p>
  <p>“Many SMEs hear their primary customers saying, ‘Do something about your carbon footprint and do it fast.’ They are faced with a mountain of open questions without adequate answers,” he explains. “SMEs also know that if they react too slowly and without the necessary level of detail, they could lose their most valuable customers.”</p>
  <p>To satisfy the demands of their customers for low-carbon production, SMEs will increasingly need to adapt their manufacturing operations to the pricing fluctuations associated with the energy mix of fossil and renewable energy. The scenarios are no longer hypothetical, according to Weigold: “Exceptionally <a href="https://energypost.eu/negative-electricity-prices-lockdowns-demand-slump-exposes-inflexibility-of-german-power/">sunny and windy periods during 2020</a> led wholesale electricity prices to go negative in Germany.”</p>
  <p>Complicating the situation are the myriad national policies and timelines worldwide, says Weigold, who provides an example. “Over 80% of the machine tools made in Germany are exported, with the lion’s share going to manufacturers in China. Now that <a href="https://climateactiontracker.org/climate-target-update-tracker/china/">China has proposed updated targets in December 2020</a>, German SMEs are unsure how they should react.”</p>
  <p>At the <a href="https://eta-fabrik.de/">ETA model factory in Darmstadt</a> which makes it possible to test various production scenarios under real-world conditions, SAP and PTW are modeling enterprise resource planning (ERP) software to the manufacturing environment.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b3bf9f508a4e46672a27553554123f737e927fbe.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b3bf9f508a4e46672a27553554123f737e927fbe.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1b3bf9f508a4e46672a27553554123f737e927fbe.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="ETA-Fabrik" src="./media_1b3bf9f508a4e46672a27553554123f737e927fbe.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1500" height="1032">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p><em>Image courtesy of Andreas Körner</em></p>
  <p>“By bringing two worlds together — the business software layer and the operational layer — we can influence the efficiency and flexibility of manufacturing processes,” Weigold says, adding that it is the first project of its type worldwide.</p>
  <h2 id="turning-climate-action-into-a-competitive-advantage">Turning Climate Action into a Competitive Advantage</h2>
  <p>SAP expects the cooperation with PTW to help it refine its new software package that enables CO<sub>2</sub> accounting for SMEs over the entire supply chain. The <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2020/11/421f493b-ba7d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff.html">SAP Business Ecology Management</a> solution makes it possible for companies to manage the CO<sub>2</sub> footprint for each product by combining their existing ERP system — for example, SAP Business One or SAP Business ByDesign — with an energy flow model for the process. SAP partners worldwide will be responsible for applying the solution to customers’ individual and industry needs.</p>
  <p><a href="https://rdcu.be/cgzMZ">Studies show</a> that SMEs are prepared to manage their carbon emissions if they have the necessary support and tools. The recently launched <a href="https://smeclimatehub.org/">SME Climate Hub</a> is a brokerage for such resources. With a growing number of members, the hub could serve as a vital part of the implementation of ambitious corporate climate action.</p>
  <p>Emissions are typically divided into three categories, or <a href="https://compareyourfootprint.com/difference-scope-1-2-3-emissions/">Scopes</a>. The main targets of SAP Business Ecology Management are the Scope 1 and Scope 2 emissions of SMEs, which directly impact the upstream Scope 3 emissions of their customers.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_130bfc8e549ce9242d7335fdbfae855a5dc34e53e.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_130bfc8e549ce9242d7335fdbfae855a5dc34e53e.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_130bfc8e549ce9242d7335fdbfae855a5dc34e53e.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Headshot: Jochen Mayerle" src="./media_130bfc8e549ce9242d7335fdbfae855a5dc34e53e.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="800" height="800">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p><em>Jochen Mayerle</em></p>
  <p>“Supply chains make up the part of the carbon footprint, which are not under direct influence of a company, but have the highest reduction potential because they give organizations insight into the hot spots in their supply chain,” says Jochen Mayerle, business process architect, SAP.</p>
  <p>Mayerle emphasizes that the new product is designed to be easy to use and its implementation does not require the hiring of an expert in sustainability. Niels Hermansen, founder of the Danish SAP partner BitPeople A/S, based in Denmark, agrees. “I like that SAP has taken the initiative in this area,” Hermansen says. “It understands that SMEs have the same requirements as big companies, but do not have the same resources.”</p>
  <p>SAP Business Ecology Management is currently being testing by numerous customers and is planned for launch the third quarter of 2021.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Sandra Thiel, Agile expert, and Chris Horak, global vice president of Solution Marketing, contributed to this story.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/sme</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/climate-21</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-bydesign</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-one</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>