<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/topic/crm-customer-experience/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Enters into Agreement to Acquire WalkMe, Driving Business Transformation by Enhancing the Customer Experience and Enriching SAP Business AI Offerings]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-enters-agreement-to-acquire-walkme</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-enters-agreement-to-acquire-walkme</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is entering into an agreement to acquire WalkMe, a leader in digital adoption platforms. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17c02c58752a8aaaec6051673cfe2308da8b06446.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17c02c58752a8aaaec6051673cfe2308da8b06446.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_17c02c58752a8aaaec6051673cfe2308da8b06446.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Enters into Agreement to Acquire WalkMe, Driving Business Transformation by Enhancing the Customer Experience and Enriching SAP Business AI Offerings" src="./media_17c02c58752a8aaaec6051673cfe2308da8b06446.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-enters-into-agreement-to-acquire-walkme-driving-business-transformation-by-enhancing-the-customer-experience-and-enriching-sap-business-ai-offerings">SAP Enters into Agreement to Acquire WalkMe, Driving Business Transformation by Enhancing the Customer Experience and Enriching SAP Business AI Offerings</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) and WalkMe Ltd. (NASDAQ: WKME) announced today that the companies have entered into a definitive agreement under which SAP will acquire WalkMe, a leader in digital adoption platforms (DAPs).</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>WalkMe’s solutions help organizations navigate constant technology change by providing users with advanced guidance and automation features that enable them to execute workflows seamlessly across any number of applications. This results in higher adoption of the underlying application and as such drives value realization.</p>
  <p>The Executive and Supervisory Boards of SAP SE and the board of directors of WalkMe have approved the transaction for US $14.00 per share in an all-cash transaction, representing an equity value of approximately US $1.5 billion. The offer price represents a 45% premium to WalkMe’s closing share price on June 4, 2024.</p>
  <p>The envisioned combination complements SAP’s Business Transformation Management portfolio around SAP Signavio and SAP LeanIX solutions to help customers on their transformation journeys.</p>
  <p>“Applications, processes, data and people are the four key elements of a successful business transformation,” said Christian Klein, CEO and member of the Executive Board of SAP SE. “By acquiring WalkMe, we are doubling down on the support we provide our end users, helping them to quickly adopt new solutions and features to get the maximum value out of their IT investments.”</p>
  <h2 id="walkme-focus-on-analyzing-adoption-and-business-transformation">WalkMe: Focus on Analyzing Adoption and Business Transformation</h2>
  <p>“We are thrilled to join forces with SAP. This acquisition marks a significant milestone in our journey, providing us with the resources and customer base necessary to enhance our product offerings and expand our market reach,” said Dan Adika, CEO of WalkMe. “By leveraging SAP’s extensive ecosystem, we are poised to unlock substantial growth opportunities and deliver even greater value to our customers. Together, we look forward to a future filled with innovation and exceptional service.”</p>
  <p>WalkMe helps organizations boost enterprise productivity and lower risk by enabling consistent, effective and efficient use of software and the workflows it enables. Its DAP works on top of an organization’s application landscape, detects where people encounter friction and provides the tailored support and automation they need to complete the job to be done, right in the flow of work, across any application. Importantly, WalkMe will continue to fully support non-SAP applications.</p>
  <p>Soon, WalkMe will launch the WalkMe<sup>X</sup> copilot, which will use WalkMe’s contextual awareness and AI to suggest the best next step for any workflow, anywhere. WalkMe<sup>X</sup> has the capability to always be on, serving as an overlay to any application, including copilots from different vendors that companies use in their landscapes. Integrating the strength of WalkMe’s adoption capabilities with SAP’s copilot Joule will boost AI assistant and productivity gains for all SAP customers. Additionally, integrating distinctive e-learning features in the SAP Enable Now solution with WalkMe will form the center of SAP’s people-centric transformation approach going forward.</p>
  <p>The acquisition is subject to customary closing conditions, including the receipt of WalkMe shareholder approval and necessary regulatory clearances, and is expected to close in the third quarter of 2024. The impact of the transaction on SAP’s non-IFRS earnings per share for fiscal 2024 is expected to be immaterial.</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>About WalkMe</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>WalkMe (NASDAQ: WKME), headquartered in Tel Aviv, Israel, pioneered DAP innovations and solutions so companies can effectively navigate the constant change brought on by technology. With WalkMe, organizations drive enterprise productivity and reduce risk by ensuring consistent, responsible, and efficient adoption of software and the workflows it powers. Our AI-driven platform sits on top of an organization’s tech stack, identifies where people experience friction, and delivers the personalized guidance and automation needed to get the job done, right in the flow of work. Customers like IBM, Nestle, ThermoFisher Scientific, and the U.S. Dept. of Defense trust WalkMe to create the people-centric experiences required to boost the effectiveness of their workflows and maximize software ROI.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>About SAP</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As a global leader in enterprise applications and business AI, SAP (NYSE:SAP) stands at the nexus of business and technology. For over 50 years, organizations have trusted SAP to bring out their best by uniting business-critical operations spanning finance, procurement, HR, supply chain, and customer experience. For more information, visit <a href="http://www.sap.com">www.sap.com</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Note to editors:</strong><br>To preview and download broadcast-standard stock footage and press photos digitally, please visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/photos">www.sap.com/photos</a>. On this platform, you can find high resolution material for your media channels.</p>
  <p><strong>For customers interested in learning more about SAP products:</strong><br>Global Customer Center: +49 180 534-34-24<br>United States Only: 1 (800) 872-1SAP (1-800-872-1727)</p>
  <p><strong>For more information, financial community only:</strong><br>Anthony Coletta, +49 6227-7-60437, <a href="mailto:investor@sap.com">investor@sap.com</a>, CEST</p>
  <p><strong>For more information, press only:</strong><br>Joellen Perry, +1 650-445-6780, <a href="mailto:joellen.perry@sap.com">joellen.perry@sap.com</a>, PT<br>Daniel Reinhardt, +49 6227-7-40201, <a href="mailto:daniel.reinhardt@sap.com">daniel.reinhardt@sap.com</a>, CEST<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p><strong>For WalkMe Investor Relations:</strong><br>John Streppa, <a href="mailto:investors@walkme.com">investors@walkme.com</a></p>
  <p><strong>Additional Important Information and Where to Find It</strong> In connection with the proposed transaction, WalkMe will prepare a proxy statement to be delivered to its shareholders and furnished to the Securities and Exchange Commission (the “SEC”). INVESTORS AND SECURITY HOLDERS ARE STRONGLY ADVISED TO READ THE PROXY STATEMENT WHEN IT BECOMES AVAILABLE AND OTHER RELEVANT DOCUMENTS FILED OR FURNISHED TO THE SEC IN CONNECTION WITH THE PROPOSED TRANSACTION OR INCORPORATED BY REFERENCE THEREIN, BECAUSE THE PROXY STATEMENT AND SUCH OTHER RELEVANT DOCUMENTS WILL CONTAIN IMPORTANT INFORMATION ABOUT THE PROPOSED TRANSACTION AND THE PARTIES TO THE PROPOSED TRANSACTION. This press release is not a substitute for the proxy statement or any other document that may be filed or furnished by WalkMe with the SEC.</p>
  <p>The proxy statement and other related documents filed or furnished to the SEC regarding the proposed transaction may be obtained for free from the SEC’s website (<a href="http://www.sec.gov/">www.sec.gov</a>), WalkMe’s website at <a href="http://www.walkme.com">www.walkme.com</a> or by directing such request to WalkMe’s Investor Relations.</p>
  <p><strong>Forward-Looking Statements</strong><br>This press release contains “forward-looking statements” within the meaning of the “safe harbor” provisions of the Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995 and other applicable securities laws. All statements other than statements of historical fact, including statements regarding the proposed acquisition of WalkMe by SAP, the expected timing for completing the proposed transaction and the terms thereof, future financial and operating results, benefits and synergies of the transaction, future opportunities for the combined businesses and any other statements regarding events or developments that may occur in the future, may be “forward-looking statements” for purposes of federal and state securities laws. These forward-looking statements involve a number of risks and uncertainties that could significantly affect the financial or operating results of SAP, WalkMe or the combined company. Words such as “expects,” “anticipates,” “intends,” “plans,” “believes,” “estimates,” “predicts,” “seeks,” “targets,” “would,” “will,” “should,” “may” and variations of such words and similar expressions are intended to identify such forward-looking statements. Such statements are based on management’s expectations as of the date they are first made, are not guarantees of future performance and involve certain risks, uncertainties and assumptions that are difficult to predict. Neither SAP nor WalkMe can give any assurances that the expectations in such forward-looking statements will be attained and, therefore, actual outcomes and results may differ materially from what is expressed or forecasted in such forward-looking statements. For example, these forward-looking statements could be affected by factors including, without limitation, risks associated with the ability to consummate the proposed transaction, the satisfaction of the conditions to the consummation of the proposed transaction, including the receipt of certain regulatory approvals, and the timing of the closing of the proposed transaction; the occurrence of any event, change or other circumstance that could give rise to the termination of the proposed transaction; the potential that WalkMe shareholders may not approve the transaction; the ability to successfully integrate operations and employees; the ability to realize anticipated benefits and synergies of the proposed transaction as rapidly or to the extent anticipated by financial analysts or investors; the potential impact of the announcement of the proposed transaction on operating results, business generally and business relationships, including with employees, customers, suppliers and competitors; unanticipated restructuring costs may be incurred or undisclosed liabilities assumed; actual or threatened legal proceedings that have been or may be instituted against SAP or WalkMe in connection with the proposed transaction or otherwise; the ability and costs related to retaining key personnel and clients; risks related to diverting management’s attention from ongoing business operations; delays, challenges, costs, fees, expenses and charges related to the proposed transaction; actions by competitors; general adverse economic, political, social and security conditions in the regions and industries in which SAP and WalkMe operate, including relating to Israel’s ongoing war with Hamas and other terrorist organizations in the Middle East and general hostilities; exposure to inflation, currency rate and interest rate fluctuations and risks associated with doing business locally and internationally, as well as fluctuations in the market price of SAP and WalkMe’s traded securities; natural catastrophes, any pandemic, epidemic or outbreak of infectious disease, warfare, protests and riots, and terrorist attacks; and those additional risks and factors discussed in reports filed or furnished with the SEC by SAP and WalkMe, including SAP’s and WalkMe’s most recent Annual Reports on Form 20-F and in any subsequent reports on Form 6-K, each of which is on file with or furnished to the SEC and available at the SEC’s website at <a href="http://www.sec.gov/">www.sec.gov</a>. Reports filed or furnished with the SEC by SAP are also available on SAP’s website at <a href="http://www.sap.com/investors/en.html">www.sap.com/investors</a> and by WalkMe on WalkMe’s website at <a href="http://www.walkme.com">www.walkme.com</a>. Moreover, other risks and uncertainties of which SAP or WalkMe are not currently aware or may not currently consider material may also affect each of the companies’ forward-looking statements and may cause actual results and the timing of events to differ materially from those anticipated. The forward-looking statements made in this press release are made only as of the date hereof or as of the dates indicated in the forward-looking statements, even if they are subsequently made available by SAP or WalkMe on their respective websites or otherwise. Neither SAP nor WalkMe undertakes any obligation to update or supplement any forward-looking statements to reflect actual results, new information, future events, changes in its expectations or other circumstances that exist after the date as of which the forward-looking statements were made.</p>
  <p>© 2024 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE and affiliated entities in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p>Please consider our <a href="https://www.sap.com/corporate/en/legal/privacy.html">privacy policy</a>. If you receive this press release in your e-mail and you wish to unsubscribe to our mailing list please contact <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a> and write Unsubscribe in the subject line.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/investor-relations</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>product/sap-leanix</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-signavio</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP's New AI Innovations and Partnerships Deliver Real-World Results]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/ai-innovations-partnerships-sap-sapphire</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/ai-innovations-partnerships-sap-sapphire</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Explore the AI capabilities and ecosystem innovations presented at SAP Sapphire in 2024, all aimed at delivering real-world results.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>news-topic/financial-management</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/abap-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/accenture</category>
            <category>news-tag/ai-ethics</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/aws</category>
            <category>news-tag/bcg</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Digital Hub Innovations Win Silver and Bronze at 2024 Stevie® Awards]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-digital-hub-innovations-win-2024-stevie-awards</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-digital-hub-innovations-win-2024-stevie-awards</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Three SAP digital hub tools won 2024 Stevie Awards for Sales & Customer Service. Read to learn more about the recognition.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-engagement</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-customer-experience</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Customer Engagement Lessons from Competitive Racing]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/digital-customer-engagement-competitive-racing</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/digital-customer-engagement-competitive-racing</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP executes digital customer engagement via digital hubs. Read to find out how competitive racing teams, like Mercedes-AMG, can benefit.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-engagement</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/mercedes</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-customer-experience</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The 6 Warmest Business Trends for 2024]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/the-6-warmest-business-trends-for-2024</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/the-6-warmest-business-trends-for-2024</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[We spent hours, days even, sifting through dozens of boring reports to get at the most important trends you need to know about. You’re welcome.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10cb580fb5893e81a56acdcaa55ae897a7bb06d21.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10cb580fb5893e81a56acdcaa55ae897a7bb06d21.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_10cb580fb5893e81a56acdcaa55ae897a7bb06d21.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Stacks of reports on a table" src="./media_10cb580fb5893e81a56acdcaa55ae897a7bb06d21.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1044">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="the-6-warmest-business-trends-for-2024">The 6 Warmest Business Trends for 2024</h1>
        <p>We spent hours, days even, sifting through dozens of boring reports to get at the most important trends you need to know about. You’re welcome.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>By SAP Insights</p>
  <p>We're back and at it again – doling out predictions for the year ahead like the all-seeing business psychics that we are.</p>
  <p>Okay, fine. Busted. We immersed ourselves in the deluge of trend reports for 2024 from all the sources we could find and extracted the stuff you really need to know.</p>
  <p>Because isn’t the world just something else right now? Never a dull moment and all that and, as much as we would all love a few dull moments at the moment, 2024 doesn’t seem to be the year that will happen.</p>
  <p>Read on and prepare yourself.</p>
  <h2 id="trend-1-everything-ai">TREND 1: Everything AI</h2>
  <p><strong>It’s 9 a.m. Do you know what your developers are doing?</strong> Here’s a hint: They’re using generative AI (GenAI) for programming. Considering the cohort we’re talking about, this is unsurprising. Historically, this group has always jumped on new tech. Now, whether they have permission to do so is another matter. Most companies don’t have AI policies yet. Will they stop developers from using GenAI? Unlikely. (<a href="https://www.oreilly.com/radar/generative-ai-in-the-enterprise/">O’Reilly</a>)</p>
  <p><strong>Why use off-the-rack when you can go couture?</strong> Last year was like the kiddie wading pool version of GenAI. Everyone jumped in, splashed around, yelled at the top of their lungs with glee, and kinda made a mess. This is the year to jump in the deep end, and that means considering industry-specific AI models that are trained on data that’s more relevant and useful to the business than just pictures of cats and dogs. Domain-specific large language models (LLMs) are trained specifically on, say, types of medical or legal data. One size definitely does not fit all. (<a href="https://www2.deloitte.com/xe/en/insights/focus/tech-trends.html">Deloitte Tech Trends 2024</a>)</p>
  <p><strong>Trust you, trust AI.</strong> Introducing AI tools to the workplace can be a touchy subject. But it turns out that when engaged workers trust the companies they work for, that equals more openness to AI in all its wondrous manifestations. What employees everywhere want is to use AI, but not be managed by it. Last year, we saw GenAI take off at a breakneck speed – and with very few guardrails. In 2024? Expect guardrails in company policies about the when, how, and why of using GenAI, including broader laws and higher expectations. (<a href="https://www.qualtrics.com/ebooks-guides/2024-ex-trends-report/">Qualtrics: 2024 Employee Experience Trends</a>; <a href="https://www.oreilly.com/radar/generative-ai-in-the-enterprise/">O’Reilly</a>)</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="no-more-irresponsible-use-of-ai">No more irresponsible use of AI</h3>
        <p>Narrow the gap between aspiration and action when it comes to responsible AI.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="/blogs/no-more-excuses-for-irresponsible-use-of-ai">Read more</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>INSIGHTS’S ADVICE:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Hey! Let’s be careful out there.</strong> You need GenAI guidelines before employees get a bit <em>too</em> creative in using it – like maybe don’t use it for legal briefs – but also be realistic. Some workers (developers) will be more inclined to experiment and there are ways to encourage that safely.</li>
    <li><strong>BYOAI.</strong> Create proprietary LLMs trained on your own data for competitiveness and security.</li>
    <li><strong>Quell the fear.</strong> Many employees think AI is out for their jobs. But in many cases AI will be an assistant rather than a replacement. That’s why communications, management, and strategy come first – without clarity there won’t be trust. And without trust, GenAI won’t result in a sufficient return on investment (ROI).</li>
  </ul>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ee54936c2c3c090f8854fa2c739e9c573af090f1.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ee54936c2c3c090f8854fa2c739e9c573af090f1.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1ee54936c2c3c090f8854fa2c739e9c573af090f1.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Engineer programming a robotic arm in a warehouse facility." src="./media_1ee54936c2c3c090f8854fa2c739e9c573af090f1.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="trend-2-cxcs-reboot">TREND 2: CX/CS reboot</h2>
  <p><strong>Botched bots.</strong> Customer service (CS) has been cut, cut, and cut again. The big human replacement hope was bots, which are fine if you’re too lazy to read the FAQ. But the novelty of your chatbot named Brian wore off a while ago. As a result, what’s also been cut back is customer trust. Let 2024 be the year when companies refocus their customer experience (CX). As chatbots improve, humans will become a premium offering. That could mean more humans available for the higher-value work of helping special and spendy clients. (<a href="https://www.mintel.com/consumer-market-news/global-consumer-trends/">Mintel: 2024 Global Consumer Trends</a>)</p>
  <p><strong><em>Not</em> everything as a service?</strong> You get a subscription, they get a subscription, everyone gets a subscription! Why? Because there’s no other choice! Subscription fatigue is real, and growth is slowing for software-as-a-service (SaaS) companies, with a 50% decrease in growth year-over-year. Lack of customization, costs, auto-renewals, belt tightening, and low ROI are all reasons why consumers and companies alike are rethinking whatever-as-a-service. There’s still something to be said for the simplicity of a one-time buy. (<a href="https://www.accenture.com/us-en/insights/song/accenture-life-trends">Accenture: Life Trends 2024</a>; <a href="https://www.maxio.com/blog/maxio-institute-h1-2023-press-release">Maxio</a>)</p>
  <p><strong>Inside knowledge</strong>. For those not going the human route this year, companies will roll out GenAI for personalized CS and marketing. How personalized? Companies will lean on GenAI for speed and for getting to know their customers beyond “What can I do for you today?” At the same time, marketers are reading the writing on the wall (think regulations and negative consumer sentiment) and will suddenly become big defenders of privacy. (<a href="https://www.forrester.com/predictions/">Forrester: Predictions 2024</a>)</p>
  <p>INSIGHTS’S ADVICE:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Give humans the luxury treatment.</strong> Bot CS will continue to grow but people respond better to other people, and that can be developed into a valuable offering. A well-trained human agent is the luxury offering of our time.</li>
    <li><strong>Audit for airware.</strong> Remember shelfware? That shrink-wrapped software you bought but your people never used? Unused cloud-based software subscriptions can be even tougher to trace. Audit your subscriptions and ax what’s costing too much and what isn’t efficient.</li>
    <li><strong>Avoid the same mistakes.</strong> Only use GenAI for CS if you’ve put in place clear goals and strategies to avoid replicating all that’s wrong with the CX.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1cf90a9f5e90df628256c9193feeafea78a81dc97.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1cf90a9f5e90df628256c9193feeafea78a81dc97.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1cf90a9f5e90df628256c9193feeafea78a81dc97.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Black engineer controls robotic arc welder on a factory production line" src="./media_1cf90a9f5e90df628256c9193feeafea78a81dc97.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1958" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="trend-3-manufacturing">TREND 3: Manufacturing</h2>
  <p><strong>Coming soon: A factory near you.</strong> Reshoring has long been the trend that never quite happened. Well, it’s happening now. As we write, there’s a factory construction boom going on in Europe, the United States, and the not-China parts of Asia such as Japan, Korea, and India. It’s thanks in part to government investment encouraging domestic production of, among other things, semiconductors (cough, cough, China). Manufacturers are also taking the opportunity to smartify and greenify their new factories. (<a href="https://www2.deloitte.com/us/en/insights/industry/manufacturing/manufacturing-industry-outlook.html">Deloitte: 2024 Manufacturing Industry Outlook</a>; <a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/chipmakers-plans-factories-europe-2023-02-16/">Reuters</a>)</p>
  <p><strong>Cobot anyone?</strong> Manufacturing is still suffering through a skills shortage and trying to do something about it by offering (more, better) benefits and other incentives. Most say they need significantly more people and yet are consistently losing them – that’s some problematic math there. But, hey, why worry about people when bots are inelegantly lurching to a warehouse (job) near you? Will the Digits and Optimus Gen 2s get all snuggly and work together rather than with humans? Is it still cobotting if the collaborator is also a bot? (<a href="https://www.pwc.com/us/en/industries/industrial-products/library/manufacturing-talent-strategy.html">PWC</a>; <a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/1/18/24043065/bmw-figure-robotics-humanoid-robot-workers-deployment">The Verge</a>)</p>
  <p><strong>Making the industrial metaverse happen.</strong> Okay, we know. The industrial metaverse got a lot of attention at first and then … what? Not much. But apparently manufacturers have been experimenting with it in the background. And now we can add the spatial Web – aka Web 3 – to manufacturers’ goals. Web 3 is focused on interactions in digital spaces (think virtual reality) and factories are signing up for virtual interactive applications. Think of it this way: Web 3 is how manufacturers get into the industrial metaverse. Once Web 3 is further developed, the industrial metaverse can finally take off. (<a href="https://www2.deloitte.com/us/en/insights/focus/tech-trends.html">Deloitte: Tech Trends 2024)</a></p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="a-guide-to-build-the-future-factory">A guide to build the future factory</h3>
        <p>Dive beneath the buzzwords to the profitable steps forward for manufacturers.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="/blogs/building-the-future-factory-a-special-report">Learn more</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>INSIGHTS’S ADVICE:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Factory shopping</strong>. Is manufacturing coming to an industrial area near you? Maybe sign up for a presale to quickly reshore your own production.</li>
    <li><strong>Don’t go botlistic … yet.</strong> Manufacturing’s hiring woes aren’t over quite yet, and don’t expect bots to do the heavy lifting of replacing lost workers. They are getting better, but the frenzied pace of adoption of software bots such as GenAI should not be confused with hardware bots, which are improving only incrementally.</li>
    <li><strong>Don’t write off the metaverse (again).</strong> Just cause Zuck keeps whiffing on the killer app doesn’t mean you will. Mixed reality apps are quietly making a lot of progress in areas such as maintenance and research and development. Now’s the time to investigate the use of spatial technologies.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17d6081901fb30aa4030a2abbc86aa1fcd22b68e2.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17d6081901fb30aa4030a2abbc86aa1fcd22b68e2.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_17d6081901fb30aa4030a2abbc86aa1fcd22b68e2.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Man watches automated robot carriers work in a modern distribution warehouse." src="./media_17d6081901fb30aa4030a2abbc86aa1fcd22b68e2.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="2160">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="trend-4-supply-chains">TREND 4: Supply chains</h2>
  <p><strong>Going micro.</strong> One way of avoiding the peaks and troughs of recent supply chain upheavals is by focusing on micro-fulfillment – smaller, compact warehouses located closer to customers. Add to that smaller amounts of customized products, also produced close(-ish), and backups at the Panama Canal become a distant memory. (<a href="https://www.maersk.com/insights/digitalisation/2023/11/24/supply-chain-visibility-trends">Maersk</a>; <a href="https://qz.com/the-shift-of-manufacturing-out-of-china-is-shaking-up-s-1851064053">Quartz</a>)</p>
  <p><strong>AI meets supply chain meets regulation</strong>. GenAI is coming for the world’s supply chains. With more regulations related to environmental, social, and governance (ESG) hitting in 2024, AI will be directing supply chain planning because of its ability to analyze tons of data and make predictions better than humans. That will be crucial toward finding out what’s going on in the chains at deeper levels. But it will only work for those with good data. (<a href="https://kpmg.com/xx/en/home/insights/2023/12/supply-chain-trends-2024.html">KPMG: Supply Chain Trends 2024</a>)</p>
  <p><strong>Designing for disaster.</strong> Sure, you can reshore production to stave off international instability. But what about when your factory is flattened by a domestic tornado? Or ships can’t travel their usual routes? The Panama Canal and the Rhine and Mississippi rivers all had low water levels due to drought last year, and shipping felt the impacts. No wonder weather risks are top of mind for supply chain professionals. To prepare for long-term weather upheavals, designs must adapt, such as building ships that can navigate shallower waters and buildings that can stand up to 200 mph winds. (<a href="https://think.ing.com/articles/extreme-weather-makes-major-trade-routes-less-reliable">ING</a>; <a href="https://commercial.allianz.com/news-and-insights/expert-risk-articles/allianz-risk-barometer-2024-natural-catastrophes.html">Allianz</a>)</p>
  <p>INSIGHTS’S ADVICE:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Use regulations to sell supply chain transparency.</strong> Supply chain pros have long struggled to prove a business case for spending money on supply chain transparency. ESG regulations will change all that and AI will help. But make sure to invest in data gathering and cleaning. It will be crucial for AI accuracy and regulatory compliance.</li>
    <li><strong>Mini making.</strong> Breaking manufacturing down into smaller chunks (think modular construction) is your power hedge against supply chain problems.</li>
    <li><strong>Talk about the weather.</strong> It’s no longer just a lame conversation starter. The weather can put you out of business. Check your infrastructure and that of your supply chain partners. Is it likely to survive disasters?</li>
  </ul>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_12196cadbfd8a79c9acf17f8557b200d54ae6280e.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_12196cadbfd8a79c9acf17f8557b200d54ae6280e.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_12196cadbfd8a79c9acf17f8557b200d54ae6280e.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Male IT holds a laptop and discusses work with female server technician, standing in a data center, rack server cabinet with cloud server icon and visualization" src="./media_12196cadbfd8a79c9acf17f8557b200d54ae6280e.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="2160">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="trend-5-enterprise-tech">TREND 5: Enterprise tech</h2>
  <p><strong>Head in both clouds.</strong> Companies have gotten the best out of the public cloud – such as efficiency and a lesser burden on IT – and are now turning to the private cloud, with its better security and customization. They’re balancing their hybrid cloud usage so that each plays to its own strengths. Upping the strength quotient are cloud and/or hybrid industry-specific platforms that can be customized. (<a href="https://www.rackspace.com/solve/2024-it-outlook-report">Solve/Rackspace Technology: 2024 IT Outlook Report</a>; <a href="https://www.gartner.com/en/newsroom/press-releases/2023-10-16-gartner-identifies-the-top-10-strategic-technology-trends-for-2024">Gartner: Top 10 Strategic Technology Trends for 2024</a>)</p>
  <p><strong>Smart shady.</strong> After smart glasses failing repeatedly and spectacularly (remember the unfortunate nickname for wearers of Google Glasses?), will 2024 be the year when smart glasses finally become cool rather than cringe? New more comfortable and useful versions – better functionality, less weight on the wearer’s nose, classic styling so you can make like a Beach Boy and surf (the Web) – mean that initial hesitancy (or outright derision) might be overcome and that means a big boost to the spatial Web. Privacy? Do we still care about privacy? (<a href="https://www2.deloitte.com/us/en/insights/focus/tech-trends.html">Deloitte: Tech Trends 2024</a>)</p>
  <p><strong>Get your data in court.</strong> Data breaches are the target of more – and often well-publicized – lawsuits, and more courts around the world are letting those cases go ahead. Another area of litigious growth is companies taking legal action against data scrapers, copyright infringers, hackers, and the like. Add AI to the legal mix for increased volume and messiness. Expect a ballooning of legal skirmishes as laws scramble to catch up and plaintiffs find new legal avenues to pursue. (<a href="https://www.freshfields.us/insights/campaigns/data-trends-2024/">Freshfields: Data Trends 2024</a>)</p>
  <p>INSIGHTS’S ADVICE:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Going public.</strong> Investigate public and hybrid clouds for industry-specific applications that can be tailored to specific business needs.</li>
    <li><strong>Never mind the fashion.</strong> While we’re not convinced that smart glasses will be <em>the</em> fashion choice, using them for work makes sense now that they’re more comfortable and have better features</li>
    <li><strong>Look both ways.</strong> Legal beefs over data hit businesses from both sides – coming from inside and outside the house. Legal prep is the solve.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_143844e4449a70bf1d5eed3d29d977f354b5f8bc4.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_143844e4449a70bf1d5eed3d29d977f354b5f8bc4.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_143844e4449a70bf1d5eed3d29d977f354b5f8bc4.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Black man sitting at a table and working from home on a laptop, greets a co-worker in a video meeting" src="./media_143844e4449a70bf1d5eed3d29d977f354b5f8bc4.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2598" height="1648">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="trend-6-hr">TREND 6: HR</h2>
  <p><strong>Where are we working again?</strong> Many employees prefer working remotely full-time or at least part of the work week. Just over half want all-the-time remote and 46% prefer a mix of both on- and off-site work. And many who were relying on promises of permanent remote work, moved to areas with lower costs of living. But what happens when employers mandate coming back to the office? Stalemate. With the skills shortage and the competition for those at the top of their game, more companies will start offering money for relocation to make working out of an office palatable again. They’ll also need to offer other sweeteners to stem the rising trend of coffee badging: showing up, getting a coffee, chatting with co-workers, then leaving to work remotely for the rest of the day. (<a href="https://www.kornferry.com/insights/featured-topics/talent-recruitment/talent-acquisition-trends-2024">Korn Ferry: Talent Acquisition Trends 2024</a>; <a href="https://finance.yahoo.com/news/return-office-mandates-aren-t-191245629.html?guccounter=1">Yahoo! Finance</a>)</p>
  <p><strong>Virtual you.</strong> You’ve heard of digital twins. Well, here comes virtual twins. That’s when employees make digital avatars of themselves using AI trained on specific skills and industries to do work on their behalf – and maybe even earn extra money doing it. Why worry about overworking employees when they can replicate themselves many times over? On the flip side, companies could support these twins and train them on proprietary data. The big question: Who – or what – owns the rights to their/its output? (<a href="https://backslash.com/news/future-of-employee-experience/">Backslash</a>; <a href="https://slate.com/human-interest/2023/02/remote-work-multiple-full-time-jobs-overmployed.html">Slate</a>)</p>
  <p><strong>The end of jobs.</strong> Who cares about jobs when what you need are skills? Technology is changing so quickly that skill obsolescence is a real concern, and that’s motivating employers and employees to focus on continual skill improvements. Makes sense that instead of hiring for specific roles, businesses will look for skills that can be applied across their companies and will offer education to make that fluidity permanent. (<a href="https://backslash.com/news/future-of-employee-experience/">Backslash</a>)</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="discover-the-top-hr-trends-for-2024">Discover the top HR trends for 2024</h3>
        <p>AI dominates the top trends, but other surprising trends bob to the surface.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="/blogs/hr-trends-2024-the-year-of-ai">See the trends</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>INSIGHTS’S ADVICE:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Go into the wilderness.</strong> Disgruntled remotes could be good recruitment targets for companies that don’t care where people work. Another strategy: Start offering relocation benefits and bonuses.</li>
    <li><strong>Meet me later.</strong> Stan, meet Stan – and Stan. A little sci-fi right now but think what it would mean to increase productivity exponentially.</li>
    <li><strong>Ditch the descriptions.</strong> Get the skills you need by ditching job descriptions and embracing the free flow of knowledge.</li>
  </ul>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>content-type/trends-predictions</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Expanded Partnership Turns Transactions into Lasting Connections]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/expanded-sap-preferred-success-sales-services-lasting-connections</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/expanded-sap-preferred-success-sales-services-lasting-connections</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Preferred Success for SAP Sales Cloud and SAP Service Cloud, expanded edition, helps businesses create personalized customer experiences.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-preferred-success</category>
            <category>product/sap-sales-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-service-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Announces New Commerce Cloud Payment Solution, Drawing on Vast Partner Ecosystem to Help Retailers Gain an Edge]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/sap-announces-new-commerce-cloud-payment-solution</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/sap-announces-new-commerce-cloud-payment-solution</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The new SAP Commerce Cloud, open payment framework, helps retailers stay ahead of changing customer expectations. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
            <category>product/sap-commerce-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Goes the Distance with EV Fleet Digitalization]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/sap-goes-the-distance-ev-fleet-digitalization</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/sap-goes-the-distance-ev-fleet-digitalization</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Longtime partners SAP and Mercedes-Benz are transforming the sustainable EV experience with digitalized corporate fleet management.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1300ce8d341537d322ce2ddfe25ec1e05ce2fbf64.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1300ce8d341537d322ce2ddfe25ec1e05ce2fbf64.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1300ce8d341537d322ce2ddfe25ec1e05ce2fbf64.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Goes the Distance with EV Fleet Digitalization" src="./media_1300ce8d341537d322ce2ddfe25ec1e05ce2fbf64.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-goes-the-distance-with-ev-fleet-digitalization">SAP Goes the Distance with EV Fleet Digitalization</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Electric vehicles (<a href="/topics/electric-vehicles">EVs</a>) are transforming the mobility experience in corporate fleet management. A great example is the partnership between <a href="https://www.mercedes-benz.com/en/">Mercedes-Benz</a> and SAP where the companies are both customers and vendors to each other. Mercedes-Benz is using SAP solutions to digitalize its omnichannel buying experience, and SAP is the first customer using its own technology to manage the company’s vehicle fleet in Germany.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As longtime partners, SAP and Mercedes-Benz have a history of shared knowledge for mutual competitive advantage. The fleet management program is grounded in the companies’ similar business philosophies and product road maps.</p>
  <p>Mercedes-Benz has committed to move the company’s B2B business to 100% digital and plans to sell 25% of all new cars online by 2025. The company selected <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm/commerce-cloud.html">SAP Commerce Cloud</a> to help support this mission. It will create a future-proof composable commerce portfolio designed to reliably power the company’s digital strategy, including a standardized offering across different markets. It will also simplify processes and reduce time-to-market.</p>
  <h2 id="benefits-of-digitalized-fleet-management">Benefits of Digitalized Fleet Management</h2>
  <p>From the SAP employee’s perspective, ordering a company EV couldn’t be simpler. Instead of time-consuming manual research and back and forth communication with the car dealer, employees can use <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/spend-management/solutions.html">the guided buying capability in SAP Ariba solutions</a> to order the EV they want directly from the Mercedes-Benz online catalog. They can choose the features they want, such as car make and model, color, and equipment packages, within SAP’s pre-set guidelines.</p>
  <p>“The car configurator automates the EV selection process end-to-end, eliminating manual steps and saving time while providing the employee with a highly personalized experience,” said Steffen Krautwasser, head of SAP’s global car fleet. “Automating the approval process assures data consistency and eliminates the need for manual quality checks.”</p>
  <p>There’s a tremendous convenience factor in captured EV data as well. In one pilot program for select EVs in SAP’s fleet, the digital twin will automatically track mileage. Drivers will no longer need to manually enter mileage every time they recharge, and SAP can use this data to better manage the fleet.</p>
  <h2 id="connected-data-drives-sustainable-business">Connected Data Drives Sustainable Business</h2>
  <p>Once ordered, EVs are tracked as assets in SAP’s financial system. After delivery, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/digital-vehicle-suite.html">SAP Digital Vehicle Suite</a> creates a digital twin that can capture relevant, secure data across the EV’s lifetime. SAP’s fleet management team can track CO2 emissions based on green energy usage, mileage, and the number of vehicles on the road. Krautwasser envisioned reporting this data to support the company’s global sustainability commitments.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-digital-vehicle-suite-delivers-a-holistic-approach-to-vehicle-sales-and-data-management">SAP Digital Vehicle Suite delivers a holistic approach to vehicle, sales, and data management</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/digital-vehicle-suite.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“Performance data from the EV digital twin can help corporate fleet managers guide employees in choosing the best vehicle for their driving needs,” said Krautwasser. “Over time, drivers can better understand travel ranges between charges.”</p>
  <p>Data is expected to help address so-called range anxiety, alerting EV drivers when their vehicle needs a charge and, most important, where to recharge. Mercedes-Benz is investing in charging infrastructure to create an ecosystem that would be integrated with public and private charge point providers in the U.S., China, and Europe.</p>
  <p>The partnership also reflects a shared commitment to sustainability. Mercedes-Benz has committed to become carbon neutral by 2038, and transition to 100% electric vehicles by 2030 wherever possible. SAP is transitioning the company’s vehicle fleet for employees in Germany to all EVs by 2025 as part of its corporate commitment to be carbon neutral by 2030.</p>
  <h2 id="omnichannel-is-fastest-path-to-customer-love">Omnichannel Is Fastest Path to Customer Love</h2>
  <p>The digital experience is extremely important for customers who expect convenience and quality. Organizations in many industries have shifted to an omnichannel strategy that offers people their preferred experience, whether online or in-person, building brand loyalty and repeat business.</p>
  <p>“We want to provide a seamless journey for employees as they research, select, purchase, and enjoy their vehicle,” said Krautwasser. “The most exciting part of our EV fleet management strategy is how we can use our knowledge to enhance the employee experience. Through data and digital services, we can get closer to our employees and act quickly based on their feedback, making improvements and introducing new offerings that keep us on top of trends and support SAP’s sustainability commitment.”</p>
  <p>EVs represent a profound business model shift for the entire automotive supply chain as automakers sell direct to customers, provide digital services from vehicle data, and explore new revenue opportunities. It’s clear that Mercedes-Benz and SAP are going the distance for a sustainable and satisfying driving experience.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Susan Galer is a communications director at SAP. Follow her @smgaler.<br>Top photo courtesy of SAP employee Jude Calvin Parong.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-sap-news-delivered-to-your-inbox-once-a-week">Get the latest SAP news delivered to your inbox once a week</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/nl/sap-news-center-newsletter/index.html">Sign up</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/automotive</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-twin</category>
            <category>news-tag/e-mobility</category>
            <category>news-tag/electric-vehicles</category>
            <category>news-tag/mercedes</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>product/sap-commerce-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[CEV Technologies and SAP Fuel E-Mobility Revolution in Croatia’s Retail Sector]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/cev-technologies-e-mobility-croatia-retail-sector</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/cev-technologies-e-mobility-croatia-retail-sector</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[To realize the potential of convenient charging within the customer experience, CEV Technologies implemented SAP E-Mobility in Croatia.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/automotive</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/electric-vehicles</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
            <category>product/sap-e-mobility</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How SAP’s Retail Partners Became Innovation Multipliers in 2023 and Created the Ultimate Consumer Experience]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/sap-retail-partners-became-innovation-multipliers-in-2023</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/sap-retail-partners-became-innovation-multipliers-in-2023</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Read to learn about the retail partners that served as innovation and growth multipliers for SAP customers in 2023.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>industry/consumer-goods-cpg</category>
            <category>news-tag/nrf</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
            <category>product/sap-commerce-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Top Retailers Using Tech to Build Lifelong Customer Relationships]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/retail-sap-customers-using-tech-to-build-lifelong-relationships</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/retail-sap-customers-using-tech-to-build-lifelong-relationships</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP customers in retail leverage tech to drive meaningful customer experiences, adopt sustainability, and position for success. Read more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/nrf</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-analytics</category>
            <category>product/sap-commerce-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Announces New AI-Driven Retail Capabilities to Enhance Customer Experience – From Planning to Personalization]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/new-ai-driven-retail-capabilities-enhance-customer-experience</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/new-ai-driven-retail-capabilities-enhance-customer-experience</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New AI retail capabilities will help retailers optimize business processes and drive profitability and customer loyalty. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/nrf</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
            <category>product/sap-emarsys-customer-engagement</category>
            <category>product/sap-predictive-demand-planning</category>
            <category>product/sap-predictive-replenishment</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bosch Rexroth AG's Journey Toward Field Service Success]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/bosch-rexroth-ag-journey-to-field-service-success</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/bosch-rexroth-ag-journey-to-field-service-success</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[At Bosch Rexroth AG, premium-quality field service support has been a key driver of success. Read more about the company's transformation.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/field-service-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[More Than Just the Numbers: Insights from 2023 Cyber Week]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/cyber-week-2023-insights</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/cyber-week-2023-insights</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Black Friday marks the beginning of the holiday shopping season. Learn about SAP customers' successes during Cyber Week 2023.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a6045a889e543a1e87aa3bb1f359ec62eca3fa7e.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a6045a889e543a1e87aa3bb1f359ec62eca3fa7e.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1a6045a889e543a1e87aa3bb1f359ec62eca3fa7e.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="More Than Just the Numbers: Insights from 2023 Cyber Week" src="./media_1a6045a889e543a1e87aa3bb1f359ec62eca3fa7e.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="more-than-just-the-numbers-insights-from-2023-cyber-week">More Than Just the Numbers: Insights from 2023 Cyber Week</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Black Friday marks the beginning of the holiday shopping season and there have been great stories of record-breaking volumes, many from SAP customers that experienced success during Cyber Week, the Monday before Black Friday to Cyber Monday.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Through Cyber Week, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm/commerce-cloud.html">SAP Commerce Cloud</a> customers achieved over a 35% year-over-year (YoY) increase in the number of orders processed, an astounding amount of $110 million in peak gross merchandising value (GMV) per minute, and a 9.3% YoY increase in overall site traffic. Essential for driving site traffic and increasing conversions is customer engagement, and on Cyber Weekend, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm/commerce-cloud.html">SAP Emarsys Customer Engagement</a> supported customers with a nine percent YoY increase of overall send volume across all channels. What’s more, SAP Commerce Cloud customers achieved a 5.04% higher conversion rate versus 2022, and retailers saw a 5.2% higher conversion rate during Cyber Week.</p>
  <p>This success was possible due to the reliability, scalability, and intelligence of <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm.html">SAP Customer Experience solutions</a> for individually curated shopping journeys across the globe.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="unlock-business-agility-and-transform-customer-experiences-with-sap-commerce-cloud">Unlock business agility and transform customer experiences with SAP Commerce Cloud</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm/commerce-cloud.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>But at SAP, it is not just about the numbers. Deriving insights from data is at the heart of SAP and the start to the holiday shopping season provided a treasure trove of learnings and understanding about how people are shopping and how retailers can <a href="/topics/crm-customer-experience">optimize their experiences</a>.</p>
  <p>By serving some of the largest brands in the world through this holiday season, here is what we learned.</p>
  <h2 id="insight-one-the-definition-of-holiday-season-is-expanding">Insight One: The Definition of “Holiday Season” Is Expanding</h2>
  <p>Traditionally, Black Friday is considered as a starting point for the holiday shopping season. However, recent research has revealed the holiday shopping is starting sooner and extending over the course of several weeks.</p>
  <p>According to <a href="https://go.criteo.com/">Criteo</a>, an SAP commerce media partner, the longest path to purchase during the holidays is <a href="https://c-grid.criteo.com/holiday-season-success-2023">about 45 days</a>. This includes Singles Day, originated in China, on November 11 and El Buen Fin, Mexico’s version of Cyber Weekend from November 17 to November 20.</p>
  <p>In 2023, SAP Emarsys Customer Engagement saw a spike on Singles Day, nearly surpassing 1 billion customer engagements — for example, email, SMS, mobile push, and web push — two weeks ahead of Black Friday. This figure was then eclipsed not once but twice during El Buen Fin, which saw overall an approximate 30% YoY increase in messages delivered.</p>
  <p>When looking at just email growth during this season, the growth of volume for the entire month of November was nearly twice what it was for Cyber Weekend. This not only underscores that holiday shopping is starting earlier, but how brands are scaling up sooner and avoiding sharp peaks, which is a win for deliverability too.</p>
  <p>Newly emerging celebrations and extended shopping seasons also mean a higher and longer strain on e-commerce sites. However, SAP Commerce Cloud prepared the customers to combat this challenge during these peak sales times leading up to Cyber Week, and delivered 100% uptime. In fact, customers that ran holiday sales events during El Buen Fin achieved 112% growth in conversion rate, with 10% higher traffic volume compared to the regular daily average of 2023.</p>
  <h2 id="insight-two-email-still-reigns-but-omnichannel-engagement-is-rapidly-growing">Insight Two: Email Still Reigns, But Omnichannel Engagement Is Rapidly Growing</h2>
  <p>While overall 2023 holiday sales are expected to <a href="https://nrf.com/media-center/press-releases/2023-holiday-reach-record-spending-levels">increase between three and four percent</a>, online sales are expected to double and <a href="https://nrf.com/media-center/press-releases/2023-holiday-reach-record-spending-levels">increase between seven and nine percent</a>. More digitally advanced customer journeys and increasingly tech-savvy buyers present an exciting opportunity for businesses to engage with shoppers more often and on their preferred channels.</p>
  <p>Aiming to capitalize on this opportunity and remain top of mind with shoppers, SAP Emarsys customers sent a record number of omnichannel messages, resulting in a nine percent YoY increase in customer engagements from 2022. Email remained the top promotional channel in terms of volume and saw a respectable 10% YoY increase.</p>
  <p>In addition to email, brands are also now investing heavily in omnichannel engagement strategies to meet customers where they prefer to shop. Mobile messages like SMS (35% YoY increase) and in-app (15% YoY increase) were utilized effectively alongside email, as were Web channel engagements, like Web push, which saw a whopping 74% increase in usage in 2023.</p>
  <h2 id="insight-three-personalization-proves-less-is-more">Insight Three: Personalization Proves Less is More</h2>
  <p>It is important to acknowledge that success does not equate to the quantity of messages, but also the quality. Bucking the notion that more is simply better, marketers using SAP Emarsys increased utilization of data-driven segmentation by 20% compared to Cyber Weekend 2022, enabling more targeted offers and personalized messages. While conversion rates would naturally be expected to dip given the extra volume, this targeted and personalized approach contributed to minimal or no change compared to baseline conversion rates during a typical weekend.</p>
  <p>Similarly, AI-powered product recommendations, delivered across channels, and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/marketing.html#ecommerce">intelligent shopping assistants from SAP Customer Experience solutions</a> also helped consumers find the right product or best deal among the seemingly limitless choices — with confidence and ease.</p>
  <p>With consumers shopping for an extended period on more channels, brands have both an obligation to meet them where they are in their journey and an opportunity to earn their business and loyalty by investing in data-driven, omnichannel strategies that better match them with personalized offers on the items they wish to buy.</p>
  <h2 id="insight-four-b2b-shoppers-share-the-holiday-fever-during-cyber-week">Insight Four: B2B Shoppers Share the Holiday Fever During Cyber Week</h2>
  <p>Black Friday is usually seen as an influential opportunity to create a revenue boost for retailers. However, SAP has the privilege of working with many B2B commerce companies in addition to a large number of retailers.</p>
  <p>According to our data, other industries outside of retail also experience the benefits of Black Friday and Cyber Monday pushes. While the retail industry had the highest volume of orders, consumer products and wholesale distribution came in close behind. Additionally, the chemicals industry saw a huge spike in AOV over the weekend and achieved a GMV increase of 51% YoY, while life sciences industry saw more than 120% YoY GMV growth.</p>
  <p>These data points indicate that Cyber Week trends are no longer limited to retailers, as various industries now achieve bigger sales volume and revenue during this period. Moving forward, organizations across all industries must put their best foot forward during Cyber Weekend activities to support profitable growth.</p>
  <h2 id="insight-five-black-friday-isnt-just-about-the-us-thanksgiving-holiday-anymore">Insight Five: Black Friday Isn’t Just About the U.S. Thanksgiving Holiday Anymore</h2>
  <p>The data from SAP Commerce Cloud also reflects the globalization trend. While North America led the biggest GMV number on Black Friday, the Europe, Middle East, and Africa (EMEA) region is comparable. In fact, the highest number of orders, about 800,000, was placed in EMEA. Additionally, the Asia Pacific and Japan (APJ) region on Cyber Monday achieved over 130% growth in conversion rate compared to last year.</p>
  <p>SAP Emarsys customers were also ready to leverage this trend and engage with customers around the world. On Cyber Monday, total send volumes saw significant YoY increases in multiple regions: by 20% in EMEA, over 27% in Middle and Eastern Europe (MEE), and over 15% in Asia.</p>
  <p>The data also highlighted differences in how consumers shop and buy in different regions. Unsurprisingly email continued to be the most used channel across the board, though EMEA proved to be the only region, outside of the Americas, that saw high growth in email volume year-on-year with a 13% increase.</p>
  <p>The MEE region saw a slight decrease in the use of email (-12% YoY) in favor of SMS, mobile push, and in-app messages. In APJ, where a mobile-first mindset is often the norm, usage of in-app (58% YoY growth) and mobile push (176% YoY growth) went up significantly compared to email growth (two percent YoY). Even in EMEA, SMS (53% YoY growth) and in-app (388% YoY growth) mobile messages outpaced email growth, underscoring the importance of an omnichannel strategy.</p>
  <p>This data illustrates the global influence of Black Friday, what used to be considered an U.S.-specific sales event. For businesses across the globe, it is crucial to recognize this shift and consider customer behaviors, so they can adapt and evolve their commerce and channel engagement strategies to gain customer loyalty and boost profitability.</p>
  <h2 id="next-step">Next Step</h2>
  <p>As market trends evolve, organizations must proactively adopt strategies for profitable and sustainable growth. With the right blend of modern technologies, agile business processes, and customer centric strategies, businesses significantly benefit from extended shopping season, through personalized omnichannel engagements, increased conversions, and lifelong customer loyalty.</p>
  <p>Moreover, with the right choice of cloud technologies, organizations can remain secure and compliant, while delivering reliable, scalable, and personalized experiences that are optimized for their industries.</p>
  <p>To learn more about how SAP Customer Experience solutions can help, please <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm.html">visit us at sap.com/crm</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Balaji Balasubramanian is senior vice president and global head of Commerce and Industry Cloud at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><em>*All data presented here is approximate and is based on various assumptions. All data is unaudited and is subject to adjustment. All financial figures are in USD. Data represents online and offline sales made by SAP global merchants.</em></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-commerce</category>
            <category>news-tag/e-commerce</category>
            <category>product/sap-commerce-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-customer-experience</category>
            <category>product/sap-emarsys-customer-engagement</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Driving Business Outcomes for ONEX Holding with Digital Customer Engagement]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/onex-holding-digital-customer-engagement</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/onex-holding-digital-customer-engagement</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The relationship between ONEX and SAP shows how virtual immersive engagements can enable and scale human interactions, not diminish them.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-engagement</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Announces Winners of the SAP Global SAP Customer Experience Partner Excellence Awards 2023]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/2023-sap-global-sap-customer-experience-partner-excellence-awards</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/2023-sap-global-sap-customer-experience-partner-excellence-awards</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Six SAP Customer Experience Partner Excellence Awards were presented at SAP Customer Experience LIVE. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_12776fa46fb88b64c135136a4cec5c53faa7fac5c.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_12776fa46fb88b64c135136a4cec5c53faa7fac5c.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_12776fa46fb88b64c135136a4cec5c53faa7fac5c.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Announces Winners of the SAP Global SAP Customer Experience Partner Excellence Awards 2023" src="./media_12776fa46fb88b64c135136a4cec5c53faa7fac5c.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-announces-winners-of-the-sap-global-sap-customer-experience-partner-excellence-awards-2023">SAP Announces Winners of the SAP Global SAP Customer Experience Partner Excellence Awards 2023</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced that it presented six global awards for partner excellence in the SAP Customer Experience line of business (LoB) during the SAP Customer Experience LIVE event.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP Global LoB Partner Excellence Awards are a partner recognition program focusing on SAP’s strategic business priorities for the following lines of business: SAP SuccessFactors, SAP Customer Experience, and Intelligent Spend and Business Network.</p>
  <p>SAP Global SAP Customer Experience Partner Excellence Awards select finalists and winners for their valuable contributions in realizing SAP’s vision for cloud growth based on data and key performance indicators.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Winners and Finalists</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP Global SAP Customer Experience Partner Excellence Award 2023 for Sales Success – Large Enterprise</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Winner: NTT DATA</li>
    <li>Finalist: Acorel</li>
    <li>Finalist: Dotan B.S. Solutions</li>
  </ul>
  <p>SAP Global SAP Customer Experience Partner Excellence Award 2023 for Sales Success – Midmarket</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Winner: Deloitte</li>
    <li>Finalist: NTT DATA</li>
    <li>Finalist: Felece Yazilim Ve Danişmanlik</li>
  </ul>
  <p>SAP Global SAP Customer Experience Partner Excellence Award 2023 for Delivery Quality</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Winner: Sybit GmbH</li>
    <li>Finalist: Axians Digital Business Solutions</li>
    <li>Finalist: Reply</li>
  </ul>
  <p>SAP Global SAP Customer Experience Partner Excellence Award 2023 for Customer Success Management</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Winner: Deloitte</li>
    <li>Finalist: Altivate</li>
    <li>Finalist: Avvale</li>
  </ul>
  <p>SAP Global SAP Customer Experience Partner Excellence Award 2023 for SAP Business Technology Platform Customer Success</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Winner: Seidor</li>
    <li>Finalist: NTT DATA</li>
    <li>Finalist: All for One Customer Experience</li>
  </ul>
  <p>SAP Global SAP Customer Experience Partner Excellence Award 2023 for Go-to-Market</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Winner: IBM</li>
    <li>Finalist: Tech Mahindra</li>
    <li>Finalist: PwC</li>
  </ul>
  <p>Visit the <a href="http://news.sap.com/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-debuts-new-cx-generative-ai-capabilities-to-enhance-customer-experiences-and-boost-business-operations">SAP Debuts New CX Generative AI Capabilities to Enhance Customer Experiences and Boost Business Operations</h3>
        <p><em><a href="/">Read the news</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><strong>Media Contact:</strong> Angelika Merz, +41 58 871-7216, <a href="mailto:angelika.merz@sap.com">angelika.merz@sap.com</a>, CET<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>This document contains forward-looking statements, which are predictions, projections, or other statements about future events. These statements are based on current expectations, forecasts, and assumptions that are subject to risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results and outcomes to materially differ. Additional information regarding these risks and uncertainties may be found in our filings with the Securities and Exchange Commission, including but not limited to the risk factors section of SAP’s 2022 Annual Report on Form 20-F.<br>© 2023 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-customer-experience-live</category>
            <category>sap-award/sap-global-lob-partner-excellence-awards</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Revolutionizing Customer Experience: The AI Advantage]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/ai-advantage-revolutionizing-customer-experience</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/ai-advantage-revolutionizing-customer-experience</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Read about the AI technology from SAP that leads to better business outcomes and an impressively satisfying customer experience.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-customer-experience-live</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Debuts New CX Generative AI Capabilities to Enhance Customer Experiences and Boost Business Operations]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/new-cx-generative-ai-capabilities</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/new-cx-generative-ai-capabilities</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[From SAP Customer Experience LIVE, SAP has announced new generative AI capabilities for the CX solution portfolio. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>product/sap-customer-data-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-customer-experience</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-customer-experience-live</category>
            <category>product/sap-emarsys-customer-engagement</category>
            <category>product/sap-sales-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-service-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Online Metals Disrupts the Manufacturing Industry and Expands Business with SAP Commerce Cloud]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/online-metals-manufacturing-industry-sap-commerce-cloud</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/online-metals-manufacturing-industry-sap-commerce-cloud</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Online Metals is disrupting the manufacturing industry and expanding its business with SAP Commerce Cloud. Learn how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_121051d714fe237b93b9bb91b6feef8b4424ee2ee.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_121051d714fe237b93b9bb91b6feef8b4424ee2ee.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_121051d714fe237b93b9bb91b6feef8b4424ee2ee.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Online Metals Disrupts the Manufacturing Industry and Expands Business with SAP Commerce Cloud" src="./media_121051d714fe237b93b9bb91b6feef8b4424ee2ee.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="online-metals-disrupts-the-manufacturing-industry-and-expands-business-with-sap-commerce-cloud">Online Metals Disrupts the Manufacturing Industry and Expands Business with SAP Commerce Cloud</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Founded in 1998 as a Seattle-based garage startup, Online Metals has since become the <a href="https://www.onlinemetals.com/en">world’s leading e-commerce metal and plastics supplier</a>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>With over 60,000 products that can be shipped directly to any location, this once garage-based business is now a successful enterprise with seven distribution and pickup locations and over 100 employees across the United States. Online Metals offers raw materials like alloy steel, brass, copper, nickel, titanium, and zinc cut-to-size or in small and medium quantities and various shapes. Customers span the creative genius of private individuals like artists and engineers to multinational corporations and government agencies.</p>
  <p>Online Metals is a company that is truly obsessed with customer experience. Its north star is the notion that “the last thing you do is the first thing the customer sees. So, let’s do it right!”</p>
  <h2 id="powering-industry-disruption">Powering Industry Disruption</h2>
  <p>Online Metals has already established itself as a digital powerhouse. It is now making even bigger waves by trailblazing the way it goes to market and engages with its customers. Fueled by its desire to continuously improve, Online Metals invested in SAP Commerce Cloud with marketplace solution provider Mirakl in order to deliver its most recent innovation: the first-of-its-kind metals and plastics catalog marketplace. The online catalog marketplace has opened the door for new sales channels and raw material manufacturers to sell their products directly via the Online Metals e-commerce platform.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-commerce-cloud-grow-your-business-through-enterprise-grade-e-commerce">SAP Commerce Cloud: Grow your business through enterprise-grade e-commerce</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm/commerce-cloud.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>From an industry perspective, the SAP-powered digital platform has empowered Online Metals to expand into disruptive new models within the metals industry. More specifically, it has enabled the team to sell products that have been traditionally non-transparent with pricing and also difficult to order in small quantities. As a result, the team can now support a growing number of micro-manufacturers throughout the U.S. that rely on a just-in-time, small-quantity metal supplier.</p>
  <p>“The SAP-licensed version of Mirakl we used allows us to quickly onboard new sellers who want to reach the millions of metal buyers Online Metals reaches. We take care to only bring on the best sellers who provide the products our metal buyers want,” said Gregory Raece, president of Online Metals. “In fact, so great was the demand to sell on Online Metals that Mirakl even awarded us a ‘Fast Start’ award at their Mirakl B2B Summit in Chicago this April.”</p>
  <p>The addition of the metal catalog marketplace has enabled the Online Metals team to better serve its customers. Sellers like <a href="https://tciprecision.com/">TCI Precision Metals</a> have already seen the benefits of using the new sales channels.</p>
  <p>“The Mirakl team is beyond excited to be at the heart of this first-of-its-kind marketplace pioneering the digital transformation in metals and plastics supplies,” said Marc Teulières, general manager B2B, Mirakl. “By pairing the Mirakl suite of solutions with a remarkable vision for digital transformation, Online Metals has created a win-win-win: buyers can find the precise products they need, suppliers are uncovering new sales opportunities, and the business is on a path to streamlined growth.”</p>
  <h2 id="driving-continuous-innovation">Driving Continuous Innovation</h2>
  <p>Every expanding business encounters obstacles in its growth journey. But with SAP technology, Online Metals has been able to support its unique business models, developing an excellent technical footprint that empowers its customers, enables flexibility and innovation, and showcases what truly matters: its distinctive and quality customer service and products.</p>
  <p>Hear more customer stories at the <a href="https://www.sap.com/events/customer-experience-live.html">SAP Customer Experience LIVE virtual experience</a>.</p>
  <p>For more information on how SAP Commerce Cloud can transform the way your business engages with its customers, visit the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm/e-commerce-platforms.html">E-Commerce area of sap.com</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Geert Leeman is chief revenue officer for SAP Customer Experience.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="join-cx-leaders-from-around-the-world-at-sap-customer-experience-live">Join CX leaders from around the world at SAP Customer Experience LIVE</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/events/customer-experience-live.html">Register now</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>industry/mining: industry/mill-products</category>
            <category>product/sap-commerce-cloud</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-customer-experience-live</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Currency of Customer Trust in Retail]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/the-currency-of-customer-trust-in-retail</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/the-currency-of-customer-trust-in-retail</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Building trustworthy customer experiences means sharing information and devoting resources to enhancing consumers’ trust.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>core-topic/sustainable-business-operations</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
            <category>content-type/business-case</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Generative AI Takes Employee Experience at Delta Air Lines to New Heights]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/generative-ai-employee-experience-delta</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/generative-ai-employee-experience-delta</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With AI and SAP, Delta Air Lines provides a positive, personalized employee experience that motivates people to go above and beyond.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>industry/travel-transportation</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Gibson Makes Beautiful Music with High Tech and Strategy]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/gibson-makes-music-high-tech-strategy</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/gibson-makes-music-high-tech-strategy</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Technology helps Gibson connect with customers easily and in the ways that they want. Learn more about the company's strategy and tech duet.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-engagement</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/e-commerce</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-emarsys</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>industry/media: industry/sports-entertainment</category>
            <category>news-tag/nrf</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Gibson Keeps Its “Massive Span” of Fans Happy]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/videos/how-gibson-keeps-its-massive-span-of-fans-happy</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/videos/how-gibson-keeps-its-massive-span-of-fans-happy</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Gibson Brands uses SAP Emarsys technology to better understand what its customers – or “fans” – want and where each person is along in a unique journey.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>content-type/video</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-emarsys</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How PILLER Increased Customer Service with SAP Customer Experience Solutions]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/piller-increased-customer-service-sap-cx</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/piller-increased-customer-service-sap-cx</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With the help of SAP, PILLER was able to share information and optimize business processes across sales, service, and marketing.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_183ba6c7acd6d09f1a49eb03d61c336ed1830707f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_183ba6c7acd6d09f1a49eb03d61c336ed1830707f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_183ba6c7acd6d09f1a49eb03d61c336ed1830707f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="How PILLER Increased Customer Service with SAP Customer Experience Solutions" src="./media_183ba6c7acd6d09f1a49eb03d61c336ed1830707f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="how-piller-increased-customer-service-with-sap-customer-experience-solutions">How PILLER Increased Customer Service with SAP Customer Experience Solutions</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><a href="https://www.piller.de/">PILLER Blowers &#x26; Compressors</a> produces high-performance blowers and compressors and customized solutions to meet specific requirements of various industries. Its global network of wholly owned subsidiaries and joint ventures enables it to serve an international customer base.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>To increase customer service quality, the company wanted to share information and optimize business processes across its sales, service, and marketing activities.</p>
  <h2 id="moving-from-manual-processes-to-integrated-activities">Moving from Manual Processes to Integrated Activities</h2>
  <p>At PILLER, different departments were using their own IT solutions.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-customer-experience-solutions-help-connect-customer-data-improve-loyalty-and-grow-your-business">SAP Customer Experience solutions help connect customer data, improve loyalty, and grow your business</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The service department had manual processes, such as Microsoft Excel spreadsheets, to dispatch service technicians. The technicians were logging into a central server to retrieve data and recording customer support by e-mails and conversations. The sales department had a basic access environment due to custom-made products with individual serial numbers. There was no master data; tailored sales quotes were done on paper, posing challenges for data updating and quality. The marketing department was conducting its business, like capturing trade-fair leads or planning and executing campaigns, by hand and with spreadsheets. All these manual activities were time intensive and prone to human error.</p>
  <p>To enable the marketing, sales, and service teams to perform to the best of their abilities, PILLER wanted solutions that allowed it to share important information. It wished to harmonize all customer-related processes, from initial contact and order management to delivery of spare parts and follow-up.</p>
  <p>“For new products or customers, it’s important that real-time master data in our core software is mirrored in our sales, service, and marketing systems. We can do this by integrating SAP Customer Experience solutions and SAP Field Service Management with SAP S/4HANA,” said Frank Münzner, in-house SAP consultant for Lead to Cash at PILLER Blowers &#x26; Compressors GmbH.</p>
  <h2 id="adopting-cloud-solutions-to-achieve-innovative-customer-service">Adopting Cloud Solutions to Achieve Innovative Customer Service</h2>
  <p>PILLER employed the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm/sales-cloud.html">SAP Sales Cloud</a> solution to help address the needs of its sales team and integrate functionalities, such as managing quotes and orders, in one place. The solution offers a search capability and a modern, intuitive user interface.</p>
  <p>The company is using the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/field-service-management.html">SAP Field Service Management mobile app</a> to help create service tickets, which are the single point of customer contact, with product serial numbers and metadata. Integrating this mobile app with the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm/service-cloud.html">SAP Service Cloud</a> solution can enable technicians to receive service ticket information on an Apple iPad, so they can have everything they need to carry out their work. This can also translate to good customer support.</p>
  <p>By deploying the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm/marketing.html">SAP Marketing Cloud</a> solution and integrating it with SAP Sales Cloud, PILLER now proactively shares data, such as service tickets, lead opportunities, and customer contacts, between the sales and marketing teams. This lets the company contact a customer with a warranty option or service cost reduction, for example.</p>
  <p>PILLER has now integrated the three SAP Customer Experience solutions for sales, service, and marketing and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/field-service-management.html">SAP Field Service Management</a> with <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/s4hana.html">SAP S/4HANA</a>, the company’s enterprise resource planning (ERP) software.</p>
  <p>PILLER partnered with <a href="https://www.fis-gmbh.de/en/">FIS Global</a> to gain advice about new functionalities and implementation support, while <a href="https://www.ibsolution.com/en/">IBsolution</a> provided guidance around leveraging the potential in terms of business transformation and digitization.</p>
  <h2 id="gaining-comprehensive-customer-visibility-with-integrated-solutions">Gaining Comprehensive Customer Visibility with Integrated Solutions</h2>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="resolve-customer-issues-faster-with-proactive-ai-enabled-field-service-management-software-from-sap">Resolve customer issues faster with proactive, AI-enabled field service management software from SAP</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/field-service-management.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The major advantage in connecting the SAP Customer Experience portfolio, SAP Field Service Management, and SAP S/4HANA is that real-time data can be available across all these solutions. While master data, such as for a new product, customer, or material, is entered and kept in SAP S/4HANA as the core software, it’s automatically pushed into the other integrated solutions.</p>
  <p>This is helping PILLER deliver highly efficient and innovative customer service and business models. The company gains a comprehensive view of worldwide customers in real time while interacting with them at each stage of their journey in a targeted manner.</p>
  <p>There are now customer-related processes across departments, sites, and systems as well as consistent communication throughout the company, thanks to standardized forms and templates. The business is achieving agile sales with faster response times and better allocation of target groups. It’s also making decisions for customer management based on facts and analyses.</p>
  <p>Other benefits the company achieved were:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>360-degree view of customers worldwide in real time</li>
    <li>90% less paper with digital processes</li>
    <li>30% reduction in effort by using digital processes</li>
  </ul>
  <p>“We’ve always combined tradition with innovation when manufacturing our blowers. With SAP Customer Experience solutions, our customer management operations are superior to those of our competitors. We’re able to keep a close eye on processes and respond quickly and accordingly,” said Thomas Henzler, CIO at PILLER Blowers &#x26; Compressors GmbH.</p>
  <h2 id="rolling-out-customer-centric-solutions">Rolling Out Customer-Centric Solutions</h2>
  <p>Combining <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm.html">SAP Customer Experience solutions</a> and the SAP Field Service Management mobile app with SAP S/4HANA is helping deliver real-time data for integrated processes.</p>
  <p>The integration of the SAP Field Service Management mobile app with SAP Service Cloud is being piloted with three service technicians and garnering positive feedback so far.</p>
  <p>Watch an <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm/sales-cloud.html?video=189daad3-437e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b">overview video</a> of SAP Sales Cloud to help build lasting customer relationships and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm/service-cloud.html?pdf-asset=983be5bb-b27d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff&#x26;page=1">learn more about SAP Service Cloud</a> to maximize customer lifetime value with connected service. Read about the benefits companies achieved with <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/customer-stories/topcon.html">SAP Customer Experience solutions</a>. View a <a href="https://www.sap.com/sea/products/scm/field-service-management/features.html?video=66ec8033-617e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b">solution demo</a> and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/field-service-management/features.html?video=f83398c5-247e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b">overview video</a> to learn how to maximize productivity and asset uptime with SAP Field Service Management. <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/field-service-management.html?video=14f5efa9-427e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b">Learn what benefits other enterprises achieved</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Karin Fent is senior director of Global Customer Success Digital Supply Chain at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-sap-news-delivered-to-your-inbox-once-a-week">Get the latest SAP news delivered to your inbox once a week</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/nl/sap-news-center-newsletter/index.html">Sign Up</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/field-service-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-customer-experience</category>
            <category>product/sap-marketing-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>product/sap-sales-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-service-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Named a Leader in 2023 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Digital Commerce]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/sap-named-a-leader-in-2023-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-digital-commerce</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/sap-named-a-leader-in-2023-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-digital-commerce</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[This is the ninth time in a row SAP has been rated a leader by Gartner in the Magic Quadrant for Digital Commerce. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/magic-quadrant</category>
            <category>product/sap-commerce-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-customer-experience</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Digital Social Objects: The Emotional Glue of Customer Experiences]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/digital-social-objects-the-emotional-glue-of-customer-experiences</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/digital-social-objects-the-emotional-glue-of-customer-experiences</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The future of customer experience revolves around products and services that have meaning. Digital social objects help create these meaningful connections.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>content-type/trends-predictions</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Five forces shaping the future of customer experience]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/research/five-forces-shaping-the-future-cx</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/research/five-forces-shaping-the-future-cx</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn about the five forces that are shaping the future of customer experience, including the rise of AI, social media, and the demand for personalization.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>content-type/original-research</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Data Transparency Supercharges AI-Fueled Customer Experiences]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/data-transparency-ai-customer-experience</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/data-transparency-ai-customer-experience</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Customers want personalized CX, but often do not understand how sharing data and AI supercharge their retail experiences. Learn how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-emarsys</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Tech Makes Shopping Quick and Easy for Bosch Customers]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/bosch-tech-makes-shopping-easy</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/bosch-tech-makes-shopping-easy</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Whether in-store or online, Bosch digital assistants and SAP Marketing Cloud connect to improve Bosch’s customer experience. Find out how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_13ffa0beda0091536a416843690b9f278471170cd.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_13ffa0beda0091536a416843690b9f278471170cd.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_13ffa0beda0091536a416843690b9f278471170cd.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="How Tech Makes Shopping Quick and Easy for Bosch Customers" src="./media_13ffa0beda0091536a416843690b9f278471170cd.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="how-tech-makes-shopping-quick-and-easy-for-bosch-customers">How Tech Makes Shopping Quick and Easy for Bosch Customers</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Benefits of <a href="/topics/ecommerce">e-commerce</a> include reaching new customers and better personalizing service. But what if your customers need – and have spent decades relying on – the in-store expertise of your associates? To find a very specific product? For use with another very specific product? To accomplish a very specific task?</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“More and more of our users are coming online…[and] they still want to have the similar guidance and the systems they had in-store,” Ganna Lobachevska, the touchpoint owner of Product Finder and Product Guidance at <a href="https://www.boschtools.com/us/en/">Bosch Power Tools Accessories</a>, told SAP at NRF 2023 for a new video. “Our overall goal is to make it easier for our users to find the right accessory for their job.”</p>
  <p>Of course, making something <em>easy to do</em> on the front end is seldom <em>easy to build</em> on the back end. And that was Bosch’s challenge when helping online shoppers narrow their search for the perfect jigsaw blade, drill bit, or abrasive wheel from a truly massive accessory portfolio.</p>
  <p>“Any company with a wide range of products has to think how they can simplify the user journey…and how they can make it easier for the customers to find the right product,” Lobachevska said. “With the Bosch <a href="https://www.bosch-professional.com/gb/en/knowledge-innovation/accessories-product-finder/">Accessory Advisor</a>, we provide a solution that makes it easier and faster.”</p>
  <p>Building that easier, faster solution meant finding a high-tech way to satisfy a peculiar demand by online shoppers.</p>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1dbf147ad03dc11ba749845b8c16dd72ecc9059a2.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1dbf147ad03dc11ba749845b8c16dd72ecc9059a2.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1dbf147ad03dc11ba749845b8c16dd72ecc9059a2.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="How High Tech Helps Bosch Shoppers Find the Right Product" src="./media_1dbf147ad03dc11ba749845b8c16dd72ecc9059a2.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://youtu.be/d6hDKHbogfg">How High Tech Helps Bosch Shoppers Find the Right Product</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="when-brick-and-mortar-set-the-bar-almost-too-high">When Brick-and-Mortar Set the Bar (Almost) Too High</h2>
  <p>Selecting a specific power tool accessory for a specific job – and ensuring it’s compatible with your specific power tool – are big reasons that people historically shopped at brick-and-mortar stores, according to Lobachevska. It makes sense, right? You can consult with a knowledgeable human sales associate.</p>
  <p>But Bosch’s e-commerce customers expect the same in-store-style expertise via a quick and painless online exchange, according to Lobachevska. And she doesn’t seem worried.</p>
  <p>“The Accessory Advisor guides the user through a series of very simple questions,” Lobachevska said. “In the end, they have three perfect recommendations for the work they want to do.”</p>
  <p>It’s pretty much an online conversation that yields the right product, according to Lobachevska. And Bosch found the right tech – and partners – to make these virtual dialogues happen.</p>
  <h2 id="tech-to-the-rescue">Tech to the Rescue</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="deliver-customer-engagements-across-channels-and-at-scale-with-sap-marketing-cloud">Deliver customer engagements across channels and at scale with SAP Marketing Cloud</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm/marketing.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“We realized that there is a need for a better user guidance,” Lobachevska said of Bosch’s decision to go with <a href="https://zoovu.com/customers/bosch-power-tools">Zoovu</a>, a Boston-based digital commerce search platform and partner solution in SAP’s industry cloud. “It offered us the best.”</p>
  <p>Zoovu’s Semantic Studio translates technical jargon into e-commerce-friendly prose, which saves time for both Bosch data managers and shoppers. A few artificial intelligence (AI)-assisted questions later, and these accessory hunters have enjoyed a smooth, seamless customer experience.</p>
  <p>“This means that our customers spend less time searching for a product,” Lobachevska said. “And when they purchase the product, it’s the right one and they are more satisfied.”</p>
  <p>This increases efficiency, according to Lobachevska. It also cuts down on returns and poor online reviews.</p>
  <h2 id="powering-forward">Powering Forward</h2>
  <p>Whether in-store or online, Bosch digital assistants and SAP Marketing Cloud connect to improve Bosch’s data analytics, business insights, and customer experience, <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2023/04/2c39bc42-6d7e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">according to an SAP assessment</a>. Those digital assistants have already helped enhance the customer experience for more than 1 million Bosch shoppers across more than 35 global markets, boosting engagement up to 65% as well as increasing customer loyalty and satisfaction.</p>
  <p>And still more can be done by connecting all of that to the Accessory Advisor, according to Lobachevska.</p>
  <p>“We would like to connect the Bosch Accessory Advisor with our CRM system, which is basically SAP Marketing Cloud,” Lobachevska said. “This will allow us to gain business insights, to build better personas, and to make the user experience even better because it’ll be more personalized.”</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/e-commerce</category>
            <category>news-tag/nrf</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
            <category>product/sap-marketing-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How High Tech Helps Bosch Shoppers Find the Right Product]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/videos/how-high-tech-helps-bosch-shoppers-find-the-right-product</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/videos/how-high-tech-helps-bosch-shoppers-find-the-right-product</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Find out how cutting-edge tech makes Bosch’s Accessory Advisor so easy: a few simple questions — like an online conversation — get you exactly what...]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>content-type/video</category>
            <category>product/sap-marketing-cloud</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>