<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/sap-services-and-support/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Retaining Customers Through Support Experience and Efficiency]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/retaining-customers-through-support-experience-and-efficiency</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/retaining-customers-through-support-experience-and-efficiency</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A smooth support experience and efficient support teams combine to delight and retain customers when it comes to customer support. Learn how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/built-in-support</category>
            <category>news-tag/incident-solution-matching</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-for-me</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Customer Support at SAP: Where Artificial Intelligence Meets Application Integration]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/customer-support-ai-meets-application-integration</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/customer-support-ai-meets-application-integration</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Customer Support is owning and driving end-to-end customer support experiences powered by AI. Read to find out how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a24c027bda61c9797c1244107749e253bbea24a8.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a24c027bda61c9797c1244107749e253bbea24a8.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1a24c027bda61c9797c1244107749e253bbea24a8.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Customer Support at SAP: Where Artificial Intelligence Meets Application Integration" src="./media_1a24c027bda61c9797c1244107749e253bbea24a8.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="customer-support-at-sap-where-artificial-intelligence-meets-application-integration">Customer Support at SAP: Where Artificial Intelligence Meets Application Integration</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>On April 1, 2024, SAP <a href="/2024/04/cloud-transformation-adoption-revolution-expectations-outcomes-meet">formed</a> Customer Services &#x26; Delivery – a new Board area that will focus on maximizing innovation adoption and customer value in the cloud.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>This is good news – not just for customers but also for the ecosystem. In recent months, SAP had already identified that when engineering teams deliver innovations, there is a corresponding need to provide customers with guidance on how they can swiftly adopt and consume innovation. Customer Services &#x26; Delivery was created to bring together the offerings that help customers tap the value of SAP’s integrated portfolio.</p>
  <p>By virtue of its function, the Customer Support organization fits into this strategic setup quite naturally. To learn more about how Customer Support is owning and driving end-to-end customer support experiences powered by AI, I met with Stefan Steinle, executive vice president and head of Customer Support, SAP SE.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Q: How would you describe the role of Customer Support in SAP’s success?</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><strong>A:</strong> Customer support is a differentiating factor among companies that are equally positioned in functional richness, usability, quality, deployability, or configurability. While signing up a new customer is considered a huge win, being able to delight and retain the customer is equally important.</p>
  <p><a href="https://support.sap.com/en/index.html">Support at SAP</a> has been singularly impactful in advancing SAP’s customer success stories by proactively responding to customer needs and building long-term relationships. In addition to helping customers solve day-to-day problems, we are business partners who proactively work with customers toward achieving their business goals.</p>
  <p>The Customer Support group encompasses much more than bug fixes. In addition to regular ticket resolutions, we use SAP Cloud ALM to help guide customers in application lifecycle management by enabling their transformation to the cloud and the operation of hybrid environments. We help customers help themselves through self-services and we proactively consult with our engineering teams to improve SAP products based on support-related feedback and learnings. Thanks to our support engineers, SAP has delivered over 1,000 improvements in the last 12 months.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Q: How is SAP’s AI story shaping up when it comes to Customer Support? What is the AI strategy for Customer Support?</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><strong>A:</strong> With our focus on value realization, the push to enhance support with AI has never been higher. To start with, we have invested in digitalizing mission-critical business processes with AI.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="revolutionize-your-business-with-generative-ai-innovations-from-sap">Revolutionize your business with generative AI innovations from SAP</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>There are three parts toward bringing these business processes into the fold of AI-powered offerings. With the help of SAP Signavio Process Transformation Suite, we can measure metrics around the customer’s business processes to gauge efficiency, bottlenecks, and opportunities for improvement. Alternatively, customers can use this as a blueprint to review these metrics themselves. The next layer delivers business transformational AI services. And finally, we have a platform that provides tools to support a closed-loop approach for AI innovation in services and support.</p>
  <p>Coming to the AI strategy for Customer Support, we believe that any innovations in AI must be in lockstep with application integration, meaning AI developments can only bring business value when they are infused and integrated into the applications used in a business process or scenario.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Q: In the context of Customer Support, could you give some examples of how AI brings business value?</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><strong>A:</strong> While the real-world applications are countless, we could broadly classify them into three groups.</p>
  <p>We use AI to correct – this means we use AI for the support experience, for personalization, and for data-driven decisions. We use AI to connect – here you find the platform, tools, and applications along customer touchpoints. We use AI to catalyze – this covers self-service, issue resolutions, and predictive and preventative support.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Q: How does SAP realize this?</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><strong>A:</strong> We do this by taking advantage of our AI development platform that can bring all the data of services and support into one place. This platform helps bring endless possibilities based on the unique needs of customers’ businesses. On our part, we ensure that we explore the power of AI across business contexts.</p>
  <p>By building AI models, we have the power to transform business in the way we want. We can plug these models into support systems and portals to extract the full value of AI in support. By collecting data and events from support systems and portals, we can even train AI models that can deliver value later. By processing the context and history of the customer, we can provide highly personalized support experiences – at runtime.</p>
  <p>I could go on, but at this point I would urge you to follow the Customer Support tracks at <a href="https://www.sap.com/events/sapphire.html">SAP Sapphire &#x26; ASUG Annual Conference Orlando on June 3–5, 2024</a>, to learn about the technologies and strategies that are shaping the future of Customer Support and business transformation. Be sure to bookmark your favorite topics from this guide: <a href="https://community.sap.com/t5/technology-blogs-by-sap/your-ultimate-guide-for-sap-sapphire-2024-orlando/ba-p/13699589">Your Ultimate Guide for SAP Sapphire Orlando in 2024</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Renuka Abraham is part of Customer Support at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="join-experts-speakers-and-peers-at-sap-sapphire-in-2024-to-explore-innovations-that-can-help-turn-your-visions-into-reality">Join experts, speakers, and peers at SAP Sapphire in 2024 to explore innovations that can help turn your visions into reality</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/events/sapphire.html">Register today</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Expanded SAP Preferred Success Services Fast-Track the Value of Cloud ERP]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/expanded-sap-preferred-success-services-fast-track-cloud-erp</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/expanded-sap-preferred-success-services-fast-track-cloud-erp</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The SAP Preferred Success service for RISE with SAP, premium can deliver more guidance and insight to help optimize cloud ERP. Find out how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a9061bfb24965c3c00629fea26b76b50e8d33ff1.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a9061bfb24965c3c00629fea26b76b50e8d33ff1.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1a9061bfb24965c3c00629fea26b76b50e8d33ff1.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Expanded SAP Preferred Success Services Fast-Track the Value of Cloud ERP" src="./media_1a9061bfb24965c3c00629fea26b76b50e8d33ff1.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="expanded-sap-preferred-success-services-fast-track-the-value-of-cloud-erp">Expanded SAP Preferred Success Services Fast-Track the Value of Cloud ERP</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Navigating disruption and uncertainty is always daunting, especially in economies and industries that evolve at different speeds. The influences of <a href="/topics/ai">AI</a>, post-globalization trends, regulatory changes, constrained capital, and other factors are impacting every region and industry, albeit at different rates and levels of severity.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>By using any of a variety of <a href="https://www.sap.com/services-support/service-offerings/preferred-success.html">SAP Preferred Success</a> services when implementing and adopting SAP S/4HANA Cloud, customers can strategically and effectively handle each change. Their efforts include 44% improved user experiences, 40% faster incident resolution, 38% better enablement and upskilling, and 38% faster time to value from their technology investments, according to a <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2023/05/18fe9a13-717e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Forrester Consulting analysis</a>.</p>
  <p>And now, with the latest offering for SAP Preferred Success, customers are going beyond navigating turbulence. They can also maximize opportunities, reduce risks, and understand how dynamic economic and market forces impact their long-term success.</p>
  <h2 id="introducing-sap-preferred-success-for-rise-with-sap-premium">Introducing SAP Preferred Success for RISE with SAP, premium</h2>
  <p>The SAP Preferred Success service for RISE with SAP, premium can deliver more guidance and insight to help accelerate and optimize the value of the cloud ERP journey, in addition to the foundational services of SAP Preferred Success.</p>
  <p>With personalized services designed to meet unique business needs proactively, customers can realize benefits, including:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Improved productivity</strong> with access to SAP knowledge and best practices</li>
    <li><strong>Accelerated ROI</strong> with tailored guidance and expert support to organize SAP solutions faster and more efficiently</li>
    <li><strong>Fewer risks</strong> by following best practice recommendations that minimize system disruptions and help ensure smooth operations</li>
    <li><strong>Better alignment</strong> by matching SAP solutions with organization goals, capitalizing on the features and innovations of every release</li>
    <li><strong>Higher efficiency</strong> by consistently fine-tuning and providing personalized recommendations aligned with specific business value drivers</li>
  </ul>
  <p>For customers such as <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/customer-stories/kyocera.html">Kyocera Document Solutions Australia</a> (Kyocera), SAP Preferred Success helps create a solid foundation for modernizing business operations. “Using SAP Preferred Success enabled us to accelerate the business acceptance of change and drive a continuous improvement landscape. It has provided an avenue to reevaluate our processes and create a more efficient business,” states Rohan Higgins, chief financial officer of Kyocera Document Solutions.</p>
  <p>As a result of the quality and caliber of the SAP expertise and active engagement, Kyocera has successfully moved 100% of its ERP processes to the cloud, leading to zero manual touchpoints across its forecasting processes. Other customers have realized additional benefits, such as more efficient business processes, smaller database sizes, infrastructure simplification, and reduction of cost centers.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="a-personalized-proactive-partnership-for-the-lifetime-of-your-cloud-solution">A personalized, proactive partnership for the lifetime of your cloud solution</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/services-support/service-offerings/preferred-success.html">Read more on SAP Preferred Success</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP Preferred Success for RISE with SAP, premium can provide additional elements for modernizing business operations, including:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>A dedicated, named enterprise adoption expert</strong> with a strong technical and functional background, who can provide expertise and help orchestrate how-to conversations supporting the build of outcome-focused plans</li>
    <li><strong>Assistance and guidance based on recommended best practices</strong> to help increase the customer’s understanding of its business processes and how the solution is being used</li>
    <li><strong>Ongoing innovation and transformation</strong> through continuous review of the customer’s calendar and plans – including the adoption of entitlements, such as business AI, sustainability, intelligent technologies exploration, and process management</li>
    <li><strong>Clean core guidance and quality checks</strong> for each project phase to help ensure the customer can leverage existing and future innovations within RISE with SAP</li>
  </ul>
  <p>With a dedicated focus on sustainability exploration, SAP Preferred Success for RISE with SAP, premium helps ensure that businesses can embrace a more sustainable future while driving growth and success in the digital age. By leveraging the comprehensive suite of tools and resources provided by SAP and orchestrated by an enterprise adoption expert, organizations can navigate their sustainability initiatives with confidence and precision.</p>
  <p>SAP Preferred Success for RISE with SAP, premium also offers a unique avenue for harnessing the transformative power of AI with cloud ERP. Through a tailored approach, customers are guided by seasoned enterprise adoption experts facilitating a comprehensive exploration of business AI. Customers are then empowered to innovate, automate, and optimize their business processes using the cutting-edge AI capabilities seamlessly integrated into the SAP ecosystem.</p>
  <p>Access to such a wealth of products, tools, and frameworks gives invaluable insights on configuring and customizing AI solutions to suit unique needs. By leveraging built-in AI capabilities from SAP, customers are not only equipped to streamline operations but also to drive innovation and achieve sustained growth in today’s dynamic business landscape.</p>
  <h2 id="accelerating-competitive-outcomes-from-cloud-erp">Accelerating Competitive Outcomes from Cloud ERP</h2>
  <p>As businesses continue to compete in an ever-evolving landscape, the need for innovative solutions that drive growth and efficiency has never been more critical. And SAP Preferred Success for RISE with SAP, premium is ready to help, offering the functional and technical guidance, personalized services, and ongoing support necessary to realize the full potential of the cloud.</p>
  <p>As demonstrated by success stories worldwide, including that of Kyocera, SAP Preferred Success for RISE with SAP, premium is helping customers not only adapt to change but also seize new opportunities for growth. This service is not just a solution; it’s a strategic partnership that can empower organizations to thrive in an ever-evolving world.</p>
  <p>Ready to amplify the impact of your cloud ERP transformation? <a href="https://sap.com/preferred-success">Visit us online</a> or contact your local SAP representative to learn more about SAP Preferred Success for RISE with SAP, premium.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Mine Ecevit is cloud ERP lead for Cloudified Services Sales and Go to Market at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-preferred-success</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Ariba and SAP Business Network Seamlessly Integrated into SAP for Me]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-ariba-business-network-integrated-sap-for-me</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-ariba-business-network-integrated-sap-for-me</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP for Me, the central access point to solution support for customers, is now available for SAP Ariba solutions and SAP Business Network.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f7e35b0ca7f6abf5c3e5f984222aa27df64caab8.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f7e35b0ca7f6abf5c3e5f984222aa27df64caab8.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1f7e35b0ca7f6abf5c3e5f984222aa27df64caab8.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Ariba and SAP Business Network Seamlessly Integrated into SAP for Me" src="./media_1f7e35b0ca7f6abf5c3e5f984222aa27df64caab8.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-ariba-and-sap-business-network-seamlessly-integrated-into-sap-for-me">SAP Ariba and SAP Business Network Seamlessly Integrated into SAP for Me</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><a href="https://me.sap.com/">SAP for Me</a> is our digital companion for our customers, providing them with a personalized one-stop shop across their SAP product portfolio. And now it’s available to SAP Ariba and SAP Business Network customers and partners.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP for Me provides a central access point to solution support. The portal offers a user-friendly interface with improved functionalities that can enable better and faster interaction with SAP support experts and can provide immediate guidance to solutions for daily business tasks. It aims to make detached information a thing of the past on the customer and partner journey to an intelligent enterprise.</p>
  <p>Since November 6, 2023, an English-language experience has been available for customers and partners to begin their exploration before the migration. And as of today, SAP Ariba and SAP Business Network knowledge-related content on SAP for Me is available in over 20 languages.</p>
  <p>SAP for Me provides an integrated and comprehensive platform to help meet the diverse needs of its users. The Services &#x26; Support dashboard features an SAP Ariba card that helps direct users to multiple resources on the legacy SAP Ariba Connect <a href="https://connectsupport.ariba.com/sites#Home-show">platform</a>, including SAP Ariba and SAP Business Network release readiness information, product documentation, announcements, and specific content related to adoption and deployment.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="say-hello-to-your-digital-companion">Say hello to your digital companion</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://me.sap.com/">Check out SAP for Me</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>When getting started with SAP for Me, know that:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>SAP Ariba Connect S-user authorizations are automatically carried over to SAP for Me – no additional access authorization is needed to use SAP for Me.</li>
    <li>The portal gives access to personalized content in the most used languages – English, German, Japanese, Simplified Chinese, French, Portuguese, and Spanish.</li>
    <li>SAP for Me offers intuitive cards that categorize and bucket information for your convenience. Support-relevant cards are mainly located in the Services &#x26; Support and Systems &#x26; Provisioning dashboards.</li>
    <li>The availability, maintenance, and subscriptions for SAP Ariba solutions and SAP Business Network can be found in the availability section of Systems &#x26; Provisioning.</li>
    <li>You can get a holistic view of licenses, orders, and consumption status.</li>
    <li>SAP for Me is also available on mobile devices. The mobile app will be enhanced with additional features and the ability to create and manage a new case.</li>
    <li>The get support application is your primary touchpoint with support.</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="get-support-easier-and-faster">Get Support, Easier and Faster</h2>
  <p>The get support application helps guide customers through technical product issues in real time or reaching SAP experts through an AI-enabled framework. It can provide an integrated and personalized support experience to help simplify and streamline the case creation process. AI can automatically recommend solutions during the interaction, predict the right product categorization, and recommend the most suitable support channel, like Expert Chat, SAP Community, or Ask an Expert Peer, when available for the selected product.</p>
  <h2 id="access-sap-support-on-the-go">Access SAP Support on the Go</h2>
  <p>With the SAP for Me mobile app, support interaction can be possible anywhere and anytime to complete tasks and access information directly on a smartphone. The mobile app can be downloaded from the Apple Store and Google Play Store.</p>
  <p>In conclusion, SAP for Me puts customer and partner interests into focus. While partners can manage their pipeline and customer success, the portal also serves as the central entry point for all support-related topics and questions for customers. It allows access to relevant information, self-services, and consumption status connected to any purchased product portfolio.</p>
  <p>The SAP for Me migration for SAP Ariba solutions and SAP Business Network is a significant milestone as we tap into the next generation of AI opportunities to create an effective experience for our customers while delivering a seamless consistency in the look, feel, and delivery of critical <a href="/topics/support">support services</a>.</p>
  <p>SAP for Me is made for you. Follow SAP for Me on LinkedIn and bookmark SAP for Me on SAP Community to stay updated.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Rohan Patel is global head of Support for SAP Procurement.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="follow-sap-news-on-linkedin-to-stay-informed">Follow SAP News on LinkedIn to stay informed</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news">Connect with us</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-for-me</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhancing Support Experiences with Support Accreditation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/enhancing-support-experiences-with-support-accreditation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/enhancing-support-experiences-with-support-accreditation</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The Support Accreditation course enables customers and partners to make the best use of SAP's offerings and tools. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c17ed9e9e6e8aba827d32e446eff7f7691e16f08.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c17ed9e9e6e8aba827d32e446eff7f7691e16f08.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1c17ed9e9e6e8aba827d32e446eff7f7691e16f08.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Enhancing Support Experiences with Support Accreditation" src="./media_1c17ed9e9e6e8aba827d32e446eff7f7691e16f08.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="enhancing-support-experiences-with-support-accreditation">Enhancing Support Experiences with Support Accreditation</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>The Support Accreditation course offered by SAP plays a vital role in educating partners, customers, and internal employees about <a href="/topics/support">SAP’s support services</a>. In this interview, Simone Engelhardt, SVP and head of Customer Engagement Support for Customer Services &#x26; Delivery at SAP, discusses the importance of support channels, the 24/7 support structure, service continuity, and best practices for interacting effectively with SAP support teams.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Feedback from participants highlights the training’s success in improving the understanding and utilization of support services. Ongoing updates help ensure the course remains relevant amidst evolving technology and business landscapes, with future developments likely to incorporate advancements in artificial intelligence (AI) and machine learning tools for support services.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Q: Can you provide an overview of the Support Accreditation training and its significance for anyone engaging with SAP’s support processes?</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><strong>Engelhardt:</strong> The Support Accreditation is a vital learning tool for our partners and customers as well as for our employees. It’s an informative course that can familiarize participants with SAP support services and help maximize their support experience. This is a unique opportunity to understand all the tools and resources available when interacting with SAP support and to learn efficient ways of engaging with our teams and resolving issues.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>In situations of urgency or escalation, customers might try to contact someone at SAP they personally know rather than follow the regular process. How does Support Accreditation address such situations and educate participants on the importance of following the proper channels?</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>That’s a great point. In urgent or escalated situations, individuals might feel tempted to bypass the usual channels and seek immediate remedies. However, these uninformed measures can result in delays. The Support Accreditation course emphasizes following the correct SAP support processes, which can ensure their issues are routed to the appropriately skilled support teams, leading to more efficient problem resolution.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Can you shed light on how the Support Accreditation training details the importance of our 24/7 support structure and how customers and partners can take advantage of it?</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The course thoroughly details our 24/7 support structure. We work to ensure that participants understand how, no matter their time zone, they can harness this around-the-clock support. It’s about making sure that our customers and partners know that they always have the backing of SAP, no matter when an issue arises.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-started-with-support-from-sap">Get started with support from SAP</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://learning.sap.com/learning-journey/getting-started-with-support-from-sap-support-accreditation">Explore the Support Accreditation course</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>How can customers and partners ensure that their issues are addressed efficiently even when their primary contacts at SAP are out of office?</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>We indeed cover this crucial aspect. The training delves into detail about the Customer Support organization, which aims to ensure service continuity even if specific account contacts at SAP are unavailable. Our course participants are made aware of the various support structures in place to assist them.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>The Support Accreditation training also covers the etiquette and best practices for interacting with SAP support. Can you talk more about this and why it’s important?</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Interacting with support teams forms a large part of managing SAP services, so etiquette and best practices in this area are covered in our course. We guide learners on the most effective ways to communicate with our teams, provide necessary information, and follow prescribed processes for optimal support assistance.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Do you have any insights related to the feedback from Support Accreditation participants? How has the course improved their understanding and utilization of our support services?</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Feedback from Support Accreditation participants has been overwhelmingly positive. Our learners report significantly improved knowledge about SAP support services and tools, and they’ve been successful in applying this knowledge to engage more effectively with SAP support. This has resulted in smoother, quicker issue resolutions, translating to improved satisfaction and service experiences.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>With technology and business requirements evolving, how will the Support Accreditation course adapt to these changes? What future developments can participants expect?</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The course isn’t static; it evolves with the technology landscape and business requirements. We continually update it to include new tools, offerings, or changes to existing processes. This helps ensure that the Support Accreditation training remains up-to-date and continues to be a valuable resource for our customers and partners. Future developments will certainly involve advancements in AI and machine learning tools in support services, so participants can be well prepared for the future of support services.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Chemicals Supplier BYK Harmonized Supply Chain Planning Processes]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/byk-harmonized-supply-chain-planning-processes</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/byk-harmonized-supply-chain-planning-processes</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[BYK, a global supplier of specialty chemicals, has implemented a new supply chain demand planning system using SAP solutions. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/chemicals</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>product/sap-integrated-business-planning-for-supply-chain</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-preferred-success</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
            <category>product/sap-supply-chain-control-tower</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Clear Path to Digital Supply Chain Excellence with SAP Preferred Success]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/digital-supply-chain-excellence-with-sap-preferred-success</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/digital-supply-chain-excellence-with-sap-preferred-success</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Preferred Success can be a guiding light for businesses keen on transforming to digital supply chain operations.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-supply-chain</category>
            <category>news-tag/digitalization</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-preferred-success</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Jowat Creates Seamless, Just-in-Time Operations with SAP Digital Manufacturing]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/jowat-creates-seamless-operations-sap-digital-manufacturing</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/jowat-creates-seamless-operations-sap-digital-manufacturing</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With SAP Digital Manufacturing, Jowat is on its way to having transparent factories with a reduction in risks, errors, and process costs.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1751a2980ab4eaba557c46a3624a271a2fe09bc21.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1751a2980ab4eaba557c46a3624a271a2fe09bc21.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1751a2980ab4eaba557c46a3624a271a2fe09bc21.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Jowat Creates Seamless, Just-in-Time Operations with SAP Digital Manufacturing" src="./media_1751a2980ab4eaba557c46a3624a271a2fe09bc21.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="jowat-creates-seamless-just-in-time-operations-with-sap-digital-manufacturing">Jowat Creates Seamless, Just-in-Time Operations with SAP Digital Manufacturing</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><a href="https://www.jowat.com/en/">Jowat Group</a> is one of the world’s top adhesive manufacturers for industrial use. Tradition and experience from 100 years of corporate development and experience allow it to act as a leading company in technology and innovation in numerous markets and application areas.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Jowat SE’s annual production amounts to 100,000 tons of industrial adhesives. Production is complex and requires high volumes of specialized chemicals and a tremendous amount of power. With raw materials and energy costs skyrocketing, premium manufacturer Jowat looked to get a tighter grip on its inventory management and production processes.</p>
  <p>To ensure maximum efficiency, Jowat requires enough raw materials to fulfill orders while minimizing waste and inventory costs. Moreover, the company needs smooth workflows, as any delay in order placement, production, or the delivery of raw materials can have huge cost implications for the company. As a result, Jowat works hard to ensure that its 24/7 manufacturing processes always run like clockwork.</p>
  <p>With demand for industrial adhesives surging, the company was eager to ensure that its production processes could scale to meet increasing order numbers and still deliver optimum efficiency.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="deliver-individualized-sustainable-and-smart-equipment-products-and-components-in-industrial-manufacturing">Deliver individualized, sustainable, and smart equipment, products, and components in industrial manufacturing</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/industrial-manufacturing.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="targeting-seamless-digital-workflows">Targeting Seamless Digital Workflows</h2>
  <p>Originally established in 1919, Jowat is no stranger to innovation. Leaders at Jowat identified that the next stage of the company’s evolution would require a radical digital transformation of its production and inventory management processes.</p>
  <p>“Our factory workers relied heavily on paper-based processes,” explained Dirk-Alexander Segger, Detmold plant manager at Jowat. “For instance, when employees had finished mixing and decanting adhesives, they handwrote notes to track the volume and type of raw materials that they used during the process. Shortly after decanting, workers would then input the information from their notes into our inventory management and manufacturing execution systems, adding to their workload and increasing the risk of errors.”</p>
  <p>Tracking materials usage manually created time delays, potential for human errors, and discrepancies between the stock numbers recorded in Jowat’s inventory system and the actual volume of raw materials available on the factory floor. Moreover, with information stored across multiple systems and in different formats, plant managers had no clarity to identify process bottlenecks or potential enhancements.</p>
  <p>Annette Podleschny-Borchardt, project lead at Jowat, commented: “To enhance efficiency, improve transparency, and prepare for growth, we decided it was time to go entirely paperless. Building digital processes would give us a more detailed, up-to-date picture of our stock position, which would help drive smarter raw materials purchasing decisions and production improvements.”</p>
  <p>“We aimed to take a more proactive approach to our manufacturing processes. Developing robust, reliable, end-to-end digital workflows was the perfect way to achieve this goal,” explained Christine Künne, head of IT and Business Process Services at Jowat SE.</p>
  <h2 id="embracing-digital-transformation">Embracing Digital Transformation</h2>
  <p>To find the best solution to support its digital transformation initiative, Jowat invited multiple technology vendors to outline the strengths of their solutions. To keep customization low, Jowat targeted a solution that it could easily adapt to meet the highly specialized nature of just-in-time chemicals manufacturing.</p>
  <p>After reviewing 15 different solutions, Jowat selected <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/digital-manufacturing-cloud.html">SAP Digital Manufacturing</a>. In addition to providing a solid foundation for digitalization, SAP Digital Manufacturing can also integrate seamlessly with Jowat’s existing SAP solutions, including <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/s4hana.html">SAP S/4HANA</a>, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/extended-warehouse-management.html">SAP Extended Warehouse Management</a>, and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform.html">SAP Business Technology Platform</a> (SAP BTP).</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sustainable-risk-resilient-manufacturing-is-here">Sustainable, risk-resilient manufacturing is here</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/digital-manufacturing-cloud.html">Learn more about SAP Digital Manufacturing</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“We were immediately interested in SAP Digital Manufacturing because it is a cloud-native solution,” commented Segger. “Previously, we used on-premise solutions that required us to carry out extensive and disruptive updates. With SAP Digital Manufacturing, we get instant access to the latest features thanks to the quarterly release schedule.”</p>
  <p>Jowat also valued SAP’s proactive engagement with the chemicals manufacturing industry. “We really appreciate that SAP is eager to co-innovate with industry leaders like Jowat to develop next-generation manufacturing solutions,” said Podleschny-Borchardt. “Through the SAP Customer Engagement Initiative, we can help expert developers at SAP build smart factory solutions that meet the needs of our sector down to the finest detail.”</p>
  <h2 id="sticking-with-the-experts">Sticking with the Experts</h2>
  <p>To ensure a smooth implementation of SAP Digital Manufacturing, Jowat relied on support from SAP Services and Support.</p>
  <p>“Whenever we hit a stumbling block, the experts helped us work through the issues. For instance, we wanted to develop a dedicated production operation dashboard, which would give plant managers fast access to key production metrics. As this was uncharted territory, it naturally took a lot of time and energy to work through and SAP was behind us every step of the way,” said Segger.</p>
  <p>Currently, Jowat is completing the first phase of the SAP Digital Manufacturing implementation at its Detmold factory before expanding the solution across all plants. Künne explained: “With a phased implementation, we can ensure that the processes we build at our Detmold plant are tried and tested to deliver maximum efficiency. This will give us the best chance of success when we roll out these processes across all our facilities.”</p>
  <p>“Consultants from SAP Services and Support brought not only their expertise to the project, but also the willingness to listen to the needs and the challenges of our industry. Because of this, we were able to collaborate extremely effectively,” added Podleschny-Borchardt.</p>
  <h2 id="driving-efficient-manufacturing-with-high-quality-data">Driving Efficient Manufacturing with High-Quality Data</h2>
  <p>With SAP Digital Manufacturing, Jowat left error-prone, manual processes behind and now benefits from seamless digital workflows with end-to-end transparency. This helps increase quality and ease work for shop floor operators. The activity confirmation is automatically done in the SAP system, enabling real-time inventory insight.</p>
  <p>Consequently, Jowat gained the following benefits:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>100% digitalized manufacturing process</li>
    <li>One source of truth for detailed production information</li>
    <li>Time savings of three person days per week through automated raw material consumption updates allowing employees focus on higher value activities</li>
    <li>100% accurate inventory</li>
  </ul>
  <p>“Today workers feed consumption information at the point of production. Previously, it would take one full-time employee three days a week to track raw materials consumption,” said Segger. “With SAP Digital Manufacturing, we have a real-time, accurate picture of our raw materials usage and needs. This is helping us optimize usage and reduce costs.”</p>
  <p>Podleschny-Borchardt added: “Production processes are so much faster now that we have built streamlined digital processes. Before, our paper-based ways of working could add up to five days to production timelines. With SAP Digital Manufacturing, we’ve shaved off this time, allowing us to produce and distribute products to our customers much faster, boosting satisfaction.”</p>
  <h2 id="planning-ahead-for-an-ai-driven-future">Planning Ahead for an AI-Driven Future</h2>
  <p>With reliable, up-to-date information in SAP Digital Manufacturing, plant managers and leaders at Jowat can have full visibility across the entire manufacturing cycle. “SAP Digital Manufacturing has helped improve the traceability of our products and given us a much more detailed understanding of our manufacturing operations. Ultimately, that helps to enhance planning and provides new insights into potential process improvements,” said Künne.</p>
  <p>Jowat’s plans for SAP Digital Manufacturing go far beyond a global rollout. The company is already exploring the potential to scale and streamline manufacturing processes further with artificial intelligence (AI) and Internet of Things (IoT) technologies.</p>
  <p>“AI holds tremendous potential for us,” reflected Podleschny-Borchardt. “We’re excited to explore how it can help us to ensure consistently excellent quality across heavily customized product lines and how we can enhance production uptime with IoT-driven predictive maintenance. Having an AI-ready solution like SAP Digital Manufacturing at the heart of our operations makes taking these next steps in our innovation journey much easier.”</p>
  <p>Summarizing the overall benefits, Künne concluded: “With the implementation of SAP Digital Manufacturing through SAP Services and Support, we see ourselves on the way to becoming a transparent factory with a reduction in risks, errors, and process costs thanks to optimized processes.”</p>
  <p><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/customer-stories/smart-press-shop.html">Discover benefits other companies have gained</a>, including improved quality with AI-assisted visual inspection. Be sure to listen to the <a href="https://event.on24.com/eventRegistration/console/apollox/mainEvent?&#x26;eventid=4294893&#x26;sessionid=1&#x26;username=&#x26;partnerref=web&#x26;format=fhvideo1&#x26;mobile=&#x26;flashsupportedmobiledevice=&#x26;helpcenter=&#x26;key=2A85021F45D14DF9C657C622AA74D180&#x26;newConsole=true&#x26;nxChe=true&#x26;newTabCon=true&#x26;consoleEarEventConsole=false&#x26;text_language_id=en&#x26;playerwidth=748&#x26;playerheight=526&#x26;eventuserid=626283838&#x26;contenttype=A&#x26;mediametricsessionid=550094581&#x26;mediametricid=6052808&#x26;usercd=626283838&#x26;mode=launch">webinar</a> about how a renowned manufacturer revolutionizes manufacturing with Industry 4.0. Also, read this <a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/dg/risk-resilient-supply-chain-manufacturing/typ.html">report</a> from Oxford Economics about making supply chains more resilient and sustainable.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>Karin Fent is senior director of Global Customer Success for Digital Supply Chain at SAP.</p>
        <p>Top image courtesy of Jowat.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>industry/mining: industry/mill-products</category>
            <category>product/sap-digital-manufacturing</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Support Accreditation: A Consultant’s Hack for Maximizing SAP’s Support Offerings]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/support-accreditation-maximizing-sap-support-offerings</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/support-accreditation-maximizing-sap-support-offerings</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Support Accreditation is a course that enables customers and partners to make the best use of SAP's offerings and tools. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/real-time-support</category>
            <category>product/sap-cloud-alm</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Why Price Promotions Are Relevant During Times of Rising Costs and High Inflation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/why-price-promotions-are-relevant</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/why-price-promotions-are-relevant</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Price promotions management helps grocery retailers and consumer product companies quickly adapt to rising costs and inflation. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a8dd9ea2036fe84d6e4484f051ebd1dd6f9b770c.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a8dd9ea2036fe84d6e4484f051ebd1dd6f9b770c.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1a8dd9ea2036fe84d6e4484f051ebd1dd6f9b770c.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Why Price Promotions Are Relevant During Times of Rising Costs and High Inflation" src="./media_1a8dd9ea2036fe84d6e4484f051ebd1dd6f9b770c.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="why-price-promotions-are-relevant-during-times-of-rising-costs-and-high-inflation">Why Price Promotions Are Relevant During Times of Rising Costs and High Inflation</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Consumer product companies and grocery retailers have leveraged the power of promotions for decades, attracting consumers and building enduring relationships with them. The approach encompasses various marketing strategies that retailers and consumer product companies employ to boost sales volume and overall turnover. A variety of tactics are leveraged, such as product and packaging modifications, advertising initiatives, alterations in product placement, and other point-of-sale (POS) campaigns.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>But when costs and inflation increase, such promotions become particularly valuable, relieving consumers’ wallets while maintaining competitiveness and fostering lasting customer loyalty. The approach is then narrowed down to short-term price reductions – where regular shelf prices of selected items or entire shopping baskets are significantly marked down for a predefined campaign period complemented by extensive advertising.</p>
  <h2 id="understand-the-true-purpose-and-impact">Understand the True Purpose and Impact</h2>
  <p>Thanks to product designers and managers in the <a href="/topics/consumer-products">consumer products industry</a> and those responsible for grocery retail marketing, many different promotion types have emerged in recent years. Even though there is a high number of variants and different mixed forms, promotions can be broadly categorized into three main types:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Filling up (household) stock</strong> encourages higher-than-normal purchase quantities for each shopping trip by offering multipacks, product bundles, larger packaging sizes, and refills.</li>
    <li><strong>First-time purchases</strong> compel consumers to try new or alternative products with trial sizes that feature smaller quantities than the standard product.</li>
    <li><strong>Traditional price-off offers</strong> promote a standard size product at a discounted price for a specific period with the support of a marketing campaign. They can be combined with other promotion types, including product bundles and multipacks.</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="close-interactions-and-dependencies">Close Interactions and Dependencies</h2>
  <p>If you look at the range of products advertised through promotions, it’s clear that branded products dominate leaflets, online offers, and flyers distributed by large grocery retail chains. In fact, the proportion of promotions with branded products often reaches 90% or more in many established markets.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="orchestrate-your-omnichannel-shopping-experience-with-sap">Orchestrate your omnichannel shopping experience with SAP</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm/customer-activity-repository.html">Find out how</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Considering these factors, consumer goods companies and grocery retailers must cooperate up to a certain level. Grocery retailers benefit from established brands because they can help ensure a broad group of consumers will notice the advertising and perceive promotional items as attractive. Consumer products companies, in turn, need grocery retailers to place new products at the point of sale and secure a competitive position for their core brands.</p>
  <p>Although both consumer goods companies and grocery retailers are interested in the success of jointly planned promotions, their actual objectives differ significantly. While retail companies are primarily running promotional campaigns to increase visit or purchase frequency and optimize cross-selling initiatives, consumer goods producers usually view expanding or securing market share as their primary goal.</p>
  <h2 id="acknowledge-the-importance-of-technology">Acknowledge the Importance of Technology</h2>
  <p>Given the critical nature of promotions, the right technology can help consumer products companies and grocery retailers realize mutually beneficial and optimized outcomes to increase their share of wallet, margin, and overall revenue. For example, technology can help streamline the promotion process, improve planning and execution, and measure campaign effectiveness.</p>
  <p>Working with leading consumer products companies and grocery retailers worldwide, SAP developed and continues to update a portfolio of solutions that can address market requirements, business challenges, and ever-evolving needs and expectations.</p>
  <h2 id="price-promotions-solutions-for-grocery-retail">Price Promotions Solutions for Grocery Retail</h2>
  <p>Retailers using SAP solutions are well-equipped to be able to address complex challenges in the promotion management process. They can increase inventory turnover and reduce food waste by leveraging real-time, data-driven insights into the evolving market landscape, supporting the promotion process, and driving smooth, error-free interactions.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="increase-revenue-volume-and-profitability-with-end-to-end-processes-for-trade-management">Increase revenue, volume, and profitability with end-to-end processes for trade management</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm/trade-management.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>With the SAP Promotion Management application, which is part of <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm/customer-activity-repository.html">SAP Customer Activity Repository</a>, retailers can plan, manage, and analyze their promotional events. The application helps streamline their promotion processes, access real-time data, and accurately evaluate results. In addition, it can gather data and integrate with the demand data foundation module of SAP Customer Activity Repository to help drive data integrity across multiple applications.</p>
  <p>Retailers can use enhanced planning capabilities from SAP Customer Activity Repository to help optimize promotion effectiveness and profitability. They can create coupons, define promotional advertising vehicles, specify promotional offers by location and language, and manage promotions by type, tactic, and incentives. Furthermore, they can exchange data across various SAP applications and support what-if simulations to help identify scenarios predicted to yield the best financial performance.</p>
  <p>Additional capabilities that further complement the promotion process in grocery retail include:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Omnichannel price and promotion service</strong> that can enable retailers to enhance the shopping experience with consistent pricing across all sales channels.</li>
    <li><strong>Retail promotion analytics</strong> that can provide valuable data-driven insights to help guide future decision-making and promotion optimization strategies.</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="price-promotions-solutions-for-consumer-products-companies">Price Promotions Solutions for Consumer Products Companies</h2>
  <p>For consumer products companies, SAP solutions help support promotion management and trade spend, which, in total, comprise the majority of business revenue. They can provide a tailored approach to promotion planning, execution, and control – enabling increased focus on revenue, volume, and profitability for themselves and their retail partners. Modern analytics capabilities are also included, such as statistical forecasting, optimization, post-evaluation, and innovative machine learning tools.</p>
  <p>Take, for example, the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm/trade-management.html">SAP Trade Management</a> solution. It can facilitate the design of promotional plans, fund management, and claims settlement while offering performance analysis to help gauge the effectiveness of trade promotions.</p>
  <p>The solution can allow businesses to shift their focus from short-term measures of promotion effectiveness to longer-term, mutually defined targets, including category growth, sustainable volume growth, and margin growth. Additionally, it can empower sales leaders to sense and predict potential risks to revenue, volume, and profitability in real time, align their strategies with retailers’ broader business objectives, and make fact-based decisions for activities best aligned with targets.</p>
  <h2 id="unlock-the-full-potential-of-every-promotion">Unlock the Full Potential of Every Promotion</h2>
  <p>In today’s competitive landscape, the ability to decode and master promotions is a strategic imperative. With the right technology and solutions in place, consumer product companies and grocery retailers can unlock the full potential of their promotions, driving revenue, enhancing margins, and securing their place in the market.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Dirk Dreisbach is chief business enterprise consultant for Business Transformation Services, Consumer Products and Retail Industries at SAP.<br>Dmitry Melnik is a vice president at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-sap-news-on-linkedin">Connect with SAP News on LinkedIn</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news">Follow us and stay in touch</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/consumer-goods-cpg</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Built-In Support Coverage Extended for SAP SuccessFactors Solutions]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/built-in-support-for-sap-successfactors</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/built-in-support-for-sap-successfactors</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is now expanding Built-In Support into SAP SuccessFactors solutions, so customers can access support right in the solution. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/built-in-support</category>
            <category>news-tag/real-time-support</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How an Expanded Partnership Amplifies the Value of SAP Business Technology Platform]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/sap-preferred-success-amplifies-value-of-sap-btp</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/sap-preferred-success-amplifies-value-of-sap-btp</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Preferred Success for SAP BTP, expanded edition helps businesses achieve agility and resilience through hands-on guidance. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-preferred-success</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP for Me Enhances the Customer Support Experience with Get Support]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/sap-for-me-customer-support-experience-get-support</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/sap-for-me-customer-support-experience-get-support</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Users can now engage with SAP support through the new get support application in SAP for Me and its use of artificial intelligence (AI).]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/built-in-support</category>
            <category>news-tag/real-time-support</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-for-me</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP for Me Now Successor of SAP ONE Support Launchpad]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/sap-for-me-successor-sap-one-support-launchpad</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/sap-for-me-successor-sap-one-support-launchpad</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[To provide customers an even better SAP experience, SAP ONE Support Launchpad is now fully part of the SAP for Me portal. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-for-me</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-one-support-launchpad</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Putting the “Real” in Real-Time Support]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/06/putting-the-real-in-real-time-support</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/06/putting-the-real-in-real-time-support</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The Real-Time Support approach aims to make the overall experience simpler and more personal and human. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/built-in-support</category>
            <category>news-tag/real-time-support</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
            <category>news-tag/schedule-an-expert</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Cloud ALM for Service: Modernizing Service Delivery with the Cloud]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/06/sap-cloud-alm-for-service-modernizing-service-delivery</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/06/sap-cloud-alm-for-service-modernizing-service-delivery</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Cloud ALM for service can help service delivery outcomes become faster, simpler to consume, and trackable. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>product/sap-cloud-alm</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Visualize and Accelerate Your Data Transformation to SAP S/4HANA Cloud]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/data-transformation-to-sap-s-4hana-cloud</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/data-transformation-to-sap-s-4hana-cloud</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Business Transformation Center helps guide you through the relevant steps required for your business transformation and data migration.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-transformation-center</category>
            <category>product/sap-cloud-alm</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-enterprise-support</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bi-Directional Support for SAP S/4HANA Gives Targeted and Timely Information]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/bi-directional-support-gives-targeted-timely-information</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/bi-directional-support-gives-targeted-timely-information</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With bi-directional support, SAP is expanding on its Real-Time Support approach to give tailored, proactive support content in real time.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/built-in-support</category>
            <category>news-tag/expert-chat</category>
            <category>news-tag/real-time-support</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Preferred Success: Where the Benefits of Cloud Adoption Outweigh the Costs]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/sap-preferred-success-benefits-cloud-adoption-outweigh-costs</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/sap-preferred-success-benefits-cloud-adoption-outweigh-costs</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A Forrester study show that SAP Preferred Success allows customers to gain an advantage from their cloud investment. Read to find out how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/forrester</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-preferred-success</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP for Me as the New, Personalized Central Entry Point for SAP Support]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/sap-for-me-new-personalized-entry-point-sap-support</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/sap-for-me-new-personalized-entry-point-sap-support</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP for Me helps make performing support-related tasks easier and more efficient in one place. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/real-time-support</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-for-me</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-one-support-launchpad</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-support-portal</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Real-Time Support from SAP Is Essential to the Digital Transformation of Jinlong]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/real-time-support-essential-to-digital-transformation-jinlong</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/real-time-support-essential-to-digital-transformation-jinlong</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Real-Time Support from SAP helps customers, like Jinlong, quickly resolve issues and accelerate their digital transformations. Learn how!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/real-time-support</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Forrester Consulting Study Shows How SAP MaxAttention Supported Better, Faster Cloud Adoption]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/forrester-consulting-study-sap-maxattention-supported-cloud-adoption</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/forrester-consulting-study-sap-maxattention-supported-cloud-adoption</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The Forrester study concluded that SAP MaxAttention delivered an impressive three-year financial impact throughout the cloud journey.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/forrester</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-maxattention</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Offers Maximum Attention for Customers’ High Standards]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/sap-offers-maximum-attention-for-customers-high-standards</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/sap-offers-maximum-attention-for-customers-high-standards</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Every customer has its own cloud strategies. That's why SAP MaxAttention prioritizes individualization within the customer's success plan.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/premium-engagement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-activeattention</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-erp</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-integrated-delivery-framework</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-maxattention</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-maxattention-summit</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Real-Time Support Channels Take Big Steps Forward in Customer Care]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/real-time-support-big-steps-forward-customer-care</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/real-time-support-big-steps-forward-customer-care</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With Real-Time Support, SAP is moving towards a bidirectional, predictive, and effortless support future. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/built-in-support</category>
            <category>news-tag/expert-chat</category>
            <category>news-tag/product-support</category>
            <category>news-tag/real-time-support</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-for-me</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-support-portal</category>
            <category>news-tag/schedule-a-manager</category>
            <category>news-tag/schedule-an-expert</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Serving Customers Better through Expanded Functionality and Enhanced Offerings in 2023]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/serving-customers-better-expanded-functionality-sap-support</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/serving-customers-better-expanded-functionality-sap-support</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With expanded functionality, enhanced transformation planning, and access to test automation solutions, 2023 will be big for SAP support.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/built-in-support</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-solution-support-innovation</category>
            <category>news-tag/machine-learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/real-time-support</category>
            <category>product/sap-cloud-alm</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-signavio</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cloud Success Services Makes It Easier to Transform]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/01/cloud-success-services-easier-transform-claudio-muruzabal-interview</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/01/cloud-success-services-easier-transform-claudio-muruzabal-interview</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The Cloud Success Services organization helps customers achieve value from their technology investment. Claudio Muruzabal explains how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/cloud-success-services</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reflecting On a Year of Transformation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/reflecting-on-support-experience-transformation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/reflecting-on-support-experience-transformation</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP's Andreas Heckmann reflects on the support experience transformation of the past year, and how it will continue in 2023.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/application-lifecycle-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/built-in-support</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-solution-support-innovation</category>
            <category>news-tag/machine-learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/real-time-support</category>
            <category>product/sap-cloud-alm</category>
            <category>product/sap-information-collaboration-hub-for-life-sciences</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Driving Continuous Innovation with Cloud Application Services]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/continuous-innovation-cloud-application-services</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/continuous-innovation-cloud-application-services</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Cloud application services play a critical role in driving digital transformation and continuous innovation in the cloud. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_142070103f917935adae56fa6e241cee98ad810d0.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_142070103f917935adae56fa6e241cee98ad810d0.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_142070103f917935adae56fa6e241cee98ad810d0.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Driving Continuous Innovation with Cloud Application Services" src="./media_142070103f917935adae56fa6e241cee98ad810d0.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="driving-continuous-innovation-with-cloud-application-services">Driving Continuous Innovation with Cloud Application Services</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>A new <a href="https://ssrn.com/abstract=4082436">study</a> from the <a href="https://ide.mit.edu/">MIT Initiative on the Digital Economy</a> found that transitioning to the cloud is paying off. Revenue growth for public firms adopting cloud technology was 2.3% to 6.9% higher than for non-adopters in the last decade, according to research results. In addition to increased revenues, companies benefit from improved productivity. Operating in a cloud environment enables organizations to use intelligent technologies, such as machine learning and artificial intelligence (AI). They are better equipped to adapt new models to service customers and employees in a hybrid work environment.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>At the same time, moving to the cloud has become more accessible. Companies can find the <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/pulse/cloud-mindset-culture-series-part-1-all-paths-lead-peter-pluim/?trackingId=RFwt9KRhStuDZ%2FVliBuisA%3D%3D">best cloud deployment model</a> based on their existing IT infrastructure as well as data residency requirements. Our customers, for example, can use our SAP data centers, hyperscalers, or their own data centers to host a cloud enterprise resource planning (ERP) environment.</p>
  <p>Operating in a cloud ERP environment is a critical step in an organization’s digital business transformation to become an intelligent, sustainable enterprise. This step is also the springboard to continuous innovation. And this continuous innovation is enabled by the cloud, more specifically by <a href="/topics/sap-cloud-application-services">cloud application services</a>.</p>
  <p>In a nutshell, cloud application services can be defined as value-added services that simplify the end-to-end management of cloud systems by delivering application operations and innovation adoption.</p>
  <p>We designed <a href="https://www.sap.com/services-support/service-offerings/cloud-application-services.html">SAP Cloud Application Services</a> to support all types of SAP cloud deployment models with SAP application management services, SAP managed data services, SAP managed security services, and SAP managed testing services. Each of these four services help drive continuous improvement and quality assurance for cloud solutions with a focus on business outcomes.</p>
  <p>Let’s take a look at managed testing services as an example.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-cloud-application-services-help-free-up-resources-to-focus-on-optimizing-business-outcomes">SAP Cloud Application Services help free up resources to focus on optimizing business outcomes</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/services-support/service-offerings/cloud-application-services.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="innovating-without-compromising-business-continuity">Innovating without Compromising Business Continuity</h2>
  <p>Most global businesses have highly complex and integrated landscapes. They want access to the latest technologies to improve operations and engagements with customers. This could include using AI-based chatbots for customer service, adding mobile payment methods, or having the ability to track their carbon footprint across the entire supply chain. But they also have concerns that introducing these new innovations may cause disruption of existing business operations. Thus, maintaining business continuity at a high quality is paramount when introducing innovations.</p>
  <p>That’s where SAP managed testing services come in. The beauty of the services is that they can improve IT systems and operations in the cloud without compromising business continuity with repeatable and seamless processes for solution adoption, testing, and quality control.</p>
  <p><a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/03/888d99c4-d17d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff.html">SAP managed testing services</a> can prevent disruption and help stabilize critical business processes across releases and other test events. Software quality is tested consistently, accurately, and efficiently with automated testing tools and services that use industry-specific test cases. Higher value services, such as data management, release management, advanced monitoring, and innovation adoption, help stabilize application operations. We offer support for all cloud deployment models with a central focus on flexible and simplified service consumption, which is central to the innovation mindset of our organization.</p>
  <p>In brief, the services can provide the quality assurance and stable foundation that companies need to confidently drive innovation with integration and upgrades to the latest technologies. Having that peace of mind is critical to developing a cloud-first mindset across the entire organization for continuous innovation.</p>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div><a href="https://www.sap.com/services-support/service-offerings/cloud-application-services.html">Learn more about SAP Cloud Application Services.</a></div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>Peter Pluim is president of SAP Enterprise Cloud Services and SAP Sovereign Cloud Delivery &#x26; Operations at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-cloud-application-services</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Trio for Support Innovation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/trio-for-support-innovation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/trio-for-support-innovation</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP's Andreas Heckmann discusses the innovative power of continuous updates, AI and machine learning, and real-time support. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/built-in-support</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-solution-support-innovation</category>
            <category>news-tag/machine-learning</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-cloud-alm</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-for-me</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-one-support-launchpad</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Upward Momentum Builds with Digitalization in the Chemicals Industry]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/upward-momentum-digitalization-chemicals-industry</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/upward-momentum-digitalization-chemicals-industry</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With the right approach to digitalization and the help of SAP Advisory Services, the chemicals industry can innovate across the value chain.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f2348930338cde065afdb2512296e4046afc65b8.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f2348930338cde065afdb2512296e4046afc65b8.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1f2348930338cde065afdb2512296e4046afc65b8.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Upward Momentum Builds with Digitalization in the Chemicals Industry" src="./media_1f2348930338cde065afdb2512296e4046afc65b8.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="upward-momentum-builds-with-digitalization-in-the-chemicals-industry">Upward Momentum Builds with Digitalization in the Chemicals Industry</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Chemical companies are on a nonstop roller coaster of market shocks and digital transformation. Sandwiched between feedstock and energy companies and downstream processing industries, they’re predestined to play a vital role in fulfilling business-to-business (B2B) and consumer expectations for sustainable, reliable, innovative, and trusted products and services.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>But rising to the challenge of today’s marketplace – especially increasing raw material and energy prices, margin pressure, supply chain complexity, and regulatory requirements – requires much more than Industry 4.0 initiatives focused on efficiency and price reduction. From operational performance to customer experience, companies must integrate data from across the enterprise into a single source to form sound decisions that make sustainability profitable and profitability sustainable.</p>
  <p>Such a transformation is undoubtedly technology intensive, but the key enablers are also unassailably human. Understanding this reality, many chemical companies rely on the <a href="https://www.sap.com/services-support/service-offerings/business-transformation.html">SAP Advisory Services</a> portfolio, provided by the Business Transformation Services group at SAP, to help transform their operations and gain a competitive edge amid fast global changes.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="transform-your-business-and-unlock-digital-innovation-with-help-from-sap-advisory-services">Transform your business and unlock digital innovation with help from SAP Advisory Services</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/services-support/service-offerings/business-transformation.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="turning-challenges-into-great-opportunities">Turning Challenges into Great Opportunities</h2>
  <p>Competitively addressing turbulence depends on the ability to view transformation through the lens of six fundamental challenges:</p>
  <p><strong>R&#x26;D Pressure across the Product Portfolio</strong> The imperative to resist margin shrinkage, mitigate risks, increase ROI, and boost growth calls for innovative products and services that offer business value and foster close partnerships with customers. By pushing forward the adoption of advanced technologies to drive global R&#x26;D, supplier, and customer collaborations and joint ventures, businesses can prevent commoditization.</p>
  <p><strong>The Need for Vertical Integration</strong> Evolving production facilities with a balance of high efficiency, global scale, flexibility, and intelligent responsiveness allows supply chains to weigh the synergistic benefits of integrated manufacturing plants or industrial parks against the flexibility of smaller plants. As a result, businesses can leverage new opportunities with disruptive business models, such as making raw materials instead of buying them and producing semi-finished or even finished goods.</p>
  <p><strong>Global Supply Chain Complexity</strong> Global supply chains must be secure enough to mitigate volatile market conditions, such as global health emergencies, rising prices for raw materials and energy, and other factors that impact economic conditions. Companies can gain this advantage by establishing commercial and logistical transparency to support optimization and global planning of demand, sales, and operations.</p>
  <p><strong>Hidden Advantages of Business Networks</strong> Business cannot stay competitive in a complex ecosystem alone. They must also scale and optimize their supply chain globally with business networks, such as the <a href="/2021/03/catena-x-automotive-alliance-picks-up-speed">Catena-X Automotive Network</a>. Doing so empowers suppliers, contract and toll manufacturers, joint ventures, and customers to collaborate openly and create new prospects for co-innovating better products and services, improving value chain efficiency, and fueling long-term growth.</p>
  <p><strong>Compliance and Sustainability Urgency</strong> A primary objective for any chemical business is ensuring compliance with industry regulations. Yet, B2B customers also favor suppliers that help meet their own environmental, social, and governance (ESG) mandates. Sustainable businesses and innovations provide balance between these two expectations, creating a highly sought-after competitive edge by gearing products and services towards a circular economy.</p>
  <p><strong>Business Agility</strong> The industry’s dynamic and fast-changing environment of mergers, acquisitions, and divestitures is creating tremendous complexity and pressure for permanent change and adaptation. Chemical companies need to balance industry-wide globalization and centralization while increasing business agility.</p>
  <p>Chemical companies with a digital strategy encompassing all these topics can address industry challenges and seize on market trends in a disruptive manner. Through <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2016/03/d2238cd0-627c-0010-82c7-eda71af511fa.html">digital innovation</a>, businesses can gain new opportunities and capabilities never previously considered possible – including increased speed and efficiency, process automation, and data transparency.</p>
  <h2 id="seizing-the-moment-with-advisory-expertise">Seizing the Moment with Advisory Expertise</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="at-sap-your-success-is-our-goal">At SAP, your success is our goal</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/support.html#services-support-offerings">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>From the perspective of SAP Advisory Services, digitalization is not just another IT term but also a critical business priority. The more intelligent and sustainable a company becomes, the more agile, flexible, and integrated its value chain becomes.</p>
  <p>Advisory experts from SAP can enable chemical companies to turn their fundamental challenges into opportunities with a well-structured, business-driven design. This approach elaborates on the steps of the digital transformation journey – leading to a road map for future architecture design. Each phase of the road map follows an ideal sequence of digital innovation, technology adoption, and industry best practices and leverages the highest value for the company in the short term.</p>
  <p>SAP Advisory Services help organizations evaluate and act on the sentiments of their customers, partners, and employees and improve their environmental impact. Chemical companies can then be well positioned to keep their workforce engaged, increase organizational agility, and deliver the products and services customers need and trust. Furthermore, they can control their varied sources and categories of spending with outstanding finance and operational efficiency and real-time enterprise insight.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_13184d5b5d29ebbc4d371c407a9c86acc71402ad2.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_13184d5b5d29ebbc4d371c407a9c86acc71402ad2.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_13184d5b5d29ebbc4d371c407a9c86acc71402ad2.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_13184d5b5d29ebbc4d371c407a9c86acc71402ad2.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="300" height="283">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p><em>Intelligent enterprise framework</em></p>
  <p>Essentially, chemical companies that work with SAP advisory experts can realize their potential as <a href="https://www.sap.com/intelligent-enterprise.html">intelligent enterprises</a>. They can make confident decisions and drive continuous innovation to adapt, innovate, and overcome challenges while making responsible choices that help reduce waste and emissions and drive long-term growth.</p>
  <p>This business model is accomplished with intelligent technologies, including business networks, a business technology platform, cloud-based infrastructures, and solutions for business process management, experience management, industry cloud, and sustainability management. Additionally, artificial intelligence (AI), blockchain, data platforms, the Internet of Things (IoT), machine learning, predictive analytics, and virtual as well as augmented realities (VR/AR) are embedded in the intelligent technologies to drive end-to-end business processes and decision-making across enterprise domains.</p>
  <h2 id="bringing-to-life-an-intelligent-and-sustainable-network">Bringing to Life an Intelligent and Sustainable Network</h2>
  <p>The pressures on the chemicals industry may be relentless, with shocks coming in from all directions. However, this doesn’t mean businesses cannot find great opportunities in this volatile environment. With the right approach to digitalization, they can transform, innovate, and collaborate across the value chain to build upward momentum and better serve customers as an intelligent and sustainable network.</p>
  <p>Learn more about the <a href="https://blogs.sap.com/2022/09/29/business-and-digital-trends-in-the-chemical-industry/">market trends and business priorities shaping various lines of businesses in the chemical industry</a> and how SAP can help guide the innovation needed to overcome them. Read the series <a href="https://blogs.sap.com/tag/business-digital-trends-in-the-chemical-industry/">“Business and Digital Trends in the Chemical Industry</a>” on SAP Community.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Ornulf Rexin is chief business consultant of Chemicals and Life Sciences for Business Transformation Services at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/chemicals</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/digitalization</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-advisory-services</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>