<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/automation/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[New Supply Chain and External Workforce Innovations Reduce Organizational Inefficiencies]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/supply-chain-external-workforce-innovations</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/supply-chain-external-workforce-innovations</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[At SAP Sapphire, we introduced supply chain and external workforce innovations to help reduce inefficiency and improve decision-making.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/automation</category>
            <category>news-tag/external-workforce-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fieldglass</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Coles Reimagines Volume Hiring with AI and Automation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/coles-reimagines-volume-hiring-with-ai-and-automation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/coles-reimagines-volume-hiring-with-ai-and-automation</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Coles uses an AI-powered solution integrated with SAP SuccessFactors to help revolutionize its hiring process and gain speed and efficiency.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_149ed3b06f07dcdc3485b441db14e19620bea42c6.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_149ed3b06f07dcdc3485b441db14e19620bea42c6.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_149ed3b06f07dcdc3485b441db14e19620bea42c6.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Coles Reimagines Volume Hiring with AI and Automation" src="./media_149ed3b06f07dcdc3485b441db14e19620bea42c6.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="coles-reimagines-volume-hiring-with-ai-and-automation">Coles Reimagines Volume Hiring with AI and Automation</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><a href="https://www.colesgroup.com.au/home/">Coles Group</a>, one of Australia’s most trusted and iconic brands, is steadfast in delivering on its purpose to help Australians eat and live better every day. Through its core business as a full-service supermarket retailer, Coles engages with millions of customers every week in its 860 supermarkets throughout Australia. The group’s other areas of business include its Click &#x26; Collect online platform, network of liquor stores, and financial services with nearly 1,000 additional retail outlets.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Guided by the organization’s clear <a href="https://colescareers.com.au/au/en/culture">vision, purpose, and strategy</a>, Coles’ team of 120,000 employees is dedicated to making a difference in the lives of customers and the local communities it serves.</p>
  <p>In fiscal year 2020/21, Coles Group hired nearly 30,000 people to deliver on its business needs. Mike Virgo, head of Talent Acquisition for Coles Group, said this hiring volume was necessary to make sure the company was “positioned well to support our customers.”</p>
  <p>The business environment, however, dramatically shifted as the public health crisis of the pandemic unfolded, resulting in repeated lockdowns and restrictions. As a neighborhood retailer dependent on in-person interaction to deliver most of its services, Coles found its workforce impacted by the pandemic. Faced with supply chain disruptions, panic buying behaviors by consumers, high employee absenteeism, and increased turnover, Coles urgently needed to step up its volume and pace of hiring to support its customers.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="create-ai-powered-experiences-that-drive-real-competitive-advantage-with-sap-successfactors">Create AI-powered experiences that drive real competitive advantage with SAP SuccessFactors</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“Around 2020-2021, we started to experience one of the most significant shifts in the employment market we’d ever seen,” Virgo said in a <a href="https://go3.events.sap.com/successconnect/virtual/2023/reg/flow/sap/sc23/catalog/page/catalog/session/1693098679863001ykJ6">session</a> at <a href="https://www.sap.com/events/successconnect/virtual.html?campaigncode=CRM-YI23-HXM-2055448&#x26;source=text-glo-SAPNews">SuccessConnect Virtual</a>. “It started to create huge challenges for organizations around the world – around how we attract, retain, and hire talent.”</p>
  <h2 id="catalyst-for-change-and-a-new-way-of-working">Catalyst for Change and a New Way of Working</h2>
  <p>To meet pressing business demands, Coles doubled its hiring volume from 30,000 to 60,000 people and increased recruitment advertising spend by a factor of three. Its talent acquisition team grew proportionally to manage the increased workload – but then labored under manual transactional activities that slowed processing times. As a result of the huge strain, variability in the candidate and hiring manager experience became noticeable.</p>
  <p>Due to the volume of work, Coles looked for ways to evolve its system to create more speed, efficiency, and scalability. With a list of criteria, Coles began to review technology solutions on the market to find one that could support its vision for a new way of working. “We wanted to reimagine how we recruit for our stores,” Virgo said. “We needed automation and AI to remove a lot of the manual work in our systems. We wanted to create more consistency and uplift the experiences we were giving our candidates and our hiring managers. And ultimately, [the solution] needed to drive commercial benefit for us.”</p>
  <p>As a key requirement, the new solution needed to integrate with <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/what-is-hxm-suite.html">SAP SuccessFactors Human Experience Management (HXM) Suite</a>. In 2020, as part of an organization-wide <a href="/australia/2021/09/08/how-coles-group-is-transforming-hr-during-the-global-pandemic">digital transformation</a> that introduced SAP S/4HANA and SAP Ariba solutions, Coles modernized its HR and payroll processing, replacing a patchwork of outdated systems with SAP SuccessFactors solutions. It became the first organization in the southern hemisphere to launch all modules of the SAP SuccessFactors portfolio in one go. With all HR processes unified on a single platform, Coles benefits from having a single source of truth for people data that is accurate and available in real time for the entire organization.</p>
  <h2 id="two-way-integration-ensures-single-source-of-truth-in-data">Two-Way Integration Ensures Single Source of Truth in Data</h2>
  <p>To help with the project, Coles chose <a href="https://www.phenom.com/">Phenom</a>, an SAP partner whose AI-powered Intelligent Talent Experience platform provides two-way integration with SAP SuccessFactors solutions. Virgo said the two-way integration “allows us to have a holistic view of the candidates that progress through the process, no matter whether the team is operating in Phenom or SAP SuccessFactors, and it allows SAP SuccessFactors to be our single source of truth.”</p>
  <p>There are several key benefits of Phenom’s solution at Coles. One is candidate attraction and engagement, which is achieved primarily through the Coles career site and chatbot. Another is recruiter automation and interview management, which provides automation and process efficiencies from when a job requisition is created in SAP SuccessFactors solutions and replicated into Phenom until a hiring manager chooses a candidate for the job. Once a candidate is chosen, the two-way integration enables the HR team to access the data in SAP SuccessFactors solutions and complete all compliance aspects, such as working rights, contract generation, and onboarding.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-how-phenom-can-compliment-sap-successfactors-recruiting">Learn how Phenom can compliment SAP SuccessFactors Recruiting</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://store.sap.com/dcp/en/product/display-2001007992_live_v1">Find out</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The Coles team gains additional efficiencies in its onboarding programs through the application of robotic process automation (RPA) powered by two bots that work in the background: <em>Ashbotty</em> processes the working rights and <em>Usain Bot</em> processes onboarding and manages pending recruits. “They take a lot of the transactional, manual work that we used to have team members doing. It can do that quickly, accurately, and it can do that 24/7 – which is particularly important for us as a seven-days-a-week business,” Virgo said.</p>
  <h2 id="ai-powered-experiences-for-candidates-and-recruiters">AI-Powered Experiences for Candidates and Recruiters</h2>
  <p>Coles reimagined the candidate experience to launch a modern, tech-enabled career site – which has been chosen as a two-time winner of Australia’s Best Careers Site. The site includes an AI-powered chatbot to guide candidates as they look for information, search relevant job postings, and submit their applications. It also includes Coles’ Expression of Interest, always-on advertising that drives the growth of its talent pool and advances its talent marketing by reducing the need to advertise every role. A Hosted Apply process, facilitated by integrations with Phenom, presents a consistent candidate experience and increases the conversion rate on applications.</p>
  <p>Phenom AI Scheduling, a key part of Coles’ hiring experience, enables candidates to book themselves an available interview slot and automates the coordination of hiring team calendars. The new solution provides a fully mobile-enabled experience to meet the demands of candidates for an omni-channel, real-time experience where they can learn, read, and apply for jobs where and when they want.</p>
  <p>Inundated by nearly 1 million applications each year to review, Coles also took steps to elevate the recruiter experience and increase the speed and accuracy of candidate screening and job matching. It implemented Phenom Fit Score, an AI-powered feature that assesses a candidate’s suitability for an open role, based on location and optimal travel distances, availability, and working rights; then, assigns a fit score and surfaces the most closely matched candidates to the recruiters. In addition, the new solution empowers in-store managers to collaborate with recruiters to review candidates and make quick hiring decisions with confidence.</p>
  <h2 id="talent-pools-grow-with-improvements-to-hiring-speed-and-efficiency">Talent Pools Grow with Improvements to Hiring Speed and Efficiency</h2>
  <p>With the new augmented solution, Coles is experiencing tangible benefits across multiple categories and key metrics for success: time-to-fill is down six days; time-to-hire is down two days, which is impressive considering candidates can book the in-store interview up to two weeks in advance; and advertising spend is down 50%.</p>
  <p>Most notably for Coles as a people-centric organization is the development of its talent pool, now numbering 2 million potential candidates. It achieves an 85% application conversion rate on up to 1 million applications per year. Through its <a href="https://www.colesgroup.com.au/media-releases/?page=coles-group-ranked-1-for-recruitment-of-aussies-with-disabilities">commitment</a> to be a safe, inclusive, and diverse workplace, Coles has applied the new solution to provide greater accessibility for more diverse candidates, resulting in an increase of 24% more hiring for people who identify as having a disability.</p>
  <p>Virgo said that the talent acquisition team will continue to evolve its solution and assess more opportunities for AI and automation to bring value to the recruitment process. Although these technologies are not cure-alls for every recruitment scenario, they can save recruiting teams precious time and resources to focus on more high-touch interactions further down the recruiting funnel. In sharing lessons learned, Virgo noted, “I think the important call out is the level of automation you can inject in your process will likely diminish as the seniority, complexity, and requirements of your roles increase because they are likely to be more high touch, perhaps need more interpretation or judgment calls from your recruiters to identify who the right talent is for your organization.”</p>
  <p>Watch <a href="https://www.sap.com/events/successconnect/virtual.html?campaigncode=CRM-YI23-HXM-2055448&#x26;source=text-glo-SAPNews">SuccessConnect Virtual</a> on demand.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="follow-sap-news-on-linkedin-to-stay-up-to-date">Follow SAP News on LinkedIn to stay up-to-date</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/automation</category>
            <category>industry/consumer-goods-cpg</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>news-tag/recruiting</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
            <category>sap-event/successconnect</category>
            <category>news-tag/talent-acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP TechEd in 2023: That’s a Wrap!]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/sap-teched-2023-wrap-up</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/sap-teched-2023-wrap-up</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Last week at SAP TechEd, SAP announced new SAP BTP innovations that help organizations and developers bring their ideas to life. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1877c9283a8cddb4da2df0b65c45dc5a6351a2863.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1877c9283a8cddb4da2df0b65c45dc5a6351a2863.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1877c9283a8cddb4da2df0b65c45dc5a6351a2863.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP TechEd in 2023: That’s a Wrap!" src="./media_1877c9283a8cddb4da2df0b65c45dc5a6351a2863.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-teched-in-2023-thats-a-wrap">SAP TechEd in 2023: That’s a Wrap!</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>SAP’s mission is to make the world run better and improve people’s lives. As we work to fulfill this purpose each day, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform.html">SAP Business Technology Platform</a> (SAP BTP) serves as the unified platform that enables our customers to accelerate their innovation with application development, integration, automation, data and analytics, and AI capabilities.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="enterprise-innovation-in-the-age-of-ai">Enterprise Innovation in the Age of AI</h3>
        <p><em><a href="">Read the news guide</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Last week at <a href="https://www.sap.com/events/teched/bangalore.html">SAP TechEd</a>, we announced new SAP BTP innovations that help organizations and developers bring their ideas to life.</p>
  <p>Thank you to everyone who attended the event virtually and in person at Bangalore. For those who couldn’t attend live, I recommend reading the <a href="https://www.sap.com/events/teched/news-guide.html">SAP TechEd news guide</a>, checking out the full list of <a href="https://go3.events.sap.com/sapteched/virtual/2023/reg/flow/sap/sapteched23/catalog/page/catalog?tab.sessionplanned=1602215152230002KZab">on-demand sessions</a>, and watching the <a href="https://go3.events.sap.com/sapteched/virtual/2023/reg/flow/sap/sapteched23/catalog/page/catalog/session/1692373933108001qRNV">executive keynote</a>, delivered by SAP CTO Juergen Mueller.</p>
  <p>Here are some of the key announcements we made.</p>
  <h2 id="turning-every-developer-into-an-ai-developer">Turning Every Developer into an AI Developer</h2>
  <p>Developers are essential to the modern world we live in, driving innovation and transformation forward across every industry. To help improve their productivity, we announced <a href="/2023/11/sap-teched-2023-sap-build-code-supercharge-developer-productivity">SAP Build Code</a>, a generative AI-powered application development solution, built on SAP BTP and optimized for Java and JavaScript development. It delivers a turn-key environment for coding, testing, integrations, and application lifecycle management.</p>
  <p>SAP Build Code has embedded generative AI capabilities with <a href="/2023/09/joule-new-generative-ai-assistant">Joule</a> to enable code generation to streamline application development. It also enables fusion development so developers can build rapidly, integrate seamlessly, and collaborate effectively with other developers and business experts. SAP Build Code complements <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/low-code.html">SAP Build</a>, our low-code solution that provides a unified environment to create and enhance enterprise applications, automate processes, and design business sites with drag-and-drop simplicity. <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/developer-tools.html">Learn more here</a>.</p>
  <h2 id="generative-ai-for-everyone">Generative AI for Everyone</h2>
  <p>More than ever before, companies are seeking to unleash the power of AI in their applications and processes. We are thrilled to unveil <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence.html">AI Foundation on SAP BTP</a>, a one-stop shop for developers to build and extend applications powered by AI and generative AI on SAP BTP. With AI Foundation, developers gain access to everything they need to quickly embed business-ready AI into their applications, leveraging the same powerful technology SAP development teams use today. This includes AI services, generative AI management, AI workload management, access to business data and context, and lifecycle management based on SAP AI Core, SAP AI Launchpad, and SAP HANA Cloud. <a href="https://sap.com/joule">Learn more here</a>.</p>
  <p>Later this quarter, AI Foundation will include a new generative AI hub capability in SAP AI Core for accessing a broad range of large language models (LLMs) from third-party providers. With the hub, developers will be able to use tooling for prompt engineering and experimentation to accelerate generative AI application development.</p>
  <h2 id="ai-powered-business-data">AI-Powered Business Data</h2>
  <p>SAP believes every data professional should have seamless and scalable access to mission-critical business data. To this end, we’ve announced new innovations that empower developers to build intelligent data applications with SAP HANA Cloud but also brings new capabilities that not only enhance the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/datasphere/features.html#business-data-fabric">business data fabric</a> with SAP Datasphere.</p>
  <p>Good data is the foundation of good AI, and SAP HANA Cloud continues to pioneer innovation in the data space by adding new vector database features to its multi-model offerings at no additional cost. Vector datastores manage unstructured data — such as text, images, or audio — to provide long-term memory and better context to AI models. This makes it easy to find and retrieve similar objects quickly. For example, users can search for suppliers based on the language in their contracts to examine payment history and trace individual orders. These powerful new vector database features enhance interactions between LLMs and an organization’s mission-critical data. The innovation puts SAP developers at the forefront of delivering radically new levels of data insight within a secure, private framework that uses industry-specific customer data to reduce hallucinations.</p>
  <p>New semantic onboarding capabilities within <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/datasphere.html">SAP Datasphere</a> enable customers to deliver business-ready data products at an accelerated pace. With the powerful semantic layer, organizations can build data products that maintain business context and application logic and forego the time-consuming tasks of extracting business data, creating data pipelines and rebuilding data context that was lost. <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/datasphere/guided-experience.html">Learn more here</a>.</p>
  <h2 id="enterprise-automation">Enterprise Automation</h2>
  <p>Integrating, analyzing, and automating end-to-end business processes is critical in today’s digital landscape. To help customers stay ahead of the competition, SAP offers <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/enterprise-automation.html?pdf-asset=d237f8b9-7e7e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b&#x26;page=1">enterprise automation</a>, one solution that combines the value of <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/integration-suite.html">SAP Integration Suite</a>, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-process-transformation.html">SAP Signavio</a>, and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/low-code.html">SAP Build</a>. At SAP TechEd, we previewed new generative AI capabilities to simplify creating processes and integrations and to recommend pre-built content. Deeper integrations across the three technologies helps companies easily mine non-SAP processes to better analyze, integrate, automate, and monitor business processes across their environment. <a href="https://blogs.sap.com/2023/05/17/introducing-new-capabilities-for-enterprise-automation/">Learn more here</a>.</p>
  <p>See you at SAP TechEd in 2024!</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>JG Chirapurath is chief marketing and solutions officer for SAP BTP and Artificial Intelligence at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-news-coverage-and-stories-from-sap-teched-in-2023">Get the latest news, coverage, and stories from SAP TechEd in 2023</h3>
        <p><em><a href="/topics/sap-teched">Read more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-teched</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/application-development</category>
            <category>news-tag/automation</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/integration</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Delivering Enterprise Automation Across Industries]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/delivering-enterprise-automation-across-industries</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/delivering-enterprise-automation-across-industries</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Enterprise automation from SAP uses best-in-class technology to help connect and automate complex, end-to-end business processes.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/automation</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/rpa</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How to Adjust the Speed and Scale of Your Financial Close]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/adjust-speed-scale-of-financial-close</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/adjust-speed-scale-of-financial-close</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Account Substantiation and Automation by BlackLine can provide a foundation for efficiency throughout the financial close process.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/financial-management</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/accounting</category>
            <category>news-tag/automation</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/financial-services</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unleashing Automation for a Resilient Aerospace & Defense Sector]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/unleashing-automation-resilient-aerospace-defense-sector</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/unleashing-automation-resilient-aerospace-defense-sector</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The aerospace and defense industry needs ways to overcome labor shortage-driven production challenges. Automation solutions and SAP can help]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/aerospace-defense</category>
            <category>news-tag/automation</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-twin</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-4-0</category>
            <category>news-tag/rpa</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-signavio</category>
            <category>product/sap-warehouse-robotics</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP and Sartorius Are Reinventing Collaboration and Manual Processes]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/sap-and-sartorius-reinventing-collaboration</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/sap-and-sartorius-reinventing-collaboration</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP and Sartorius developed a prototype that aims to replace manual practices with automated cross-company orchestrations. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/automation</category>
            <category>news-tag/blockchain</category>
            <category>industry/healthcare</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-innovation-center-network</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Recognized as Visionary in 2022 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Robotic Process Automation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/sap-visionary-gartner-robotic-process-automation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/sap-visionary-gartner-robotic-process-automation</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Gartner has ranked SAP as a Visionary in the 2022 Magic Quadrant for Robotic Process Automation (RPA) for its SAP Process Automation solution.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/automation</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/low-code-no-code</category>
            <category>news-tag/rpa</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Manufacturers Supercharge Massive Supply Chain Advantage with Industry 4.0]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/06/manufacturers-supply-chain-advantage-industry-4-0</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/06/manufacturers-supply-chain-advantage-industry-4-0</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Industrial manufacturers can gain a competitive advantage with digitalized supply chains to understand and respond to market demands faster.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/automation</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-4-0</category>
            <category>news-tag/internet-of-things</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Next Phase for Robotic Process Automation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/next-phase-advanced-rpa-robotic-process-automation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/next-phase-advanced-rpa-robotic-process-automation</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With advanced RPA, SAP enables customers to derive even more value and free up employees to undertake more interesting activities.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1dd2c32b428934735b8ac109b65f46aab0501d990.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1dd2c32b428934735b8ac109b65f46aab0501d990.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1dd2c32b428934735b8ac109b65f46aab0501d990.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="The Next Phase for Robotic Process Automation" src="./media_1dd2c32b428934735b8ac109b65f46aab0501d990.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="the-next-phase-for-robotic-process-automation">The Next Phase for Robotic Process Automation</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="easily-build-intelligent-bots-with-a-low-code-design-studio-for-hyperautomation">Easily build intelligent bots with a low-code design studio for hyperautomation</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/robotic-process-automation.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>When it comes to responding to an urgent need by quickly developing an automation solution to minimize laborious, time-consuming, and error-prone manual work, robotic process automation (<a href="/topics/rpa">RPA</a>) delivers great value.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>But this is just a first step. Taken to the next level, intelligent RPA, also called “hyperautomation,” offers even more valuable benefits by combining traditional RPA with artificial intelligence (AI) and low-code/no-code development.</p>
  <p>As an example, repetitive tasks and routine activities in finance, purchasing, and customer service were preventing Villeroy &#x26; Boch, one of Europe’s oldest ceramic manufacturers, from improving operational efficiency and delivering great customer service. The German premium tableware and bathroom products company implemented SAP Intelligent RPA for routine activities, helping streamline workflows and free up staff to focus on strategic activities.</p>
  <p>Like other SAP customers benefiting from hyperautomation, Villeroy &#x26; Boch started with automating simple, frequently occurring tasks, such as responding to standard e-mail inquiries with attended RPA bots. Previously known as robotic desktop automation, attended RPA is a software assistant for the human user and interacts with a desktop application while respecting applicable business logic.</p>
  <p>Operating internationally in 125 countries demands smooth workflows and operational efficiency across several business functions, but the ceramics group always had a bigger vision. The company wanted to create a fully automated invoice error-handling process by combining SAP Intelligent RPA and SAP AI Business Services to handle unstructured data and documents.</p>
  <p>Now advanced RPA bots autonomously trigger tasks and automate more complex work such as processing attachments from e-mails according to their type and predefined confidence thresholds. So far, the 10 digital assistants Villeroy &#x26; Boch has deployed are handling 66,000 documents a year.</p>
  <p>“Although we’re just at the beginning of our journey with SAP Intelligent RPA, we are already realizing its potential to help us work more efficiently, serve customers better, and gain competitive advantage,” said Daniel Neuhaeuser, head of ERP Core Solutions at Villeroy &#x26; Boch.</p>
  <p>The advantages of going beyond traditional RPA and tapping the potential of hyperautomation are becoming more widely acknowledged. Industry analysts have forecast that the worldwide hyperautomation-enabling software market will reach nearly US$600 billion by 2022.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="try-sap-intelligent-rpa-today">Try SAP Intelligent RPA today</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/td/sap-intelligent-robotic-process-automation-free-trial.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Hyperautomation services such as SAP Intelligent RPA enable companies to quickly and easily create bots to emulate human users and automate tedious, repetitive, mundane tasks. For example, today’s office workers spend a lot of time moving between different applications and must often reenter or copy and paste data, such as a customer’s name and address details, from one application to another.</p>
  <p>Earlier this year, SAP Intelligent RPA was cited as a Strong Performer in <a href="https://reprints2.forrester.com/#/assets/2/702/RES161538/report">The Forrester Wave™: Robotic Process Automation, Q1 2021</a>. According to the report, “SAP’s RPA solution is a strong alternative for SAP customers, particularly for enterprises concerned with bots disrupting core SAP systems and those usually needing the central SAP development team to design, develop, and maintain RPA for clear accountability, or for companies seeking a feature-rich RPA tool that comes with a broad ecosystem of partners.”</p>
  <p>Typically, customers report that SAP Intelligent RPA deployments free up between 15 and 30% of employees’ time, which means they can focus on tasks that deliver greater value to the organization and improve the customer experience.</p>
  <p>Specific benefits of using SAP Intelligent RPA include being able to use tools such as <a href="https://insights.sap.com/tackling-software-developer-shortage-citizen-developers-lcnc/">low-code or no-code platforms</a>, built-in integration and content for business process management, and fast, cost-effective deployment. By opening current tools to everyone in the enterprise, SAP Intelligent RPA extends its reach beyond software developers. Business users who have no coding skills but have functional expertise and technical acumen can become citizen developers and build their own automations.</p>
  <p>To support this mission and help automate tasks in business processes, SAP Intelligent RPA offers a new bot-building and execution experience and a cloud-based design studio. This allows users to create and deploy software bots as digital assistants that automate repetitive tasks through a low-code approach.</p>
  <p>This low-code tooling speeds up implementation time and offers a short time to value. More than 200 prebuilt bots are now available within SAP Intelligent RPA to help automate tasks, improve productivity, and make work more interesting for employees.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/automation</category>
            <category>news-tag/low-code-no-code</category>
            <category>news-tag/rpa</category>
            <category>product/sap-intelligent-rpa</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Five Ways to Make the Most of Your Data]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/five-ways-to-make-the-most-of-your-data</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/five-ways-to-make-the-most-of-your-data</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Data is no longer a byproduct of business; it is at the heart of digital businesses. Read to learn how to derive value from your data.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b289ee5de80da992711d931f6888981d72b5f6dd.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b289ee5de80da992711d931f6888981d72b5f6dd.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1b289ee5de80da992711d931f6888981d72b5f6dd.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Five Ways to Make the Most of Your Data" src="./media_1b289ee5de80da992711d931f6888981d72b5f6dd.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="five-ways-to-make-the-most-of-your-data">Five Ways to Make the Most of Your Data</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>It used to be that companies viewed data as a byproduct of their business. Companies knew it had value but didn’t know how to properly utilize it.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>But as economies have digitized, business leaders now recognize that data is at the heart of digital businesses. It fuels differentiation, strategy, rapid innovation, and other important elements of running a successful business. Moreover, truly data-driven companies tend to generate 8% to 10% more profit and are 23 times more likely to acquire new customers – which fuels significantly higher market valuation – compared to their peers.</p>
  <p>In the meantime, organizations struggle to unite and access real-time data. Companies generate a lot of data, and while they have good intentions to use that data, it’s stuck in siloes. That makes it hard to leverage data to optimize business processes across the organization. According to research firm, <a href="https://go.forrester.com/blogs/hadoop-is-datas-darling-for-a-reason/">Forrester</a>, “Between 60% and 73% of all data within an enterprise goes unused for analytics.”</p>
  <p>Below are some suggestions for customers embarking on an enterprise data strategy that will help bring data of all kinds together, allowing companies to turn data into business value.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="register-for-the-sap-data-and-analytics-virtual-forum">Register for the SAP Data and Analytics Virtual Forum</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://events.sap.com/sap-data--and-analytics-virtual-forum-accelerating-outcomes/en/home">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="leave-your-data-where-it-is">Leave Your Data Where It Is</h2>
  <p>Too often companies try to centralize data via a large, top-down project where data from across the organization must be brought into a central repository. The problem with this approach: by the time you bring together data from across different parts of an organization into one place, it’s outdated.</p>
  <p>People need to shift their mindset to connecting – rather than collecting – data. When you consider your data strategy, prioritize a digital business platform that can automatically pull data from wherever it resides – whether that’s your supply chain or finance teams’ applications or somewhere else. Doing that helps ensure your employees can work with real-time information from across the company.</p>
  <h2 id="make-sure-you-can-handle-all-data-types">Make Sure You Can Handle All Data Types</h2>
  <p>Organizations generate all kinds of data – structured, unstructured, relational, and geospatial, to name a few. Too often organizations approach each type of data differently and separately, which replicates the problem of unconnected data that doesn’t come together in one holistic picture.</p>
  <p>Select a platform with data capabilities that can analyze and knit together these different types into a unified whole. Businesses need a modern platform that treats data as multimodal and multidimensional. By looking at the multiple facets of data, business leaders can make new correlations that help to make better decisions while accurately anticipating future opportunities and threats.</p>
  <h2 id="harness-data-to-drive-automation">Harness Data to Drive Automation</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-business-technology-platform-the-platform-for-the-intelligent-enterprise">SAP Business Technology Platform: The platform for the Intelligent Enterprise</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The real power of data kicks in when you can use it to drive automation and machine-augmented decision-making. There’s no reason to maintain so many manual processes, like invoice reconciliation or handling basic customer complaints in call centers. If you can harness data appropriately, many types of tasks can be automated – freeing employees to do more strategic work.</p>
  <p>Automation also augments employees’ on-the-spot decision-making capabilities. For example, a consumer packaged goods company could use data from cameras and machines to help a quality control manager determine whether to approve a certain batch of products. <a href="https://insights.sap.com/what-is-machine-learning/">Machine learning</a> can process varied pieces of information, such as the Internet of Things (IoT) data or bill-of-material changes, faster than a human, providing an extra level of support on the front lines.</p>
  <p>To advance automation, you need a platform that allows you to embed machine learning and artificial intelligence (AI) into your business applications – and one that can handle varied data sources in real-time.</p>
  <h2 id="democratize-data">Democratize Data</h2>
  <p>While data used to be the preserve of elite analysts and data scientists, now it’s a priority to democratize data. Information needs to be easily accessed not just by executives but by people on the front lines so they can use it to make decisions. Enabling self-service access to data also reduces the time IT departments spend on manual work, like running reports.</p>
  <p>Your platform must make it easy for everyone to access and analyze data, so be sure to evaluate the usability of your data management solutions. Ask questions such as: Is it user-friendly and intuitive? What kind of training is involved to empower people with self-service analytics tools?</p>
  <h2 id="protect-your-data">Protect Your Data</h2>
  <p>Related to access is the importance of security. One of the hallmarks of digital business is the ability to seamlessly connect across your organization but also externally to your customers, partners, and suppliers. But this is fraught with risk – especially in this day and age of ransomware.</p>
  <p>Your data platform must take into account any areas of exposure or vulnerability and build in the right security, access controls, and governance to protect your data – and information shared across your network.</p>
  <p>Finally, remember how you use your data will make the difference between success and failure in the next decade. It’s the foundation of digital transformation and will help launch new digital business models that go beyond automation – and truly redefine how companies operate and differentiate themselves. <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">SAP Business Technology Platform</a> provides a platform with database and data management, analytics, and intelligent technology – like embedded AI – solutions that customers around the world are already using.</p>
  <p>So choose wisely. Because with the right platform, your company will be poised for success now and in the future.</p>
  <p>To learn more about this topic, attend the “SAP Data and Analytics Forum: Accelerating Outcomes,” which will be held virtually from September 14 to October 7. <a href="https://events.sap.com/sap-data--and-analytics-virtual-forum-accelerating-outcomes/en/home">Find more information and register for the event</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Raghu Ramanathan is chief revenue officer for Platform and Technologies at SAP.</em><br><em><a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2021/07/28/five-ways-to-make-the-most-of-your-data/?sh=4d86bd7ddb44">This article also appeared on SAP BrandVoice on Forbes.</a></em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/automation</category>
            <category>topic/data-analytics</category>
            <category>news-tag/database-and-data-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/internet-of-things</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>