<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/carbon-neutrality/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sustainability Takes Flight across Aviation Industry]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/sustainability-aviation-industry</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/sustainability-aviation-industry</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Airplane manufacturers are moving towards a holistic strategy for sustainable design throughout an airplane’s entire life cycle. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/aerospace-defense</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-footprint</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-neutrality</category>
            <category>news-tag/circular-economy</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>product/sap-enterprise-product-development</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhancing Sustainability with People and Technology: A Transformation Story from SAP]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/enhancing-sustainability-people-technology-21-million-trees</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/enhancing-sustainability-people-technology-21-million-trees</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[As part of it's commitment to climate protection, SAP has added the goal of planting 21 million trees by the end of 2025.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14a74ac1e4d51fe757620cf88f165b999289e4684.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14a74ac1e4d51fe757620cf88f165b999289e4684.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_14a74ac1e4d51fe757620cf88f165b999289e4684.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Enhancing Sustainability with People and Technology: A Transformation Story from SAP" src="./media_14a74ac1e4d51fe757620cf88f165b999289e4684.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="enhancing-sustainability-with-people-and-technology-a-transformation-story-from-sap">Enhancing Sustainability with People and Technology: A Transformation Story from SAP</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Climate change is one of the biggest challenges of the 21st century and settling for doing “less harm” is no longer sufficient. It is urgently time to “do more good.” As an enabler and exemplar, SAP is committed to contributing to climate protection and has added the goal of planting 21 million trees by the end of 2025 to a comprehensive portfolio of measures.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Why does this matter? Trees are an essential part of our earth and invaluable in maintaining the stability of our planet. According to the United Nations (UN), over <a href="https://www.un.org/sustainabledevelopment/biodiversity/">80% of terrestrial animals and plants live in forests</a> and approximately 1.6 billion people rely on forests for their daily subsistence. Moreover, forests absorb about <a href="https://www.iucn.org/resources/issues-briefs/forests-and-climate-change">2.6 billion tons of CO<sub>2</sub></a> each year — a third of the CO<sub>2</sub> emissions that are released due to the burning of fossil fuels.</p>
  <p>Forest restoration and protection has become an important pillar of addressing climate change through nature-based solutions. SAP’s goal to restore ecosystems and foster sustainable development by planting 21 million trees before the end of 2025 is therefore an important addition to its portfolio of climate measures and <a href="https://www.weforum.org/agenda/2021/04/carbon-offsetting-climate-crisis/">complements</a> much needed action to avoid emissions in the first place.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-accelerates-climate-protection-to-achieve-carbon-neutrality-by-2023">SAP Accelerates Climate Protection to Achieve Carbon-Neutrality by 2023</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/03/sap-carbon-neutrality-goal-2023">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="harnessing-the-power-of-technology">Harnessing the Power of Technology</h2>
  <p>Deforestation and disasters such as wildfires accelerate climate change. However, digital technologies can help fight it: for example, the nongovernmental organization <a href="https://discover.sap.com/mobile-innovation-lab/en-us/rainforest.html">Rainforest Connection is working with SAP and using discarded smart phones, machine learning, and an app</a> to track and stop illegal loggers.</p>
  <p>To scale impact even further, SAP is collaborating with customers and partners to co-innovate solutions that enable systemic change toward a more inclusive, <a href="https://www.ellenmacarthurfoundation.org/publications/completing-the-picture-climate-change">circular, and decarbonized economy</a>. <a href="/2020/06/climate-21-track-greenhouse-gas-emissions">Climate 21</a> was launched to build analytical and transactional capabilities into enterprise applications, which can help customers understand and minimize the greenhouse gas footprint of their products and operations along their value chains. Additional programs focusing on a circular economy and holistic steering and reporting are under way to <a href="/2021/06/sapphire-now-sustainability-management-by-sap">accelerate sustainable business transformation</a> further.</p>
  <h2 id="leading-by-example">Leading by Example</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="build-sustainability-directly-into-your-core-business-processes-with-sap">Build sustainability directly into your core business processes with SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/sustainability.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>To walk the talk, SAP is reducing its own greenhouse gas emissions as well as taking action to protect and restore forests.</p>
  <p>The journey started back in 2009, when SAP set the first goal of reducing its global greenhouse gas emissions to the year-2000 level by 2020. <a href="/2018/03/sap-integrated-report-2020-targets-met-early">This target was met at the end of 2017</a>, despite growing more than fourfold in the interim. The next milestone is in 2023, when SAP aims to become <a href="/2021/03/sap-carbon-neutrality-goal-2023">carbon neutral in its own operations</a> – two years earlier than previously envisaged.</p>
  <p>To achieve this, the company follows a three-pillar approach: <strong>avoid</strong>, <strong>reduce</strong>, <strong>compensate</strong>. The goal is to avoid emissions in the first place; for example, by using virtual telecommunication instead of business flights, a practice that has naturally expanded during the pandemic and was one major driver for SAP overachieving by 43% on its target for reducing net carbon emissions in 2020, generating 135 kilotons (kt) instead of the anticipated 238 kt.</p>
  <p>Secondly, if a share of its greenhouse gas emissions cannot yet be avoided, SAP aims to reduce it through innovations, among others in the areas of building efficiency, data center operations, carpooling, and car sharing, as well as e-mobility. For example, SAP is powering its own data centers and facilities with 100% renewable electricity and working toward 33% e-cars in its global car fleet by 2025. Green IT initiatives foster sustainable IT equipment usage and promote tools such as <a href="https://www.ecosia.org/">Ecosia</a> as default search engine. In 2020, SAP implemented additional energy and climate measures within its operations, ranging from opening a new office with energy-efficient design in Australia and implementing more efficient data center technology in Germany to introducing a bike fleet at SAP Hungary and installing photovoltaic systems in Austria.</p>
  <h2 id="million-trees-by-the-end-of-2025">21 Million Trees by the End of 2025</h2>
  <p>For emissions that cannot yet be reduced or avoided, the company thirdly invests in high-quality carbon credits. For example, SAP has been a long-term investor of the <a href="/2020/08/sap-lcf-investment-livelihoods-carbon-funds">Livelihoods Carbon Funds (LCF)</a> since 2012. In close collaboration with rural communities and partners across the world, these funds realize valuable projects that enable sustainable development and environmental benefits, such as carbon dioxide capture, improved water quality, and habitats for wildlife, as well as income opportunities for rural communities.</p>
  <p>SAP has also donated funds to restore ecosystems and improve people’s lives. In 2020, Eden Reforestation Projects planted over 1.3 million trees in Madagascar, Haiti, Indonesia, and Nepal on behalf of SAP. In 2021, SAP continued to support organizations on a mission to restore native forests. For example, SAP partnered with the <a href="/uk/2021/06/sap-partners-with-the-carbon-community-on-new-scientific-forestry-research-to-drive-climate-change-efficiency">UK charity The Carbon Community</a> on new scientific forestry research to enhance nature-based solutions to climate change and improve the efficiency of carbon removal from the atmosphere. In Australia, ReForest Now planted 20,000 trees for SAP, which will help restore critically endangered subtropical rainforest.</p>
  <p>Yet much more climate action is needed. In support of the <a href="https://www.decadeonrestoration.org/">UN Decade on Ecosystem Restoration 2021-2030</a>, SAP recently joined the <a href="https://www.1t.org/">1t.org corporate alliance</a><u>,</u> which aims to conserve, restore, and grow trees worldwide, with a pledge to plant 21 million trees by the end of 2025.</p>
  <p>As the <a href="https://www.decadeonrestoration.org/join-movement">UN correctly states</a>: “Restoration is a monumental task. Over the next 10 years, every action counts. Every single day. Every country, company, organization, and individual have a role to play.”</p>
  <p>We invite you to join us and the UN Decade for Ecosystem and help build a more sustainable tomorrow.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-neutrality</category>
            <category>news-tag/greenhouse-gas-emissions</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Accelerates Climate Protection to Achieve Carbon-Neutrality by 2023]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/03/sap-carbon-neutrality-goal-2023</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/03/sap-carbon-neutrality-goal-2023</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP has announced its intention to achieve carbon-neutrality by the end of 2023, two years earlier than previously stated.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_19d36522df6973ef89439b8c7028f4f5c82fbe843.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_19d36522df6973ef89439b8c7028f4f5c82fbe843.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_19d36522df6973ef89439b8c7028f4f5c82fbe843.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Accelerates Climate Protection to Achieve Carbon-Neutrality by 2023" src="./media_19d36522df6973ef89439b8c7028f4f5c82fbe843.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-accelerates-climate-protection-to-achieve-carbon-neutrality-by-2023">SAP Accelerates Climate Protection to Achieve Carbon-Neutrality by 2023</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-the-2020-sap-integrated-report">Read the 2020 SAP Integrated Report</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="http://www.sapintegratedreport.com/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced its intention to become carbon-neutral in its own operations by the end of 2023 – two years earlier than previously stated. This announcement coincided with the publication of <a href="http://www.sapintegratedreport.com/">SAP’s Integrated Report 2020</a>.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Last year, the company reduced its greenhouse gas (GHG) emissions more than planned, mainly due to changes in the way its 100,000 employees across the world worked and traveled during the <a href="/covid-19">COVID-19</a> pandemic.</p>
  <p>A sharp decline in business flights contributed significantly to SAP’s reduced carbon footprint in 2020. With employees working predominantly from home, carbon emissions caused by the daily commute and the operation of office buildings fell. As a result, SAP was able to overachieve by 43% on its target for reducing net carbon emissions in 2020, generating 135 kilotons (kt) instead of the anticipated 238 kt. By way of comparison, SAP’s emissions in 2019 were 300 kt. By accelerating faster toward carbon-neutral operations, SAP anticipates the current development and underscores its role as a front-runner in climate protection.</p>
  <p>In striving to become carbon-neutral, SAP takes into account all of its direct and indirect emissions, as well as selected emissions arising in the supply chain, including those linked to business flights, business travel in rental cars and third-party data centers. The company uses the approach of first avoiding, second reducing and third compensating emissions. Whenever possible, SAP aims to avoid the creation of GHGs through a variety of business practices, such as using telecommunication technologies rather than traveling. If emissions cannot be avoided, SAP leverages innovations, such as energy-efficient lighting in offices, efficient cooling systems in data centers and alternative mobility solutions. Lastly, SAP offsets unavoidable emissions by supporting climate projects and working with partners who meet the gold standard advanced by <a href="https://www.goldstandard.org/">The Gold Standard Foundation</a> or equivalent quality standards. In addition, SAP continuously drives new corporate initiatives, such as putting an internal carbon price on business flights.</p>
  <p>Since 2017, SAP has also been pursuing a <a href="/2019/07/sap-emissions-reduction-targets">science-based climate target</a> certified by the Science Based Targets initiative (SBTi) to make its own contribution to limiting global warming to 1.5°C above preindustrial levels. While its zero-carbon goal applies chiefly to its own operations, SAP’s science-based climate target also encompasses the upstream and downstream value chain. SAP has been using 100% renewable energy to power all of its data centers since 2014. Thanks to its <a href="/2014/03/sap-greens-its-cloud-will-power-data-centers-and-facilities-with-100-percent-renewable-electricity-in-2014">green cloud</a>, SAP can offer customers cloud solutions that are carbon-neutral.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP supports the <a href="http://www.sap.com/unglobalgoals">Sustainable Development Goals</a> set in 2015 by the United Nations General Assembly, focusing particularly on goal 13, Climate Action. Here, SAP’s greatest strength lies in its ability to help its more than 400,000 customers worldwide implement climate protection measures through offerings such as the <a href="/2020/06/launch-sap-carbon-product-carbon-footprint-analytics">Climate 21</a> program. Together with customers and partners, SAP will provide more information on solutions in this context as well as on the circular economy, holistic steering and reporting at the virtual <a href="https://events.sap.com/sap-sustainability-summit/en/home">SAP Sustainability Summit</a> taking place on April 28–29, 2021.</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="http://news.sap.com/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP on Twitter at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Media Contact:</strong> Bettina Wunderle, +49 7544 970538, <a href="mailto:bettina.wunderle@sap.com">bettina.wunderle@sap.com</a>, CET<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>Any statements contained in this document that are not historical facts are forward-looking statements as defined in the U.S. Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995. Words such as “anticipate,” “believe,” “estimate,” “expect,” “forecast,” “intend,” “may,” “plan,” “project,” “predict,” “should” and “will” and similar expressions as they relate to SAP are intended to identify such forward-looking statements. SAP undertakes no obligation to publicly update or revise any forward-looking statements. All forward-looking statements are subject to various risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results to differ materially from expectations. The factors that could affect SAP’s future financial results are discussed more fully in SAP’s filings with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (“SEC”), including SAP’s most recent Annual Report on Form 20-F filed with the SEC. Readers are cautioned not to place undue reliance on these forward-looking statements, which speak only as of their dates.<br>© 2021 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-neutrality</category>
            <category>news-tag/un-sdgs</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>