<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/hannover-messe/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hannover Messe: What Can AI Do for Manufacturing?]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/hannover-messe-ai-manufacturing</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/hannover-messe-ai-manufacturing</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[At Hannover Messe 2024, SAP and its partners showed how they are embedding AI to help companies achieve excellence in manufacturing.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/catena-x</category>
            <category>news-tag/hannover-messe</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-x</category>
            <category>product/sap-digital-manufacturing</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Smart Manufacturing Creates Opportunity for Partner-Driven, AI-Infused Innovation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-partner-ai-innovation-smart-manufacturing</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-partner-ai-innovation-smart-manufacturing</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In the age of business AI, SAP partners are developing and delivering industry innovations across discrete manufacturing.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_149e02fca5b080a1038dfae06eb31000b8cc98754.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_149e02fca5b080a1038dfae06eb31000b8cc98754.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_149e02fca5b080a1038dfae06eb31000b8cc98754.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Smart Manufacturing Creates Opportunity for Partner-Driven, AI-Infused Innovation" src="./media_149e02fca5b080a1038dfae06eb31000b8cc98754.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="smart-manufacturing-creates-opportunity-for-partner-driven-ai-infused-innovation">Smart Manufacturing Creates Opportunity for Partner-Driven, AI-Infused Innovation</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>One of the perks of my job is that I get to spend a considerable amount of time with our industry partners. Whether I’m talking with a startup software company or an established global service partner, two words — two letters actually — are the hot topic of almost every engagement lately: artificial intelligence, specifically <strong>business AI</strong>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-at-hannover-messe-bring-out-new-manufacturing-excellence">SAP at Hannover Messe: Bring out new manufacturing excellence</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://events.sap.com/hannovermesse/en/home">Learn how</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As we navigate this brave new world of business AI, SAP partners are playing an essential role as equal parts technology disrupters, trusted advisors, and innovation multipliers. They work and live at the edge, breaking technology rules with every new solution and innovation they bring to the table. These companies are passionate about their AI-driven solutions, which will provide what SAP manufacturing customers want most for their businesses nowadays: more efficiency, accuracy, and agility in their production operations and supply chains. Their energy and passion are positioning them to redefine the rules of engagement regarding how partner ecosystems work.</p>
  <p>It doesn’t matter what kind of partner you are — you could be on the build, implement/service, or sell sides of the SAP partner ecosystem, the opportunities to innovate, and co-innovate with SAP and other partners, solutions that bring value to customers in discrete manufacturing industries are as limitless as our imaginations. It’s an exciting time to be an SAP industry partner.</p>
  <h2 id="innovative-solutions-from-sap-and-partners-give-our-manufacturing-customers-a-competitive-edge">Innovative Solutions from SAP and Partners Give Our Manufacturing Customers a Competitive Edge</h2>
  <p>Giving our manufacturing customers the business AI solutions they need to thrive in highly competitive and often volatile markets is an absolute must. Whether those solutions are developed by an SAP partner, SAP itself, or collaboratively is secondary.</p>
  <p>This new drive to co-innovate on our customers’ behalf is creating opportunities for partners to develop and deliver industry innovations in three areas of discrete manufacturing:</p>
  <ol>
    <li><strong>Solutions that enable efficient, accurate, and agile manufacturing and supply chains</strong> by integrating processes, removing data silos, and seamlessly connecting manufacturing and supply chain applications with the whole of the business.</li>
    <li><strong>Solutions that improve decision-making</strong> by using AI to analyze data from internal and external sources in context and produce insights that increase manufacturing operations’ resilience and help customers strike the right balance among cost, sustainability, and customer satisfaction.</li>
    <li><strong>Solutions that promote collaboration within a business ecosystem</strong>. Many of the company executives I’ve spoken with recently wanted to talk about Manufacturing-X, the growing cross-industry initiative in which companies across various manufacturing value chains come together within a global business ecosystem to define a standard that enables them to share production and supply chain data across platforms and technology to further increase resilience, sustainability, and competitiveness.</li>
  </ol>
  <p>We are bringing this customer-focused, partner-driven approach to life this week at Hannover Messe, bringing center stage the latest, most compelling innovations to emerge from SAP and our partner ecosystem, across both discrete and process manufacturing — many embedded with business AI.</p>
  <p>Some of the showcases that have been developed collaboratively in action include:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Modular manufacturing that orchestrates production cells with a hard independent fleet manager</li>
    <li>High-speed bottling that captures traceability data and in-line quality assurance</li>
    <li>A centralized operations control center that manages an offsite process production line</li>
    <li>AI-enhanced visual inspection and guided instructions during component assembly</li>
    <li>A quick guided journey through an Industrial Metaverse, showing how assets inside a power plant can be intelligently and remotely managed</li>
  </ul>
  <p>SAP partners are playing an integral part in our presence at Hannover Messe, just as they are in our overarching industry vision. Partners including Accenture, Camelot ITLab, Cideon Software &#x26; Services, FORCAM, Kinexon, Systema, and TeamViewer are all exhibiting their solutions alongside their SAP counterparts, demonstrating the true power of partnership and innovation at every turn.</p>
  <p>By leveraging resources like the new SAP AI Launchpad and generative AI hub, our partners will introduce industry innovations that will add immediate value for customers in the discrete and process manufacturing space. Hence, they have the intelligent digital tools they need to be future-ready.</p>
  <p>Kinexon’s OS extension to the SAP Digital Manufacturing solution is one example. Kinexon OS orchestrates the shop floor and automates previously manual processes, improving production speed, quality, and asset utilization. It is providing customers with an essential pathway to modular production and autonomous manufacturing.</p>
  <p>For those of you at the event, stop by the SAP space and experience innovation and partnership in perfect harmony firsthand. An electric injection molding machine developed by Fanuc with support from partner Syntax will be cranking out made-to-order drinking vessels.</p>
  <p>Come enjoy a cup of inspiration on us. It’s a small but meaningful taste of what’s possible for partners in our collaborative, customer-focused, and business AI-driven cloud ecosystem.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Sven Denecken is senior vice president and chief marketing and solutions officer for Industries &#x26; CX at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="the-power-of-partnership-drive-customer-success-with-solutions-from-sap-delivering-trusted-advice-and-deep-product-knowledge">The power of partnership: drive customer success with solutions from SAP, delivering trusted advice and deep product knowledge</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/partners.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/hannover-messe</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Unveils AI-Driven Supply-Chain Innovations to Transform Manufacturing]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-hannover-messe-ai-supply-chain-innovations-transform-manufacturing</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-hannover-messe-ai-supply-chain-innovations-transform-manufacturing</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New AI supply chain advancements from SAP will unleash a transformative wave of productivity, efficiency and precision in manufacturing.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_139d76aac37abd129378ce3f34ce615947934235d.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_139d76aac37abd129378ce3f34ce615947934235d.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_139d76aac37abd129378ce3f34ce615947934235d.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Unveils AI-Driven Supply-Chain Innovations to Transform Manufacturing" src="./media_139d76aac37abd129378ce3f34ce615947934235d.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-unveils-ai-driven-supply-chain-innovations-to-transform-manufacturing">SAP Unveils AI-Driven Supply-Chain Innovations to Transform Manufacturing</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>HANNOVER</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced AI advancements in its supply chain solutions that will unleash a transformative wave of productivity, efficiency and precision in manufacturing. AI-driven insights from real-time data will help companies use their own data to make better decisions across supply chains, streamline product development and improve manufacturing efficiency.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-at-hannover-messe-bring-out-new-manufacturing-excellence">SAP at Hannover Messe: Bring out new manufacturing excellence</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://events.sap.com/hannovermesse/en/home">Learn how</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“Businesses today are confronted with challenges ranging from supply chain disruptions and labor shortages to geopolitical uncertainties,” said Muhammad Alam, member of the Executive Board of SAP SE, SAP Product Engineering. “SAP recognizes the imperative for agility and intelligence, driving innovation with AI-powered solutions to streamline supply chain and manufacturing processes. Companies can enhance operational efficiency and improve supply chain resiliency while delighting customers with superior service, paving the way for sustained growth and market competitiveness.”</p>
  <p>Accurate and relevant real-time information helps mitigate the impact that supply-chain disruptions have on suppliers, manufacturers and distributors worldwide. SMA Solar Technology AG and other customers have already witnessed the benefits of SAP’s solutions, including an approximately 15% increase in supply chain workforce productivity, a 10% decrease in overall supply chain planning costs and a 10% reduction in inventory carrying costs and stock turnover rate.</p>
  <p>“SMA Solar modernizes its manufacturing execution systems to support sustainable, risk-resilient manufacturing operations with the power of AI-enabled visual inspection in the SAP Digital Manufacturing solution,” said Heiko Kehm, SMA Solar head of IT Order to Cash.</p>
  <p>Sixty-three percent of supply chain executives and 52% of operations executives have an AI strategy linked to business objectives, according to “<a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2024/04/2214aa25-b77e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">The Importance of AI in Supply Chain and Operations</a>,” a global 2024 IDC InfoBrief sponsored by SAP*. Fifty-one percent of the 2,000 survey respondents are embedding AI into supply chain planning business processes and key applications for real-time decision-making. Another 58% are using AI to increase operational efficiency and employee productivity.</p>
  <p><a href="https://community.sap.com/t5/supply-chain-management-blogs-by-sap/ai-powered-supply-chain-solutions-better-decisions-better-outcomes/ba-p/13675845">Key improvements</a> to SAP’s supply chain solutions to support customers’ AI-centric strategy include:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Optimizing decisions across the supply chain with AI-driven insights:</strong> Companies can now leverage higher volumes of machine data and integrate AI-driven visual inspection by computer into their production processes, enabling a remarkable increase in quality through automation.</li>
    <li><strong>Streamlining product development:</strong> Product developers can now use SAP’s AI copilot Joule to gather and enhance new product ideas quickly and effectively using natural language queries. Joule also helps tag product designs with business data, so they visually contextualize business-critical information.</li>
    <li><strong>Detecting equipment anomalies</strong>: Using AI, asset operators can proactively address potential breakdowns based on sensor data collected from smart devices and edge gateways. This new capacity utilizes the cutting-edge Cumulocity IoT platform from Software AG, which is planned to be embedded in the SAP Asset Performance Management application in Q3.</li>
    <li><strong>Improving field response:</strong> Customers can optimize driving routes and allocate job assignments efficiently with integrated real-time traffic data and machine-learning-trained models, which enable the right field service technicians to reach their destinations on time.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>Find more details about the innovations SAP will show at Hannover Messe <a href="https://events.sap.com/hannovermesse/en/home">here</a>.</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <p>*IDC InfoBrief, sponsored by SAP, The Importance of AI in Supply Chain and Operations, document #US52042224, April 2024.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>About SAP</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As a global leader in enterprise applications and business AI, SAP (NYSE: SAP) stands at the nexus of business and technology. For over 50 years, organizations have trusted SAP to bring out their best by uniting business-critical operations spanning finance, procurement, HR, supply chain, and customer experience. For more information, visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/">www.sap.com</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Note to editors:</strong><br>To preview and download broadcast-standard stock footage and press photos digitally, please visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/photos">www.sap.com/photos</a>. On this platform, you can find high resolution material for your media channels.</p>
  <p><strong>For customers interested in learning more about SAP products:</strong><br>Global Customer Center: +49 180 534-34-24<br>United States Only: 1 (800) 872-1SAP (1-800-872-1727)</p>
  <p><strong>For more information, press only:</strong><br>Dana Roesiger, +49 6227 7 63900, <a href="mailto:dana.roesiger@sap.com">dana.roesiger@sap.com</a>, CET<br>Julie Schneider, +1 (650) 687-2788, <a href="mailto:julie.schneider@sap.com">julie.schneider@sap.com</a>, PT<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>This document contains forward-looking statements, which are predictions, projections, or other statements about future events. These statements are based on current expectations, forecasts, and assumptions that are subject to risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results and outcomes to materially differ. Additional information regarding these risks and uncertainties may be found in our filings with the Securities and Exchange Commission, including but not limited to the risk factors section of SAP’s 2023 Annual Report on Form 20-F.<br>© 2024 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p>Please consider our <a href="https://www.sap.com/corporate/en/legal/privacy.html">privacy policy</a>. If you received this press release in your e-mail and you wish to unsubscribe to our mailing list please contact <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a> and write Unsubscribe in the subject line.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-supply-chain</category>
            <category>news-tag/hannover-messe</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[HANNOVER MESSE: Making Manufacturing More Resilient]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/hannover-messe-making-manufacturing-more-resilient</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/hannover-messe-making-manufacturing-more-resilient</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[At the 2023 Hannover Messe trade show, SAP showed visitors how it enables resilient, sustainable production and supply chain operations.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/circular-economy</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-supply-chain</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/hannover-messe</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-4-0</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-x</category>
            <category>product/sap-digital-manufacturing</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[HANNOVER MESSE 2023: SAP Generates New Data-Driven Insights for Resilient Manufacturing]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/sap-hannover-messe-2023-data-driven-insights-resilient-manufacturing</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/sap-hannover-messe-2023-data-driven-insights-resilient-manufacturing</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[At HANNOVER MESSE 2023, SAP will showcase its unique position to accelerate the journey to resilient manufacturing. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/catena-x</category>
            <category>news-tag/hannover-messe</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-x</category>
            <category>news-tag/oxford-economics</category>
            <category>product/sap-digital-manufacturing</category>
            <category>product/sap-responsible-design-and-production</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hannover Messe Showcases Digitalization at Every Level]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/06/hannover-messe-showcases-digitalization</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/06/hannover-messe-showcases-digitalization</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[At Hannover Messe, SAP showed how Industry 4.0 processes pave the way toward becoming customer-centric, robust, sustainable enterprises.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digitalization</category>
            <category>news-tag/hannover-messe</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-4-0</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP at Hannover Messe: Automated Material Supply in Intralogistics with IIoT]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/hannover-messe-automated-material-supply-iiot</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/hannover-messe-automated-material-supply-iiot</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[At Hannover Messe exhibition, SAP will showcase automated material supply in intralogistics with IIoT. Learn more about the event.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11174721b72ee01f1bdf33708a811e10c1525f623.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11174721b72ee01f1bdf33708a811e10c1525f623.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_11174721b72ee01f1bdf33708a811e10c1525f623.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP at Hannover Messe: Automated Material Supply in Intralogistics with IIoT" src="./media_11174721b72ee01f1bdf33708a811e10c1525f623.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-at-hannover-messe-automated-material-supply-in-intralogistics-with-iiot">SAP at Hannover Messe: Automated Material Supply in Intralogistics with IIoT</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>At this year’s virtual <a href="/topics/hannover-messe">Hannover Messe</a> exhibition, SAP will show how Industry 4.Now can help make supply chains more flexible and dynamic, including through the use of the Industrial Internet of Things (IIoT).</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“Many of our customers have seen their global supply chains take on a tremendous level of complexity,” says Dominik Metzger, head of Product Management, Manufacturing, and Industrial IoT at SAP. Those operating in production industries typically find themselves enmeshed in an intricate web of international suppliers and sub-suppliers. “That’s why plenty of companies are really struggling with disruptions,” Metzger explains. “Some of them have to do with <a href="/covid-19">COVID-19</a>, but others have been apparent since before the pandemic.”</p>
  <p>In terms of macroeconomic trends, the introduction of significant trade tariffs between China and the U.S. as well as the post-Brexit EU/UK Trade and Cooperation Agreement have rattled the established structures of many organizations.</p>
  <p>“For that reason, if anything is a top priority for our customers – right now and after the pandemic – it is measures that lower costs and boost productivity in efficient ways,” Metzger says. “For those of us at SAP, the core question is: How can we leverage our innovative technologies to help our customers automate their processes?”</p>
  <p>At the virtual Hannover Messe 2021 exhibition, SAP plans to unveil an array of new functions and applications that are set to make industrial process data usable all along the value chain starting in the second quarter.</p>
  <p>“That includes data generated during manufacturing, maintenance, logistics, and so on, which needs to be integrated deep within SAP applications,” Metzger shares. Value cannot be created for companies with data alone; it also has to be analyzed in a business context. “That context lies in SAP systems – in our intelligent suite, our industry cloud, and our manufacturing and logistics solutions.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="join-sap-at-hannover-messe">Join SAP at Hannover Messe</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://events.sap.com/en-hannover-messe-2021/en/home?url_id=ctabutton-de-hm21-newscenter:CRM-DE21-EVE-HM21COMNC1">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="supplying-materials-automatically-with-iot-robotics-and-edge-computing">Supplying Materials Automatically with IoT, Robotics, and Edge Computing</h2>
  <p>Metzger’s product management team has put together an IIoT portfolio that enables customers to fully automate their resupply and stock removal processes in SAP S/4HANA, to name just two examples. This is made possible by robotics, the digitalization of intralogistics processes, and an intelligent framework of rules that derives potential actions from real-time data.</p>
  <p>In assembly line manufacturing, things like forklifts and manual transport systems are needed to retrieve materials for subsequent installation. Areas like these are where companies often implement the ‘kanban’ process, which involves supplying materials exactly where production and assembly employees need them on the line.</p>
  <p>“Sensors are now being built into these kanban bins in order to ‘connect’ the materials,” Metzger explains. “A sensor can tell when the weight of its bin has fallen below a certain threshold, which is when more materials are automatically procured to resupply the bin.”</p>
  <p>Meanwhile, an intelligent, cloud-based system of rules interprets the sensor data to determine when actions should be triggered in specific business processes and applications. Systems like SAP S/4HANA, SAP Digital Manufacturing Cloud, and SAP Predictive Asset Insights are highly integrated into the rules to help ensure that the right processes are automatically activated at the right time. Procedures pertaining to kanban, the posting of goods, and quality assurance are just a few pertinent examples.</p>
  <p>“We refer to this combination of IoT and SAP Edge Services as ‘Industrial IoT’ because we’re using IoT data in an industrial context,” Metzger says.</p>
  <p>In a further innovation, autonomous guided vehicles (AGVs) are responsible for retrieving materials instead of forklift drivers. Metzger describes this fully automated approach to supplying assembly lines and carrying away finished products as a “best-in-class” logistics process, but one that only works when completely integrated between SAP systems for manufacturing execution (MES) and warehouse management.</p>
  <p>These new functions are designed to be used in the context of SAP Digital Manufacturing Cloud, where they can be implemented and employed seamlessly thanks to the integration of SAP Manufacturing solution systems and others for logistics.</p>
  <h2 id="lower-implementation-costs-through-standardization">Lower Implementation Costs Through Standardization</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="industry-4now-agile-production-in-uncertain-times">Industry 4.Now: Agile Production in Uncertain Times</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/03/industry-4now-agile-production-uncertain-times">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>According to a <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/supply-chain-management/industry-4-0.html?overlay=%252Fcmp%252Fdg%252Findustry4-mpi%252Findex.html">study that SAP conducted with the MPI Group</a>, customers tested these productivity-boosting innovations at specific plants and warehouses in 2020, but have not yet rolled them out more broadly in many cases.</p>
  <p>“That’s because until now, the integration of operational technology like AGVs or machines, sensors, and other equipment wasn’t standardized very well in business software,” Metzger explains. “This meant that such projects involved a relatively large amount of implementation effort, and thus higher costs – which led to something of a catch-22 with regard to the fundamental idea of reducing costs and increasing productivity.”</p>
  <p>In the meantime, however, SAP has put much of its focus on integrating automation technologies into industry standards like the OPC Unified Architecture and on implementing the administration shell.</p>
  <h2 id="sap-relies-on-cloud-edge-architecture-to-reduce-costs">SAP Relies on Cloud-Edge Architecture to Reduce Costs</h2>
  <p>“Over the last six or seven years, we’ve invested a huge amount of effort in lowering the total cost of ownership of these implementations so that customers can operate them at scale. Along with standardization, the main thing that’s helping us here is our own technological innovation in terms of cloud-edge architecture,” Metzger says. In the past, the fact that SAP hardware infrastructure had to be set up at every plant was another reason why implementing new solutions was expensive.</p>
  <p>“These days, however, all these processes run in the cloud,” Metzger continues. This means that it takes just one data center to control processes like warehouse robotics, digital manufacturing, or IIoT at 100 plants or more.</p>
  <p>“When you’re dealing with automation processes in particular, you can’t afford to have an Internet connection fail for a few seconds,” Metzger says. “It was for high-availability scenarios like these that we introduced SAP Digital Manufacturing Cloud for edge computing.”</p>
  <p>This involves an edge device – basically a small-scale server – that helps ensure that mission-critical processes always keep running at a plant. Instead of being implemented anew at each facility, these processes are configured centrally in the cloud for each specific plant and run at the edge in a container at the plant.</p>
  <p>SAP Edge Services and other IoT offerings from the company enable customers to turn use cases like these into reality. “It gives you the best of both worlds,” Metzger says. “It significantly improves your ability to scale up thanks to cloud computing, all while reducing your total cost of ownership. Plus, edge computing gives you the degree of robustness you need to control mission-critical processes.”</p>
  <p>In addition, auto ID technology is to be offered as a new function in SAP Edge Services and IoT solutions from SAP. This technology makes it possible to automatically associate the movement of a physical object with a specific process step. “Real-time status updates like these are a big step forward in terms of supply chain reliability,” Metzger says. “This way, companies can make sure they’re always available to their customers and able to adapt to bottlenecks around the world.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>To find out more about how IIoT can help your company reduce costs and increase its productivity, <a href="https://events.sap.com/en-hannover-messe-2021/en/registration.aspx">register here for the virtual Hannover Messe exhibition</a>, scheduled for April 12–16, 2021.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/hannover-messe</category>
            <category>news-tag/iiot</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-4-now</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>