<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/xaas/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unleashing As-A-Service Growth: High-Tech Leaders Share Lessons Learned]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/unleashing-xaas-growth-high-tech-leaders-share-lessons</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/unleashing-xaas-growth-high-tech-leaders-share-lessons</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Two high-tech companies share their experiences with everything-as-a-service (XaaS) business models. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/financial-management</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>industry/high-tech</category>
            <category>news-tag/quote-to-cash</category>
            <category>news-tag/recurring-revenue-models</category>
            <category>product/sap-billing-and-revenue-innovation-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/subscription-billing</category>
            <category>news-tag/xaas</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Manufacturers Monetize Beyond Products: As-a-Service Builds Customer Relationships]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/as-a-service-builds-customer-relationships-manufacturing</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/as-a-service-builds-customer-relationships-manufacturing</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[As-a-service business models have helped manufacturers turn services into ongoing revenue streams and build relationships. Learn how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/financial-management</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>news-tag/quote-to-cash</category>
            <category>news-tag/recurring-revenue-models</category>
            <category>product/sap-billing-and-revenue-innovation-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/xaas</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Three Market Leaders on What It Takes to Become a Service-Based Business]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/three-market-leaders-service-based-xaas-business</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/three-market-leaders-service-based-xaas-business</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[At SAP Sapphire, industry leaders shared XaaS experiences, including business drivers and results, lessons learned, and future strategies.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/grow-with-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/quote-to-cash</category>
            <category>news-tag/recurring-revenue-models</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-billing-and-revenue-innovation-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/xaas</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Is a Leader in the IDC MarketScape for Worldwide Enterprise Subscription and Usage Management Applications]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/idc-marketscape-enterprise-subscription-and-usage-management</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/idc-marketscape-enterprise-subscription-and-usage-management</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is a Leader in the IDC MarketScape for Enterprise Subscription and Usage Management Applications. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc</category>
            <category>news-tag/quote-to-cash</category>
            <category>news-tag/recurring-revenue-models</category>
            <category>product/sap-billing-and-revenue-innovation-management</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/subscription-billing</category>
            <category>news-tag/xaas</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tackling Today’s Billing and Revenue Challenges for Media]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/09/tackling-billing-and-revenue-challenges-for-media</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/09/tackling-billing-and-revenue-challenges-for-media</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Automated, secure, accurate billing processes are a must for today’s media companies. SAP Billing and Revenue Innovation Management can help.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/financial-management</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/quote-to-cash</category>
            <category>news-tag/recurring-revenue-models</category>
            <category>product/sap-billing-and-revenue-innovation-management</category>
            <category>industry/telecommunications</category>
            <category>news-tag/xaas</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Transforming How Products and Services Are Offered and Sold]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2021/09/solution-order-management-transform-products-services-offered-sold</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2021/09/solution-order-management-transform-products-services-offered-sold</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Solution order management illustrates that significant added value comes from business process innovation. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_168974d465266f6b6227e97c9b9606df18440f4ef.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_168974d465266f6b6227e97c9b9606df18440f4ef.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_168974d465266f6b6227e97c9b9606df18440f4ef.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Transforming How Products and Services Are Offered and Sold" src="./media_168974d465266f6b6227e97c9b9606df18440f4ef.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="transforming-how-products-and-services-are-offered-and-sold">Transforming How Products and Services Are Offered and Sold</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Today, we see an increasing shift to “servitization” or “everything-as-a-service” business models, which includes new digital business models such as streaming. This changes not only how products and services are consumed, but also how and when they are ordered and paid for.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>This trend challenges traditional ways of doing business as it focuses on keeping customers for life by establishing longer term recurring revenue streams. Business models like these allow products and services to be offered in a completely new way instead of adapting or optimizing existing business processes.</p>
  <p>How can your company or line of business achieve this? To remain successful, businesses across industries continuously re-evaluate how to create additional value for their customers. At SAP, we are working with our customers to reimagine business processes that increase productivity and unveil growth opportunities. This includes, among other things, how new offerings are sold to customers in order to increase customer loyalty at the end of the day.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="explore-sap-s4hana-cloud">Explore SAP S/4HANA Cloud</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/s4hana-erp/features/cloud-release.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="from-selling-products-and-services-to-providing-bundled-solutions">From Selling Products and Services to Providing Bundled Solutions</h2>
  <p>While traditional business models are about selling physical goods and services, solution business models are built around the customers’ needs. Companies embracing these modern business models offer a combination of physical goods, services, and subscriptions to serve their customers’ needs holistically. And customers benefit from a one-stop-shop solution.</p>
  <p>Whether offering products or services, these new models expand the responsibility of companies beyond the initial sale to include all elements of a solution along the entire life cycle; for example, the delivery of a machine, its installation, and corresponding maintenance services. The technical and the business processes must support the customer on this journey and minimize the business risk for the solution provider. Delivering this kind of solution-based value maximizes customer satisfaction and drives margin growth by selling higher value services.</p>
  <p>This requires an <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iKISx5-kuEU">order management solution</a> that recognizes all the components of the order and has the ability to administer each step in the process — from capture to fulfillment, service, billing, and managing the profitability of the bundled solution.</p>
  <p>The <a href="https://www.sap.com/dmc/exp/2021-06-sapphireinnovation-news/sap-s-4hana-cloud-solution-order-management-enables-transformation-to-selling-bundled-solutions/">new solution order management process in SAP S/4HANA Cloud</a> enables businesses to sell bundled solutions, including subscriptions, and leverage innovative capabilities for intelligent quote-to-cash. Let me highlight three impressive key capabilities.</p>
  <h2 id="combining-products-services-projects-and-subscriptions-in-a-single-order">Combining Products, Services, Projects, and Subscriptions in a Single Order</h2>
  <p>As a first step, SAP S/4HANA Cloud makes it possible to quickly design and sell holistic offerings, integrated into the order-to-cash process. Take, for example, our customer AAF Lufttechnik GmbH, a company that manufactures air filter systems, which have been in increased demand over the last couple of months. With SAP S/4HANA Cloud and solution order management, AAF Lufttechnik GmbH plans to combine the sales of the air filter systems together with the corresponding installation and maintenance services as a one-stop-shop solution.</p>
  <h2 id="monetizing-services-with-pay-as-you-go-subscription-models">Monetizing Services With “Pay-As-You Go” Subscription Models</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="test-drive-sap-s4hana-today">Test drive SAP S/4HANA today</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/s4hana-erp.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>With SAP S/4HANA Cloud, customers can facilitate new business models by offering a variety of different pricing models. These include subscriptions for one-time, recurring, and pay-per-use offerings. SAP Subscription Billing enables the design of flexible price plans, rating, and charging of metered usage data from technical systems, such as sensors from the Internet of Things (IoT). Subscriptions are now part of the end-to-end quote-to-cash process, built into SAP S/4HANA Cloud. All subscriptions can be managed end-to-end.</p>
  <h2 id="rethinking-flexible-billing-measuring-solution-profitability-and-automating-revenue-recognition">Rethinking Flexible Billing, Measuring Solution Profitability, and Automating Revenue Recognition</h2>
  <p>With the help of SAP S/4HANA Cloud, billing data from different sources can be flexibly integrated — from one-time orders, long-running contracts, deliveries, and external data — into a single invoice, which is consistent with the order. Because companies also need to carefully guard the profitability of solutions, SAP S/4HANA Cloud provides margin analysis for orders, including all elements of the bundle. It also automates revenue recognition for sales products, service contracts, recurring subscriptions, and projects, and supports a simplified period-end closing.</p>
  <p>Today, solution and subscription models are top of mind for businesses across industries. Solution order management illustrates that significant added value comes from business process innovation. By integrating order-to-cash processes using the latest technology innovations, customers can unlock new opportunities for growth. That is why <a href="https://roadmaps.sap.com/board?BC=42F2E964F4E71EDA97D709D42DEA80E2&#x26;range=2021Q1-2022Q4#Q2%202021">we at SAP continue</a> to enable end-to-end processes and deliver business value to our customers.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Thomas Saueressig is a member of the Executive Board of SAP SE.</em><br><em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/pulse/transforming-how-products-services-offered-sold-thomas-saueressig/">This story was originally published on LinkedIn</a>.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/blog/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/blog/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/blog/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/blog/article-read-more</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/executive-blog</category>
            <category>news-tag/quote-to-cash</category>
            <category>news-tag/recurring-revenue-models</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/subscription-billing</category>
            <category>news-tag/xaas</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>