<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/sap-fioneer/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Join Us at the SAP and SAP Fioneer Financial Services Forum]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/06/join-us-sap-and-sap-fioneer-financial-services-forum</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/06/join-us-sap-and-sap-fioneer-financial-services-forum</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The SAP and SAP Fioneer Financial Services Forum brings together the best minds in the finance, banking, and insurance worlds. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/banking</category>
            <category>news-tag/financial-services</category>
            <category>industry/insurance</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fioneer</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Fioneer Starts Operations]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/sap-fioneer-starts-operations</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/sap-fioneer-starts-operations</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP announced the launch of SAP Fioneer, the joint venture Dediq GmbH for the financial services industry. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1435ed5c132e10b9b8ac3bfc64ce34d511afd956b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1435ed5c132e10b9b8ac3bfc64ce34d511afd956b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1435ed5c132e10b9b8ac3bfc64ce34d511afd956b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Fioneer Starts Operations" src="./media_1435ed5c132e10b9b8ac3bfc64ce34d511afd956b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-fioneer-starts-operations">SAP Fioneer Starts Operations</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-financial-services-software-from-sap">Learn more about financial services software from SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/financial-services.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced the global launch of SAP Fioneer, a joint venture for the financial services industry (FSI) between SAP and Dediq GmbH.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The launch follows the announcement to establish the company made in April of this year by SAP and Dediq, an entrepreneurial investor focused on information technology and digital businesses. SAP Fioneer expands the financial service software offered by SAP. It also develops new solutions to serve its customers in the rapidly changing banking and insurance industries.</p>
  <p>Today’s go-live of SAP Fioneer marks another important milestone in SAP’s long history of success in the FSI market. More than 800 of the world’s top 1,000 banks and insurance companies are SAP customers. SAP Fioneer focuses fully on accelerated innovation in the area of core banking, core insurance and FSI-specific finance solutions and is mandated to extend the SAP for Banking and SAP for Insurance solution portfolios to cover banking and insurance processes holistically.</p>
  <p>“As in any other industry, companies in financial services need to transform their business to stay ahead of the competition,” said Christian Klein, CEO and Member of the Executive Board, SAP SE. “SAP Fioneer will help them meet their needs for speed, scalability and cost-efficiency through digital business innovation, cloud technology and solutions that cover banking and insurance processes end to end. SAP has a long and successful track record in the financial services industry, and I am convinced that SAP Fioneer will become a leading global provider of financial services software solutions and platforms.”</p>
  <p>SAP Fioneer enables customers to innovate and transform their business by combining premier technology with development expertise and a global network of customers, partners and colleagues. SAP Fioneer will have operations in more than 10 countries in Europe, North and Latin America and the Asia-Pacific region by the end of 2021. SAP will continue to sell and support SAP solutions for enterprise information management and line-of-business solutions to FSI companies, and SAP customers will remain SAP customers.</p>
  <p>“Our customers can expect the same high-quality engagement they are used to, but now also benefit from new capabilities. Solutions of SAP Fioneer will be based on integrated data and allow customers to move FSI processes to SAP Business Technology Platform in the cloud,” said Dirk Kruse, CEO, SAP Fioneer. “We are excited to accelerate the business transformations of our customers with innovative solutions that will be built as part of SAP’s industry cloud solutions, all based on SAP technologies and applications.”</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="http://news.sap.com/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP on Twitter at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Media Contact:</strong> Daniel Reinhardt, +49-6227-7-40201, <a href="mailto:daniel.reinhardt@sap.com">daniel.reinhardt@sap.com</a>, CET<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>Any statements contained in this document that are not historical facts are forward-looking statements as defined in the U.S. Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995. Words such as “anticipate,” “believe,” “estimate,” “expect,” “forecast,” “intend,” “may,” “plan,” “project,” “predict,” “should” and “will” and similar expressions as they relate to SAP are intended to identify such forward-looking statements. SAP undertakes no obligation to publicly update or revise any forward-looking statements. All forward-looking statements are subject to various risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results to differ materially from expectations. The factors that could affect SAP’s future financial results are discussed more fully in SAP’s filings with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (“SEC”), including SAP’s most recent Annual Report on Form 20-F filed with the SEC. Readers are cautioned not to place undue reliance on these forward-looking statements, which speak only as of their dates.<br>© 2021 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>news-tag/financial-services</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fioneer</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Update on SAP Fioneer]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/update-on-sap-fioneer</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/update-on-sap-fioneer</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With an update on SAP Fioneer, SAP confirmed two external experts find the valuation is fair and the decision-making process compliant.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fioneer</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Financial Services Company Named “SAP Fioneer”]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/05/sap-fioneer-financial-services-company</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/05/sap-fioneer-financial-services-company</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP and Dediq have announced the name (SAP Fioneer) and leadership team of their joint venture for the financial services industries.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>news-tag/financial-services</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fioneer</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Forms Strategic Partnership for Financial Services Industries]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/sap-dediq-strategic-partnership-financial-services</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/sap-dediq-strategic-partnership-financial-services</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Dediq GmbH will jointly expand SAP’s financial services portfolio with a significant investment in new solutions. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_194e78d92ffd98985530dbcdfc49016d6dfbd6f72.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_194e78d92ffd98985530dbcdfc49016d6dfbd6f72.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_194e78d92ffd98985530dbcdfc49016d6dfbd6f72.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Forms Strategic Partnership for Financial Services Industries" src="./media_194e78d92ffd98985530dbcdfc49016d6dfbd6f72.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-forms-strategic-partnership-for-financial-services-industries">SAP Forms Strategic Partnership for Financial Services Industries</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF and MUNICH</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) and investment company Dediq GmbH today announced that they have agreed to enter into a partnership in the area of financial services.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>To better serve the rapidly changing banking and insurance industry, the two companies will jointly expand SAP’s <a href="/topics/financial-services">financial services</a> portfolio with a significant investment in new solutions. These solutions will be based on SAP software and be integrated into SAP’s overall portfolio and product roadmap.</p>
  <p>Pending regulatory approval, SAP and Dediq will form a dedicated Financial Services Industry (FSI) Unit, which will be jointly owned by the two companies. Both SAP and Dediq will provide the FSI Unit with the funding, technology, and development expertise, as well as a broad ecosystem of partners necessary to rapidly establish it as a major force in the FSI IT market. Dediq’s investment in the unit will be more than 500 million Euro.</p>
  <p>“Through partnering with Dediq, we will significantly increase our support for the digital transformation of customers in the Financial Services Industry and deliver innovative cloud solutions at an accelerated pace that help them transform their business holistically,” said Christian Klein, CEO, SAP SE. “Financial services is a key industry for SAP, and today we not only reiterate but also reinforce our commitment to this market.”</p>
  <p>SAP has a long history of success in the FSI market. More than 80% of the top 1,000 banks and insurers are SAP customers. The new FSI Unit will fully focus on accelerated innovation in the area of core banking, core insurance and FSI-specific finance solutions to meet the needs for digital innovation and cost efficiency of financial services customers.</p>
  <p>“The FSI market offers a huge opportunity for us,” said Luka Mucic, Member of the Executive Board, SAP SE. “To unleash this potential, we will use our unique capability to provide enterprise-grade solutions. Jointly, we will extend our existing FSI portfolio to cover banking and insurance processes end to end. Helping our customers to become more agile through digital business innovation and cloud technology will be front and center for our new FSI Unit. The new unit will be very flexible and customer-centric with full autonomy to set its strategic direction. At the same time, it will be a strong member of the SAP family. Customers will benefit from SAP’s leading technology and the FSI Unit’s agility and focus on their specific needs.”</p>
  <p>As part of its industry cloud portfolio strategy to thoroughly serve its 25 industries with tailored solutions, SAP has forged a number of partnerships. This latest one with Dediq marks a further milestone in the implementation of this strategy. SAP customers can expect the same high-quality engagement, with new capabilities now made possible by the new FSI Unit. The new solutions will cover the full cycle of banking and insurance operations processes, and help meet regulatory requirements. They will be based on integrated data and provide an opportunity to move FSI processes to the SAP Business Technology Platform in the cloud. For example, lending solutions for banks will cover all stages from origination and credit risk assessment to re-financing and bank management, with all related data kept in one place. This will significantly reduce IT cost and complexity.</p>
  <p>“We strongly believe in the strategy of the new FSI Unit,” said Matthias Tomann, Managing Partner, Dediq. “We see the future of FSI software solutions in the cloud. SAP’s platform has unrivalled potential when it comes to supporting the core operations of large-scale businesses like banks and insurers as well as new emerging ecosystems. Making this vision a reality in financial services is highly exciting to us.”</p>
  <p>SAP will continue to sell and support SAP solutions for enterprise information management and line-of-business solutions and SAP customers will remain SAP customers. The new FSI Unit will focus its investment on core FSI areas such as commercial lending, retail banking, core insurance as well as insurance finance and bank management. The new solutions will be built as part of SAP’s industry cloud solutions, based on SAP technologies and applications such as SAP HANA, SAP S/4HANA, SAP Business Technology Platform and others.</p>
  <p>“Today’s financial services industry is challenged to balance agility and innovation with risk, resiliency and scale. With this announcement, SAP is responding to the needs of its clients to improve speed of innovation while continuing to provide enterprise-class and mission-critical products and services to the industry,” said Jerry Silva, vice president of IDC Financial Insights.</p>
  <p>Pending antitrust approval, the new FSI Unit is expected to be in place in the second half of 2021. Corresponding preparations are scheduled to start in the coming weeks.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-what-customers-and-partners-have-to-say-about-this-news">Read what customers and partners have to say about this news</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="read-statements-from-partners-and-customers-here"><a href="/">Read statements from partners and customers here</a>.</h3>
  <p>Visit the <a href="/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP on Twitter at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <h3 id="about-dediq">About Dediq</h3>
  <p>Dediq is an entrepreneurial investor focused on information technology and digital businesses. Dediq is working together with its portfolio companies to create exceptional products and services. Each Dediq investment is set up separately, independently and with an unlimited time horizon. Dediq is based in Munich. For more information, visit <a href="http://www.dediq.com">www.dediq.com</a>.</p>
  <h3 id="about-sap">About SAP</h3>
  <p>SAP’s strategy is to help every business run as an intelligent enterprise. As a market leader in enterprise application software, we help companies of all sizes and in all industries run at their best: 77% of the world’s transaction revenue touches an SAP system. Our machine learning, Internet of Things (IoT), and advanced analytics technologies help turn customers’ businesses into intelligent enterprises. SAP helps give people and organizations deep business insight and fosters collaboration that helps them stay ahead of their competition. We simplify technology for companies so they can consume our software the way they want – without disruption. Our end-to-end suite of applications and services enables business and public customers across 25 industries globally to operate profitably, adapt continuously, and make a difference. With a global network of customers, partners, employees, and thought leaders, SAP helps the world run better and improve people’s lives. For more information, visit <a href="http://www.sap.com">www.sap.com</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Note to editors:</strong><br>To preview and download broadcast-standard stock footage and press photos digitally, please visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/photos">www.sap.com/photos</a>. On this platform, you can find high resolution material for your media channels. To view video stories on diverse topics, visit <a href="http://www.sap-tv.com">www.sap-tv.com</a>. From this site, you can embed videos into your own Web pages, share video via email links, and subscribe to RSS feeds from SAP TV.</p>
  <p><strong>For customers interested in learning more about SAP products:</strong><br>Global Customer Center: +49 180 534-34-24<br>United States only: 1 (800) 872-1SAP (1-800-872-1727)</p>
  <p><strong>For more information, press only:</strong><br>Joellen Perry, SAP, +1 (650) 445-6780, <a href="mailto:joellen.perry@sap.com">joellen.perry@sap.com</a>, PT<br>Daniel Reinhardt, SAP, +49-6227-7-40201, <a href="mailto:daniel.reinhardt@sap.com">daniel.reinhardt@sap.com</a>, CET<a href="http://www.news-sap.com/press-room/">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>Any statements contained in this document that are not historical facts are forward-looking statements as defined in the U.S. Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995. Words such as “anticipate,” “believe,” “estimate,” “expect,” “forecast,” “intend,” “may,” “plan,” “project,” “predict,” “should” and “will” and similar expressions as they relate to SAP are intended to identify such forward-looking statements. SAP undertakes no obligation to publicly update or revise any forward-looking statements. All forward-looking statements are subject to various risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results to differ materially from expectations. The factors that could affect SAP’s future financial results are discussed more fully in SAP’s filings with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (“SEC”), including SAP’s most recent Annual Report on Form 20-F filed with the SEC. Readers are cautioned not to place undue reliance on these forward-looking statements, which speak only as of their dates.<br>© 2021 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.<br>Please consider our <a href="https://www.sap.com/corporate/en/legal/privacy.html">privacy policy</a>. If you received this press release in your e-mail and you wish to unsubscribe to our mailing list please contact <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a> and write Unsubscribe in the subject line.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/financial-services</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fioneer</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>