<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/qualtrics/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Agrees to Sell Its Stake in Qualtrics as Part of Qualtrics Acquisition by Silver Lake and CPP Investments]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/sap-agrees-to-sell-its-stake-in-qualtrics</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/sap-agrees-to-sell-its-stake-in-qualtrics</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP SE (NYSE: SAP), today announced it has agreed to sell all of its 423 million shares of Qualtrics International Inc. as part of the ...]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/investor-relations</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/experience-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/qualtrics</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Great Resignation Points to a Serious Sustainability Issue]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/great-resignation-serious-sustainability-issue</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/great-resignation-serious-sustainability-issue</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The Great Resignation is a sustainability warning to companies that have not focused on culture and leadership for a while. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/people-sustainability</category>
            <category>news-tag/qualtrics</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-workforce-analytics</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Measuring the Carbon Footprint of Employees Can Help You Make More Informed and Strategic Business Decisions]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/measuring-employee-carbon-footprint-business-decisions</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/measuring-employee-carbon-footprint-business-decisions</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Executives can make informed decisions when considering the social and actual carbon footprint of employees in planning. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/experience-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/people-sustainability</category>
            <category>news-tag/qualtrics</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-product-footprint-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-employee-central</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-people-analytics</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-workforce-analytics</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Grupo Perez Companc Uses SAP SuccessFactors and Qualtrics to Empower Leaders and Transform Culture]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/grupo-perez-companc-sap-successfactors-qualtrics</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/grupo-perez-companc-sap-successfactors-qualtrics</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Grupo Perez Companc is transforming the way it works for the better with Employee Experience Management solutions from SAP and Qualtrics.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/qualtrics</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Qualtrics and SAP SuccessFactors Recruiting: Automating In-Moment Listening Across the Entire Candidate Journey]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/09/qualtrics-and-sap-successfactors-recruiting-listening-candidate-journey</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/09/qualtrics-and-sap-successfactors-recruiting-listening-candidate-journey</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Qualtrics and SAP SuccessFactors, through deepened integration, are improving the candidate experience with in-moment listening.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/qualtrics</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-recruiting</category>
            <category>sap-event/successconnect</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Job Seekers Rush to Find New Opportunities with Better Pay and Work-Life Balance]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/09/job-seekers-new-opportunities-better-pay-work-life-balance</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/09/job-seekers-new-opportunities-better-pay-work-life-balance</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Research from Qualtrics and SAP shows job seekers are rushing to look for new jobs amid inflation and recession concerns. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/future-of-work</category>
            <category>news-tag/qualtrics</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Psychologists Say Your Flex Work Desires Are Perfectly Normal. But Does Your Boss Agree?]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/psychologists-say-flex-work-perfectly-normal-does-boss-agree</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/psychologists-say-flex-work-perfectly-normal-does-boss-agree</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Psychologists agree the optimal work model for the average global employee is hybrid. But it's not necessarily the best model for every one.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/accenture</category>
            <category>news-tag/covid-19</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/future-of-work</category>
            <category>news-tag/qualtrics</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[CPG Trends: Great Places to Work Attract Great Customers Too]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/06/cpg-trends-great-places-to-work-attract-great-customers-too</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/06/cpg-trends-great-places-to-work-attract-great-customers-too</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Regardless of where employees work at CPG companies, digital technology is central to creating a personalized employee experience. Learn why.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/consumer-goods-cpg</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/qualtrics</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-work-zone</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The New, Intelligent SAP Service Cloud Powers the Future of Customer Service]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/new-intelligent-sap-service-cloud</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/new-intelligent-sap-service-cloud</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The new intelligent SAP Service Cloud re-imagines how service is executed and revolutionizes customer service. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/qualtrics</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-service-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Ideal Work Environment: What Is It and How to Deliver It]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/02/ideal-work-environment-what-is-it-how-to-deliver-it</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/02/ideal-work-environment-what-is-it-how-to-deliver-it</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Workers today expect more flexibility in their work environment. How can businesses provide the right tools, experiences, and capabilities?]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e5a7f7b4548009f6307ffbd3d0fa8ada45c8d093.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e5a7f7b4548009f6307ffbd3d0fa8ada45c8d093.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1e5a7f7b4548009f6307ffbd3d0fa8ada45c8d093.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="The Ideal Work Environment: What Is It and How to Deliver It" src="./media_1e5a7f7b4548009f6307ffbd3d0fa8ada45c8d093.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="the-ideal-work-environment-what-is-it-and-how-to-deliver-it">The Ideal Work Environment: What Is It and How to Deliver It</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>The hiring market continues to heat up, anxious employees are making retention more challenging, and workers expect more flexibility in their work environments. How can businesses provide the right tools, experiences, and capabilities necessary to create a workplace in which employees can thrive?</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In today’s changing world of work, employees expect better experiences – especially when it comes to their learning, development, and growth. However, employees struggle with multiple outdated or inadequate systems and tools that create a fragmented digital experience at work.</p>
  <p>The pressure is undoubtedly on executives, organizational leaders, and their HR teams to fill those gaps to create a workplace culture that is motivating, empowering, and fulfilling. They are expected to provide personalized work experiences that include access to individualized learning and growth, guided and simplified technology interfaces, continuous process improvements, embedded listening, and increased productivity and efficiency.</p>
  <p>Organizations that deliver on these promises exceptionally well are usually more effective in attracting, retaining, and developing the best talent. However, this is easier said than done because no single definition of an ideal workplace meets everyone’s expectations. To create a truly empowering, engaging, and enriching environment, decision-makers must consider the unique locations, job roles, personal responsibilities, and situations that each employee faces daily.</p>
  <p>At SAP SuccessFactors, we understand the importance of fostering an environment where people are thriving, collaborating, and ready to succeed today and tomorrow – no matter where they work. And in virtually every case, that experience begins with technologies that cater to each employee’s whole self even as they evolve, making everyone consistently feel valued, heard, and recognized.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="provide-an-employee-centric-hr-user-experience-with-sap-successfactors-work-zone">Provide an employee-centric HR user experience with SAP SuccessFactors Work Zone</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/workzone-hr.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="personalized-integrated-experience">Personalized, Integrated Experience</h2>
  <p>A good starting point is giving employees the freedom to reimagine their work experience with hyper-personalized, team-centric, and project-focused workspaces created through the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/workzone-hr.html">SAP SuccessFactors Work Zone solution</a>. This integrated digital experience connects the entire SAP software landscape and third-party applications to help streamline work and intelligently surface relevant content, recommendations, insights, and actions.</p>
  <p>By providing employees with a more simplified and unified digital experience tailored to their unique needs, SAP SuccessFactors Work Zone can enable companies to increase employee productivity and efficiency.</p>
  <p>For example, <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/11/90572075-047e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">AKT Solutions Limited</a> (AKT Global) resolved the presence of inefficient communication and collaboration across borders and time zones to improve productivity and lower employee stress. As a result, its employees work smarter and faster now that they have 24/7 access to everything they need to keep up with changes – no matter where they work, what device they use, or where they are based.</p>
  <h2 id="culture-of-continuous-and-agile-learning">Culture of Continuous and Agile Learning</h2>
  <p>Employees need on-demand access to individualized and engaging learning programs as part of their everyday experience. With learning established as a priority in the workspace, they are empowered to develop skills at their convenience and participate in opportunities to further develop their expertise and leadership abilities.</p>
  <p><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/corporate-lms.html">SAP SuccessFactors Learning</a> helps to foster a continuous and agile culture with learning that is personalized and relevant for each employee while being embedded into daily activities. Through learning workspaces employees can get access to relevant learning applications, information, collaboration tools, and content from any source – all through a single entry point and embedded into the flow of work – to be able to benefit from a more simplified and contextual way of learning. Organizations can then help ensure their people feel empowered to own their career path and growth while helping them become more engaged and develop the skills that align with current and future business needs.</p>
  <p><a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/10/90d46430-007e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Rich Products Corporation</a> (Rich’s) is taking advantage of the solution to support a culture of continuous learning. The family-owned food company sought to elevate its training and development program with a modern, consumer-grade learning experience for its associates. By mapping and enabling access to learning content with individualized recommendations, Rich’s offers its associates a customized view of their development plans and objectives and connects them to integrated external content libraries and resources on demand.</p>
  <h2 id="employees-retained-with-opportunities-they-want">Employees Retained with Opportunities They Want</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="turn-employees-into-ambassadors-with-employee-experience-management">Turn employees into ambassadors with employee experience management</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm/employee-experience-management.html?sort=title_asc&#x26;tab=all">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>According to joint research from <a href="https://www2.deloitte.com/us/en/insights/focus/technology-and-the-future-of-work/importance-of-investing-in-employees.html">Deloitte Consulting and the MIT Sloan Management Review</a>, making job opportunities visible and accessible in the workforce helps improve retention by aligning employee interests with strategic priorities. But first, most companies require a conscious shift that embraces each employee’s whole self – who they are today, who they are becoming, and the value they bring as individuals.</p>
  <p>By adding the <a href="/2021/10/sap-successfactors-opportunity-marketplace-drives-internal-mobility-and-upskilling-to-help-organizations-future-proof-their-business">SAP SuccessFactors Opportunity Marketplace</a> solution to their workspace, employees can find short-term assignments, fellowships, learning recommendations, and mentors. The solution can empower everyone across the organization to pursue multiple opportunities for professional development, networking, and project participation.</p>
  <h2 id="meaningful-work-shaped-by-real-time-feedback">Meaningful Work Shaped by Real-Time Feedback</h2>
  <p>Measuring work experiences helps businesses remain agile and strive to give employees what they need to feel supported, productive, and engaged. With <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm/employee-experience-management.html?sort=title_asc&#x26;tab=all">Experience Management solutions from SAP and Qualtrics</a>, organizations can evaluate how employees are doing, listen to their feedback, and respond to their concerns quickly and effectively.</p>
  <p>To enable a people-centric business transformation, luxury retailer <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2019/12/de86ec87-767d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff.html">Chalhoub Group</a> combines employee experience data with operational HR data. This approach allows the business to gain new insights, identify areas for improvement, and foster a culture where all employees are engaged and fully equipped to provide exceptional customer service. Chalhoub uses Experience Management solutions from SAP and Qualtrics to actively listen to its workforce and provide the right training, processes, and tools. The company is capturing feedback at every interaction touchpoint and discovering new ways to meet unique employee needs and continuously improve everyday work experiences.</p>
  <p>As a result, the company is redesigning and optimizing key aspects of the employee journey. For example, its HR transformation priorities are supported by hard data on the issues that employees really care about, driving greater emphasis on employee well-being and recognition as top strategic goals.</p>
  <h2 id="all-wrapped-with-a-human-experience">All Wrapped with a Human Experience</h2>
  <p>HR organizations are constantly challenging their business executives and organizational managers. They know that seemingly adequate access to technology is no guarantee that an employee’s specific needs are met. Meanwhile, it is understood that remote and <a href="/2021/08/essential-but-under-supported-improving-deskless-worker-experience">deskless workers</a> face even more complexity in their experiences, such as limited bandwidth and privacy controls, as they juggle work with their personal circumstances.</p>
  <p>With SAP SuccessFactors Work Zone, SAP SuccessFactors Learning, SAP SuccessFactors Opportunity Marketplace, and Experience Management solutions from SAP and Qualtrics, organizations can deliver engaging, individualized experiences that enable everyone to thrive.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Stephanie Craig is global director of Solution Marketing for SAP SuccessFactors.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/future-of-work</category>
            <category>news-tag/qualtrics</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-learning</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-opportunity-marketplace</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-work-zone</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Augmented Reality Boosts Online Shopping Sales up to 200%]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/01/augmented-reality-boosts-online-shopping-sales-up-to-200</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/01/augmented-reality-boosts-online-shopping-sales-up-to-200</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Indian startup Adloid uses augmented reality (AR) to deliver immersive, personalized online shopping experiences. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_109aa8b1916fb632815d9652558727d406a69acb7.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_109aa8b1916fb632815d9652558727d406a69acb7.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_109aa8b1916fb632815d9652558727d406a69acb7.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Augmented Reality Boosts Online Shopping Sales up to 200%" src="./media_109aa8b1916fb632815d9652558727d406a69acb7.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="augmented-reality-boosts-online-shopping-sales-up-to-200">Augmented Reality Boosts Online Shopping Sales up to 200%</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>For shoppers who’ve yearned for an immersive, personalized experience that’s open 24/7, mobile <a href="/topics/augmented-reality">augmented reality (AR)</a> technology is the real-time deal of the next era. Bangalore-based startup <a href="https://www.adloid.io/index.php">Adloid</a> is leading the charge with a platform that turns two-dimensional search and discovery into a full-fledged 3D experience, whether someone is in the market for automobiles or bikes, household furniture, consumer electronics, or personal lifestyle products.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“Our AR platform gives consumers and companies personalized virtual shopping and training experiences, expanding the horizon of what AR can do for any brand or company,” said Kanav Singla, founder and CEO of Adloid. “We’re making the benefits of this technology more accessible and contextual to create an immersive experience for customers or employees on an e-commerce Website or within applications, directly from someone’s mobile device.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="can-artificial-intelligence-take-the-guesswork-out-of-the-customer-journey">Can Artificial Intelligence Take the Guesswork Out of the Customer Journey?</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/12/can-artificial-intelligence-take-the-guesswork-out-of-the-customer-journey">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="convenient-try-before-you-buy-shopping">Convenient ‘Try Before You Buy’ Shopping</h2>
  <p>Unlike earlier AR tech that relied on clunky headsets with varied compatibility, Adloid’s AR platform runs on any smartphone, allowing customers to experience products at scale, in context. Once the online shopper logs in through their phone, the device’s camera scans their real-world surroundings and virtually mirrors the retailer’s or manufacturer’s product.</p>
  <p>“People can see how a new sofa or chair would fit into their home or apartment with a click of their smartphone,” said Singla. “Consumers can virtually try on jewelry, makeup, and other products. Remote workers can see if that laptop, screen, and desk configuration will fit in their home office. It’s as if the actual products are in front of you.”</p>
  <p>He added that manufacturers were interested in using the AR platform within training modules for industrial machinery service technicians, providing them with hands-on learning in a virtual setting.</p>
  <h2 id="immersive-product-discovery-experience">Immersive Product Discovery Experience</h2>
  <p>On the consumer side, AR technology is tailor-made for online shoppers who can’t get enough information about products they might purchase.</p>
  <p>“For someone trying to decide between different car models, AR lets them virtually go inside the trunk to see how much space is in there,” said Singla. “They can open and close the sunroof or try out the controls on the entertainment console, experiencing various car options before going to the showroom.”</p>
  <p>Automotive manufacturers are among the startup’s biggest customers, along with e-commerce platforms of all sizes, retailers with or without brick-and-mortar stores, and manufacturers located in the U.S., Germany, and India.</p>
  <h2 id="augmented-reality-increases-sales">Augmented Reality Increases Sales</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-sap-labs-india">Learn more about SAP Labs India</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/india/about/labs-india.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Some customers using Adloid have increased sales conversions from online channels up to 200%. One online retailer tripled the number of online customers who purchased consumer items after using the tool. AR also boosts customer engagement time viewing product images and videos from an average of 30 seconds to a whopping eight minutes.</p>
  <p>“Instead of being limited by a finite number of pre-posted images or videos, AR allows people to interact longer with products in a more personalized way, creating a powerful sales channel that’s always on at the customer’s convenience,” said Singla. “People can better understand how a product would fit into their lives, in many cases motivating them to make a purchase decision during that single online session.”</p>
  <h2 id="connected-data-for-intelligent-enterprise">Connected Data for Intelligent Enterprise</h2>
  <p>Adloid securely anonymizes all customer data and doesn’t store any personal images or other information once someone ends their AR session. However, organizations can extract valuable insights from the tool’s analytics.</p>
  <p>“A car might come in six colors, but which ones are customers viewing the most? Companies can see what options people are most interested in, then connect back to inventory management to make sure they can meet market demands,” said Singla.</p>
  <p>Indeed, one of Adloid’s biggest strengths is working with the SAP Startup Studio for India, <a href="https://www.sap.com/india/about/labs-india.html">SAP Labs India’s</a> startup accelerator program. Singla said that his team gained validation for product iterations, along with access to SAP solutions, including <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">SAP Business Technology Platform</a>, and the company’s enterprise customers.</p>
  <p>“Working with a global leader like SAP gives our product immediate credibility because we learned what customers were looking for,” he said. “Adloid is integrated with <a href="https://www.qualtrics.com/">Qualtrics</a>, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/crm/e-commerce-platforms.html">SAP Commerce Cloud</a>, and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/s4hana-erp/pricing.html">SAP S/4HANA</a>, helping companies connect data to become intelligent enterprises.</p>
  <h2 id="ar-bridges-gap-between-e-commerce-and-cx">AR Bridges Gap Between E-Commerce and CX</h2>
  <p>Singla’s entrepreneurial spirit was initially sparked by his family, all of whom own businesses. He founded his first startup at age 21 during his undergraduate studies in engineering, then saw a major selling gap as e-commerce took off.</p>
  <p>“Companies went online with their catalogs, but customers couldn’t more fully experience these products,” he said. “I launched Adloid to turn e-commerce into 3D commerce where customers can try out products virtually on their mobile device. We expect AR will provide immersive experiences in more consumer and B2B online sites including fashion, travel and tourism, and large industrial machinery.”</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Follow me @smgaler.</em><br><em><a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2021/09/28/augmented-reality-boosts-online-shopping-sales-up-to-200/?sh=249fcb717b26">This blog also appeared on SAP BrandVoice on Forbes.</a></em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/ar</category>
            <category>news-tag/e-commerce</category>
            <category>news-tag/qualtrics</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-commerce-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-labs-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/startups</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Kaspersky Empowers Its People by Fostering a Listening Culture]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/kaspersky-empowers-its-people-by-fostering-listening-culture</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/kaspersky-empowers-its-people-by-fostering-listening-culture</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Understanding its employees is critical to everything Kaspersky does. The SAP Qualtrics Employee Experience solution helps do just that.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18117bf5d567c0ed4efe2af0e5c56aa850f825c0e.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18117bf5d567c0ed4efe2af0e5c56aa850f825c0e.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_18117bf5d567c0ed4efe2af0e5c56aa850f825c0e.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Kaspersky Empowers Its People by Fostering a Listening Culture" src="./media_18117bf5d567c0ed4efe2af0e5c56aa850f825c0e.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="kaspersky-empowers-its-people-by-fostering-a-listening-culture">Kaspersky Empowers Its People by Fostering a Listening Culture</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="kaspersky-building-a-better-workplace-centered-on-the-employee-experience">Kaspersky: Building a Better Workplace Centered on the Employee Experience</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2021/12/728bfa83-0a7e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Kaspersky is one of the world’s leading cybersecurity companies, and its innovative technologies protect businesses, industrial and critical infrastructure, and governments, as well as individual users across the globe. The company serves a single goal: to defend the digital world and make it safer for everyone.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The driving force of Kaspersky is its employees – the world-class professionals who research cyber-threats and create leading security technologies. The company relies on the knowledge and expertise of its employees, and therefore strives to provide an exceptional workplace experience for its people to attract and retain the best talent.</p>
  <p>“We have long known that, to make Kaspersky a great place to work, we need to listen to the wants, needs, and desires of our employees,” says Marina Alekseeva, the company’s chief human resources officer. “Previously, we didn’t have a unified resource to conduct employee surveys, and we wanted to launch a platform that we could integrate with our core HR system to listen to employees’ feedback more regularly, to understand how they feel and learn about their concerns.”</p>
  <p>To support the shift to a continuous listening strategy, Kaspersky selected <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/employee-engagement.html">SAP Qualtrics Employee Engagement</a> to help gather employee experience data at regular touchpoints and gain insights based on employee feedback.</p>
  <p>Kaspersky deployed the SAP Qualtrics Employee Engagement solution in just four weeks, building dynamic surveys and response surveys all while working remotely due to the <a href="/covid-19">COVID-19</a> pandemic. Integration between the SAP Qualtrics Employee Engagement solution and SAP SuccessFactors Human Experience Management (HXM) Suite enables the company to combine employee experience data with operational HR data to get a better understanding of its workforce.</p>
  <p>Kaspersky conducted 10 global surveys and more than 30 local pulse surveys in 2020, providing new insights into the employee experience and helping the company to identify areas for improvement.</p>
  <p>The results were very encouraging: 80% of Kaspersky’s 4,000 employees participated in the 2020 global engagement survey (a 14% increase on the previous year), and shorter pulse survey participation rates were also high. Moreover, 50% of employees took the time to enrich their responses with free-text comments, providing deeper insights into their thoughts and feelings.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="gain-real-time-insights-with-employee-engagement-surveys-and-feedback">Gain real-time insights with employee engagement surveys and feedback</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/employee-engagement.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Business leaders also benefit from instant access to survey analytics. For example, in the past, they could wait up to two months to see the outcome of a global engagement survey; today, they can track results and participation rates in real time via interactive dashboards.</p>
  <p>But what’s the point of conducting employee surveys and gathering data if you don’t act on it? With unique insight into the employee experience, Kaspersky can take targeted action to support its people, fast. For example, just two days after receiving feedback on remote working conditions, Kaspersky made a new company policy to deliver a desk chair to any employee who needs one, so that they could work more comfortably – and therefore productively – from home. Although it may seem trivial, having a comfy chair can make a huge difference to your employees’ health, well-being, and happiness. Kaspersky wants to ensure that its people have everything they need to work at their best.</p>
  <p>Regular pulse surveys also gave managers a convenient way to check in with their team while they were working remotely during the COVID-19 lockdowns, helping them to monitor employee well-being and workload, and to provide support to prevent burnout and maintain pre-pandemic performance levels.</p>
  <p>“Understanding our employees is critical to everything we do,” says Alekseeva. “With the SAP Qualtrics Employee Engagement solution, we get regular feedback that helps us to build a more attractive and engaging workplace.”</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Edith Krieg is part of SAP Reference Management and Content.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/covid-19</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/qualtrics</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
            <category>news-tag/well-being-at-work</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Purolator Prepared Its Workforce for Digital Business]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/how-purolator-prepared-its-workforce-for-digital-business</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/how-purolator-prepared-its-workforce-for-digital-business</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Purolator launched its Evolve program to help managers lead workers through digital transformation and foster a more engaged workforce.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15874a104a32d56ceed14fff0cc7b651777658c4b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15874a104a32d56ceed14fff0cc7b651777658c4b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_15874a104a32d56ceed14fff0cc7b651777658c4b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="How Purolator Prepared Its Workforce for Digital Business" src="./media_15874a104a32d56ceed14fff0cc7b651777658c4b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="how-purolator-prepared-its-workforce-for-digital-business">How Purolator Prepared Its Workforce for Digital Business</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>For employees at leading Canadian courier company Purolator Inc., the last few years have seen unprecedented change. The <a href="/covid-19">COVID-19</a> pandemic resulted in a surge in demand for e-commerce delivery services, resulting in a shift away from a primarily business-to-business model and exponential growth for the company. Meanwhile, innovative technologies such as robotic process automation (RPA) and Internet of Things (IoT)-based tools are fundamentally changing ways of working.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>To continue to adapt to a new business environment and compete and succeed in the market, Purolator knew it needed to focus on supporting and enabling its frontline personnel. Managers play a crucial role helping workers get accustomed to new technologies and deliver services that meet the high expectations of today’s consumers. However, mostly recruited for their operational, technical, and project management skills, many managers didn’t have the skills required to become transformational leaders and agents of change.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="explore-purolators-story-in-depth">Explore Purolator's story in depth</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/11/42ebb110-057e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="filling-skills-gaps-to-transform-managers-into-leaders">Filling Skills Gaps to Transform Managers into Leaders</h2>
  <p>To help managers lead workers successfully through a digital transformation and foster a more engaged workforce, the courier firm launched its “Evolve” program in 2018. This leadership development initiative involves multifunctional groups of over 20 managers who receive 10 days of on-site training over a five-month period. In between sessions, participants are able to apply learned skills and competencies in the workplace while skills are reinforced by online microlearning modules and coaching using the SAP SuccessFactors Learning solution.</p>
  <p>Getting feedback from course participants to enable continuous improvement for the learning experience has been a key part of Purolator’s strategy. To achieve this, the company uses <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm/employee-experience-management.html">Experience Management solutions from SAP and Qualtrics</a> to capture feedback before, during, and after the course. In this way, Purolator is able to learn about participant expectations and discover what is going right and how the training experience can be improved.</p>
  <h2 id="supporting-employees-as-they-adapt-to-a-digital-world">Supporting Employees as They Adapt to a Digital World</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="put-employees-at-the-heart-of-everything-you-do-with-sap-successfactors">Put employees at the heart of everything you do with SAP SuccessFactors</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm/hxm-suite.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>So far, more than 200 participants – most of them in frontline manager roles – have become leaders thanks to the Evolve program. These managers are supporting and guiding their teams through the company’s digital transformation and helping them learn how to use new technologies. This has enabled the company to change the way it does business without having to look outside its existing workforce for the necessary digital skills.</p>
  <p>Continuous improvement projects initiated during the program have also yielded significant benefits for the company. In response to issues identified by the participants themselves, the projects involved the design and implementation of a solution using change management concepts learned during the course.</p>
  <p>“Overall, the program has generated over CAD 21 million in saved revenue,” comments Tennyson Devoe, senior director of Safety and Organizational Excellence at Purolator. “Furthermore, we’ve seen a significant reduction in our injury frequency rate and improved union relations.”</p>
  <p>Another important benefit is increased cross-functional collaboration with the program nurturing strong relationships between managers from different areas of the business.</p>
  <p>“Even a few years after completing the program, participants still keep in touch using SAP SuccessFactors Human Experience Management Suite,” confirms Devoe. “This means they can share ideas and reach out for support when they need it.”</p>
  <p>The Evolve program has won numerous national and international awards, including four gold awards at the 2020 Brandon Hall Group Excellence in Leadership Development Awards.</p>
  <h2 id="navigating-uncertain-times-through-strong-leadership">Navigating Uncertain Times through Strong Leadership</h2>
  <p>With the COVID-19 pandemic prompting a significant increase in business volume and the hiring of thousands of new drivers, the ability of Purolator’s employees to adapt to rapid change has been tested over the last two years. Despite these challenges, the lessons learned by the alumni of the Evolve program have helped the company navigate through uncertain times.</p>
  <p>“We now have a frontline workforce that has successfully adapted to running digitalized processes,” concludes Devoe. “What’s more, thanks to the strong leadership of our managers, our employees now have the confidence to view change as an opportunity to learn and grow.”</p>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div><a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/11/42ebb110-057e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Learn more about Purolator’s HR transformation.</a></div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>Kristin Muellner is director of Customer Stories &#x26; Reference Engagement at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/qualtrics</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-learning</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP and Qualtrics Launch Concur Experience Optimizer]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/sap-qualtrics-launch-concur-experience-optimizer</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/sap-qualtrics-launch-concur-experience-optimizer</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Concur Experience Optimizer allows companies to confidently adapt travel and expense programs for the future of work.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_19df49332a53eac873d442dae13bca69f3900e27f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_19df49332a53eac873d442dae13bca69f3900e27f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_19df49332a53eac873d442dae13bca69f3900e27f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP and Qualtrics Launch Concur Experience Optimizer" src="./media_19df49332a53eac873d442dae13bca69f3900e27f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-and-qualtrics-launch-concur-experience-optimizer">SAP and Qualtrics Launch Concur Experience Optimizer</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="ensure-that-your-travel-and-expense-programs-align-with-employee-needs">Ensure that your travel and expense programs align with employee needs</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.concur.com/experience-optimizer">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong><em>BELLEVUE and PROVO —</em></strong> <a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) and <a href="http://www.qualtrics.com">Qualtrics</a> (Nasdaq: XM) today announced the availability of Concur Experience Optimizer, a new solution that allows companies to improve employee experiences and confidently adapt travel and expense programs for the future of work.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <ul>
    <li><em>Industry-First Solution Helps Companies Redesign Travel and Expense Programs Using Employee Sentiment Data</em></li>
  </ul>
  <p>Concur Experience Optimizer combines the listening and analysis capabilities of Qualtrics EmployeeXM, the leading product for employee experience management, with operational intelligence data from Concur Travel and Concur Expense solutions to help companies design travel programs for the hybrid workplace, improve spend management processes and increase employee retention.</p>
  <p>Many employees are ready to return to pre-pandemic levels of business travel, with seven in ten (70%) expecting to go back to traveling as much as they did before the pandemic, according to <a href="https://www.qualtrics.com/blog/business-travel-study/">recent research</a> from Qualtrics, the leader and creator of the Experience Management (XM) category, and the SAP Concur organization. A small majority (54%) of business travelers say traveling for business is still very important or critical to their role and four in five (84%) say they are willing to travel within the next year.</p>
  <p>Yet the experience of traveling for business is unlikely to go back to exactly the way it was pre-pandemic due to marked changes in employee expectations. Global business travelers expect new benefits — like the ability to choose direct flights or select premium seating — from their employers to help ensure their health and safety, <a href="https://www.concur.com/newsroom/article/survey-uncovers-travelers-requirements-return-to-business-travel">research</a> said. Alongside business travel, employee spending behavior is also evolving with more non-travel purchases initiated directly by employees, requiring new expense categories to support remote, hybrid and in-person work.</p>
  <p>“People are a company’s greatest asset, and it’s no secret that retaining employees has become even more critical,” said Mike Koetting, SAP Concur solution area lead at SAP. “A company’s travel and expense programs can directly impact an employee’s experience. Concur Experience Optimizer helps organizations understand the reasons behind employee behavior so they can make adjustments that are in line with both employee sentiment and business objectives.”</p>
  <p>“Our research shows that demand for business travel is returning to pre-pandemic levels, but getting the employee experience right is more nuanced and complicated than ever before,” said Jay Choi, Qualtrics chief product officer. “It’s critical for organizations to understand how employees feel about the new world of travel and use that experience data to meet their evolving health and safety needs.”</p>
  <p>Concur Experience Optimizer uses technology from Qualtrics and SAP Concur solutions, plus expert services from SAP Concur Experience Management consultants to help companies listen, analyze and act on employee feedback to create continuous feedback loops and understand the impact of adjustments made over time. Companies can easily capture employee sentiment with science-backed feedback templates and view the results through simple, intuitive dashboards that show the impact of sentiment against operational data metrics. Those insights can be turned into focused action plans to improve employees’ travel and expense experiences, compliance, and budget predictability.</p>
  <p>With Concur Experience Optimizer, companies can level up their entire program — from buying behavior to supplier options to workflow — to:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Improve employee experiences.</strong> Better understand how policies are affecting employee sentiment, safety, well-being, productivity and attrition risk.</li>
    <li><strong>Effectively manage spend.</strong> Gain insight into the critical influences that impact employee buying decisions and organizational spending patterns, supporting early detection of potential saving opportunities and closing policy and process gaps.</li>
    <li><strong>Reduce risk and non-compliant spend.</strong> Identify risks in programs and adjust processes that allow for noncompliant and potentially fraudulent spending.</li>
    <li><strong>Optimize programs for growth.</strong> Make confident travel, expense, compliance and spend management program adjustments to lead healthy business growth with enhanced visibility into critical business problems.</li>
    <li>​​ <strong>Drive sustainability.</strong> Make enhancements that align with organizational sustainability objectives, enhance the organization’s brand and reduce the carbon footprint.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>“Concur Experience Optimizer brings together the horsepower of SAP Concur and Qualtrics to allow finance leaders and travel managers to be active drivers of improved employee experiences,” said Kevin Permenter, Research Director at IDC. “This solution has potential to help companies get ahead of spend problems by shaping spend with employee sentiment as a guide.”</p>
  <p>To learn more visit <a href="https://www.concur.com/experience-optimizer">Concur.com/experience-optimizer</a>.</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP on Twitter at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>About Qualtrics</strong><a href="https://www.qualtrics.com/">Qualtrics</a>, the leader and creator of the Experience Management (XM) category, is changing the way organizations manage and improve the four core experiences of business—customer, employee, product and brand. Over 13,500 organizations around the world use Qualtrics to listen, understand and take action on experience data (X-data)—the beliefs, emotions and intentions that tell you why things are happening, and what to do about it. The Qualtrics XM Platform is a system of action that helps businesses attract customers who stay longer and buy more, engage employees who build a positive culture, develop breakthrough products people love and build a brand people are passionate about. To learn more, please visit <a href="https://www.qualtrics.com/">qualtrics.com</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>About SAP Concur</strong> SAP Concur is the world’s leading brand for integrated travel, expense and invoice management solutions, driven by a relentless pursuit to simplify and automate these everyday processes. The highly rated SAP Concur mobile app guides employees through business trips, charges are directly populated into expense reports, and invoice approvals are automated. By integrating near real-time data and using AI to analyze transactions, businesses can see what they’re spending, improve compliance and avoid possible blind spots in the budget. SAP Concur solutions help eliminate yesterday’s tedious tasks, make today’s work easier and support businesses to run at their best. Learn more at <a href="http://www.concur.com">concur.com</a> or the SAP Concur <a href="http://www.concur.com/newsroom">blog</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>About SAP</strong> SAP’s strategy is to help every business run as a sustainable intelligent enterprise. As a market leader in enterprise application software, we help companies of all sizes and in all industries run at their best: 87% of the world’s total global commerce touches an SAP system. Our machine learning, Internet of Things (IoT), and advanced analytics technologies help turn customers’ businesses into sustainable intelligent enterprises. SAP helps give people and organizations deep business insight and fosters collaboration that helps them stay ahead of their competition. We simplify technology for companies so they can consume our software the way they want, without disruption. Our end-to-end suite of applications and services enables business and public customers across 25 industries globally to operate profitably, adapt continuously, and make a difference. With a global network of customers, partners, employees, and thought leaders, SAP helps the world run better and improve people’s lives. For more information, visit <a href="https://www.sap.com/index.html">www.sap.com</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Note to editors:</strong><br>To preview and download broadcast-standard stock footage and press photos digitally, please visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/photos">www.sap.com/photos</a>. On this platform, you can find high resolution material for your media channels. To view video stories on diverse topics, visit <a href="http://www.sap-tv.com">www.sap-tv.com</a>. From this site, you can embed videos into your own Web pages, share video via email links, and subscribe to RSS feeds from SAP TV.</p>
  <p><strong>For customers interested in learning more about SAP products:</strong><br>Global Customer Center: +49 180 534-34-24<br>United States Only: 1 (800) 872-1SAP (1-800-872-1727)</p>
  <p><strong>For more information, press only:</strong><br>Alex Vaught, +1 (425) 590-0844, <a href="mailto:alex.vaught@sap.com">alex.vaught@sap.com</a>, PT<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>Any statements contained in this document that are not historical facts are forward-looking statements as defined in the U.S. Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995. Words such as “anticipate,” “believe,” “estimate,” “expect,” “forecast,” “intend,” “may,” “plan,” “project,” “predict,” “should” and “will” and similar expressions as they relate to SAP are intended to identify such forward-looking statements. SAP undertakes no obligation to publicly update or revise any forward-looking statements. All forward-looking statements are subject to various risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results to differ materially from expectations. The factors that could affect SAP’s future financial results are discussed more fully in SAP’s filings with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (“SEC”), including SAP’s most recent Annual Report on Form 20-F filed with the SEC. Readers are cautioned not to place undue reliance on these forward-looking statements, which speak only as of their dates. © 2021 SAP SE. All rights reserved. SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/qualtrics</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-concur</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Employee Health, Corporate Compliance, and the New COVID-19 Vaccine Mandate: Are You Prepared?]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/new-covid-19-vaccine-mandate-compliance</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/new-covid-19-vaccine-mandate-compliance</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The new COVID-19 vaccine mandate poses challenges for businesses. SAP and Qualtrics can help tackle requirements with confidence.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_163bccda7cde8245575fd5d41938530ab9ca243a0.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_163bccda7cde8245575fd5d41938530ab9ca243a0.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_163bccda7cde8245575fd5d41938530ab9ca243a0.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Employee Health, Corporate Compliance, and the New COVID-19 Vaccine Mandate: Are You Prepared?" src="./media_163bccda7cde8245575fd5d41938530ab9ca243a0.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="employee-health-corporate-compliance-and-the-new-covid-19-vaccine-mandate-are-you-prepared">Employee Health, Corporate Compliance, and the New COVID-19 Vaccine Mandate: Are You Prepared?</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><a href="/covid-19">COVID-19</a> vaccination mandates are upon us. States, localities, and specific business sectors have created a range of approaches to combat the spread of the virus and protect their employees as they navigate evolving regulations around returning to work.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As of September 9, the U.S. government has stepped in, announcing that it will require businesses with 100 or more employees to ensure their workers are either vaccinated or tested once a week. This mandate poses multiple challenges for organizations that need to respond immediately to avoid the risk of fines. Businesses are looking for robust solutions to facilitate the process of securely uploading vaccination and testing status data.</p>
  <p>Agility and scalability are top of mind. With a pandemic that is constantly evolving, organizations need a configurable solution that can adapt as regulations change and scale as programs ramp up. At the same time, employees may have strong feelings about the mandate – and <a href="https://www.qualtrics.com/blog/vaccine-policies-for-employees/">some may object</a>. While compliance is a must, so is listening and trust-building. Organizations need a transparent and noninvasive approach to collecting data that helps generate employee buy-in.</p>
  <h2 id="fast-effective-vaccination-and-testing-management">Fast, Effective Vaccination and Testing Management</h2>
  <p>SAP and Qualtrics have been helping organizations worldwide navigate the global pandemic and offer solutions to help with vaccine mandates. With powerful vaccination and testing management capabilities, organizations can meet evolving vaccination requirements and improve employee safety and well-being. The result is fewer regulatory, legal, and workplace health risks.</p>
  <p>With <strong><a href="https://www.qualtrics.com/lp/vaccination-testing-manager/?utm_medium=email&#x26;utm_source=sap&#x26;utm_campaign=US-EX-vaccination-testing-manager">Qualtrics Vaccination &#x26; Testing Manager</a></strong>, also known as an <a href="https://www.sap.com/programs/covid-vaccinations.html">employee vaccine management system</a>, organizations can more quickly and simply gather COVID-19 vaccination status and ongoing test results from employees, contractors, and on-site visitors and spot issues in real time. All relevant information is securely maintained, helping businesses to comply with requirements, reduce risks, and avoid fines.</p>
  <p>Qualtrics Vaccination &#x26; Testing Manager also provides a critical tool for following through on the most important objective: protecting employee health and well-being. Data is managed in a more secure manner that helps protect employee privacy. And while employee perspectives on the mandate will likely remain diverse, the solution helps organizations better listen to employee perspectives as regulations evolve while enabling the transparency and insight needed to have honest and informed conversations moving forward.</p>
  <h2 id="compliance-safety-rapid-ramp-up">Compliance, Safety, Rapid Ramp-Up</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="request-a-demo-of-qualtrics-vaccination--testing-manager-today">Request a demo of Qualtrics Vaccination &#x26; Testing Manager today</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.qualtrics.com/lp/vaccination-testing-manager/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Pre-built and run in the cloud, Qualtrics Vaccination &#x26; Testing Manager helps organizations get up and running in days — versus weeks to months with other solutions. It also uses a combination of mobile-friendly digital forms, automated workflows and reminders, and intuitive dashboards that have been designed to confirm vaccination status and test results more securely and at scale.</p>
  <p>What sets Qualtrics Vaccination &#x26; Testing Manager apart from many other offerings is its breadth, agility, and intuitive use:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Breadth:</strong> It is a single, centralized solution that supports the processes needed to meet COVID-19 attestation requirements and broader workplace safety needs, including vaccine attestation, ongoing testing uploads, and daily symptom checking. It also provides dashboards for tracking details and generating insights on demand.</li>
    <li><strong>Agility:</strong> With a lightweight and no-code setup, the solution enables organizations to ramp up quickly. HR teams can manage processes without dependency on IT. And with flexible configuration options, the solution can adapt to future needs and legal regulations as they change.</li>
    <li><strong>Intuitive use:</strong> With low administrative overhead and automated workflows, users are smoothly guided through all processes. Vaccination and testing status can be collected via multiple digital channels, such as e-mail, SMS, or via QR code and Web page. Automated workflows, meanwhile, guide employees through the vaccination attestation process, with triggered actions and reminders for uploading vaccination cards, test results, or proof of exemption.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>As for helping keep sensitive employee data secure, Qualtrics Vaccination &#x26; Testing Manager includes built-in features that maintain personal health information and vaccination data separately from employee records. In addition, the solution is ISO 27001 and FedRamp compliant and HITRUST certified, which means its technology platform provides customers the tools to manage HIPAA compliance if needed. <a href="https://www.qualtrics.com/lp/vaccination-testing-manager/?utm_medium=referral&#x26;utm_source=SAPweb&#x26;utm_campaign=US-EX-vaccination-testing-landing-page">Learn more about Qualtrics Vaccination &#x26; Testing Manager here</a>.</p>
  <h2 id="readily-available-extensible-solution-for-existing-customers">Readily Available, Extensible Solution for Existing Customers</h2>
  <p>For existing customers using the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm/products.html#active_tab=item_1602592051931">SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central solution</a>, SAP also offers a <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/06/80473e7e-e47d-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">health and vaccine tracking portlet</a> free of charge.</p>
  <p>Available through the upgrade center of the SAP SuccessFactors solution, this portlet uses the flexible metadata framework technology already built into SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central. Organizations can customize and extend the portlet to meet a variety of monitoring needs as vaccination and testing requirements evolve.</p>
  <p>Additionally, the portlet can produce analytics to identify and support high-risk employees based on location, business unit, department, age, work area, and more. Businesses can use practical, real-time dashboards and reporting to safely bring the workforce back to the office. For more information about the portlet, read this article on <a href="https://blogs.sap.com/2021/06/22/a-safe-return-to-the-workplace-with-sap-successfactors-employee-central/">Safely Returning to the Workplace with SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central</a>.</p>
  <h2 id="the-mandates-are-here-move-forward-today">The Mandates Are Here, Move Forward Today</h2>
  <p>At SAP, we know that we’re all in this pandemic together, and a big part of SAP’s mission today is to help our customers make it through. These solutions enable organizations to tackle vaccination and testing requirements with confidence and without delay. They can get up and running more quickly with a cloud-based, pre-built solution that is intuitive, transparent, and flexible enough to adapt to change.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="stay-ahead-of-changing-vaccination-requirements-with-solutions-from-sap-and-qualtrics">Stay ahead of changing vaccination requirements with solutions from SAP and Qualtrics</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/programs/covid-vaccinations.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="for-more-information-about-moving-forward-visit-us-at-sapcomprogramscovid-19-vaccine-management">For more information about moving forward, visit us at <a href="https://www.sap.com/programs/covid-vaccinations.html">sap.com/programs/covid-19-vaccine-management</a>.</h3>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <table>
          <thead>
            <tr>
              <th>Quote</th>
            </tr>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td>For a live demo, visit the SAP SuccessFactors booth at the HR Technology Conference September 28 – October 1.</td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
              <td>Amanda Crittenden is global solution marketing lead for Employee Experience Management for SAP SuccessFactors.</td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/covid-19</category>
            <category>news-tag/qualtrics</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sustainable Business at Veolia ANZ: A Culture of Employee Engagement]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/veolia-anz-culture-of-employee-engagement</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/veolia-anz-culture-of-employee-engagement</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Aug 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Veolia ANZ builds a culture of employee engagement with SAP solutions as part of its sustainable business mission. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d9756ca8715dfa6172ff87e4a03e6f2be81050f0.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d9756ca8715dfa6172ff87e4a03e6f2be81050f0.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1d9756ca8715dfa6172ff87e4a03e6f2be81050f0.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Sustainable Business at Veolia ANZ: A Culture of Employee Engagement" src="./media_1d9756ca8715dfa6172ff87e4a03e6f2be81050f0.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sustainable-business-at-veolia-anz-a-culture-of-employee-engagement">Sustainable Business at Veolia ANZ: A Culture of Employee Engagement</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Sustainable business is one post-pandemic trend that’s here to stay, especially among global market leaders like <a href="https://www.veolia.com/anz/">Veolia ANZ</a>, a longtime champion of ecological transformation.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>With approximately 4,600 employees in Australia and 182,000 worldwide, Veolia ANZ has extended its sustainable business commitment to both customers and workers. The company’s COVID-19 crisis response team in Australia and New Zealand began using <a href="https://www.qualtrics.com/">Experience Management solutions from SAP and Qualtrics</a> this past year to stay connected with workers and address their challenges.</p>
  <p>“It’s critical that we constantly communicate with employees to understand their challenges and act quickly to address their needs,” said Alexandre Moreau, chief people and safety officer at Veolia ANZ. “We needed a quick and easy solution to keep people connected, whether it was managers and their teams or customers. Qualtrics helped us make sure that our people were okay and receiving the support they needed.”</p>
  <p>Sustainability is in Veolia’s DNA. The company’s business portfolio includes providing environmental solutions across water, waste management, and energy. With operations and treatment facilities nationwide, it serves customers of all sizes – from local cafes and food chains to industrial facilities. One of its business units helps municipal water customers provide safe drinking water for their communities and industrial clients to more sustainably manage water in their operations, while its energy division helps companies build energy resilience and become carbon neutral.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="put-employees-at-the-heart-of-everything-you-do-with-sap-successfactors">Put employees at the heart of everything you do with SAP SuccessFactors</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="listening-translates-employee-feedback-into-engagement">Listening Translates Employee Feedback Into Engagement</h2>
  <p>As a designated essential service during the <a href="/covid-19">pandemic</a>, Veolia ANZ provided the same level of support for customers despite significant challenges, including social distancing, schedule disruptions, and lockdowns. During the height of the crisis, it needed even more flexibility to respond to highly changeable situations. For example, workloads increased in the health sector because of pandemic-related activities. Meanwhile, some employees were working remotely, while others had to be in the field. The company used XM solutions from SAP and Qualtrics to stay in touch with employees.</p>
  <p>Kate Moonen, head of Marketing and Digital Experience at Veolia ANZ, was part of the company’s pandemic response team. Speaking during <a href="https://open.spotify.com/episode/1Xe6n7mvEGJCwKz4A7kOgl">The Best Run Podcast by SAP ANZ</a>, she discussed how short, but targeted surveys helped the company stay in touch with its diverse workforce that includes truck drivers, machine operators, engineers, lawyers, and sustainability experts in urban and remote locations.</p>
  <p>“We really wanted to understand that our people, particularly essential workers, were feeling supported,” she said. “Did they have enough PPE equipment to do their jobs safely? What were their concerns about their mental health and well-being? Based on that feedback, it helped our team formulate what we were going to communicate and what actions we needed to take to continue to support our people.”</p>
  <p>Initially, the team was surprised at the high employee engagement levels with the surveys. Over time, the company rolled out new activities based on the feedback. These included regularly scheduled, anywhere, any device communications with senior leadership through live webinars and question-and-answer sessions. In response to employee requests, executives also sent short video messages that employees could watch on their mobile phones, with personalized stories from company leaders about their lives outside of work and how they adapted to the changed working environment.</p>
  <p>“People felt they wanted to take the opportunity to be heard,” said Moonen. “We would often share regular communications with them about what came out of the latest pulse and what we were going to do about it. If you’re asking people for their time, it’s critical to demonstrate what you’re doing with that feedback to meet their needs.”</p>
  <h2 id="continuous-dialogue-through-employee-surveys">Continuous Dialogue Through Employee Surveys</h2>
  <p>Just like any aspect of sustainable business, employee engagement is not a one-and-done effort.</p>
  <p>“We’re seeing strong employee engagement every time we roll out a new survey,” said Moreau. “Instead of waiting a year to connect with employees, Qualtrics has given us a more agile response tool with a quick pulse check that our people appreciate and we can rely on for updated feedback to make better decisions. We want to know how people are feeling in a fast-changing business environment.”</p>
  <h2 id="go-digital-for-fast-action">Go Digital for Fast Action</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="the-future-of-business-has-feelings">The future of business has feelings</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/experience-management-xm.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Moreau said companies should be explicit about what employees have shared and how they’re taking action. Even if there isn’t an immediate answer, people appreciate the transparency.</p>
  <p>Moonen also advised employers not to overthink the survey process.</p>
  <p>“Sustainable business is all about agility,” she said. “Collecting the feedback and acting quickly is far more valuable than spending months iterating questions. Digital technology gives us the ability to constantly evolve and adapt as customer expectations, market conditions, and employee experiences shift.”</p>
  <h2 id="future-of-work-is-in-employee-experience">Future of Work Is in Employee Experience</h2>
  <p>In the wake of the pandemic, many employees yearn for a greater sense of belonging. They want more help with their individual career goals and to have pride in their workplace. Getting the employee experience right is part of every organization’s transformational journey to sustainable business.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Follow me @smgaler.</em><br><em><a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2021/07/08/sustainable-business-at-veolia-anz-we-make-sure-our-people-are-okay/?sh=5a8244291c0f">This blog also appeared on SAP BrandVoice on Forbes.</a></em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-engagement</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/experience-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/qualtrics</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-anz</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Real-Time Data Gives People the Go Ahead to Mingle in a Post-Pandemic World]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/06/proximity-monitor-real-time-data-post-pandemic-world</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/06/proximity-monitor-real-time-data-post-pandemic-world</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Real-time data gives organizations the confidence to safely bring people back to in-person activities. Proximity Monitor offers just that.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1925da3b1198d1410aa5949435e5487267fdf758b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1925da3b1198d1410aa5949435e5487267fdf758b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1925da3b1198d1410aa5949435e5487267fdf758b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Real-Time Data Gives People the Go Ahead to Mingle in a Post-Pandemic World" src="./media_1925da3b1198d1410aa5949435e5487267fdf758b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="real-time-data-gives-people-the-go-ahead-to-mingle-in-a-post-pandemic-world">Real-Time Data Gives People the Go Ahead to Mingle in a Post-Pandemic World</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>As we confront each dynamic challenge in a <a href="http://news.sap.com/covid-19">post-pandemic world</a>, intelligent technology is safely getting people back to work, eating out, going shopping, attending sporting events and concerts, and other in-person activities. Already in Europe, organizations have turned to <a href="https://www.ey.com/en_uk/news/2020/12/ey-launches-proximity-monitor-helping-to-get-fans-back-into-venues-to-watch-live-sporting-events">Proximity Monitor</a>, a cloud-based service that monitors human interactions by collecting and analyzing people’s location-based data every few seconds.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“COVID-19 has been a digital catalyst, and the world won’t be the same even when it recedes. We are starting to look at the workplace and social environments through an entirely new lens,” said Chris Gant, EY global leader for Proximity Monitor. “Whether it’s in the workplace, at a sporting event, or at a concert, organizations can help promote safety with visibility into people’s behavior in the controlled space in which they operate.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="find-out-more-about-the-power-of-partnership-with-sap">Find out more about the power of partnership with SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/partner.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="anonymized-real-time-data-for-safety">Anonymized, Real-Time Data for Safety</h2>
  <p>To share their location data wirelessly, people can turn on the Proximity Monitor phone app or use other devices such as a lanyard or wristband. The solution uses <a href="https://www.sap.com/uk/products/cloud-analytics.html#:~:text=What%20is%20SAP%20Analytics%20Cloud,supports%20advanced%20analytics%20enterprise%2Dwide.">SAP Analytics Cloud</a> and <a href="https://www.sap.com/uk/products/hana/cloud.html">SAP HANA Cloud</a> running on EY Client Technology platform to capture real-time data as people interact in any environment, summarizing risk levels on a digital dashboard. Besides measuring the distance between individuals, the solution analyzes the length of time people are near each other and at what time of day, as well as where they are gathering. Companies can configure risk parameters and resultant actions based on low, medium, and high designations. There’s also an option to add <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/experience-management-xm.html">Experience Management solutions from SAP and Qualtrics</a>. Best of all, the data is completely anonymized.</p>
  <p>“None of the data we capture in the solution is personally identifiable by individuals,” said Gant. “Even if an alert was sent to warn a person that they were nearby someone who tested positive for COVID-19, it would not contain any personal data about them or the name of the person they were near.”</p>
  <h2 id="data-fuels-resilient-business-decisions">Data Fuels Resilient Business Decisions</h2>
  <p>The development of Proximity Monitor unfolded as quickly as the pandemic itself during the past year. After initially focusing on contact tracing and social distancing, the solution has morphed into a fast-evolving tool for short- and long-term planning of space.</p>
  <p>“Clients can take action based on dashboard insights. It could be anything from sending alerts and strengthening communication to redesigning workspaces and organizing people flow,” said Gant. “In a world that’s adjusted to COVID-19, the design of workspace is going to change. Organizations need to re-establish how workspaces will be used, which you can do in near real time with Proximity Monitor.”</p>
  <p>Gant added that typical go-lives take about a couple of weeks and can be scaled easily for any number of people.</p>
  <h2 id="trusted-data-says-when-its-safe-to-mingle">Trusted Data Says When It’s Safe to Mingle</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-all-the-cloud-analytics-features-you-need-in-a-single-solution">Get all the cloud analytics features you need in a single solution</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/cloud-analytics.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Proximity Monitor thrives on uncertainty, analyzing in-the-moment data to reduce risk as people go about their day at work or leisure. In the workplace, data can help leaders and employees feel more confident about location decisions. The same applies to attendees at in-person events. For example, a recent major sporting event organizer piloted Proximity Monitor to help meet the group’s stringent COVID-19 protocols.</p>
  <p>“They used the solution to help protect people running and participating in the event, distinguishing between those kept inside a protective bubble and those operating on the outside of the bubble,” said Gant. “They could make sure that different groups of people were not mingling too closely with others or going to locations they shouldn’t be going to.”</p>
  <p>Universities are starting to use EY Proximity Monitor to plan for social distancing reinforcement as they ready for in-person learning. They want to make sure students and faculty understand and can physically follow protocols across various spaces, whether in the classroom, library, dorms, or other campus locations. A massive European cultural event is also using Proximity Monitor to help monitor the health and safety of its artists, production team, and guests.</p>
  <h2 id="global-future-for-industry-safety">Global Future for Industry Safety</h2>
  <p>Fresh from having won a prestigious <a href="https://www.sap.com/idea-place/sap-innovation-awards/2021-entries.winners.html">SAP Innovation Award</a> this year, Gant said EY teams were exploring emerging use cases, like wayfinding to reduce risk as people navigate unfamiliar surroundings such as complex conference venues and large events.</p>
  <p>“Organizations need to regulate the flow of people across locations, preventing crowds and queues from forming,” he said. “They can make better space management decisions based on the concentration of people in that building cumulatively at any time.”</p>
  <p>Gant saw tremendous potential for Proximity Monitor in the global market, including North America.</p>
  <p>“The wow factor comes alive for clients when they see the fantastic data insights on the dashboard and realize how they can use it to solve their unique challenges,” he said. “Organizers of live music and cultural events are excited about it as a way of giving confidence that it is safe to return. We’re also collaborating with several UK government clients around using Proximity Monitor for workspace management and redesign.”</p>
  <p>Customer feedback to date has been overwhelmingly positive according to Gant, and it’s no wonder. Informed, anonymized data is pitch perfect for organizations navigating through these uncertain times.</p>
  <p>Real-time data is giving organizations the confidence to safely bring people back to social events, offices, schools, and other in-person activities.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Follow me @smgaler</em><br><em>This blog also appeared on <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2021/06/01/real-time-data-gives-people-the-go-ahead-to-mingle-in-a-post-pandemic-world/?sh=6e91f2f127fd">SAP BrandVoice on Forbes</a>.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/covid-19</category>
            <category>news-tag/qualtrics</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Don’t Forget That Employees Are Customers Too]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/06/employees-are-customers-too</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/06/employees-are-customers-too</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The best organizations create a great employee experience that allows people to make their greatest contribution. Read to learn more!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d578109f29a6fe11824fd2286eecc844fe9ee8b1.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d578109f29a6fe11824fd2286eecc844fe9ee8b1.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1d578109f29a6fe11824fd2286eecc844fe9ee8b1.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Don’t Forget That Employees Are Customers Too" src="./media_1d578109f29a6fe11824fd2286eecc844fe9ee8b1.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="dont-forget-that-employees-are-customers-too">Don’t Forget That Employees Are Customers Too</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Global workers in a recent <a href="http://www.sap.com/forresterhxm">employee experience (EX) survey</a> rated the technology they use every day among the top five most important factors directly impacting their work experience. The other four things, which also rose in importance, were flexibility, safety at work/travel safety, work-life balance, and benefits.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Commissioned by <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm.html">SAP SuccessFactors</a>, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm/employee-experience-management.html?tab=1&#x26;sort=title_asc">Qualtrics</a>, and EY, the survey from Forrester Consulting collected global feedback from about 900 full-time employees.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-the-report-close-the-employee-experience-gap">Read the report: Close the Employee Experience Gap</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/programs/experience-wins.html#forrester">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="managing-the-hybrid-work-experience">Managing the Hybrid Work Experience</h2>
  <p>While the <a href="/covid-19">pandemic</a> continues to be a bumpy ride for many organizations, changing workforce conditions are making EX more important than ever in the new normal.</p>
  <p>“Many industries are experiencing unexpected commercial demand and opportunity,” said Marc Havercroft, global chief customer officer at SAP SuccessFactors. “They’re struggling with talent shortages as some economies begin to rise, while others face setbacks. Organizations have to manage hybrid work models, connecting employees with their managers as well as teams company-wide.”</p>
  <p>Digitalization has surged during the past year and will only become more prevalent, supporting productivity and job satisfaction for people whether they stay remote, opt for partial in-person work, or need to be onsite given the nature of their responsibilities. Havercroft said that SAP SuccessFactors customers have relied on the cloud-based <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm/hxm-suite.html">SAP SuccessFactors Human Experience Management (HXM) Suite</a> to help build a strong EX throughout recruitment, onboarding, and performance management.</p>
  <p>“Our global, multi-language platform was instrumental in helping organizations know what employees have been going through to provide a supportive EX from the pandemic’s early stages through this unpredictable recovery and beyond,” he said. “Companies of all sizes are virtually bringing people on board, using the tools to make introductions, get them productive quickly, and provide what they need to excel.”</p>
  <p>Indeed, surveyed employees in the Forrester research were encouraged by management and senior leadership to adopt digital tools that promote collaboration, mobility, and remote work. However, 40% of employees found their technology difficult to use, and over half said that it lacked important features. For example, three-quarters reported that the applications and data they needed were not always accessible on desktop and mobile devices. Closing gaps like these will be an important part of effective EX moving forward.</p>
  <h2 id="technology-strengthens-human-bonds-at-work">Technology Strengthens Human Bonds at Work</h2>
  <p>Reliance on technology doesn’t negate the human factor. One of the most surprising results of this pandemic year was how digitalization brought people together.</p>
  <p>“Technology takes on the administrative tasks, giving people more time to connect as human beings, especially between managers and their direct reports. That relationship is paramount to someone’s work experience,” said Havercroft. “Companies can capture work-related data using the technology, so people can do what they do best – empathetically listening to solve problems and making more valuable contributions by applying their creativity and knowledge. We’re seeing this happen across every geography and industry.”</p>
  <h2 id="how-to-close-the-ex-gap">How to Close the EX Gap</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="experience-wins-with-the-sap-successfactors-hxm-suite">Experience wins with the SAP SuccessFactors HXM Suite</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm/hxm-suite.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The same survey findings revealed numerous gaps between a company’s EX aspirations and the reality employees faced. For example, almost 80% of HR leaders predicted that EX will be one of the most important factors in meeting business objectives. However, a paltry 9% of respondents said employee needs were the number one consideration when setting EX strategies, and less than a third of HR managers said it made the top three priorities. Technology can help close the gap between earlier workforce norms and changing employee expectations.</p>
  <p>“We’ve had EX technology for a while, but Industrial Age societal constructs haven’t completely caught up to the reality of hybrid work,” said Havercroft. “The pandemic turbo-charged this humankind evolution, forcing companies to use the technology more fully to actually enhance our core human capabilities.”</p>
  <h2 id="ex-has-direct-impact-on-customer-experience">EX Has Direct Impact on Customer Experience</h2>
  <p>One of the major learnings for businesses worldwide has been that employees are their core asset and should be treated accordingly. There’s valid argument for changes that will improve EX and cascade to a better CX.</p>
  <p>“Look at those moments that matter for your employees and give them the ability to do their job well so they can deliver a fantastic customer experience,” said Havercroft. “The magic of business is when you bring people together, fostering their ability to develop ideas, innovate, fail fast, and learn so they can create more new value for customers.”</p>
  <p>In a brand-driven marketplace, it’s worth remembering that employees are customers too. The best organizations don’t hire great people and tell them what to do. They create a great EX that allows people to make their greatest contribution.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Follow me: @smgaler</em><br><em><a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2021/05/18/ex-survey-dont-forget-that-your-employees-are-customers-too/?sh=4f00ce457a5b">This story originally appeared on SAP BrandVoice on Forbes</a></em>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/qualtrics</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP CEO Christian Klein at SAPPHIRE NOW: Together We Are Reinventing How Businesses Run]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/06/sapphire-now-keynote-ceo-christian-klein</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/06/sapphire-now-keynote-ceo-christian-klein</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In his SAPPHIRE NOW keynote, CEO Christian Klein covered how, together with customers, partners, and employees, SAP is reinventing how businesses run.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/business-process-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
            <category>news-tag/qualtrics</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Employee Experience Becomes a Top Priority for HR Leaders, Highlighting Challenges – Study]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/employee-experience-study-hr-leaders</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/employee-experience-study-hr-leaders</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Get the results of an employee experience study from Forrester Consulting LLC commissioned by SAP, Qualtrics, and EY.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/future-of-work</category>
            <category>news-tag/qualtrics</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[2020 Tech Trends: Experience Management]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/videos/2020-tech-trends-experience-management</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/videos/2020-tech-trends-experience-management</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[People-centricity is in! By the end of this year, digitally trustworthy companies will generate 20 percent more online profit than those that are not, according...]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_190e484c1dc1670c83a52830eb96c92df1cb62734.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_190e484c1dc1670c83a52830eb96c92df1cb62734.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_190e484c1dc1670c83a52830eb96c92df1cb62734.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="2020 Tech Trends: Experience Management" src="./media_190e484c1dc1670c83a52830eb96c92df1cb62734.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="tech-trends-experience-management">2020 Tech Trends: Experience Management</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_190e484c1dc1670c83a52830eb96c92df1cb62734.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_190e484c1dc1670c83a52830eb96c92df1cb62734.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_190e484c1dc1670c83a52830eb96c92df1cb62734.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="2020 Tech Trends: Experience Management" src="./media_190e484c1dc1670c83a52830eb96c92df1cb62734.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ebnpt3oDbZg">2020 Tech Trends: Experience Management</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>People-centricity is in! By the end of this year, digitally trustworthy companies will generate 20 percent more online profit than those that are not, according to Garter.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>A study by SAP revealed that customer support is the most defining moment in customer experience. Daniel Newman from Futurum Research shares his insights into what it takes to succeed in 2020.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/video</category>
            <category>news-tag/experience-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/qualtrics</category>
            <category>news-tag/ux</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>