<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/back-to-best/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 May 2021 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Viral Video from SAP Parent Hits at the Core of Working Parent Life]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/05/viral-video-working-parent-life</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/05/viral-video-working-parent-life</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 May 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[An SAP employee's recent viral video highlighted the struggles of working parent life. With Back to Best for Parents, SAP wants to help.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d90eecaed328766330a90a175eb7cc9345794026.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d90eecaed328766330a90a175eb7cc9345794026.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1d90eecaed328766330a90a175eb7cc9345794026.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Viral Video from SAP Parent Hits at the Core of Working Parent Life" src="./media_1d90eecaed328766330a90a175eb7cc9345794026.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="viral-video-from-sap-parent-hits-at-the-core-of-working-parent-life">Viral Video from SAP Parent Hits at the Core of Working Parent Life</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-the-back-to-best-for-parents-program">Learn more about the Back to Best for Parents program</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/back-to-best-for-parents">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Last month, Colleen Chulis, regional vice president of Regulated Industries at SAP SuccessFactors, <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/posts/colleen-chulis_my-8-year-old-daughter-asked-me-last-night-ugcPost-6788524137762631680-ILse">posted a video of her daughter</a> imitating a typical work scene – and it quickly racked up nearly 15 million views.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Eight-year-old Adele snaps her fingers at imaginary kids and pets while pretending to carry on an urgent conversation for work, taking frantic notes on a sticky pad.</p>
  <p>More than 26,000 comments on the post, many from fellow working parents, note that the impression is a spot-on representation of the hectic <a href="https://insights.sap.com/remote-work-new-normal/">nature of the workday at home</a>. Like many working parents, Chulis juggles her everyday work responsibilities while her kids — Adelle, Luke, 10, and Declan, 6 — are all attending school through hybrid learning. It’s no simple task.</p>
  <p>After a year of video conferences and e-mail at home, it’s no surprise that kids are integrating this everyday reality into their playtime just like they might play pretend school. But while videos and moments like these are lighthearted and special, thinking about what else children are absorbing from their parents this year is less so.</p>
  <p>A <a href="https://www.apa.org/news/press/releases/stress/2020/sia-mental-health-crisis.pdf">recent study from the American Psychological Association</a> found that seven in 10 parents say family responsibilities are a significant source of stress in their life; 47% of mothers who still have children at home for remote learning reported worsened mental health; and parents were more likely than those without children to have received treatment from a mental health professional since the <a href="/covid-19">pandemic</a> began.</p>
  <p>Chulis’s tale told with love and humor shines a light on every parent’s struggle with the juggle. “This has been a year like no other, with every person across the globe affected in some way. Thankfully, I have felt very well supported by SAP – the benefit policies, my team, and my management. My children have popped into the background of my Zoom calls many times – and everyone just smiles and says hello,” she said. “I’ve felt such kindness and warmth from my colleagues and customers – and I’ve loved getting a chance to peek into their lives and say hello to their children, significant others, roommates, or pets as well!”</p>
  <p>The pandemic has made the difficult task of balancing work and home more difficult than ever. <a href="/2021/01/back-to-best-for-parents-program">We want to help</a>. That’s why SAP and The Female Founder Collective have joined forces. Back to Best for Parents provides special offers, resources, and content to make life easier for parents trying to juggle it all in the tough times of COVID-19.</p>
  <p>To learn how you can improve your own experience as a working parent or how to help working parents you know or employ, visit <a href="https://discover.sap.com/back-to-best-for-parents/en-us/index.html">Back to Best for Parents</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>April Crichlow is global vice president and head of Marketing for SAP SuccessFactors.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/back-to-best</category>
            <category>news-tag/covid-19</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Innovative Tech Helps Carhartt Meet Customer Demand]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/03/carhartt-innovative-tech-customer-demand</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/03/carhartt-innovative-tech-customer-demand</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Behind the scenes at Carhartt, technology transformation with SAP became crucial to keep up with fast-paced growth. Hear their story.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_163ce6b3539a057f2c0d6cee58f4632e958447132.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_163ce6b3539a057f2c0d6cee58f4632e958447132.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_163ce6b3539a057f2c0d6cee58f4632e958447132.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Innovative Tech Helps Carhartt Meet Customer Demand" src="./media_163ce6b3539a057f2c0d6cee58f4632e958447132.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="innovative-tech-helps-carhartt-meet-customer-demand">Innovative Tech Helps Carhartt Meet Customer Demand</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>What do hard workers on the job site have in common with A-list celebrities? <a href="https://www.carhartt.com/">Carhartt</a>. From construction workers and farmers to firefighters and tradespeople, some of the hardest-working people on the planet rely on Carhartt. Now, perhaps surprisingly, rappers, movie stars, and models are also choosing Carhartt to make a fashion statement.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“When a celebrity wears our product, it certainly creates a buzz around the company,” said Carhartt CIO John Hill. “It raises brand awareness and exposes products that some consumers may not be aware of.”</p>
  <p>Behind the scenes, technology transformation became crucial for Carhartt to keep up with fast-paced growth. So, after more than 130 years in business and continued growth in popularity, it became imperative for U.S.-based company to transform both its apparel offerings and its business foundation.</p>
  <p>“It’s important to realize that Carhartt was as far away from a virtual company as you could be,” Hill said. “We quickly realized that not only did we need to transform our technology, but also the processes that the technology was enabling. We identified hundreds of pain points that existed across that value chain. And if we can get rid of those pain points with SAP technology, ultimately we were going to provide a better experience for our associates and our customers.”</p>
  <p>After thoroughly researching different options, Carhartt realized tapping the power of SAP’s intelligent enterprise was the best solution. Yet this hugely innovative upgrade coincided with one of the biggest challenges of our time; believe it or not, Carhartt went live during the worst of the pandemic.</p>
  <h2 id="closing-shop-was-never-an-option">Closing Shop Was Never an Option</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="video-for-carhartt-happy-customers-benefit-from-a-digitally-native-brand-experience">Video: For Carhartt, Happy Customers Benefit from a Digitally Native Brand Experience</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/covid-19/back-to-best.html?=campaigncode=CRM-YD21-SOC-CUSTREF&#x26;video=1ccc2b2a-d57d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>It was a top priority for Carhartt to remain open and provide a frictionless shopping experience for customers, ensuring there was no downtime and no negative impacts on business. “At the end of the day, the brand needs to be able to react to the demands of those customers. Ultimately the customer doesn’t care what it takes to deliver,” said Hill.</p>
  <p>With his office closed, Hill’s technology team prepared to go live while they worked from their homes.</p>
  <p>“You can’t underestimate the challenge of doing a large scale of digital transformation, while you’re growing the business at the pace we are, and still serving customers,” said Hill.</p>
  <p>Yet, he shares that bringing SAP technology online proved easy.</p>
  <p>“Frankly, the harder thing in dealing with a pandemic has been there’s no blueprint of how to plan,” Hill shared. “We were taking down our revenue on a weekly basis, and then increasing it the next week. So it was a very difficult year from that perspective. The actual technology transformation felt like a more normal course of business during the year.”</p>
  <h2 id="strained-supply-chains">Strained Supply Chains</h2>
  <p>Businesses across the planet share Carhartt’s forecasting challenges.</p>
  <p>“People know what they want and they want it when they want it,” said President of SAP North America DJ Paoni. “And they know how they want it. Every customer in every industry has acknowledged that <a href="/covid-19">COVID-19</a> has put the maturing of the global economy on fast-forward. So those companies that have a more sophisticated digital technology are certainly able to pivot faster and connect with their customers on a whole new level.”</p>
  <p>Carhartt believes further investment in digital technologies is a winning strategy that will also provide a fantastic experience for customers.</p>
  <p>“So far, we implemented SAP solutions to support our retail businesses,” said Hill. “This year, we will be implementing solutions to support our wholesale and our direct-to-consumer e-commerce business. I believe that the marketplace has continued to reward those customers that deliver not only a great product, but also a digitally native experience.”</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <table>
          <thead>
            <tr>
              <th colspan="2">Promo</th>
            </tr>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td>
                <h3 id="understand-tomorrows-trends-drive-personalized-shopping-and-run-a-sustainable-fashion-business">Understand tomorrow’s trends, drive personalized shopping and run a sustainable fashion business</h3>
              </td>
              <td><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/fashion-apparel.html">Learn more</a></strong></td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
        <h3 id="meet-carhartt-cio-john-hill-and-hear-the-advicehe-shares-with-his-peers-on-getting-real-with-sap">Meet Carhartt CIO John Hill and hear the advicehe shares with his peers on <a href="https://www.sap.com/covid-19/back-to-best.html?=campaigncode=CRM-YD21-SOC-CUSTREF&#x26;video=1ccc2b2a-d57d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff">Getting Real with SAP</a>.</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2021/03/24/innovative-tech-helps-carhartt-meet-customer-demand/?sh=654825a85117">This story originally appeared on SAP BrandVoice on Forbes</a>.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="make-your-organization-more-resilient-and-agile-in-todays-challenging-environment-get-back-to-best-with-sap">Make your organization more resilient and agile in today’s challenging environment: Get back to best with SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/covid-19/back-to-best.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/accenture</category>
            <category>news-tag/back-to-best</category>
            <category>industry/consumer-goods-cpg</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/e-commerce</category>
            <category>news-tag/fashion</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Will Technology Keep Us Together? Ask Vodafone]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/03/technology-together-vodafone-cio-ignacio-garcia</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/03/technology-together-vodafone-cio-ignacio-garcia</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Mar 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Vodafone CIO Ignacio Garcia recently appeared on Getting Real with SAP to discuss leveraging technology to serve customers amid COVID-19.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e5eb9658e7797cedc7b5a1fe87983fdcf92873d7.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e5eb9658e7797cedc7b5a1fe87983fdcf92873d7.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1e5eb9658e7797cedc7b5a1fe87983fdcf92873d7.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Will Technology Keep Us Together? Ask Vodafone" src="./media_1e5eb9658e7797cedc7b5a1fe87983fdcf92873d7.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="will-technology-keep-us-together-ask-vodafone">Will Technology Keep Us Together? Ask Vodafone</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>It is easy to feel isolated these days, so it’s no wonder that we seem to rely on our smartphones more than ever to stay in touch through calls, texts, and social media.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>But the global health crisis has been challenging for everyone – including the companies that have been working hard to keep us connected, like Vodafone Group. Vodafone is a multinational technology communications company that serves more than 300 million mobile customers around the world.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="watch-the-episode-with-vodafone-conquering-the-challenge-head-on-by-doubling-service">Watch the episode with Vodafone: Conquering the Challenge “Head-On” By Doubling Service</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/covid-19/back-to-best.html?video=10d8458c-d17d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="quick-response-to-customers-and-employees">Quick Response to Customers and Employees</h2>
  <p>Ignacio Garcia, CIO of Corporate Information Systems at Vodafone, recently appeared on <em>Getting Real with SAP</em>. There, he discussed how companies are leveraging technology to manage their business and continue to serve customers in the age of <a href="/covid-19">COVID-19</a>.</p>
  <p>“You can imagine what we were thinking: How much extra demand are we going to have?” says Garcia. “We needed to keep our employees safe and make sure we supported our customers in the best possible way.”</p>
  <p>Vodafone was able to do both.</p>
  <p>In short order, the company developed a <a href="https://www.vodafone.com/covid19">five-point plan</a> to help the communities it serves. Keystones of the plan were a commitment to maintaining the quality of service and providing network capacity and network services for critical government functions.</p>
  <p>Vodafone also made sure to quickly address the needs of a global workforce that encompasses more than 100,000 employees. Vodafone offered support for working at home, created richer virtual training opportunities for its people, and adjusted performance goals and objectives to align with new business needs.</p>
  <h2 id="the-right-technology-pays-dividends">The Right Technology Pays Dividends</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="make-your-organization-more-resilient-and-agile-in-todays-challenging-environment-get-back-to-best-with-sap">Make your organization more resilient and agile in today’s challenging environment: Get back to best with SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/covid-19/back-to-best.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Vodafone’s business agility was not merely the result of good luck.</p>
  <p>Less than a year ago, Vodafone completed a massive global rollout of SAP S/4HANA to help improve operational efficiency in business functions such as finance, supply chain, and IT.</p>
  <p>It was an impressive project covering more than 20 countries. And in addition to establishing a single digital core for the company, it included retooling Vodafone’s worldwide HR systems. “Using the power of the technology was fundamental, having a single data model, a single way to optimize and understand the different markets,” says Garcia.</p>
  <h2 id="stay-creative">Stay Creative</h2>
  <p>Vodafone may have been ahead of the curve in its ability to meet the challenges of COVID-19. But many other companies are responding with technology-driven innovation. There has been an incredible degree of creativity in how businesses have reacted.</p>
  <p>Staying connected will only be one of the challenges we face in the days ahead. This is a critical time for all of us – as individuals and as businesses.</p>
  <p>Check out <a href="https://www.sap.com/covid-19/back-to-best.html?video=10d8458c-d17d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff">this episode of <em>Getting Real with SAP</em></a> to learn more.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em><a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2021/03/03/will-technology-keep-us-together-ask-vodafone/?sh=655f126042da">This story originally appeared on SAP BrandVoice on Forbes.</a></em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/back-to-best</category>
            <category>news-tag/covid-19</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/service-industries</category>
            <category>industry/telecommunications</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Celebrating Women by Finding Ways to Improve Life for Working Mothers]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/03/celebrate-women-working-mothers-panel</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/03/celebrate-women-working-mothers-panel</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A working mothers panel held by SAP's Back to Best for Parents program and the Female Founder Collective discussed juggling it all.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d90eecaed328766330a90a175eb7cc9345794026.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d90eecaed328766330a90a175eb7cc9345794026.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1d90eecaed328766330a90a175eb7cc9345794026.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Celebrating Women by Finding Ways to Improve Life for Working Mothers" src="./media_1d90eecaed328766330a90a175eb7cc9345794026.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="celebrating-women-by-finding-ways-to-improve-life-for-working-mothers">Celebrating Women by Finding Ways to Improve Life for Working Mothers</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>The theme for this year’s International Women’s Day was #ChooseToChallenge. To forge a gender-equal world, we all need to <a href="https://www.internationalwomensday.com/Theme">challenge gender bias and inequality</a> wherever we see them, including the workplace.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Before <a href="/covid-19">COVID-19</a>, that might have meant interacting with colleagues at the office differently or supporting corporate initiatives <a href="https://www.sap.com/corporate/en/purpose/equality.html">like women in tech</a>. But since COVID-19, work and home have been happening in the same place. To challenge gender inequality at work also means addressing it in the home.</p>
  <p>As part of the <a href="/2021/01/back-to-best-for-parents-program">launch</a> event for <a href="https://discover.sap.com/back-to-best-for-parents/en-us/index.html">Back to Best for Parents</a>, I had the honor of participating in a panel discussion last month devoted to just this issue. It turned out to be one of the most candid panel discussions of my career. Out of the nearly 300 attendees (90% of whom were working parents), we heard again and again that they are exhausted, overwhelmed, lonely, and grieving for the loss of their pre-pandemic lives.</p>
  <p>We’ve seen it in the recent article “<a href="https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2021/02/04/parenting/working-moms-coronavirus.html">Primal Scream</a>” in <em>The New York Times</em>: working parents — mothers in particular — are in crisis. My fellow panelists and I, all mothers ourselves, found ourselves trading war stories of the past 11 months.</p>
  <p>Our discussion was in the spirit of the times when work and life are all mashed together. Nobody checked any part of themselves at the door. Listening to the questions from the attendees and the answers from the panel felt more like a late-night discussion among friends. But the friends in this case also happened to be on my shortlist of trailblazing women in business. At the event were fashion designer Rebecca Minkoff; Katya Libin, founder of <a href="https://heymama.co/?gclid=CjwKCAiAjeSABhAPEiwAqfxUReSscH9o38DBgORRIaHVL8y9OZ3N1FQNiPGluPPLMAvuR9Jvfou5lhoCmawQAvD_BwE">Hey Mama</a>; Joan Nguyen, founder of <a href="https://bumobrain.com/">BumoBrain</a>; and Blessing Adesiyan, founder of <a href="https://motherhonestly.com/">Mother Honestly</a>.</p>
  <p>The <a href="https://discover.sap.com/back-to-best-for-parents/en-us/index.html">Back to Best for Parents</a> program provides special offers, resources, and content to make life easier for parents trying to juggle it all in the tough times of COVID-19. We’ve launched in cooperation with the <a href="https://www.femalefoundercollective.com/%5C">Female Founder Collective</a> because we realize that working parents are facing unprecedented pressures and companies need to do more to help.</p>
  <p>To kick off this incredible partnership, our panel talked about all things parenting, working from home, and juggling it all. I found myself taking notes just so I could incorporate these solutions into my own life. Here are some of my favorite gems from the conversation.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-the-back-to-best-for-parents-program">Learn more about the Back to Best for Parents program</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/back-to-best-for-parents">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="plan-for-fun">Plan for Fun</h2>
  <p>One of the complaints of working moms is that they never get a moment to rest their minds from the work of planning and coordination, even at the end of a long workday. So suggesting a bit more planning might seem counterintuitive. But setting aside time each night for a specific activity, like arts and crafts, letter writing, or game night, and letting the whole family know in advance does two things. It gives the kids — and grown-ups — something to look forward to.</p>
  <p>Adeysian shared, “As my 11-year-old said, it was like an Advent calendar that extended into January.” One other effect of planning for fun? It gives the kids a sense of structure and predictability, which can counteract any anxiety they might be feeling in these unpredictable times. We might be spending all our time together, but that doesn’t always mean it’s quality time.</p>
  <h2 id="give-some-of-your-time-to-others">Give Some of Your Time to Others</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="make-your-organization-more-resilient-and-agile-in-todays-challenging-environment-get-back-to-best-with-sap">Make your organization more resilient and agile in today’s challenging environment: Get back to best with SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/covid-19/back-to-best.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>How can making even less time for yourself have a positive impact? Because it can boost what Libin called “ROE” or return on energy. We spend 15 minutes chasing down a toddler so they can put on their shoes or take their medicine, and we might feel drained. We spend time giving career advice to another working parent who might need it, and we can feel restored.</p>
  <p>As Libin said, “In these times where many of us can feel isolated or absorbed in our own struggles, we can take the time, whether it’s five minutes or 30, to share our expertise and give back. What we’ve seen from the community at HeyMama is that it leaves people feeling renewed and connected.”</p>
  <h2 id="go-easy-on-yourself">Go Easy on Yourself</h2>
  <p>This was the note the whole panel ended on and it seemed like the point everybody had been trying to get to. When we say <a href="https://www.sap.com/covid-19/back-to-best.html">Back to Best</a>, we have to acknowledge that best means something different for every parent. But there is one thing it doesn’t mean for any parent, and that’s <em>perfect</em>. It was a relief to hear, even from such an accomplished panel, that there are days when they don’t feel like they’re getting anything right. Especially for moms, it’s common to feel like you’re not getting work right because you’re thinking about your kids and you’re not getting parenting right because you’re thinking about work.</p>
  <p>As an alternative to worrying, the whole panel offered up this advice: Focus on what you can do and stop wasting time and energy thinking of everything you should do. Allow yourself to be imperfect. “Give yourself some grace,” is the way Adesiyan phrased it. After she spoke, you could feel everybody on the video chat exhale.</p>
  <p>If we’re going to enlist the help of companies in the struggles of working parents, the first thing we’ve got to encourage is a new mindset, one in which we extend some grace to one another because we see the bigger picture. We’ve got to stop thinking of employees as assets and think of the whole employee and their whole experience of work and life together.</p>
  <p>The demographics of the attendees were a window into just how widespread the struggles of working parents are. Of the event attendees, most had about two children. They came from 30 different industries and 75 different cities in at least three countries, and 86% of them said their responsibilities had increased because of COVID-19. The struggle of working parents during a pandemic is real, but so is the opportunity for everybody — from working parents to their employers — to take action.</p>
  <p>The pieces of advice here are just the tip of the iceberg. For parents, they are small steps toward feeling safer and more engaged. For leaders who share this advice with the teams, it’s a step toward smarter, more resilient business environments.</p>
  <p>To learn more about how you can improve your own experience as a working parent or how to help working parents you know or employ, visit the <a href="https://discover.sap.com/back-to-best-for-parents/en-us/index.html">Back to Best for Parents</a> website.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>April Crichlow is global vice president and head of Marketing for SAP SuccessFactors.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/back-to-best</category>
            <category>news-tag/business-beyond-bias</category>
            <category>news-tag/covid-19</category>
            <category>non-sap-event/international-womens-day</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Four Ways to Support New Parents Returning to Work During COVID-19 and Beyond]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/support-new-parents-during-covid-19</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/support-new-parents-during-covid-19</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Returning to the workforce during a pandemic is particularly unchartered territory. Learn four ways to support new parents during COVID-19.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14a6047f67a4717247328933c8e3ec1c4ad62c5b3.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14a6047f67a4717247328933c8e3ec1c4ad62c5b3.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_14a6047f67a4717247328933c8e3ec1c4ad62c5b3.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Four Ways to Support New Parents Returning to Work During COVID-19 and Beyond" src="./media_14a6047f67a4717247328933c8e3ec1c4ad62c5b3.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="four-ways-to-support-new-parents-returning-to-work-during-covid-19-and-beyond">Four Ways to Support New Parents Returning to Work During COVID-19 and Beyond</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>There have been numerous articles on how difficult the <a href="/covid-19">pandemic</a> has been on the workforce, from combating isolation and loneliness to prioritizing self-care and easing and managing the burdens placed on working parents. But what about the challenges that have been placed on a specific set of working parents? That is, those who are caring for a baby, took leave, and are returning to work during the pandemic.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>How are these parents being welcomed back and supported during a time when they are managing great change in both their personal and professional lives?</p>
  <p>Here are the stories of two women who work for large, international companies. In describing their personal experiences of returning to work after maternity leave, they show how other employers and managers can best support their people in similar situations.</p>
  <p>Rebecca knew that 2020 would include major life changes. She had accepted a new role at her tech company and was expecting her second child in March. But like with everything else in 2020, things didn’t go as planned. Her baby arrived six weeks early and stayed in the neonatal intensive care unit for weeks. Then, a few days after her baby was released from the hospital, the world shut down for the pandemic.</p>
  <p>Her husband still went to his job each day as an essential worker while she faced the demands of a toddler and newborn at home. In addition, given the global economic slowdown, she was anxious about her job security while she was on leave. “It was really scary,” she said. “My face and my name were not in the mix.”</p>
  <p>Employees returning to work after a major life event are at risk of burnout, a loss in productivity, or leaving the workforce. But new parents who are returning to the workforce during a pandemic were, and still are, in particularly uncharted territory. One of the most important things HR leaders can do is <em>listen and seek to understand</em> these parents as they return to work – whether it’s from home or the office.</p>
  <p>“My manager at the time was always reassuring me that I needed to focus on my family,” she said. “Her constant reassurance was really helpful.”</p>
  <p>It’s critical that organizations have visibility into the changing needs of all employees as they adjust to new ways of working. Listening to employee concerns and getting insights into their well-being means you can improve the employee experience, a critical part of business continuity.</p>
  <p>For managers to lead people effectively today, they need more insights about employees, says Christine Andrukonis, the founder of Notion Consulting and an expert in helping leaders change behavior.</p>
  <p>“I like to say that 50% of the work is about the work itself and 50% of the work is about the people and what’s happening behind-the-scenes for the people involved in the work,” she explained to <a href="https://thriveglobal.com/stories/listening-employees-better-leader-empathy-culture/">Thrive Global</a>. “And leaders have to have that mindset. Until they can appreciate that half of this success relies on the human beings and what’s going on with them, it’s going to be really hard to optimize everything at 100%.”</p>
  <p>Managers in particular can do more to provide resources and support. Here are four ways to start.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-saps-guide-to-creating-a-healthy-and-positive-work-experience">Read SAP's guide to creating a healthy and positive work experience</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2020/12/38b8b98b-bf7d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="set-expectations-and-manage-communication">Set Expectations and Manage Communication</h2>
  <p>With childcare availability and schools in flux, many new parents are also in a critical phase of bonding with their newborns.</p>
  <p>After Rebecca returned to work, she said one of the biggest challenges was the sustained level of expectation to deliver. For example, despite the company’s generous offer of an extended 10 days of paid time off, she said she couldn’t take PTO days in light of her growing workload.</p>
  <p>“When the pandemic first hit, I didn’t feel any reset of expectations. Part of this is potentially just on me and my work ethic,” she said. “You can offer all the time off in the world, but if the expectations on delivery don’t change, I can’t use that time.”</p>
  <p>While paid time off and flexible leave policies are incredibly important, employees need ongoing discussions with managers to make the most of those offerings. Otherwise, company-wide e-mail communication and brochures do little to help new parents.</p>
  <p>“Management conversations are really important, because those are the ones that feel real,” she said. “They’re tangible to you as an employee.”</p>
  <p>To provide companies with tools to help ensure employees have the emotional and mental health support to navigate constant change, Thrive Global and SAP published the guide, “<a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2020/12/38b8b98b-bf7d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff.html">Creating a Healthy and Positive Work Experience</a>.” Managers and leaders can learn about improving their communication, expectation setting, and workload management for all workforces – including remote, on-site, and hybrid.</p>
  <h2 id="support-caretakers-and-new-moms-in-career-transitions">Support Caretakers and New Moms in Career Transitions</h2>
  <p>After Michele, a marketing and event planning executive, returned to work in the summer, she had to recalibrate her skills when conferences turned into virtual events. She received a major first assignment upon her return.</p>
  <p>“The good news is that I love the fact that they trusted me,” she said. “The bad news is that babies are quite demanding.”</p>
  <p>Since giving birth to her second child in early March, Michele was juggling breastfeeding a newborn as she worked remotely. While her company offered a one-month transition period through part-time hours, her workload wasn’t commensurate with a part-time schedule.</p>
  <p>“That benefit is great, but the truth is I was working full-time,” she said, adding that she often took early calls with colleagues in Europe while also communicating with her local team.</p>
  <p>Managers should have conversations to evaluate if and how they can ease employees back into the workforce to ensure a manageable workload. Many high performers don’t want to turn down a career-advancing opportunity, but managers can do their part to help set boundaries toward longer-term goals. For example, they can assign high-visibility opportunities in a later phase of post-leave return, so boundaries don’t limit employees’ careers.</p>
  <p>To make sure caretakers have more opportunities in the workplace, many companies are trying to identify learning and development opportunities that challenge the employee, allowing them to gain new skills and grow.</p>
  <h2 id="sustain-personal-mental-and-physical-health">Sustain Personal Mental and Physical Health</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="discover-more-about-the-back-to-best-for-parents-program-from-sap-successfactors-time-for-kids-and-the-female-founder-collective">Discover more about the Back to Best for Parents program from SAP SuccessFactors, TIME for Kids, and The Female Founder Collective</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/01/back-to-best-for-parents-program">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In typical times, caring for a newborn can be an isolating experience. With social distancing measures in place, many feel grief and frustration that they can’t share this milestone with others. Michele said that having her second baby during this health crisis highlighted this void.</p>
  <p>“They say it takes a village to raise a child,” she said. “What’s different today is everybody is scared. I don’t expect anyone to come and bring me a lasagna just because I gave birth. But at the same time, I don’t have the same social interactions compared to what I had with my first.”</p>
  <p>Some psychologists are concerned that <a href="https://www.today.com/parents/covid-19-pandemic-leads-more-postpartum-depression-t179221">pandemic isolation is contributing to more anxiety and postpartum depression</a>, which can begin anytime within the first year after birth. According to the <a href="https://www.who.int/mental_health/maternal-child/maternal_mental_health/en/">World Health Organization</a>, before the pandemic about 10% of pregnant women and 13% of women who had just given birth experienced a mental health disorder, primarily depression. Companies can support these employees by offering <a href="/2020/04/mequilibrium-employee-resilience">resources that allow them to seek help</a>, including virtual appointments for addressing physical and mental health.</p>
  <p>Many employees can benefit from professional or <a href="/2020/03/bravely-personalized-employee-coaching">virtual coaching</a> for stress management, emotional support, and actionable guidance. And, especially for new parents, employers should provide clear communication about these benefits.</p>
  <p>In addition, <a href="https://www.bankrate.com/finance/credit-cards/losing-sleep-survey/">financial wellness has been linked to overall health</a>. <a href="https://www.sapappcenter.com/en/product/display-0000043365_live_v1/Best%20Money%20Moves">Financial wellness platforms</a> can help employees create a manageable budget and pay down debt. With less to worry about when it comes to personal finances, employees have the opportunity to be at their best and most productive.</p>
  <h2 id="advance-learning-and-career-development-initiatives">Advance Learning and Career Development Initiatives</h2>
  <p>For many new parents, returning to the workplace can remind them of their first day in the office as they face new people and ways of working. Employers can help provide a smoother transition through mentorship platforms and introductions to key team members.</p>
  <p>And it’s important that <a href="https://www.sap.com/covid-19/back-to-best.html?btp=b6a01620-b32c-4850-8119-ab359299ca32&#x26;pdf-asset=26a1418c-bf7d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff&#x26;page=1">leaders continually offer opportunities and experiences that develop employees</a>. “Up is not the only way to grow in one’s career,” Terrence Seamon, an executive career transition consultant at The Ayers Group, <a href="https://thriveglobal.com/stories/know-employees-growth-ambitions-motivations-develop-talent/">told Thrive Global</a>.</p>
  <p>Mentors can share learning programs to help guide their mentees, and employers can support frequent dialogue and feedback. A <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/succession-development.html">succession and development solution</a> can provide smart recommendations for people on whom to connect with to help them develop.</p>
  <p>Through a <a href="https://www.successfactors.com/en/products-services/learning-development/learning.html">learning management system</a>, employees can create a plan to help tackle issues specific to them, whether it’s returning to work after having a baby or getting up to speed on any changes that occurred in their particular area of work. Some <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/content-stream-skillsoft.html">solution</a><u>s</u> deliver an immersive learning experience to help employees achieve their goals.</p>
  <h2 id="support-and-understand-employees">Support <em>and</em> Understand Employees</h2>
  <p>During any challenge, people must be the priority for businesses. But generous benefits for new parents could make little impact on employees if companies and managers aren’t listening as well. As Rebecca put it, in her return to work she “actually felt really supported but not understood.” It’s important that your people know that, in the face of uncertainty, they will remain the backbone of business continuity.</p>
  <p>“If you’re going to offer a benefit from a corporate level, you need to ensure that a manager can truly work with a team to let them take advantage of those benefits,” Michele said. “You know, walk the talk.”</p>
  <p>For new parents, recognition can go a long way. “If they know that you are going the extra mile,” Michele said, “just send a quick email saying, ‘We see what you’re going through, and we appreciate you.’”</p>
  <p><a href="https://discover.sap.com/back-to-best-for-parents/en-us/index.html">Discover more ways</a> to offer support to working parents when they need it most so they can get back to best and experience wins in their personal and professional lives.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Carolyn Judge Phillip is vice president of Corporate Marketing for SAP SuccessFactors.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sign-up-for-the-weekly-sap-news-center-newsletter">Sign up for the weekly SAP News Center newsletter</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/nl/sap-innovation-and-transformation-newsletter/index.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/back-to-best</category>
            <category>news-tag/covid-19</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dear Working Parents: A Gift to Get Back to Best]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/01/back-to-best-for-parents-program</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/01/back-to-best-for-parents-program</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With the Back to Best for Parents program, SAP wants to close the gap between working parents' challenges and the employer support needed.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f9bd0cf220ad690c178c3ad212dd2b66d65dc899.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f9bd0cf220ad690c178c3ad212dd2b66d65dc899.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1f9bd0cf220ad690c178c3ad212dd2b66d65dc899.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Dear Working Parents: A Gift to Get Back to Best" src="./media_1f9bd0cf220ad690c178c3ad212dd2b66d65dc899.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="dear-working-parents-a-gift-to-get-back-to-best">Dear Working Parents: A Gift to Get Back to Best</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>It’s Monday. You wake up early, make breakfast for the family, and get your kids ready for virtual school while simultaneously trying to start your work day. You balance helping with homework and attending back-to-back meetings, dreaming of downtime to squeeze in a short workout or a few precious moments to yourself. All of this is compounded by pandemic stress and uncertainty.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In the midst of <a href="/covid-19">COVID-19</a>, working parents encounter unprecedented pressure, impacting their personal and professional lives. With <a href="https://en.unesco.org/themes/education-emergencies/coronavirus-school-closures">1.2 billion children</a> globally who have faced either full or partial school closures, working parents, particularly women, find themselves feeling overwhelmed as they struggle to develop in their career while taking care of their families and managing their households. In September, <a href="https://news.stanford.edu/2020/06/29/snapshot-new-working-home-economy/">865,000 women</a> left the U.S. workforce, four times more than men. <a href="https://www.cnn.com/2021/01/08/economy/women-job-losses-pandemic/index.html">In December, the U.S. economy lost 140,000 jobs, and all of them were held by women</a>, reinforcing the gravity of the situation and the devastating loss to businesses and the economy at large.</p>
  <p>Public awareness of this situation may be reaching a tipping point. This month, Girls Who Code CEO Reshma Saujani and 50 other women of note <a href="https://www.marshallplanformoms.com/">penned a letter</a> to President Biden, asking him to make financial relief for working mothers part of his administration’s first 100 days.</p>
  <p>Calls to action for the public sector are good, but there is a huge opportunity for the private sector to step up too.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-the-back-to-best-for-parents-program">Learn more about the Back to Best for Parents program</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/back-to-best-for-parents">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="the-opportunity-for-employers">The Opportunity for Employers</h2>
  <p>Gone are the days where employees abide by the unwritten rule of checking their personal situations at the door. For the first time in our collective history, we now have work, school, and home life all under one roof. The employee experience and caring for the whole person is more important than ever. It’s not just the right thing to do, it is what employers must do — especially for their working parents.</p>
  <p>By taking the time to listen and understand employees, leaders can foster smarter, more responsive, and more resilient business environments that make employees feel safe, engaged, and productive. According to Thrive Global, <a href="https://thriveglobal.com/stories/arianna-huffington-data-insights-remote-work-home-support-employees/">85% of U.S. employees</a> wish their employer would do more to help them adapt and manage during the pandemic. Parents especially need supportive resources to manage family, wellness, time, and career during this challenging period. This will result in greater engagement, productivity, and overall well-being.</p>
  <h2 id="the-back-to-best-for-parents-program">The Back to Best for Parents Program</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="make-your-organization-more-resilient-and-agile-in-todays-challenging-environment-get-back-to-best-with-sap">Make your organization more resilient and agile in today’s challenging environment: Get back to best with SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/covid-19/back-to-best.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In recognition of the increasing needs of working parents, SAP SuccessFactors, <a href="https://www.timeforkids.com/">TIME for Kids</a>, and <a href="https://www.femalefoundercollective.com/">The Female Founder Collective</a> have joined forces to deliver an exciting, first-of-its-kind program to help parents get back to best. The Back to Best for Parents program brings together special offers, resources, and content to support parents by helping them integrate work and life during this challenging time in our history. While the program is open to all, SAP also wants to help customers close the gap between the real challenges working parents experience and the support they need their employers to provide.</p>
  <p>The Back to Best for Parents program delivers tools and knowledge that parents can use. Plus, businesses can extend these resources and a variety of offers to equip and assist the working parents among their employees in addressing challenges across home, career, children’s learning and enrichment, time management, and health and well-being. Over the next month, the program will release feature videos with helpful tips for children and parents, podcasts discussing challenges and solutions for parents and professionals, and specific resources to support the well-being of the whole family.</p>
  <p>As a mother of two young children myself, and after countless conversations with SAP employees, customers, and the community, I know that this is a step in the right direction. As leaders, we have a responsibility to do what we can to support the exponential challenges of parenting and care giving in this period of time. The companies that commit to this will be able to have stronger, happier, and more resilient workforces that will pay dividends in the years to come after the pandemic.</p>
  <p><a href="https://www.sap.com/back-to-best-for-parents">Learn more about the curated offers</a> from The Female Founder Collective companies, and if you are an SAP customer interested in the free three-month subscription to TIME for Kids, reach out to <a href="mailto:SAP.HXM.Offer@sap.com">SAP.HXM.Offer@sap.com</a> for an offer link that you can share with your employees.</p>
  <p>Together, we can empower one another to get back to best and bring our happiest and most productive selves to our jobs and to our families.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>April Crichlow is global vice president and head of Marketing for SAP SuccessFactors.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/back-to-best</category>
            <category>news-tag/covid-19</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>