<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/industry/utilities/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[What Generative AI Can Do for Utilities]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/what-generative-ai-can-do-for-utilities</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/what-generative-ai-can-do-for-utilities</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With practice, utilities see using Generative AI to better manage power lines, predict and prevent outages, and train field workers.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>industry/utilities</category>
            <category>content-type/expert-opinions</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP's Industry Cloud Drives Innovation in Utilities Through Cloud-Based Apps and Partner Collaborations]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/sap-industry-cloud-drives-innovation-in-utilities</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/sap-industry-cloud-drives-innovation-in-utilities</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP's industry cloud is driving innovation in the utilities sector through cloud-based apps and partner collaborations. Read to learn how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-co-innovation-lab</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-store</category>
            <category>industry/utilities</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[300 Days of Sun: Communities Power Their Own Future]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/300-days-of-sun</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/300-days-of-sun</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Lebanon faces daunting economic and energy problems. A new documentary explores how citizens are looking to the sun for solutions.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>core-topic/sustainable-business-operations</category>
            <category>industry/oil-gas-energy</category>
            <category>industry/utilities</category>
            <category>content-type/expert-opinions</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Delivers the Future of Intelligent Customer Experience for Utilities]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/future-intelligent-cx-for-utilities</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/future-intelligent-cx-for-utilities</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[An industry-first approach to CX for utilities allows for involving end customers in the energy transition journey. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>product/sap-commerce-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-customer-experience</category>
            <category>product/sap-emarsys-customer-engagement</category>
            <category>product/sap-sales-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-service-cloud</category>
            <category>industry/utilities</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Take: Biden and Big Oil, the New Frenemies]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/the-take-big-oil-biden-frenemies</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/the-take-big-oil-biden-frenemies</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Big Oil contributes to climate change while seeing record profits, but dependence on fuel keeps things complicated. Get SAP's take.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>content-type/perspective</category>
            <category>industry/oil-gas-energy</category>
            <category>news-tag/the-take</category>
            <category>industry/utilities</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Supports Utilities Across the EU to Enable Energy Transition]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/utilities-energy-transition-eu</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/utilities-energy-transition-eu</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP supports utilities in the energy transition across the EU to address the need for decarbonization along with volatile energy prices.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>industry/oil-gas-energy</category>
            <category>industry/utilities</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Take: Solar Power Generation Is Booming in the U.S.]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/the-take-utility-scale-solar-surge</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/the-take-utility-scale-solar-surge</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In the U.S., utility-scale solar is surging amid mandates to move to net-zero. Get SAP's take on its advantages and opportunities.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/perspective</category>
            <category>news-tag/renewable-energy</category>
            <category>news-tag/the-take</category>
            <category>industry/utilities</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How to Build – and Benefit from – a Supplier Diversity Program]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/how-to-build-and-benefit-from-a-supplier-diversity-program</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/how-to-build-and-benefit-from-a-supplier-diversity-program</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With leadership, data-driven metrics, and relationship-building skills, enterprises can glean value from their diverse supplier programs.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>industry/oil-gas-energy</category>
            <category>industry/utilities</category>
            <category>content-type/what-is</category>
            <category>stage/acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Buying and Selling Renewable Energy Enables Communities across Europe to Become More Independent and Sustainable]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/09/exnaton-buying-and-selling-renewable-energy</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/09/exnaton-buying-and-selling-renewable-energy</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Thanks to an innovative solution developed by Exnaton, you can take your surplus solar energy to the market. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_19c8daa63aba95e847020c46340b735287f3308a9.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_19c8daa63aba95e847020c46340b735287f3308a9.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_19c8daa63aba95e847020c46340b735287f3308a9.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Buying and Selling Renewable Energy Enables Communities across Europe to Become More Independent and Sustainable" src="./media_19c8daa63aba95e847020c46340b735287f3308a9.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="buying-and-selling-renewable-energy-enables-communities-across-europe-to-become-more-independent-and-sustainable">Buying and Selling Renewable Energy Enables Communities across Europe to Become More Independent and Sustainable</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Going to market is an age-old activity when it comes to buying and selling goods – from cash crops to cattle, everything under the sun has been traded in some form or another. Now, you can even take your surplus solar energy to the market, thanks to an innovative solution developed by a team of young Swiss entrepreneurs.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“There is no life on earth without the sun, and it’s there for everyone,” said Anselma Wörner, COO and one of the three cofounders of Exnaton, a Swiss company that develops software for communities trading renewable energy in local neighborhoods.</p>
  <p>Wörner was explaining how her company created a smart energy system at the recent <a href="https://tacinsights.eventsair.com/international-sap-conference-for-utilities-2022/conference-brochure">International Conference for Utilities, presented by SAP and TAC Events</a> in Munich, Germany. “We have a new generation of prosumers – people who consume and produce their own energy – who are using new connected technologies and renewable power like solar to exchange energy through the grid.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="become-a-sustainable-intelligent-enterprise-with-sap-solutions">Become a sustainable, intelligent enterprise with SAP solutions</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/sustainability.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="sun-powered">Sun Powered</h2>
  <p>Humans have always depended on the sun for light, heat, and food, and its all-encompassing power has influenced cultures and religions around the world. Although advances in technology have decreased our dependence, the importance of solar energy in our efforts to reduce our carbon footprint is a reminder that we still depend on it for survival. That’s why the cofounders picked the name <a href="https://www.exnaton.com/about-us">Exnaton</a> for their enterprise. Looking for a word that connects “energy” and “exchange,” they hit upon the Egyptian pharaoh Akhenaten (pronounced Echnaton) who raised the status of the sun above that of all other gods and created an early monotheism that briefly became a state religion.</p>
  <p>The goal of Exnaton is to help integrate prosumers into the grid. Currently, the legal framework is very complex, and there is no clear ROI for them. There are no feed-in tariffs or policy mechanisms designed to accelerate investment in renewable energy technologies by offering long-term contracts to renewable energy producers.</p>
  <p>“At the moment, there is no value for the community, and we want to change that,” said Wörner, who is responsible for fundraising, data science, and recruiting at Exnaton. “What most people don’t realize is that renewable energy is not always produced when it’s needed most. So, when it is available, prosumers should be able to sell their energy directly.”</p>
  <p>People who own solar panels could actually sell a lot of energy to other households, if only they had the means. Wörner and her team believe it should be as easy to sell to other consumers as it is to sell any other products on the market. “Prosumers are faced with fragmented solutions, complex regulations, and frustrating user experiences. What they need are simple solutions, trusted local providers, and proactive community and user groups,” she explained.</p>
  <h2 id="community-centric">Community Centric</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="thrive-in-a-time-of-energy-transition-with-utilities-management-systems-that-support-a-sustainable-future">Thrive in a time of energy transition with utilities management systems that support a sustainable future</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/energy-utilities.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Enter Exnaton’s EnergyCommunity software add-on for <a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/energy-utilities.html">SAP for Utilities</a> solutions, which won an <a href="https://www.sap.com/idea-place/sap-innovation-awards/submission-details-2022.html?idea_id=2903">SAP Innovation Award</a> in the Partner Paragon category together with Best Practice Consulting (BPC) and is now available on SAP Store. This user-centric extension enables utility companies to empower prosumers to buy and sell energy within their local communities and also track all relevant data.</p>
  <p>Here’s how it works. Any prosumers in the community can sell their solar energy to any consumers in the grid. The EnergyCommunity tracks their energy data and informs them exactly where the energy is coming from and how much CO2 it is generating. The utility company can easily bill these energy exchanges with their regular SAP billing system thanks to the integration offered by Exnaton in working with the SAP system integrator BPC. At the same time, the utility company can sell additional hardware installations to members of the community, making it an attractive option for all parties.</p>
  <p>“The EnergyCommunity makes it easy to exchange energy within the community. Participating in their local community creates a closer bond between people, and the platform provides a new customer channel for the utility company,” said the technology expert, who has a PhD in Information Systems. “At the end of the day, with Exnaton’s energy sharing software-as-a-service platform, energy suppliers can offer their customers more independence.”</p>
  <p>Exnaton is responding to the challenge faced by prosumers who currently have no possibility to sell their extra energy directly on the market and the one faced by utilities companies as they realize they must offer new models as they transition to renewables with a decentralized approach. A number of utility companies are already running the solution in communities across Germany, Austria, Luxemburg, and Switzerland, and the goal is to expand to other European countries where there is a strong regulatory framework. More importantly, the solution enables energy companies to equip their customers for a <a href="/topics/sustainability">sustainable future</a>.</p>
  <h2 id="future-focused">Future Focused</h2>
  <p>Over 733 million people on the planet still don’t have access to affordable, sustainable energy, which is why providing energy is goal seven on the list of the <a href="https://sdgs.un.org/goals">UN Sustainable Development Goals</a>. For Exnaton, goal seven is its core business, but at the same time, it is equally committed to goal 11, developing sustainable cities and communities; goal 12, enabling responsible production and consumption; and goal 13, taking urgent action to combat climate change and its impact.</p>
  <p>The good news, according to the recent <a href="https://ec.europa.eu/commission/presscorner/detail/en/ip_21_5554">State of the Energy Union</a> report, is that renewables overtook fossil fuels as the number one power source in the European Union for the first time in 2020. Renewables generate 38% of electricity, compared to 37% for fossil fuels. Also, at least two million people in the EU are already involved in more than 7,700 energy communities, and engagement is rising. Energy communities have also contributed up to 7% of nationally installed capacities of renewables, estimated at 6.3 GW.</p>
  <p>For Wörner and the team at Exnaton, producing energy where it is consumed decreases the dependence of the region on imported resources. Energy from the sun is practically limitless, and it more than covers the entire demand of the planet. With advances in technology and solutions like the EnergyCommunity, households and small businesses benefit from electricity powered by the sun, making renewable energy accessible and cost effective. What could be more natural, sensible, or sustainable?</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em><a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2022/08/31/buying-and-selling-their-own-renewable-energy-makes-prosumers--more-independent-and-sustainable/?sh=7aa6082d492f">This article was first published on forbes.com</a>.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/renewable-energy</category>
            <category>sap-award/sap-innovation-awards</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-store</category>
            <category>news-tag/un-sdgs</category>
            <category>industry/utilities</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Take: Hurricanes, Typhoons, Floods and Droughts -- Helping Water Utilities Address Extreme Weather]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/09/the-take-hurricanes-water-utilities-extreme-weather</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/09/the-take-hurricanes-water-utilities-extreme-weather</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Climate change is fueling extreme weather events across the planet. Get SAP's take on the impact and challenges for water utilities.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/perspective</category>
            <category>news-tag/the-take</category>
            <category>industry/utilities</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Netze BW: A Digital Companion for Service Technicians]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/09/netze-bw-digital-companion-for-service-technicians</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/09/netze-bw-digital-companion-for-service-technicians</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Netze BW and SAP developed an Apple Watch app so service technicians stay connected and safe while in the field. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-apphaus</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>sap-award/sap-innovation-awards</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>industry/utilities</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Smart Meters Expand Sustainable Horizon of Smart Cities]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/american-water-smart-meters-sustainable-horizon</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/american-water-smart-meters-sustainable-horizon</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Utilities like American Water crunch intelligent data to meet sustainability objectives and build trusted relationships with customers.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/data-analytics</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>industry/utilities</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How This Belgian Utility Delivers Clean Water across the Country]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/04/how-farys-delivers-clean-water-across-belgium</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/04/how-farys-delivers-clean-water-across-belgium</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Farys succeeds by adopting cutting-edge technology to drive socially responsible operations. Read to learn how its use of SAP BTP helps.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-integration-suite</category>
            <category>industry/utilities</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Introduces E-Mobility Solution for Electric Vehicle Fleet]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/02/sap-e-mobility-solution-ev-fleet</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/02/sap-e-mobility-solution-ev-fleet</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is applying its own e-mobility enterprise software to achieve the goal of an emissions-free car fleet by 2030.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f2e6d93c35becc557821fc7ed743ef1675c177c4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f2e6d93c35becc557821fc7ed743ef1675c177c4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1f2e6d93c35becc557821fc7ed743ef1675c177c4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Introduces E-Mobility Solution for Electric Vehicle Fleet" src="./media_1f2e6d93c35becc557821fc7ed743ef1675c177c4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-introduces-e-mobility-solution-for-electric-vehicle-fleet">SAP Introduces E-Mobility Solution for Electric Vehicle Fleet</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Beginning with Austria, SAP is applying its own e-mobility enterprise software to achieve the goal of an emissions-free car fleet by 2030.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The e-mobility transformation is underway, and chances are good that you are witnessing it on the streets of your own town. More and more consumers are choosing electric-powered transport over the internal combustion engine, and this despite supply chain disruptions due to the ongoing global pandemic.</p>
  <p>As battery range improves, charging infrastructure expands, and government incentives gain traction, the popularity of electric vehicles (EVs) <a href="https://www.rolandberger.com/en/Insights/Publications/E-Mobility-booms-despite-the-pandemic.html">appears to be taking off</a>. According to the Electric Vehicle World Sales Database, in 2021 all regions witnessed strong <a href="https://www.ev-volumes.com/">increases in EV sales</a>, with growth rates three to eight times higher than for the overall light-vehicle market. By 2026, <a href="https://www.bcg.com/publications/2021/why-evs-need-to-accelerate-their-market-penetration">according to a BCG study</a>, EVs will account for more than half of light vehicles sold globally.</p>
  <p>But there are still hurdles to overcome. Case-in-point is a charging infrastructure that is unevenly distributed and cannot keep up with demand. For example, Europe only has around <a href="https://www.reuters.com/world/us/five-facts-state-us-electric-vehicle-charging-network-2021-09-01/">62 public charging points</a> per 100,000 inhabitants, while the U.S. has roughly 37 charge points on the same per-capita basis. This is causing many potential EV converts to take a “wait-and-see” stance until they are assured of a viable charging infrastructure in their area.</p>
  <p>The successful transition to e-mobility will therefore require huge <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2021/09/19/how-to-meet-the-demand-of-ev-infrastructure-and-maintain-a-stable-grid/?guccounter=1&#x26;guce_referrer=aHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuZ29vZ2xlLmNvbS8&#x26;guce_referrer_sig=AQAAAGe8ekyPOciu-TGbgfCwhPudGlf8Zw3PXfJGKdyHhB11ULnWaRdby3cPGZwxCEF8Dl8sJsDyY_Ym5kzshncALcYunE5ZWHhAUemKukl2YWOUXTFgP0kZNiJ7eBSC-TrHLzziTH6sK5D5Zgm2s5A3HjOS5hUDIY3fay-No8XdcWse">investments in infrastructure</a> and related technologies. Industry experts agree that demand can only be satisfied through a <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2021/09/19/how-to-meet-the-demand-of-ev-infrastructure-and-maintain-a-stable-grid/">range of options,</a> which includes semi-public charging options like privately run charging stations, office and retail parking lots, home garages, and government-provided locations.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-accelerates-its-move-to-an-emission-free-car-fleet">SAP Accelerates Its Move to an Emission-Free Car Fleet</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/11/sap-accelerates-move-to-emission-free-car-fleet">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="sap-e-mobility-intelligent-charging-experience">SAP E-Mobility: Intelligent Charging Experience</h2>
  <p>Establishing a ubiquitous charge-point network is only one side of the coin. Charge-point providers will also need to provide consumers an easy, intelligent, and automated charging experience. Think of the one-click online-shopping experience consumers have become accustomed to and you get the idea. Achieving this level of service requires an intelligent software platform that is interconnected with other mobility-related business tasks and immediately recognizes the charging profile of your vehicle when you register at the charging point.</p>
  <p>In September 2021, <a href="/2021/09/sap-e-mobility-solution-sustainable-electric-vehicles">SAP launched</a> SAP E-Mobility, a standardized, cloud-based solution that provides a complete package that enables charge point operators to run their business efficiently and profitably.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_119ce1ae56b92d9cc66762d568b744f6093e77f3e.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_119ce1ae56b92d9cc66762d568b744f6093e77f3e.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_119ce1ae56b92d9cc66762d568b744f6093e77f3e.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Ulrich Scholl, VP and chief product manager for SAP E-Mobility" src="./media_119ce1ae56b92d9cc66762d568b744f6093e77f3e.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="600" height="600">
    </picture>“SAP E-Mobility is targeted at companies where mobility is the core business, such as logistics companies managing large vehicle fleets or mobility-as-a-service providers such as public transit, municipalities, and private ground transportation,” explains Ulrich Scholl, vice president and chief product manager for SAP E-Mobility.
  </p>
  <p>The enterprise-grade capabilities of SAP E-Mobility offer integration with other software solutions for expense reimbursement management, analytics, cost management, billing, and invoicing.</p>
  <h2 id="transition-to-an-emissions-free-car-fleet-by-2030">Transition to an Emissions-Free Car Fleet by 2030</h2>
  <p>Since 2009, SAP has made sustainability a key pillar of its corporate strategy and annually discloses its own sustainability performance in an <a href="https://www.sap.com/integrated-reports/2020/en.html">integrated report</a>. It is only logical, therefore, that SAP would use the business software it develops to increase its own operational efficiency. This is exactly what the company is doing with SAP E-Mobility.</p>
  <p>To make good on its promise to <a href="/2021/03/sap-carbon-neutrality-goal-2023">become carbon neutral</a> by 2023, SAP is applying the standard solution for its own electric vehicles, which comprise nearly one-fifth of its total fleet of around 27,000 company cars. Battery electric vehicles have been part of the company’s fleet since 2010, and their share is growing as part of the company’s <a href="/2021/11/sap-accelerates-move-to-emission-free-car-fleet">transition to an emissions-free fleet</a> by 2030. Coupled with the decision to go 100% electric by latest 2030 is a pledge to employees that the charging infrastructure at its facilities can meet growing demand.</p>
  <h2 id="e-vehicle-charging-infrastructure-flexibility-is-key">E-Vehicle Charging Infrastructure: Flexibility Is Key</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-targets-carbon-neutrality-by-2023">SAP Targets Carbon-Neutrality by 2023</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/03/sap-carbon-neutrality-goal-2023">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The SAP Austria office in Vienna was the company’s first corporate location to implement SAP E-Mobility. Currently one-quarter of the 400 company cars at SAP Austria are battery electric vehicles, with a significant transition to electric planned in the coming years.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_181ebe12abba9fc0664656385118b1ae2e67856e9.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_181ebe12abba9fc0664656385118b1ae2e67856e9.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_181ebe12abba9fc0664656385118b1ae2e67856e9.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Charging station at SAP in Vienna" src="./media_181ebe12abba9fc0664656385118b1ae2e67856e9.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2400" height="1500">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p><em>Photo courtesy of Michael Gruber.</em></p>
  <p>The charging infrastructure is operated by SAP’s facility management team in Vienna as part of its overall responsibility for asset management. Charging capacity is supplemented by a photovoltaic system that is also connected to the electricity grid.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c9b49f090338e3e88dd8377c9f429bfed5ee9eb0.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c9b49f090338e3e88dd8377c9f429bfed5ee9eb0.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1c9b49f090338e3e88dd8377c9f429bfed5ee9eb0.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Steffen Krautwasser, head of Global Car Fleet at SAP" src="./media_1c9b49f090338e3e88dd8377c9f429bfed5ee9eb0.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="600" height="600">
    </picture>“Flexibility is key to any enterprise charging concept because employees want to be able to charge their cars at work, public charging points, and private charging points at home,” says Steffen Krautwasser, head of Global Car Fleet at SAP. “The operation of our charging infrastructure in Austria is based on our strategic adoption road map of SAP E-Mobility and marks a critical milestone for adoption at our other locations.”
  </p>
  <p>Strong fluctuations in office use during the pandemic have shown the importance of flexibility. Close coordination between the fleet manager and facilities manager in creating an adaptable strategy is of the utmost importance. SAP E-Mobility enables flexible charging at work and supports reimbursement of private charging at home via <a href="https://www.concur.com/">SAP Concur</a> software for travel and expense management.</p>
  <h2 id="charge-point-sharing-for-sustainable-e-mobility-in-cities">Charge-Point Sharing for Sustainable E-Mobility in Cities</h2>
  <p>Some cities and communities are looking to bridge the current shortage in public charging capacity by opening private charging infrastructure to the public. “Since the number of public charging stations is increasing more slowly than demand, it is particularly relevant to open up semi-public charging points to as many users as possible,” says Scholl.</p>
  <p>This is where the versatility of SAP’s new solution comes through.</p>
  <p>“SAP E-Mobility gives us the ability to open up access and billing options to any user, and we can scale the system to new requirements rapidly as required,” says Robert Diglas, head of regional facilities for SAP in Austria, Switzerland, Central Europe, and Ukraine. “For example, the flexible solution will enable us to open up our charging points to customers and business partners if and when we decide to do so.”</p>
  <p>But SAP’s e-mobility vision extends well beyond the office parking lot. In 2021, the company started a co-innovation project with UnternehmerTUM, the city of Munich, and other partners from the mobility and energy industries. Together, they are developing new concepts based on <a href="https://mobility.unternehmertum.de/en/citizen-mobility-1">Citizen Mobility</a> to improve charge-point coverage in German cities.</p>
  <p>The integration of private charge points is just one focus area, according to Scholl. “With SAP E-Mobility, we are just beginning to help our customers and partners turn mobility as a service into a reality,” he says. “The collaboration with innovative partners and real-life testing by citizens has delivered innovative use cases and thoughtful insights into how sustainable e-mobility, as one mode of urban transportation, can work in the future.”</p>
  <p>Customers and partners can experience the SAP E-Mobility solution in action at the company’s <a href="https://blogs.sap.com/2021/12/15/sap-e-mobility-charging-infrastructure-lab-opens/">e-mobility lab locations</a> in Walldorf, Germany, and Bangalore, India.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/automotive</category>
            <category>product/sap-e-mobility</category>
            <category>industry/utilities</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Distributed Energy Resources (DER) and the Rise of the Prosumer]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/distributed-energy-resources-der-and-the-rise-of-the-prosumer</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/distributed-energy-resources-der-and-the-rise-of-the-prosumer</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Discover how distributed energy resources (DER), prosumers, and microgrid users are paving the way to a shift to renewable energy sources.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1420fa9c0cd21e919a3c0163f4f060ae6edabaf63.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1420fa9c0cd21e919a3c0163f4f060ae6edabaf63.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1420fa9c0cd21e919a3c0163f4f060ae6edabaf63.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="solar power panels" src="./media_1420fa9c0cd21e919a3c0163f4f060ae6edabaf63.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1044">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="distributed-energy-resources-der-and-the-rise-of-the-prosumer">Distributed energy resources (DER) and the rise of the prosumer</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>For over a century, utilities companies have accomplished marvels of engineering that have brought power to billions of people around the world. Without their enormous and complex undertakings, we could never be where we are today. However, modern utilities companies are under growing pressure to reduce carbon emissions and transition to renewable energy sources. So, for the first time in their long history, utilities are not the sole energy providers, as distributed energy resources (DERs) owned by third parties and prosumers are also producing power for the grid. Lower costs for photovoltaic (PV) solar equipment and other renewable energy assets, along with government incentives, are driving the growth of DERs in the energy sector.</p>
  <p>Leading the charge toward these new operational models are prosumers, also known as “active consumers.” As a whole, prosumers demand more from their utility service providers, including more control over on-demand services, improved self-sufficiency, and transparency on their own terms. While DER asset owners may at first seem like a competitor on the energy market, the most innovative and fearless utilities industry leaders not only accept that these changes are coming but are already seizing new opportunities for growth and industrial diversification.</p>
  <h2 id="what-is-der-and-how-is-it-changing-trends-in-the-utilities-industry">What is DER and how is it changing trends in the utilities industry?</h2>
  <p>Distributed energy resources include any assets used for generating, storing, or distributing power that exist outside the central utilities-run power grid. These can include assets like photovoltaic cells for solar energy, wind turbines, and local battery systems such as those on electric vehicles (EVs). Typically DER assets have a capacity less than 10 MW, are located at or near the consumer, and exist “behind-the-meter,” meaning they are on the consumer-side of power grid metering systems.</p>
  <p>These resources are in contrast to the traditional utilities-owned assets, including the remotely-located central power plants and high-voltage transmission lines necessary for large-scale electrical distribution. However, the ability for the owners of DER assets to bring additional resilience and flexibility to the electrical grid through the use of modern technologies makes them a valuable component in the market. For example, energy storage DERs like battery banks and connected EVs can be used to assist utilities companies in the event of a blackout by helping to kick-start the larger generators of the utilities companies so that they can more easily restore power to the whole network. Between the social and political pressures for a more energy-efficient future and the expectations for a more stable energy grid, DERs have the potential to optimize and bring better value to existing grid networks.</p>
  <h2 id="what-are-prosumers-and-how-do-they-work-with-utilities">What are prosumers and how do they work with utilities?</h2>
  <p>“Prosumer” is a <em>portmanteau</em> word combining “producer” and “consumer.” Energy prosumers typically remain connected to the central grid. However, they are also capable of producing and even storing energy – typically with photovoltaic solar panels and EV batteries. Depending on the amount of power generated, this energy can either be used to offset monthly bills or be sold back as surplus to utilities companies, or other energy distribution services. This model may be applied to both residential and commercial prosumers, with a growing number of businesses plugging their solar panels and EV fleets into the grid.</p>
  <p>Prosumers typically fall into three categories:</p>
  <ol>
    <li>Those who optimize self-consumption rates without a direct connection to the electrical grid</li>
    <li>Those who optimize self-consumption while remaining connected to the grid</li>
    <li>Those who provide flexibility services at the systems level (virtual power plants)</li>
  </ol>
  <p>Based upon current growth rates, DER assets that are connected to the main electrical grid (categories two and three above) are major stakeholders, while isolated prosumers are growing in numbers but are currently less significant to the overall energy model.</p>
  <p>DERs in the U.S. are expected to generate <a href="https://www.greentechmedia.com/articles/read/5-takeaways-on-the-future-of-the-u.s-distributed-energy-resources-market">387 GW of power</a> by 2050. Of these DERs, small-scale solar is one of the most common forms for prosumers, who are currently responsible for <a href="https://www.eia.gov/electricity/data/browser/#/topic/0?agg=2,0,1&#x26;fuel=vtvv&#x26;geo=g&#x26;sec=g&#x26;linechart=ELEC.GEN.DPV-US-99.A~ELEC.GEN.SUN-US-99.A~~~~~ELEC.GEN.TSN-US-99.A&#x26;columnchart=ELEC.GEN.ALL-US-99.A~ELEC.GEN.COW-US-99.A~ELEC.GEN.NG-US-99.A~ELEC.GEN.NUC-US-99.A~ELEC.GEN.HYC-US-99.A~ELEC.GEN.WND-US-99.A&#x26;">nearly one-third</a> of all solar energy produced in the U.S. For prosumers, most modern PV systems are generally established as a two-way connection up and down the existing grid, allowing them both consumer power from the grid when necessary and the ability to supply it to the grid when possible.</p>
  <p>Another model for prosumers includes microgrid and energy-storing prosumers who can fit into different categories depending on their specific setup. A university campus, for example, could establish a microgrid where it supplies and provides all of its power needs independent of the rest of the main power grid. Furthermore, microgrids can generally connect or disconnect from the main power grid as needed, offering the flexibility to consume from the main grid or to function as a virtual power plant, depending on capacities and needs.</p>
  <h2 id="how-do-behind-the-meter-microgrid-and-der-energy-models-work">How do behind-the-meter, microgrid, and DER energy models work?</h2>
  <p>DER encompasses more than just renewable energy production or prosumers; it refers to any kind of behind-the-meter or off-grid power generation and storage. A familiar model is that of a diesel backup generator or a series of backup battery cells for energy storage. These are traditional examples of DER, but with more advanced technology, new systems are constantly evolving.</p>
  <p>With the growth of the electric vehicle market, for example, it is projected that EV car companies will soon turn into virtual power stations and energy storage systems. The growth of artificial intelligence (AI) has made this more feasible, as smart charging/discharging can be used to charge at off-peak times. This gives the grid more flexibility and stability in terms of energy storage – and this kind of AI also facilitates lower charging costs for EV owners when coupled with variable rates on their electricity bill when they charge at off-peak hours.</p>
  <p>This increased adoption of AI systems also makes room for new energy startups looking to capture a share of the market. Competitive new startups and utilities giants alike are leveraging AI technologies to better address customer needs. AI is being used to forecast load requirements and generation capabilities, as well as for grid optimization and network planning, all of which can prevent outages, save money, and improve operational efficiency.</p>
  <h2 id="the-age-of-the-prosumer-challenges-and-benefits">The age of the prosumer: Challenges and benefits</h2>
  <p>Prosumerism and “smart,” data-driven business models are driving change that better meets consumer demands to economize, show more corporate transparency, and minimize environmental footprints. While these new models definitely present some challenges, they also provide an opportunity for existing utilities companies to integrate with this new breed of customers to provide win/win benefits across a more diverse range of product and service provisions.</p>
  <ul>
    <li>DER hardware, installation, and maintenance are all growing cheaper and more efficient over time, especially for PV systems. The price of PV systems has dropped by <a href="https://www.seia.org/solar-industry-research-data">more than 70% over the past decade</a>, which helps explain the exponential growth in these types of systems. In fact, with an average annual growth rate for installations in the <a href="https://www.seia.org/solar-industry-research-data">U.S. of 42% each year</a> over the past decade, it’s no surprise that solar represents the largest share of new electrical generating capacity for 2021. And of course, the improved performance and dropping costs of PV technologies benefit both the small prosumer and the utility-grade hardware buyer alike.</li>
    <li>Utilities companies can also support prosumers more directly by addressing their extensive equipment and technology needs by vertically integrating services like tech support and educational services for customers. This can be realized in the form of volume-discounted maintenance and installation of things like PV equipment, solar panels, and batteries.</li>
    <li>Finally, switching to alternative energy sources and DER assets also has the potential to reduce political and financial dependency and risk associated with the use of finite, geo-specific resources like coal and oil. This is particularly evident in light of the reduction in the <a href="https://www.irena.org/newsroom/pressreleases/2021/Jun/Majority-of-New-Renewables-Undercut-Cheapest-Fossil-Fuel-on-Cost">cost to produce renewable energy</a>.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>In other words, it may appear that prosumers and DERs represent a threat by taking a share of the energy market from major utilities providers. But in reality, the world’s energy consumption is only going to continue to grow, along with customer demands for transparency and sustainability. By seizing upon these trends and applying their formidable customer networks, extensive resources, and decades of experience, utilities providers can leverage and monetize DERs in order to improve their operational efficiency – and better serve their customers.</p>
  <h2 id="smart-data-driven-utilities-solutions-benefit-prosumers-and-utilities-alike">Smart, data-driven utilities solutions benefit prosumers and utilities alike</h2>
  <p>To handle the growing number of DERs being integrated into the power grid without becoming overwhelmed, utilities companies need to rely more heavily on smart utility infrastructures. These AI-powered solutions can improve data collection and management in order to inform operators of risk, inefficiency, and opportunities to optimize systems and grids. These can then be targeted predictively to augment the overall benefit that prosumers bring to the power grid, as well as the value they receive as contributors.</p>
  <p>And while there are emerging opportunities for energy sector businesses to engage with their consumer networks, low customer satisfaction with electrical utility companies in both Europe and North America continues to present an issue. With more players and energy distribution startups in the game, the expectations of consumers and prosumers alike are on the rise. The providers best positioned to succeed will be those that find ways to add meaningful support and value to this competitive and increasingly complex market.</p>
  <p>Through the use of smart, AI-powered utilities solutions, providers can manage, analyze, and leverage data across their consumer networks. This can allow utilities companies of the future to personalize customer experiences and energy savings plans, as well as develop <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/apm/what-is-predictive-maintenance.html">predictive insights</a> as to when and where customers will want to upgrade or augment their DER and prosumer assets and hardware.</p>
  <h2 id="alternative-energy-sources-and-utilities-sector-business-models">Alternative energy sources and utilities sector business models</h2>
  <p><a href="/research/passionates-how-they-are-changing-your-strategy">Growing social pressure</a>, political complexity, and disastrous climate events are fueling the drive to decarbonization. And, the desire for more efficient and cost-effective energy sources is motivating a new generation of more engaged consumers.</p>
  <p>For innovators and thought leaders in the energy generation and distribution sector, the future of their industry is highly dependent upon the provision of superior customer satisfaction. This means reshaping infrastructure and services around the customers of the future – specifically, the prosumers. If managed strategically, this can lead to a win/win for both the utilities sector <em>and</em> prosumers. To bring prosumer-pleasing solutions to life requires the ability to gather and understand a wide variety of disparate and complex data sets. And not just to collect this data and look at it in isolation, but to bring it to life with intelligent systems, <a href="/blogs/what-generative-ai-can-do-for-utilities">using AI</a> and machine learning tools to make it tell actionable stories, make insightful recommendations, and help inform fast, smart decisions in real time.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="explore-utilities-and-energy-management">Explore utilities and energy management</h3>
        <p>Learn how smart solutions and resources can help you diversify your business.</p>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/utilities.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>industry/oil-gas-energy</category>
            <category>industry/utilities</category>
            <category>content-type/best-practice-how-to-guide</category>
            <category>content-type/use-case</category>
            <category>stage/acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Smart Metering: Helping Customers Reduce Consumption]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/smart-metering-helping-customers-reduce-consumption</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/smart-metering-helping-customers-reduce-consumption</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Discover how smart meters, advanced metering infrastructure (AMI), and smart grids, give customers the data and support needed to reduce energy consumption.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_195e10339a1fc417336b3ee0b272a5b97956b1f70.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_195e10339a1fc417336b3ee0b272a5b97956b1f70.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_195e10339a1fc417336b3ee0b272a5b97956b1f70.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="smart meters gauging energy usage" src="./media_195e10339a1fc417336b3ee0b272a5b97956b1f70.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1044">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="smart-metering-helping-customers-reduce-consumption">Smart metering: Helping customers reduce consumption</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Global energy demand is on the rise – forecasted to increase almost 50% over the next three decades, according to the <a href="https://www.eia.gov/outlooks/ieo/">U.S. Energy Information Administration</a>. At the same time, extreme weather events are expected to continue, taxing the capabilities of an aging utilities infrastructure and unreliable energy grids. Consumer awareness about how and when to use energy is critical in order to optimize energy resources. Smart meters are at the heart of giving customers the information they need to reduce consumption, lower their bills, and support the environment.</p>
  <h2 id="what-is-a-smart-meter">What is a smart meter?</h2>
  <p>Smart meters are <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/what-is-iot.html">Internet of Things</a> (IoT) devices that attach to homes and businesses to track energy, water, and natural gas consumption. Whereas traditional meters only measure overall consumption, smart meters track exactly when and how much electricity – or water or gas – is used and transmit that information to utilities in near real time.</p>
  <p>Using <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/what-is-artificial-intelligence.html">artificial intelligence</a> (AI) and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/what-is-machine-learning.html">machine learning</a>, the data generated by smart meters can be parsed to determine how to lower operating costs, increase efficiency, and forecast demand. That ability to track usage, analyze it, and plan ahead could result in smart meters saving utility companies up to <a href="https://www.businessinsider.com/smart-meters-utilities-iot-energy-water?international=true&#x26;r=US&#x26;IR=T">US$157 billion by 2035</a>. Smart meters are also a gateway for consumers to become prosumers, allowing them to produce, store, and consume energy.</p>
  <p>Knowledge is power, and smart meter data benefits consumers by helping them:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Reduce energy consumption with detailed energy usage information that pinpoints energy-guzzling activities and appliances.</li>
    <li>Optimize energy usage by taking advantage of time-of-use tariffs and replacing outdated, power-hogging appliances with more energy-efficient ones.</li>
    <li>Manage their costs with notifications that alert them when their account hits a certain threshold or is higher than usual – to avoid an unexpectedly high bill at month end.</li>
  </ul>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div>With the ability to adapt and react to usage patterns and energy prices, [smart meters] could represent massive energy savings if applied to the broader population. Widespread implementation could contribute to a greener, more stable electric grid for everyone.</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div><a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/arielcohen/2020/08/31/get-smart-ai-and-the-energy-sector-revolution/?sh=5b70fe6b6044">Forbes</a></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="what-is-a-prosumer">What is a prosumer?</h2>
  <p>“Prosumer” is a <em>portmanteau</em> word combining “producer” and “consumer.” Energy prosumers typically remain connected to the central grid. However, they are also capable of producing and even storing energy – typically with photovoltaic solar panels and EV batteries. Depending on the amount of power generated, this energy can either be used to offset monthly bills or be sold back as surplus to utilities companies or other energy distribution services. This model may be applied to both residential and commercial prosumers, with a growing number of businesses plugging their solar panels and EV fleets into the grid.</p>
  <h2 id="smart-utilities-billing-supports-smart-engaged-customers">Smart utilities billing supports smart, engaged customers</h2>
  <p>With smart meters, power companies gain significant opportunities to improve the customer experience. Rather than relying on transactional communications around billing and payment, companies can use the data gathered from smart meters to drive communications that increase customer satisfaction, trust, and engagement.</p>
  <p>Companies can analyze this data and use it to send personalized recommendations to customers via text, e-mail, or as part of the billing process. For example, they can offer pool owners more efficient pool pumps, or encourage those with EVs to charge their vehicles when energy demands – and costs – are lower. This ability to personalize communications while helping customers save money and energy moves utilities from being seen as mere service providers to being valued energy partners. And at a time when there is rising competition in the energy sector, this opportunity to strengthen relationships with customers is paramount.</p>
  <p>Despite these benefits, smart meters haven’t quite come into their own yet. In the U.S., <a href="https://www.smart-energy.com/regional-news/north-america/75-of-us-households-have-smart-meters-report/">75% of homes</a> have smart meters, whereas about <a href="https://www.businessgreen.com/feature/4025086/getting-smart-meters-track-reach-half-britain-homes-businesses-2021">40% of UK</a> and <a href="https://www.smart-energy.com/industry-sectors/smart-meters/australia-new-directions-proposed-to-optimise-smart-meter-rollout/">fewer than 25%</a> of Australian households use them. As smart meter technology evolves, consumers will soon be able to set budgets and receive alerts via an app on their phone to let them know that they’ve left their stove on or have a water leak. They’ll also be able to integrate IoT devices such as smart thermostats or smart lighting into their home networks to better understand and manage their energy consumption. And with <a href="https://www.eia.gov/todayinenergy/detail.php?id=48396">renewable energy use growing</a>, consumers will be able to connect solar panels and batteries to the <a href="/resources/smart-grid-ai-in-energy-technologies">smart grid</a>, becoming prosumers. This will allow them to both store energy and sell excess power back to the grid – making them more active and engaged in the overall conversation around energy and the environment.</p>
  <h2 id="the-benefits-of-advanced-metering-infrastructure-ami">The benefits of advanced metering infrastructure (AMI)</h2>
  <p>AMI integrates smart meters, communication networks, and data management systems to provide two-way communications between utility providers and customers.</p>
  <p>The benefits of AMI include:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Increasing reliability and better managing outages by being able to pinpoint outage locations quickly and automatically alert utilities when the power comes back on</li>
    <li>Evaluating and managing energy consumption by providing accurate information about power usage and patterns that can be used to improve customer engagement</li>
    <li>Improving data quality and billing by providing accurate readings and alerting customers to usage anomalies as they happen rather than after the fact</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="smart-meters-and-ami-support-smart-grids">Smart meters and AMI support smart grids</h2>
  <p>Increasingly severe weather events have highlighted the weaknesses of existing power grids. And the global impact from flooding, forest fires, hurricanes, and heat is expected to continue to rise. As just one example, a recent McKinsey report on <a href="https://www.mckinsey.com/business-functions/sustainability/our-insights/climate-risk-and-response-physical-hazards-and-socioeconomic-impacts">climate risk and response</a> noted that in “Ho Chi Minh City, direct infrastructure asset damage from a 100-year flood could rise from about $200 to $300 million today, to $500 million to $1 billion in 2050.” That, coupled with <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2021/09/16/europes-energy-crisis-is-making-the-market-nervous-ahead-of-winter.html">rising energy prices</a>, calls for better overall energy management, which is where smart grids come into the picture.</p>
  <p>Smart grids, which integrate smart meters, renewable technologies, sensors, communications networks, and monitoring systems, allow utilities and their customers to exchange information and energy. This improves the grid’s reliability, quality, and efficiency, optimizing energy usage and catching and adjusting for small problems before they balloon into big issues.</p>
  <p>Smart grids also have self-healing, predictive capabilities. They can identify faults, isolate them, and react to them, reconfiguring energy flow around affected areas to protect the broader grid. They also can access weather and energy usage forecasts to adjust for upcoming situations. Using <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/cloud-analytics/what-is-predictive-analytics.html">predictive analytics</a>, they can also anticipate future maintenance and system management needs.</p>
  <h2 id="can-smart-metering-and-smart-grids-help-eliminate-overloads">Can smart metering and smart grids help eliminate overloads?</h2>
  <p>The short answer is “yes.” The connected, communicative nature of smart meters and smart grids allows for a much more nuanced response to everyday energy use, as well as to overloads and emergencies. Smart grids use edge computing, 5G, IoT, cloud, advanced streaming analytics, and AI to assess grid conditions in real time and rapidly adapt and respond to ever-changing demands. Customers can support overload management by reducing their consumption in response to current conditions.</p>
  <p>For example, they can respond to alerts and notifications via phone apps that advise them to:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Reduce their energy use or turn off non-essential appliances and devices in the face of impending brownouts or outages.</li>
    <li>Turn heating systems down in cold snaps and reduce AC usage in heat waves to decrease the surge in demand and lessen the risk of blackouts.</li>
    <li>Save money by charging EVs and running washing machines, dryers, dishwashers, or other appliances when their power company’s time-of-use tariffs are lower.</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="smart-meter-technologies-drive-greener-cleaner-smarter-energy-solutions">Smart meter technologies drive greener, cleaner, smarter, energy solutions</h2>
  <p>Energy solutions like smart metering and smart grids have many eco-friendly benefits including the reduction in diesel and gas consumption, as utilities would no longer need to dispatch meter readers in trucks.</p>
  <p>Smart meters can support:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>The integration of renewables into smart grids, reducing dependency on gas, nuclear, and coal-fired power</li>
    <li>Smart technology that can turn on and off heat pumps and other appliances to align usage with supply and demand without negatively impacting homeowners</li>
    <li>Encouraging consumers to use renewable energy when the supply is robust so that excess demand doesn’t need to be met by carbon-based energy sources</li>
    <li>Supporting local energy, which is cleaner energy – a decentralized smart grid will be able to connect microgrids where prosumers sell excess solar or wind energy back to utilities or even trade it with their neighbors</li>
    <li>Evolving smart cities. While cities only cover 2% of the Earth’s surface, <a href="https://unhabitat.org/topic/climate-change">UN research shows</a> that they account for more than 60% of greenhouse gas emissions and use 78% of the Earths’ energy</li>
  </ul>
  <p>But greener energy isn’t just about the power that gets used; it’s also about the energy that’s wasted – about two-thirds <a href="https://cleantechnica.com/2020/01/16/how-much-energy-does-the-us-consume-where-does-it-come-from-pew-research/">of all energy</a> in the U.S. annually. Smart meters can pinpoint energy wasted by not turning off lights or leaving devices on standby to help eliminate wastage. Because the cleanest energy is energy that isn’t used at all.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="explore-smart-metering-solutions">Explore Smart Metering solutions</h3>
        <p>Monitor, manage, and forecast energy consumption with analytics in real time.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/utilities.html#smart-metering">Learn more</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>core-topic/sustainable-business-operations</category>
            <category>industry/oil-gas-energy</category>
            <category>industry/utilities</category>
            <category>content-type/what-is</category>
            <category>content-type/use-case</category>
            <category>stage/acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Smart Grid: How AI is Powering Today’s Energy Technologies]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/smart-grid-ai-in-energy-technologies</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/smart-grid-ai-in-energy-technologies</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Discover how AI and Big Data analytics are powering smart grid solutions and modernizing energy technologies and customer service in the utilities sector.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10d6a8fe9ef30ae8bceecbee6d9c4632359c5f356.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10d6a8fe9ef30ae8bceecbee6d9c4632359c5f356.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_10d6a8fe9ef30ae8bceecbee6d9c4632359c5f356.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Wind turbines" src="./media_10d6a8fe9ef30ae8bceecbee6d9c4632359c5f356.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1044">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="the-smart-grid-how-ai-is-powering-todays-energy-technologies">The smart grid: How AI is powering today’s energy technologies</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Like oxygen, the power grid is essential to modern life but is not always top of mind – until problems occur. Today, aging grid infrastructure is taking a beating from severe weather events around the world, resulting in power outages that threaten health, safety, and economic activity. At the same time, a number of other factors are also putting pressure on century-old grids. The way that energy is produced is rapidly changing – more wind and solar, less coal and fossil fuel. This shift requires new processes and ways of managing. The “who” is also shifting, with energy now produced not only by the major energy companies, but also by a plethora of new competitors and prosumers (consumers who produce energy).</p>
  <p>And not only is the natural world changing fast, but the technological world is advancing at a gallop as well. Cloud-connected artificial intelligence (AI) technologies like machine learning, data analytics, and the Internet of Things (IoT) are driving the advancement of smart grids capable of managing far more complex power generation and distribution. These technologies herald significant opportunity for those in the complex energy ecosystem that are able to harness them.</p>
  <h2 id="what-is-a-prosumer">What is a prosumer?</h2>
  <p>Prosumer is a <em>portmanteau</em> word combining “producer” and “consumer.” Energy prosumers typically remain connected to the central grid. However, they are also capable of producing and even storing energy – typically with photovoltaic solar panels and EV batteries.</p>
  <p>Depending on the amount of power generated, this energy can either be used to offset monthly bills or be sold back as surplus to utilities companies or other energy distribution services. This model may be applied to both residential and commercial prosumers, with a growing number of businesses plugging their solar panels and EV fleets into the grid.</p>
  <h2 id="what-is-a-smart-grid">What is a smart grid?</h2>
  <p>A smart grid is a network that integrates energy distribution and digital communication technology in a two-way flow of electricity and data. This enables utility companies to optimize the generation, transmission, and distribution of electricity. And it also allows consumers to benefit from the stories all that data is telling – helping them to better understand the energy they use and even the energy they produce and store through things like solar panels and EV batteries.</p>
  <h2 id="what-is-the-difference-between-the-traditional-grid-and-a-smart-grid">What is the difference between the traditional grid and a smart grid?</h2>
  <p>The main difference between <a href="https://electricalacademia.com/electric-power/difference-traditional-power-grid-smart-grid/">traditional systems and smart grids</a> lies in the ability to exchange information in both directions across the network, from utility companies to consumers and vice versa. Some of the top features that differentiate smart grids include:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Technology:</strong> <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/what-is-artificial-intelligence.html">AI</a>, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/what-is-cloud-computing.html">cloud</a>, and digital technologies allow all the devices and assets within the grid to communicate, supporting better control and self-regulation.</li>
    <li><strong>Distribution:</strong> Energy generated by prosumers and other renewable energy sources – such as solar or wind – can be intermittent and uneven. Smart grid technologies help to coordinate, store, and distribute power from such sources into a steady and reliable stream.</li>
    <li><strong>Generation:</strong> <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/cloud-analytics/what-is-predictive-analytics.html">Predictive analytics</a> in smart systems means that high-demand strains can be forecasted and distributed to multiple plants and substations.</li>
    <li><strong>Sensors:</strong> <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/what-is-iot.html">IoT</a> sensors across the network can help detect risk early on, redistributing power to decrease outages and help balance loads without direct intervention by operators.</li>
    <li><strong>Self-repair and predictive maintenance:</strong> Sensors can also be used to detect mechanical problems and do simple troubleshooting and repairs, notifying technicians only when necessary – <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/apm/what-is-predictive-maintenance.html">before anything actually breaks down</a>.</li>
    <li><strong>Customer choice:</strong> More energy suppliers, cooperatives, and micro-generators can join the grid, allowing consumers to have more choice in how they receive energy.</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="applications-of-ai-in-smart-energy-solutions-the-utilities-sector-perspective">Applications of AI in smart energy solutions: The utilities sector perspective</h2>
  <p>Artificial Intelligence is the driving “intelligent agent” behind smart grids – evaluating the environment and taking actions to maximize a given goal. AI is fundamental to the integration of renewable energy, the stabilization of energy networks, and the reduction of financial risks associated with instability in the infrastructure.</p>
  <p>For instance, the self-learning, adaptability, and calculation capabilities of AI have significant potential to address the intermittent nature of renewable energy. An imbalance in peaks of production and consumption are often represented through “<a href="https://www.energy.gov/eere/articles/confronting-duck-curve-how-address-over-generation-solar-energy">the duck curve</a>” and can make these sources of energy difficult to control. The use of <a href="https://iopscience.iop.org/article/10.1088/1755-1315/510/2/022012/pdf#:~:text=Smart%20grid%20is%20a%20highly,series%20of%20value%2Dadded%20services.">AI in smart grids</a> will help address this challenge by rebalancing inequity between production and consumption loads.</p>
  <p>Smart grid technologies help to make utilities sector activities more transparent and competitive. Some of the applications of AI and machine learning in smart grids include:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Agility and resilience:</strong> When renewable energy is generated by new partners like cooperatives and prosumers, it is often intermittent and variable. Sensors and automation can be used to identify parts of the grid that are vulnerable and respond with automated rerouting – storing surplus energy during peak generation times and rerouting it during gaps in the flow.</li>
    <li><strong>More precise forecasting:</strong> The utilities sector faces widespread price variability due to changes in consumption. <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/cloud-analytics/what-is-predictive-analytics.html">Predictive analytics</a> models can be used to more reliably predict power loads and renewable energy generation. By combining data from advanced metering infrastructure (AMI) with AI, predictions are more accurate than traditional approaches.</li>
    <li><strong>More sophisticated outage alerts:</strong> The network of sensors, meters, and actuators in a smart grid can give a “<a href="https://www.smartgrid.gov/document/last_gasp_message_outage_notification_v30">last gasp</a>” short signal transmission, including time and date, to indicate a <a href="https://skyvisionsolutions.files.wordpress.com/2015/04/sgcc-outage-restoration-fact-sheet.pdf">loss in power</a> due to partial or complete outages. In addition, the predictive capabilities of AI and the real-time data of <a href="/resources/smart-metering-helping-customers-reduce-consumption">smart meters</a> can notify operators of outages right before they happen. These systems can even differentiate between individual, street, and zonal outages.</li>
    <li><strong>Optimized power yield:</strong> The use of AI-powered sensor networks in generation stages can also be used to optimize power output. In a similar way, solar energy also benefits from AI tools to increase productivity by predicting solar radiation.</li>
    <li><strong>Improved automated switching:</strong> The ability of AI tools to predict grid imbalances and to differentiate between a brief power interruption and a full-on outage will soon allow switching protocols to be automated. This will allow utility companies to reroute energy or isolate affected areas before severe damages occur or the outage expands to other areas. These tools are a line of defense that ensures the safety of the essential equipment used to isolate and repair faults.</li>
    <li><strong>More flexible demand-side management (DSM):</strong> Peaks in energy demand put utility companies under great strain. Using AI and smart meters in homes and offices can help with scheduling, planning, executing, and monitoring changes in energy demand to ensure that providers can meet them. Doing this can have a major impact on power usage, as shown by the U.S. <a href="https://www.ferc.gov/sites/default/files/2020-05/06-09-demand-response_1.pdf">Federal Energy Regulatory Commission</a>, which found that peak loads can be reduced by up to 150 GW through demand management. Similarly, the <a href="https://www.epri.com/research/products/1016987">Electric Power Research Institute (EPRI)</a> has estimated these smart tools could lead to a 175 GW reduction in summer energy peaks by 2030.</li>
    <li><strong>Improved security:</strong> <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/financial-management/what-is-cybersecurity.html">Cybersecurity</a> is a key concern for all business sectors. And the increasing number and complexity of <a href="https://www.energy.gov/articles/securing-americas-energy-infrastructure-cyber-threats">cyberattack</a> strategies presents a risk to both existing and new electrical grids. AI tools can help reduce this risk by detecting network attack features, malware, and intrusion and by providing network security protection for power systems. In addition, other technologies, like <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/what-is-blockchain.html">blockchain</a>, can provide transparent, tamper-proof, and secure systems that enable novel business solutions, especially when combined with smart contracts.</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="applications-of-ai-in-smart-energy-solutions-the-consumer-perspective">Applications of AI in smart energy solutions: The consumer perspective</h2>
  <p>Recent surveys from the <a href="https://www.ofgem.gov.uk/publications/consumer-survey-2020-update-consumer-engagement-energy">UK</a> and <a href="https://www.utilitydive.com/news/three-things-consumers-want-from-electricity-providers-1/520821/">U.S.</a> show less-than-great customer attitudes toward utility companies. With the rise in energy suppliers and prosumers, utilities companies will need to leverage smart solutions to help nurture better customer engagement and satisfaction. Below are some of the ways smart grid technologies can help to improve customer satisfaction:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Lower costs:</strong> AI-powered smart grid management and smart metering allow customers to get hourly assessments of their power usage – helping them to see not only when and where they use the most energy but offering personalized tips and suggestions for optimizing their typical daily routines to lower usage during peak times. It also helps prosumers manage energy production which can be sold back to the grid to reduce costs even further.</li>
    <li><strong>Improved sustainability and transparency:</strong> Smart grid data can help customers become more aware of where their energy is coming from, increasing their engagement and helping to <a href="https://www.utilitydive.com/news/ai-in-the-utility-industry/543876/">democratize the grid</a>. This can help to give them new <a href="https://www.nrel.gov/docs/fy11osti/50988.pdf">perspectives</a> on energy provision and the ability to choose more sustainable options.</li>
    <li><strong>Fewer outages:</strong> As mentioned, AI tools can help reduce the number of outages and mitigate their impact both for residential and commercial customers. This means an increase in security and confidence for consumers – especially as weather events and record temperatures bring fears of brownouts and other disruptions.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>Recently, a UK distribution system operator announced a pilot project to use smart meter data to help consumers improve energy management, optimize network loads, and reduce carbon emissions. The trial could save customers millions of pounds and potentially reduce millions of tons of greenhouse gas emissions from the UK’s annual carbon footprint. This is just one example of the potential benefits of smart grids for customers and the environment.</p>
  <h2 id="big-data-in-energy-why-it-matters">Big Data in energy: Why it matters</h2>
  <p>From the point of view of both customers and utilities companies alike, it’s not simply the <em>ability</em> of these technologies to gather and manage large and disparate amounts of <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/what-is-big-data.html">Big Data</a> that matters – it’s the ability to leverage and understand all that data and use it to optimize power usage and inform operations. Big Data is key to helping:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Better integrate renewable and alternative power in utilities companies by learning to predict and manage intermittence, and balance a myriad of small inputs from prosumer players.</li>
    <li>Protect consumers by anticipating outages and redirecting resources in a fraction of a second – rather than after everything has gone down.</li>
    <li>Save money for companies and consumers alike by digitally learning from past activities and using that intel to better manage and automate day-to-day activities.</li>
    <li>Provide fast, actionable insights that let utilities companies make confident and quick decisions in an increasingly competitive environment.</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="how-todays-utilities-industry-is-preparing-for-the-smart-grid-of-the-future">How today’s utilities industry is preparing for the smart grid of the future</h2>
  <p>There is no question that the future of energy is moving toward more decentralized, flexible, and sustainable power provision. But we are talking about a global industry that is over a century old – and often must rely upon infrastructures from nearly that long ago to serve billions of people and their rapidly changing demands.</p>
  <p>Other challenges include complex regulatory changes, the rise of prosumers, and new startups emerging in deregulated regions. Like any journey of business and <a href="/resources/what-is-digital-transformation">digital transformation</a>, the move to smarter grid management starts with a few cautious steps before breaking into a run. Utilities sector technologies are undoubtedly powering and enabling the evolution of this sector. However, for meaningful change to occur, utilities companies will need establish strong communication, customer engagement, and change management plans including:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Communicating a vision of the smart grid and aligning teams and stakeholders around it</li>
    <li>Strengthening consumer education about the changes and opportunities to come</li>
    <li>Providing win/win motivation for consumers, prosumers, and potential distribution partners</li>
    <li>Developing metrics to monitor progress in the implementation and effectiveness of smart grids</li>
    <li>Keeping the customer experience and customer retention in mind, given the additional competition and decentralization of a smart energy market</li>
  </ul>
  <p>The first step on the journey is to communicate with team leaders and subject specialists across your business, to break down silo walls and find the wealth of information often hidden within. Then, look at how you can implement smart technologies to drive your business forward.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="explore-smart-utilities-solutions">Explore smart utilities solutions</h3>
        <p>Transform the most important facets of your business, support energy transition.</p>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/utilities.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>core-topic/sustainable-business-operations</category>
            <category>industry/oil-gas-energy</category>
            <category>industry/utilities</category>
            <category>content-type/what-is</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How a European Utilities Company Makes Maintenance More Efficient, Transparent, and Cost-Effective]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/european-utilities-company-retipiu-makes-maintenance-efficient-transparent-cost-effective</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/european-utilities-company-retipiu-makes-maintenance-efficient-transparent-cost-effective</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Read to learn how Retipiù is increasing productivity and improving customer service with smart asset maintenance using SAP solutions.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16f49651583a397641725139ac5d57886a78fc80f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16f49651583a397641725139ac5d57886a78fc80f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_16f49651583a397641725139ac5d57886a78fc80f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="How a European Utilities Company Makes Maintenance More Efficient, Transparent, and Cost-Effective" src="./media_16f49651583a397641725139ac5d57886a78fc80f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="how-a-european-utilities-company-makes-maintenance-more-efficient-transparent-and-cost-effective">How a European Utilities Company Makes Maintenance More Efficient, Transparent, and Cost-Effective</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>The Italian natural gas and electricity provider RetiPiù S.r.l. is in charge of 2,900 kilometers of gas and electricity networks that serve homes, businesses, and public spaces in 25 towns across the northern Italian province of Monza and Brianza.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="maximize-asset-health-and-performance-with-sap-intelligent-asset-management-software">Maximize asset health and performance with SAP Intelligent Asset Management software</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/supply-chain-management/asset-management-eam.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="managing-ever-complex-asset-networks-at-minimum-cost">Managing Ever Complex Asset Networks at Minimum Cost</h2>
  <p>As these networks grow and become more complex, RetiPiù must ensure safety and reliability through daily maintenance performed by its field workers. It is also crucial for them to quickly identify critical network events and efficiently prioritize, schedule, and track field-service assignments and maintenance activities.</p>
  <p>But disparate asset management systems made it hard to prioritize and schedule maintenance calls. In addition, they were not integrated with the company’s core enterprise resource planning (ERP) system.</p>
  <h2 id="moving-from-reactive-to-predictive-maintenance">Moving from Reactive to Predictive Maintenance</h2>
  <p>To increase efficiency and optimize resources, RetiPiù looked to move from a reactive to a predictive maintenance model. The goal was to understand critical events as early as possible, track and trace issues from alert to resolution, get better visibility into maintenance schedules and work-order status, and use that information to better manage maintenance across the network.</p>
  <p>To meet these goals, RetiPiù required a <strong>unified <a href="/topics/intelligent-asset-management">intelligent asset maintenance</a> system</strong> that workers could access from the field and that was integrated with its intelligent ERP software.</p>
  <h2 id="one-central-asset-intelligence-system-to-speed-up-maintenance-cycles-and-lower-costs">One Central Asset Intelligence System to Speed up Maintenance Cycles and Lower Costs</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-the-industry-40-intelligent-assets-report">Read the Industry 4.0 Intelligent Assets Report</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/dg/intelligent-assets/index.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As its utilities networks continue to grow, RetiPiù S.r.l. deployed <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/s4hana-erp.html">SAP S/4HANA</a> to help improve data quality and access for engineers and back-office teams. Building on that digital transformation, it then added the SAP Enterprise Asset Management solution to help configure digital twins for equipment and activate predictive models respectively. These algorithms help assess and prioritize maintenance requirements and optimize resources. The company leverages the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/iot-data-services.html">SAP Internet of Things (SAP IoT)</a> solution to gather detailed sensor data from across the network assets to share information via mobile applications with field technicians, who get information and update the status of work orders in real time.</p>
  <h2 id="increasing-productivity-and-improving-customer-service-with-smarter-asset-maintenance">Increasing Productivity and Improving Customer Service with Smarter Asset Maintenance</h2>
  <p>The system currently supports thousands of pieces of equipment. In addition to making maintenance simpler and more efficient, asset and maintenance data – including cost data – are immediately available for analysis in <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/s4hana-erp.html">SAP S/4HANA</a>. As a public utility, the real beneficiaries are RetiPiù customers that now have faster activation service. And in addition, RetiPiù benefits by being rewarded by the Italian government for its continually reliable service.</p>
  <p>The most <strong>striking benefits</strong> the utilities company gained are:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>100% increase in assets that can be managed on the network – from 12,000 to 24,000 pieces of equipment</li>
    <li>50% reduction in maintenance cost</li>
    <li>15%-20% less time needed to activate new gas customers</li>
    <li>Increased efficiency and resource optimization</li>
    <li>Improved prioritization of field-service assignments and maintenance tasks</li>
    <li>Improved field operations effectiveness through mobile system access to maintenance staff</li>
    <li>One single platform to manage data and analytics for all assets – creating a fully integrated and transparent maintenance process from order to the field and back</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="real-time-data-transfer-from-technician-mobile-apps-to-back-end-erp-systems">Real-Time Data Transfer from Technician Mobile Apps to Back-End ERP Systems</h2>
  <p>“In choosing an intelligent, predictive maintenance solution, integration with our core ERP systems was key. With <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/s4hana-erp.html">SAP S/4HANA</a> and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/supply-chain-management/asset-management-eam.html">SAP Intelligent Asset Management</a>, we have <strong>one unified system</strong> that provides everyone the visibility they need to work efficiently and effectively,” says Massimo De Filippi, director of Technical and Information Services and Design at RetiPiù S.r.l.</p>
  <p>He continues: “This project has allowed RetiPiù to ensure service continuity and avoid shutdowns. We can provide quality service while also reducing costs. We are a public company, so the ultimate benefit is for the citizens.”</p>
  <p>“By being able to access data and reports in real time, field engineers can intervene promptly whenever issues arise, improving the customer experience and strengthening our reputation as a trusted energy provider,” says Mario Carlo Borgotti, managing director of RetiPiù.</p>
  <p>In regard to future plans and after being live with the gas network, RetiPiù now has a template for rolling out intelligent asset management and predictive maintenance to its electricity and public lighting networks. As the next step, it will enable simulation of maintenance requirements for new assets that have yet to be added and include geolocation services for route optimization.</p>
  <p>To learn more about how to enable intelligent asset management processes, <a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/dg/intelligent-assets/index.html">download the report</a>, “The Building Blocks of Industry 4.0 with Intelligent Assets.”</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Karin Fent is senior director of Global Customer Success Digital Supply Chain at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/asset-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/enterprise-asset-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>industry/utilities</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Energy Transition: Utilities Take Center Stage]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/resources/energy-transition</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/resources/energy-transition</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn how clean energy transition and decarbonization are driving change in the energy and utilities sectors and leading toward a carbon-neutral future.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ee8c9b53a1a7ad387289bd543e597fb3a6da830e.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ee8c9b53a1a7ad387289bd543e597fb3a6da830e.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1ee8c9b53a1a7ad387289bd543e597fb3a6da830e.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Wind turbines on a hill" src="./media_1ee8c9b53a1a7ad387289bd543e597fb3a6da830e.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1044">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="energy-transition-utilities-take-center-stage">Energy transition: Utilities take center stage</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The <a href="https://data.worldbank.org/indicator/EG.ELC.ACCS.ZS">World Bank</a> tells us that the current global electrification rate is sitting at about 90% and has risen by over 15% in just 20 years. It is utility companies around the globe that are delivering that energy and – no strangers to disruption and change – they have been keeping our power flowing for well over a century. But as the post-pandemic dust begins to settle, key players in the utilities industry are taking a good look around and realizing that they’re operating in a very different landscape than ever before. If the energy sector wishes to meet its net-zero goals and still remain profitable, it will mean addressing new players and practices and responding to rapidly changing customer demands and behaviors.</p>
  <p>When it comes to clean energy transition, the world will be looking to the utilities sector for leadership and technological innovation as we collectively strive for decarbonization.</p>
  <h2 id="what-is-energy-transition">What is energy transition?</h2>
  <p>Energy transition refers to the shift from fossil-based systems of energy production and consumption – including oil, natural gas, and coal – to renewable energy sources such as wind and solar. The shift also encompasses the trend toward a connected network of distributed energy sources and away from traditionally centralized utilities and single sources of power.</p>
  <h2 id="decarbonization-and-the-economic-shift-toward-sustainable-energy">Decarbonization and the economic shift toward sustainable energy</h2>
  <p>In their extensive <a href="https://www.goldmansachs.com/insights/pages/gs-research/carbonomics-green-engine-of-economic-recovery-f/report.pdf">Carbonomics</a> report, Goldman Sachs notes that, in 2021, spending on renewable energy projects is predicted to surpass upstream oil and gas spending for the first time in history. Part of the reason these projects are so attractive is that the cost of delivering renewable energy is rapidly decreasing. A recent International Renewable Energy Agency (IRENA) <a href="https://www.irena.org/-/media/Files/IRENA/Agency/Publication/2020/Jun/IRENA_Power_Generation_Costs_2019.pdf">report</a> takes a look at the global weighted average levelized cost of electricity (LCOE) of renewable energy projects and finds that in the past 10 years “utility-scale solar photovoltaics (PV) fell 82%; concentrated solar power (CSP) by 47%; onshore wind by 39%; and offshore wind down more than 29%.”</p>
  <p>The report goes on to state that oil and gas spending is down more than 60% from 2014 and that the global oil reserve life (ratio of oil reserves to oil production) has also dropped significantly. In response to these trends, <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/arielcohen/2020/11/17/goldman-sachs-renewable-power-will-become-the-largest-area-of-spending-in-the-energy-industry-in-2021/?sh=4c2c2e4563eb">Forbes</a> tells us that in the past year “many private investment banks, including Deutsche Bank, Morgan Stanley MS, and Citi Bank, have also announced their strategies to reduce their exposure to the oil and gas sector. Additionally, big private equity firms are now increasingly putting their investments into decarbonization technologies.”</p>
  <p>At the moment, utilities companies find themselves in a time of increased investor appetite for renewables projects and continually lowering costs of related infrastructure and start-up costs.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sustainability-and-business-performance">Sustainability and business performance</h3>
        <p>Explore how sustainability is affecting competitiveness and profits.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="/research/environmental-sustainability-affects-competitiveness">Read the report</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="utility-scale-renewable-energy-sources-and-technologies">Utility-scale renewable energy sources and technologies</h2>
  <p>In the long-term quest to eliminate fossil fuel dependency, there are several arenas of human activity that will need to be decarbonized over time including transport, heavy industry, manufacturing, and the built environment. However, as the provider of energy to most of those other industries, the <a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/utilities.html">utilities sector</a> is on point for clean energy transition initiatives.</p>
  <h2 id="what-is-utility-scale">What is utility-scale?</h2>
  <p>We are seeing growing networks of smaller, more widely scattered energy generators and distributors, as well as greater overall demand for renewable energy sources like solar and wind.</p>
  <p>The term “utility-scale” serves as a yardstick by which we measure the capacity of all these resources. To be considered utility-scale, an energy system or network should be able to generate at least 10 megawatts or more – with reliability and consistency.</p>
  <p>Below are some of the most common renewable energy sources and the pros and cons their utility-scale implementation may present.</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Solar energy:</strong> Traditional solar modules use concentrating solar power (CSP) technologies and are limited due to their functional need for direct sunlight. However, the technologies around photovoltaic (PV) solar modules (that can use both direct and diffuse sunlight) have been advancing at a rapid pace. And their cost has been declining at an equally speedy rate, seeing the price of crystalline silicon PV modules drop by over <a href="https://www.irena.org/costs/Power-Generation-Costs/Solar-Power">80% since 2010</a>. When you factor in the $0.00 price of sunshine and the steadily lowering balance of system (BoS) costs, solar is becoming an increasingly profitable option within the utilities industry.</li>
    <li><strong>Hydropower:</strong> This is, of course, the backbone of energy production for many of the world’s largest utilities sector players. Hydroelectric power is clean, abundant, and pairs well with other renewable energy sources to fill intermittency gaps. Problem is: the building of utilities-grade dams involves engineering projects of epic cost and proportion. It also typically involves contentious land reclamation efforts and the potential for disasters of equally epic proportion if anything should ever fail or burst. In other words, if the infrastructure already exists, hydropower is great for the utilities industry. But if it doesn’t, it can be unfeasible to develop.</li>
    <li><strong>Wind energy:</strong> Since 2010, the cost of wind turbines has lowered significantly, with <a href="https://www.irena.org/costs/Power-Generation-Costs/Wind-Power">IRENA</a> predicting an ongoing drop in both set-up and O&#x26;M costs over the next 10 years. Additionally, improvements in turbine technology have led to larger rotor diameters and higher hub heights, meaning that more energy can be harvested from the same wind speeds and space allocation. Wind power projects often elicit complaints of noise and wildlife threat, but they can also result in homegrown profits for landowners so they are also seen as a good opportunity for regional economic growth. A major challenge for the utilities sector is the unreliability of wind. Due to its intermittency, wind power must either be stored in <a href="/blogs/future-batteries-save-civilization">high-capacity batteries</a> or paired with more reliable (often fossil-based) energy sources to sustain the grid during times of low generation. Nonetheless, the energy sector’s reliance on wind power has risen by about <a href="https://www.nationalgeographic.com/environment/article/wind-power">25% per year</a> for the past decade.</li>
    <li><strong>Geothermal energy:</strong> Where available, this can be a highly efficient source of energy due to its “always-on” nature. And compared to wind or solar farms, it has a relatively small geographic footprint. But from the point of view of the utilities sector, this power source is limited due to the price of establishing geothermal power infrastructures and the limited availability of these sources around the world. Furthermore, the constant circulation of hot water in and out of the ground can cause seismic disruptions and lead to earthquakes – especially as geothermal power sources tend to exist primarily in areas of already-high levels of seismic activity.</li>
    <li><strong>Bioenergy:</strong> Biomass is plentiful – often existing as a byproduct of other agricultural or production industries (corn husks, manure, landfill gas). But there is a bit of contention around biomass as a fuel source. The “carbon neutrality” of certain biofuels is achieved because the plants or trees involved – when alive – contributed sufficient oxygen production during their lifetimes to offset the CO2 generated by their eventual combustion. Many also question the assertion that forests are entirely renewable resources given that they can take up to a hundred years to regrow. For utilities companies in developing nations or largely rural areas, biomass options can be interesting, but when it comes to the urban power grids, the cost and complexity of biomass as a power source makes it challenging to implement on a large scale.</li>
    <li><strong>Tidal and wave energy:</strong> In areas of dense coastal population, there are utilities companies currently making headway with <a href="https://www.nsenergybusiness.com/features/tidal-energy-projects-2020/">tidal energy projects</a>. However, these energy technologies are still in their infancy. The potential benefit of tidal power is enormous and virtually limitless so it definitely represents an interesting area of exploration for the energy sector. But at the moment, there is still uncertainty over the long-term environmental impact of such projects. Furthermore, the technology is not yet streamlined enough to produce sufficient wattage to justify the enormous expense of initiating ocean energy projects.</li>
    <li><strong>Batteries:</strong> The challenge of many renewable energy sources is the fact that they can be unreliable and intermittent. Utility-scale batteries can enhance grid reliability to protect against unexpected demand or shortage. Battery integration can also allow power companies to gradually wean themselves off fossil fuels with minimal disruption. However, such industrial batteries are currently produced by only a few specialist manufacturers, and while they are definitely lowering in price, they are still expensive to purchase and maintain.</li>
    <li><strong>Smart, cloud-based technologies:</strong> The application of artificial intelligence (AI)-powered smart technologies and metering in utilities can improve efficiency, collect and analyze valuable data, minimize waste, and help to protect against (and anticipate) risk. Internet of Things (IoT) networks and connected systems can also help to automate and monetize prosumer and distributed power generation networks.</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="net-zero-emissions-goals-in-a-complex-utilities-market">Net-zero emissions goals in a complex utilities market</h2>
  <p>In the U.S., investor-owned utilities (IOUs) provide energy to <a href="https://www.eia.gov/todayinenergy/detail.php?id=40913">over 70%</a> of the population. But as <a href="https://www.greentechmedia.com/">Greentech Media</a> reminds us, they are under extreme pressure to “turn enough profit to retain their investors in a difficult, constrained, low-margin business.” As the utilities industry prepares for energy transformation, IOUs must address some old and familiar challenges, as well as some new factors that are affecting their sector.</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Natural and political disruptions:</strong> The <a href="https://wmo.int/topics/extreme-weather">World Meteorological Organization</a> tells us that weather-related disasters have increased five-fold in the past 50 years, making disaster and climate change preparedness a costly but necessary priority for the utilities sector. Also, as one of the most heavily <a href="http://www.perillon.com/blog/10-most-regulated-industries-in-the-us">regulated</a> of all industries (more so than even automobiles, banking, or air traffic), the utilities industry is especially vulnerable to global and regional political shifts, which can often add to the pressure to remain profitable.</li>
    <li><strong>Changing customer expectations and behaviors:</strong> Decarbonization, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/digitization-vs-digitalization.html">digitalization</a>, and decentralization are changing a century-old relationship between customers and energy providers. Demand response and smart meter technologies let utilities customers reduce their power consumption at peak times in return for lower, off-peak electricity. Improvements in energy storage capacity for electric vehicles (EV) and solar panel batteries also mean that customers can generate and distribute their own power – hence the rise of the “prosumer” (producer/consumer).</li>
    <li><strong>Less control over power sources and greater complexity within the grid:</strong> In one of the world’s most regulated industries, Texas stands out for having an unregulated power grid. As a result, many renewable energy players are flocking to the state, intent on disrupting the industry with clean energy startups. In fact, as <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/features/2021-03-08/tesla-is-plugging-a-secret-mega-battery-into-the-texas-grid">Bloomberg Green</a> informs us, Tesla has quietly been building a 100 megawatt storage battery near Houston and, in August 2021, filed with the Public Utility Commission of Texas to sell electricity on the retail market. With the growing availability and capacity of AI-powered digital technologies – and rapid advancement of battery technologies – it has become increasingly feasible for small-scale players to connect with millions of prosumers to create highly viable power storage and distribution stations. Further, the rise of prosumers alone can lead to hundreds of thousands of power generation and storage points being added to the grid, making it exponentially more complex for utilities companies to manage and operate.</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="sustainable-and-renewable-energy-change-is-the-only-way-forward">Sustainable and renewable energy: Change is the only way forward</h2>
  <p>In the 2020s, it’s no longer a matter of “if” we should transition to more sustainable energy sources, but “how” and “when.”</p>
  <p>Utilities companies are uniquely positioned with the scope, experience, and existing customer base to rethink their business models and begin a profitable journey toward net zero. Here are some examples of competitive strategies:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Lean into the DER and prosumer markets and build new partnerships.</strong> Based upon what we’re seeing around the world (and even in Texas), the digital technology and engineering capacity now exists for clean energy startups to begin to proliferate – scooping up both residential and industrial prosumers and becoming energy retailers and DER providers. For utilities companies, this can either shake out as a risk or an opportunity, depending upon their appetite for innovation and willingness to partner with new players in the market.</li>
    <li><strong>Invest in smart digital solutions and nurture data-driven business practices.</strong> In the energy sector of the future, it will be data that becomes an especially valuable commodity. Companies will achieve a competitive edge by leveraging <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/business-technology-platform.html">AI</a> and powerful <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/data-management.html">database</a> and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp.html">ERP</a> technologies to make sense of their data and to deliver actionable insights. From managing prosumers and multiple renewable energy sources to economical energy distribution and storage, utilities companies will increasingly rely on advanced analytics and data-driven practices to remain profitable and meet a rapidly shifting market and consumer base. The growth in smart technologies also has the potential to improve customers’ ability to self serve and personalize their services and usage.</li>
    <li><strong>Improve communication and customer experience strategies.</strong> The latest survey data from both the <a href="https://www.instituteofcustomerservice.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/ICS-UKCSI-Exec-Summary_July-21.pdf">UK</a> and <a href="https://www.smart-energy.com/industry-sectors/customer-services-management/customer-satisfaction-remains-stagnant-with-us-residential-water-utilities/">U.S.</a> shows unimpressive levels of consumer satisfaction and points to the fact that utilities companies may have some work to do on the customer relations front. Just as it’s a time of great change and upheaval for the energy sector, it’s also a time of confusion for consumers trying to figure out the best way to manage their power usage, what options are available to them as prosumers, and how to optimize the intel available from smart meter technologies. Energy providers need to partner with their own customers, just as they may need to partner with disruptive startups in order to best compete. Doing so, they can not only advertise and promote their brand but share information, increase communications relevance, and generally throw back the curtain on their ongoing plans for energy transition.</li>
  </ul>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div data-valign="middle">In the power and utilities sector, shifting business models, energy options, and the potential for new competitors to enter the market are creating an urgency to improve the relationship with customers.</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div data-valign="middle"><a href="https://www2.deloitte.com/content/dam/Deloitte/ca/Documents/energy-resources/ca-energy-and-resources-en-utilities-new-era-customer-choice-aoda.pdf">Deloitte 2021</a></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="digital-utilities-transformation-and-clean-energy-transition">Digital utilities transformation and clean energy transition</h2>
  <p>In his novel <em>The World Without Us</em>, Alan Weisman describes what would happen to the world around us if humans disappeared. The book gives an account of what would occur in New York City within hours of the power being shut off. The subways would be flooded and, almost immediately, the city’s infrastructures would begin to collapse like dominos. While an extreme example, this nonetheless reminds us of how much our survival depends upon reliable and accessible sources of power – and how over the past hundred years utility companies have created marvels of engineering and invention to fuel those needs.</p>
  <p>In the 2020s, this industry is under unprecedented pressure to innovate and reform, for the benefit of the earth and all of us on it. The good news: with this pressure comes tremendous opportunity to build on an impressive legacy and blaze the trail to a more sustainable future.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="utilities-solutions">Utilities solutions</h3>
        <p>Explore utilities management systems that support a sustainable future.</p>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/utilities.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>core-topic/sustainable-business-operations</category>
            <category>industry/oil-gas-energy</category>
            <category>industry/utilities</category>
            <category>content-type/what-is</category>
            <category>stage/acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP.iO Foundries North America Teams with Accenture to Launch Two New Sustainability Cohorts]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/sap-io-foundries-north-america-accenture-sustainability-cohorts</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/sap-io-foundries-north-america-accenture-sustainability-cohorts</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Two new sustainability cohorts at SAP.iO Foundries North America will focus on consumer and retail, as well as energy and natural resources.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18a9e57b35a1e76871086aab84bc36f553d94aa72.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18a9e57b35a1e76871086aab84bc36f553d94aa72.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_18a9e57b35a1e76871086aab84bc36f553d94aa72.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP.iO Foundries North America Teams with Accenture to Launch Two New Sustainability Cohorts" src="./media_18a9e57b35a1e76871086aab84bc36f553d94aa72.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sapio-foundries-north-america-teams-with-accenture-to-launch-two-new-sustainability-cohorts">SAP.iO Foundries North America Teams with Accenture to Launch Two New Sustainability Cohorts</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) and Accenture welcome two new cohorts to SAP.iO Foundries North America, SAP’s external startup accelerator program. Thirteen startups were selected for the cohorts among hundreds of applicants by a jury of SAP and Accenture experts, partners and customers.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The startups in the cohorts are building innovative solutions to drive sustainability for consumer and retail companies across the value chain in areas including reusable packaging and responsible and ethical supply chain. The startups will also focus on helping companies in the energy and natural resources industries manage sustainability goals including compliance, regulation, tracking and carbon trading.</p>
  <p>Over the next 16 weeks, the startups will work alongside curated sustainability and technology experts from Accenture and SAP, with access to SAP technology and application programming interfaces (APIs) and opportunities to collaborate with SAP and Accenture customers around the world. The startups will integrate with SAP solutions such as <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/product-footprint-management.html">SAP Product Footprint Management</a> and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/responsible-design-and-production.html">SAP Responsible Design and Production</a> and leverage Accenture’s <a href="https://www.accenture.com/us-en/services/sustainability-index?c=acn_glb_responsiblebusimediarelations_11730836&#x26;n=mrl_0121">Sustainability Services</a> and broad industry knowledge, building upon the companies’ long-standing partnership and shared commitment to <a href="https://newsroom.accenture.com/news/accenture-and-sap-extend-partnership-to-help-companies-accelerate-sustainability-transformation-drive-new-sources-of-value-and-lead-in-the-circular-economy.htm">using technology to help the world build a more sustainable future</a>. The following startups are participating in the SAP.iO Foundries North America sustainability cohorts:</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="build-sustainability-directly-into-your-core-business-processes-with-sap">Build sustainability directly into your core business processes with SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/sustainability.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="consumer-and-retail">Consumer and Retail</h2>
  <ul>
    <li><a href="https://algramo.com/en">Algramo</a> offers a circular platform that encourages consumers to buy in a more convenient, affordable way with zero waste and connects people, brands and retailers to change consumption habits.</li>
    <li><a href="https://ecocart.io/business/">EcoCart</a> calculates the carbon emissions of business activities, then programmatically offsets those emissions by funding impactful certified carbon offset projects like planting trees or building windfarms.</li>
    <li><a href="http://www.everledger.io/">Everledger</a> leverages blockchain and Internet of Things technology to offer transparency into supply chains for clarity on quality, origin, sustainability footprint and compliance standards.</li>
    <li><a href="http://evrythng.com/">EVRYTHNG</a> helps customers run their business differently with real-time data intelligence from each of their products end to end, from factory to consumer and beyond.</li>
    <li><a href="http://www.inspectorio.com/">Inspectorio</a> provides a dynamic and risk-assessment-based quality compliance program for digitalization, automation, transparency and traceability.</li>
    <li><a href="https://www.thelimeloop.com/">LimeLoop</a> is a platform for sustainable shipping including reusable packaging, real-time tracking and predictive analytics.</li>
    <li><a href="https://specright.com/">Specright</a> delivers a purpose-built platform for specification management that changes how brands, suppliers, manufacturers and retailers manage data and collaborate to bring products to market.</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="energy-and-natural-resources">Energy and Natural Resources</h2>
  <ul>
    <li><a href="http://www.bidgely.com/">Bidgely</a> accelerates a clean energy future by enabling utilities and consumers to make data-driven energy decisions.</li>
    <li><a href="https://camus.energy/">Camus Energy</a> empowers utilities and energy providers with systemwide visibility, forecasting and advanced controls to balance local renewable supply with flexible demand for a distributed, zero-carbon future.</li>
    <li><a href="http://www.empower.eco/">Empower</a> incentivizes transparent and traceable collection, sourcing and recycling of plastic waste globally.</li>
    <li><a href="https://www.oilx.co/">OilX</a> is the world’s first digital oil analyst. It leverages satellite technology and AI to create a digital twin of the oil supply chain, from well to wheel.</li>
    <li><a href="https://carbonara.energy/">Singularity Energy</a> is a data and analytics company that helps customers reduce their carbon emissions.</li>
    <li><a href="http://www.supplhi.com/">SupplHi</a> covers the vendor management activities from vendor scouting to vendor qualification, vendor performance evaluation and assessment of vendor financials, compliance and sustainability.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>Visit the <a href="http://news.sap.com/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP on Twitter at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Media Contact:</strong> Stacy Ries, +1 (484) 619-0411, <a href="mailto:stacy.ries@sap.com">stacy.ries@sap.com</a>, ET<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>Any statements contained in this document that are not historical facts are forward-looking statements as defined in the U.S. Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995. Words such as “anticipate,” “believe,” “estimate,” “expect,” “forecast,” “intend,” “may,” “plan,” “project,” “predict,” “should” and “will” and similar expressions as they relate to SAP are intended to identify such forward-looking statements. SAP undertakes no obligation to publicly update or revise any forward-looking statements. All forward-looking statements are subject to various risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results to differ materially from expectations. The factors that could affect SAP’s future financial results are discussed more fully in SAP’s filings with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (“SEC”), including SAP’s most recent Annual Report on Form 20-F filed with the SEC. Readers are cautioned not to place undue reliance on these forward-looking statements, which speak only as of their dates.<br>© 2021 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>industry/consumer-goods-cpg</category>
            <category>industry/oil-gas-energy</category>
            <category>news-tag/renewable-energy</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-io</category>
            <category>industry/utilities</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sustainability Is Opportunity at SAP for Utilities Conference]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/sustainability-is-opportunity-at-sap-for-utilities-conference</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/sustainability-is-opportunity-at-sap-for-utilities-conference</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 29 Oct 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[North American utilities organizations discussed sustainability at this year's SAP for Utilities annual conference. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_12e52ba8efa72574cf8018a601d2f5c6afab9e93a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_12e52ba8efa72574cf8018a601d2f5c6afab9e93a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_12e52ba8efa72574cf8018a601d2f5c6afab9e93a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Sustainability Is Opportunity at SAP for Utilities Conference" src="./media_12e52ba8efa72574cf8018a601d2f5c6afab9e93a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sustainability-is-opportunity-at-sap-for-utilities-conference">Sustainability Is Opportunity at SAP for Utilities Conference</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>As the climate crisis intensifies, <a href="/2021/10/integrating-climate-action-end-to-end">SAP has made it clear</a> that the company is committed to helping its customers combat these challenges and embrace sustainable alternatives.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Enabling climate action through technology is top of mind for customers in industries around the globe, but the topic was particularly remarkable to the gathering of North American utility organizations at the annual <a href="https://events.asug.com/sapforutilities">SAP for Utilities</a> conference in San Diego on October 17-19. These are organizations that not only face the emergency environmental situations intensified by climate change, like hurricanes and fires, but are also daily witnesses to energy consumption and, increasingly, adoption of more sustainable energy sources.</p>
  <p>It’s no surprise then that sustainability was a key track at the conference, addressing head-on the challenges that North American utilities face as they grow and innovate against the looming presence of climate change. With keynotes from world-renowned experts and boots-on-the-ground insight – 90% of the track sessions were led by customers – here are the top takeaways on how sustainability is shaping the utilities industry.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="inspire-and-shape-a-digital-world-by-reinventing-power-generation-with-sap-solutions">Inspire and shape a digital world by reinventing power generation with SAP solutions</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/energy-utilities.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="technology-is-the-most-critical-tool-to-combat-climate-challenges">Technology Is the Most Critical Tool to Combat Climate Challenges</h2>
  <p>While utilities have been responding to the impact of climate challenges for decades, the last few years have made the challenge acute: more intense natural disasters, the swift adoption of electric vehicles, and even the overnight shift to remote work. All of these have a significant impact on the energy grid – and when coupled with an escalation of regulation around sustainability, utilities are working under incredible market complexity.</p>
  <p>The response, from industry experts and utility managers alike, was clear: to manage these challenges, companies need to gather, track, and understand their data. And the only way to do that is through <a href="https://insights.sap.com/digitization-vs-digitalization/">digitization</a> and smart software.</p>
  <p>“The most important thing is the ability to measure: to know where you started and where you’re going to, where the journey ends,” said Brian Roach, managing director of Regulated Industries at SAP. “What we’re seeing now is a lot of investment in the understanding of, say, your carbon footprint and having a predictable and consistent means of measuring that.”</p>
  <h2 id="the-singular-impact-of-the-electric-vehicle">The Singular Impact of the Electric Vehicle</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-carbon-footprint-solution-helps-companies-redesign-for-sustainability">SAP Carbon Footprint Solution Helps Companies Redesign for Sustainability</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/09/sap-product-footprint-management-redesign-sustainability">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>For the past century, the energy industry has looked more or less the same. But factors are colluding to upend that stasis, and none more so than the electric vehicle. Elon Musk recently went on record <a href="https://www.barrons.com/articles/tesla-elon-musk-electric-vehicle-production-51633202912">that U.S. electricity production needs to double</a> in order to power the transition to electric vehicles. That is a tall order for utilities. It’s also an amazing opportunity to define new approaches in the ecosystem and create new business, particularly when it comes to taking advantage of off-cycle electrical demand.</p>
  <p>“This is where smart technology must be applied: determining when you charge, what the right time of day is, what the rates are, the priorities of what gets charged first,” said Tony Posawatz, president and CEO of Invictus iCAR LLC, in the opening keynote. “This is where some of the horsepower that exists in the industry will come to bear.”</p>
  <h2 id="the-opportunity-is-now-to-transform-the-industry">The Opportunity Is Now to Transform the Industry</h2>
  <p>Despite the clear external pressures – regulations, customer expectations and demand, the fast-evolving climate crisis – the tone was one of optimism and excitement. This is a turning point for the industry, and organizations are eager to rise to the challenge.</p>
  <p>“I’ve been in this industry for decades, and for the first 10 years or so it was pretty stable; there wasn’t a lot of significant change. But right now, we are in a transformative state. I see it as a huge opportunity for us to be the ones who formulate what the future of utilities looks like,” said Michael O’Donnell, regional vice president of Utilities for SAP, in the opening keynote. “For me, it couldn’t be a more exciting time. You call it disruption; I call it opportunity for us to shape this and change the future.”</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Mallory Kuno works within Communications at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/climate-change</category>
            <category>news-tag/electric-vehicles</category>
            <category>industry/utilities</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SaskPower Workshops Powerful New App to Win SAP Hackathon]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/saskpower-workshops-powerful-new-app-to-win-sap-hackathon</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/saskpower-workshops-powerful-new-app-to-win-sap-hackathon</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A virtual hackathon around SAP BTP led SaskPower to a solution that will save time and labor on a cumbersome energy meter return process.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_131ff7ba58274947c087ac9f1e4b5de09348690f1.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_131ff7ba58274947c087ac9f1e4b5de09348690f1.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_131ff7ba58274947c087ac9f1e4b5de09348690f1.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SaskPower Workshops Powerful New App to Win SAP Hackathon" src="./media_131ff7ba58274947c087ac9f1e4b5de09348690f1.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="saskpower-workshops-powerful-new-app-to-win-sap-hackathon">SaskPower Workshops Powerful New App to Win SAP Hackathon</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-business-technology-platform-accelerate-business-outcomes-with-integration-data-to-value-and-extensibility">SAP Business Technology Platform: Accelerate business outcomes with integration, data to value, and extensibility</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>SaskPower, <a href="https://www.saskpower.com/">Saskatchewan’s leading energy supplier</a>, recently participated in a virtual hackathon around SAP Business Technology Platform to workshop a solution that will save the company time and labor surrounding its cumbersome energy meter return process.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SaskPower is responsible for serving over 540,000 customer accounts within Saskatchewan’s geographic area of approximately 652,000 square kilometers. With that many customers spread across such a vast territory, sorting the 700 to 950 energy meters that are expected to be returned to the company daily during its AMI smart meter rollout is no small task. The manual process of entering serial numbers into a spreadsheet to determine the dispensation of this returned inventory is time- and labor-intensive, and prone to errors. The process needed to be energized.</p>
  <p>When the SaskPower team received an invitation to participate in the three-day virtual hackathon on SAP Business Technology Platform, they jumped at the chance to use SAP technology to solve this business problem. Leading into the event, SaskPower got its business partners excited, picked out team uniforms, briefed the developer team on the task, and then dove in.</p>
  <p>“The hackathon was a great opportunity to try out SAP tools available to our business,” said Terry Chadwick, SAP solutions architect at SaskPower. “We didn’t even think about saying no. Our team was very excited, and we jumped in to see what we could come up with.”</p>
  <p>On day one, the SaskPower team learned all about the SAP tools at their disposal. On day two, they went to work building a conceptual framework and application. Finally, on day three, the team put the finishing touches on the app and presented to the judges. The app framework was built using a combination of SAP products, including SAP Cloud Application Programming Model and SAPUI5, SAP Workflow Management, SAP Business Rules Management, SAP Launchpad service, SAP Conversational AI, and business optical character recognition.</p>
  <p>The result was a win for the SaskPower team with the development of the <strong>Mobile Meter Return app</strong>. Returning meters will no longer require manual data entry, and validations in the app will help protect against manual data entry errors. Now, when meters come back into the facility, meters will be scanned and validated. The tool will automatically perform the goods movement processes to receive the meters into the warehouse, recommending how the meter will be managed — for example, the meter could be marked for retirement or for reuse.</p>
  <p>SaskPower plans to take the theoretical to the practical and is building the app, with plans to have it fully deployed in the field by August 2021.</p>
  <p>“We had a great experience at the hackathon and winning is a testament to the hard work our team put in,” said Terry Collins, solutions architect at SaskPower. “Our coach from the SAP BTP team could not have been more supportive, and we have a great deal of trust in him and his team. Because of the strength of this relationship, we’re able to collaborate and create solutions that make our business nimbler and, ultimately, more intelligent.”</p>
  <p>Explore how SAP Business Technology Platform brings together intelligent enterprise applications with database and data management, analytics, and integration and extension capabilities into one platform for both cloud and hybrid environments, including hundreds of prebuilt integrations for SAP and third-party applications. <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">Request a demo now</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Bruno Guerrero is a senior solution advisor for SAP Business Technology Platform.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="inspire-and-shape-a-digital-world-by-reinventing-power-generation-transmission-distribution-and-retail">Inspire and shape a digital world by reinventing power generation, transmission, distribution, and retail</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/energy-utilities.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>industry/utilities</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Future Grid: Why Australia Is Proving Grounds for Renewable Energy]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/03/future-grid-renewable-energy-australia</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/03/future-grid-renewable-energy-australia</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Available on SAP Store, Future Grid is filling the visibility gap to better manage the accelerated transition to renewable energy. Learn how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/data-analytics</category>
            <category>news-tag/renewable-energy</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-io</category>
            <category>news-tag/startups</category>
            <category>industry/utilities</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sydney Water Runs SAP]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/videos/sydney-water-runs-sap</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/videos/sydney-water-runs-sap</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Water is an increasingly rare commodity. That is why a responsible use of water becomes more important than ever. Sydney Water, a water supplier, is...]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_104b3d7e7bd50d1207db074f773214640c5276652.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_104b3d7e7bd50d1207db074f773214640c5276652.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_104b3d7e7bd50d1207db074f773214640c5276652.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Sydney Water Runs SAP" src="./media_104b3d7e7bd50d1207db074f773214640c5276652.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sydney-water-runs-sap">Sydney Water Runs SAP</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_104b3d7e7bd50d1207db074f773214640c5276652.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_104b3d7e7bd50d1207db074f773214640c5276652.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_104b3d7e7bd50d1207db074f773214640c5276652.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Sydney Water Runs SAP" src="./media_104b3d7e7bd50d1207db074f773214640c5276652.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qxp7fzZsok0">Sydney Water Runs SAP</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Water is an increasingly rare commodity. That is why a responsible use of water becomes more important than ever.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Sydney Water, a water supplier, is aware of this responsibility that covers an area of more than 12.000 km2. In order to continue providing world class service to its customers, Sydney Water has updated its billing processes to optimize its workflows and help provide its customers bills that are easy to understand. Together with SAP, the water supplier decided to act and replaced the outdated system with a modern and flexible billing platform.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/financial-management</category>
            <category>content-type/video</category>
            <category>news-tag/climate-change</category>
            <category>industry/public-sector</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>industry/utilities</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>