<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/sap-for-me/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Retaining Customers Through Support Experience and Efficiency]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/retaining-customers-through-support-experience-and-efficiency</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/retaining-customers-through-support-experience-and-efficiency</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A smooth support experience and efficient support teams combine to delight and retain customers when it comes to customer support. Learn how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/built-in-support</category>
            <category>news-tag/incident-solution-matching</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-for-me</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Ariba and SAP Business Network Seamlessly Integrated into SAP for Me]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-ariba-business-network-integrated-sap-for-me</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-ariba-business-network-integrated-sap-for-me</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP for Me, the central access point to solution support for customers, is now available for SAP Ariba solutions and SAP Business Network.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f7e35b0ca7f6abf5c3e5f984222aa27df64caab8.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f7e35b0ca7f6abf5c3e5f984222aa27df64caab8.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1f7e35b0ca7f6abf5c3e5f984222aa27df64caab8.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Ariba and SAP Business Network Seamlessly Integrated into SAP for Me" src="./media_1f7e35b0ca7f6abf5c3e5f984222aa27df64caab8.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-ariba-and-sap-business-network-seamlessly-integrated-into-sap-for-me">SAP Ariba and SAP Business Network Seamlessly Integrated into SAP for Me</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><a href="https://me.sap.com/">SAP for Me</a> is our digital companion for our customers, providing them with a personalized one-stop shop across their SAP product portfolio. And now it’s available to SAP Ariba and SAP Business Network customers and partners.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP for Me provides a central access point to solution support. The portal offers a user-friendly interface with improved functionalities that can enable better and faster interaction with SAP support experts and can provide immediate guidance to solutions for daily business tasks. It aims to make detached information a thing of the past on the customer and partner journey to an intelligent enterprise.</p>
  <p>Since November 6, 2023, an English-language experience has been available for customers and partners to begin their exploration before the migration. And as of today, SAP Ariba and SAP Business Network knowledge-related content on SAP for Me is available in over 20 languages.</p>
  <p>SAP for Me provides an integrated and comprehensive platform to help meet the diverse needs of its users. The Services &#x26; Support dashboard features an SAP Ariba card that helps direct users to multiple resources on the legacy SAP Ariba Connect <a href="https://connectsupport.ariba.com/sites#Home-show">platform</a>, including SAP Ariba and SAP Business Network release readiness information, product documentation, announcements, and specific content related to adoption and deployment.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="say-hello-to-your-digital-companion">Say hello to your digital companion</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://me.sap.com/">Check out SAP for Me</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>When getting started with SAP for Me, know that:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>SAP Ariba Connect S-user authorizations are automatically carried over to SAP for Me – no additional access authorization is needed to use SAP for Me.</li>
    <li>The portal gives access to personalized content in the most used languages – English, German, Japanese, Simplified Chinese, French, Portuguese, and Spanish.</li>
    <li>SAP for Me offers intuitive cards that categorize and bucket information for your convenience. Support-relevant cards are mainly located in the Services &#x26; Support and Systems &#x26; Provisioning dashboards.</li>
    <li>The availability, maintenance, and subscriptions for SAP Ariba solutions and SAP Business Network can be found in the availability section of Systems &#x26; Provisioning.</li>
    <li>You can get a holistic view of licenses, orders, and consumption status.</li>
    <li>SAP for Me is also available on mobile devices. The mobile app will be enhanced with additional features and the ability to create and manage a new case.</li>
    <li>The get support application is your primary touchpoint with support.</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="get-support-easier-and-faster">Get Support, Easier and Faster</h2>
  <p>The get support application helps guide customers through technical product issues in real time or reaching SAP experts through an AI-enabled framework. It can provide an integrated and personalized support experience to help simplify and streamline the case creation process. AI can automatically recommend solutions during the interaction, predict the right product categorization, and recommend the most suitable support channel, like Expert Chat, SAP Community, or Ask an Expert Peer, when available for the selected product.</p>
  <h2 id="access-sap-support-on-the-go">Access SAP Support on the Go</h2>
  <p>With the SAP for Me mobile app, support interaction can be possible anywhere and anytime to complete tasks and access information directly on a smartphone. The mobile app can be downloaded from the Apple Store and Google Play Store.</p>
  <p>In conclusion, SAP for Me puts customer and partner interests into focus. While partners can manage their pipeline and customer success, the portal also serves as the central entry point for all support-related topics and questions for customers. It allows access to relevant information, self-services, and consumption status connected to any purchased product portfolio.</p>
  <p>The SAP for Me migration for SAP Ariba solutions and SAP Business Network is a significant milestone as we tap into the next generation of AI opportunities to create an effective experience for our customers while delivering a seamless consistency in the look, feel, and delivery of critical <a href="/topics/support">support services</a>.</p>
  <p>SAP for Me is made for you. Follow SAP for Me on LinkedIn and bookmark SAP for Me on SAP Community to stay updated.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Rohan Patel is global head of Support for SAP Procurement.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="follow-sap-news-on-linkedin-to-stay-informed">Follow SAP News on LinkedIn to stay informed</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news">Connect with us</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-for-me</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pushing the Boundaries of Procurement Customer Support with Innovations]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/procurement-customer-support-innovations</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/procurement-customer-support-innovations</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In this interview, SAP's Rohan Patel gives insight into how SAP support can benefit procurement customers. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1560e17ebf571c1cad896fad5b3fe9c897622bb2c.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1560e17ebf571c1cad896fad5b3fe9c897622bb2c.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1560e17ebf571c1cad896fad5b3fe9c897622bb2c.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Pushing the Boundaries of Procurement Customer Support with Innovations" src="./media_1560e17ebf571c1cad896fad5b3fe9c897622bb2c.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="pushing-the-boundaries-of-procurement-customer-support-with-innovations">Pushing the Boundaries of Procurement Customer Support with Innovations</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>In today’s environment, customers are reevaluating how they use and source software solutions to run their business. The move from on-premise only solutions to the cloud is SAP’s reality as a cloud vendor.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“Customers undergo a cloud transformation because they want to accelerate their time to realize business value and they want to take advantage of innovations faster,” says Rohan Patel, global vice president, Customer Support and Innovation, Product Support – Procurement, SAP. “That’s what helps them maintain a competitive edge. And they want to do this while decreasing overall cost and minimizing risk.”</p>
  <p>This is where <a href="https://support.sap.com/en/offerings-programs/strategy.html">Real-Time Support</a> from SAP can add real value. In this conversation, Patel gives insight into how SAP support can benefit procurement customers.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Q: How are you supporting procurement customers on their journey to the cloud?</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><strong>A:</strong> Support in the old, on-premise world is what I like to call ‘break-fix’ support. When something failed, the IT department submitted a ticket for support, the problem was fixed, and communication ended until another issue arose. Being a break-fix support provider doesn’t work in the cloud environment. Support requires speed and foresight. Support today identifies problems and optimizes products before customers even notice something’s not working as it should.</p>
  <p>SAP’s strategy is predictive and proactive. We want continuous dialogue with customers to provide insights and guidance that are a value-add so we’re there long before something breaks. Success in the cloud requires adoption outside of the traditional IT environment. Business end users and lines of business, like procurement, supply chain, and HR, expect easy-to-use support portals that are intuitive and quickly anticipate user needs.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-creates-support-programs-to-drive-an-innovative-and-consistent-experience">SAP creates support programs to drive an innovative and consistent experience</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://support.sap.com/en/offerings-programs/strategy.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Can you share some examples of how SAP is using data to enhance predictive support?</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The tools we use not only help us deliver a great experience to our customers, they also continue to improve the SAP solution itself. Consider the cloud health monitoring tools within <a href="https://support.sap.com/en/alm/sap-cloud-alm.html">SAP Cloud ALM</a>, our application lifecycle management solution that helps streamline the way our customers implement and operate their cloud and hybrid environments across the entire business.</p>
  <p>These tools can analyze what’s happening at the customer experience layer – for example, how long it takes a specific page to load, how long a user needs to complete a task, and any delays that could frustrate users, hinder adoption, and slow business outcomes. We act proactively at the engineering and cloud operations layer to help continuously improve that user experience.</p>
  <p>We also use knowledge and data to improve the support experience, such as with <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-network.html">SAP Business Network</a>, which has millions of active trading partners. This business-to-business network of companies connecting, transacting, and partnering with numerous shared processes and information expands the SAP footprint well beyond the four walls of traditional operations.</p>
  <p>Equally important is that our consumers today aren’t just IT support users, but rather work in departments throughout the clients’ operations. We’ve taken steps to help meet the needs of all those different user types. We can provide quick, easy-to-understand guidance and answers to their questions using intuitive, personalized, and real-time channels driven by both humans and artificial intelligence (AI). This recommendation engine can provide guided answers based on who the users are, what they’re doing in the application, or what questions they ask. Users can quickly get useful and relevant content for answering their questions. The data from those guided-answer experiences is then fed into the product road map to help make the entire user experience more optimal and eliminate problems before they happen.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>What have procurement customers seen in 2023 from SAP support?</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Our procurement coverage in 2023 hits two themes: harmonization and Real-Time Support. Let me begin with the harmonization perspective. We’re taking significant steps to create a customer support experience that’s consistent across all SAP solutions – most notably a single entry point to SAP support with <a href="https://me.sap.com/">SAP for Me</a>. SAP Fieldglass solutions went live on SAP for Me case management in March 2023, and SAP Ariba solutions and SAP Business Network will soon follow. The SAP for Me portal can give users the information and answers they need, specific to the solution they’re using. Earlier this year, procurement support went live on <a href="https://community.sap.com/">SAP Community</a>, where our business and IT users can access blog posts, tips, and connect with experts. Even customers and partners can provide an additional layer of insights and guidance, especially to a specific industry.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-real-time-support">Learn more about Real-Time Support</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://support.sap.com/en/offerings-programs/strategy.html">Explore now</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>This year we have been working to bring our Real-Time Support concept to reality for procurement. When I talk about Real-Time Support, I mean support that is always on, continuously evolves, and adapts to customer needs. This can be direct access to support experts for business-critical processes when and where customers need it. It’s the live support channels such as <a href="https://support.sap.com/en/my-support/product-support.html?anchorId=section_519294480">Expert Chat</a>, Ask an Expert Peer, context-sensitive help, <a href="https://support.sap.com/en/my-support/product-support.html?anchorId=section_1255553798">support built into our software</a>, and <a href="/2022/05/artificial-intelligence-future-of-customer-support-experiences">AI-driven self-service access</a> to a vast knowledge base and user community.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>What do you see in the future of support for procurement?</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>I envision a day when customers don’t need to see or hear from us because we’re already working behind the scenes to give our customers a seamless, reliable, and delightful experience. The ultimate vision is preventative support with the help of AI and machine learning – in other words, self-healing IT systems.</p>
  <p>Of course, there will always be times when customers need us. In those times, SAP is prepared to offer as simple of a support experience as possible, such as with <a href="https://support.sap.com/en/my-support/product-support.html?anchorId=section_1255553798">Built-In Support</a> and direct access to experts or a quick call to solve an issue the moment it occurs. We also continuously look to disrupt ourselves by using new technologies such as ChatGPT to enable self-help or self-guidance and provide the best possible customer experience.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>What sets the SAP support experience apart in the industry?</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP mindfully takes steps that help give customers the best support experience possible. We can provide a cohesive array of support channels, self-service tools, and cloud health and integration monitoring. Even with these successes in hand, SAP will continuously push the boundaries of customer support with new innovations, help ensure support interactions are delightful, and offer Real-Time Support that can bring ambition to life.</p>
  <p>Follow Rohan Patel on <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/rohan-patel-1897941/">LinkedIn</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Regina Postman is part of Customer Support and Innovation Communications at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="follow-sap-news-on-linkedin">Follow SAP News on LinkedIn</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news">Connect with us</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/product-support</category>
            <category>news-tag/real-time-support</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fieldglass</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-for-me</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP for Me Enhances the Customer Support Experience with Get Support]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/sap-for-me-customer-support-experience-get-support</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/sap-for-me-customer-support-experience-get-support</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Users can now engage with SAP support through the new get support application in SAP for Me and its use of artificial intelligence (AI).]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/built-in-support</category>
            <category>news-tag/real-time-support</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-for-me</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Meeting the Customer in Real Time: Support Whenever They Need It]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/customer-experience-real-time-support</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/customer-experience-real-time-support</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP's Bente Vollan describes the support experience SAP customers can expect with Real-Time Support. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/product-support</category>
            <category>news-tag/real-time-support</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-for-me</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP for Me Now Successor of SAP ONE Support Launchpad]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/sap-for-me-successor-sap-one-support-launchpad</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/sap-for-me-successor-sap-one-support-launchpad</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[To provide customers an even better SAP experience, SAP ONE Support Launchpad is now fully part of the SAP for Me portal. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-for-me</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-one-support-launchpad</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP for Me as the New, Personalized Central Entry Point for SAP Support]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/sap-for-me-new-personalized-entry-point-sap-support</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/sap-for-me-new-personalized-entry-point-sap-support</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP for Me helps make performing support-related tasks easier and more efficient in one place. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/real-time-support</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-for-me</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-one-support-launchpad</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-support-portal</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Real-Time Support Channels Take Big Steps Forward in Customer Care]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/real-time-support-big-steps-forward-customer-care</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/real-time-support-big-steps-forward-customer-care</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With Real-Time Support, SAP is moving towards a bidirectional, predictive, and effortless support future. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/built-in-support</category>
            <category>news-tag/expert-chat</category>
            <category>news-tag/product-support</category>
            <category>news-tag/real-time-support</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-for-me</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-support-portal</category>
            <category>news-tag/schedule-a-manager</category>
            <category>news-tag/schedule-an-expert</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Trio for Support Innovation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/trio-for-support-innovation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/trio-for-support-innovation</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP's Andreas Heckmann discusses the innovative power of continuous updates, AI and machine learning, and real-time support. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/built-in-support</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-solution-support-innovation</category>
            <category>news-tag/machine-learning</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-cloud-alm</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-for-me</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-one-support-launchpad</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Brings Cloud Software Repurchases in Minutes to Customers and Partners]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/sap-for-me-on-sap-store-cloud-software-repurchases</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/sap-for-me-on-sap-store-cloud-software-repurchases</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With SAP for Me on SAP Store, customer and partners have efficiency, simplicity, insights, and transparency into repurchasing and upselling.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/sap-teched</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-for-me</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-store</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP’s New Recognition System Improves Partner Visibility to Attract New Customers]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/09/sap-partner-visibility-new-recognition-system</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/09/sap-partner-visibility-new-recognition-system</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[To improve SAP partner visibility, the new Competency Framework from the SAP PartnerEdge program showcases experience and skill sets.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-for-me</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-partneredge</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ask an Expert: SAP for Me]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/ask-an-expert-sap-for-me</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/ask-an-expert-sap-for-me</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP for Me grants customers transparency across their complete SAP Portfolio and access to self-services. Learn more from an expert.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15e03e0ab460574fec9b13733d20ba74b4dfa706e.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15e03e0ab460574fec9b13733d20ba74b4dfa706e.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_15e03e0ab460574fec9b13733d20ba74b4dfa706e.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Ask an Expert: SAP for Me" src="./media_15e03e0ab460574fec9b13733d20ba74b4dfa706e.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="ask-an-expert-sap-for-me">Ask an Expert: SAP for Me</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Oguzhan Genis, business product owner of SAP for Me, answers five questions about the portal.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><strong>Q: How would you describe the experience of using SAP for Me?</strong></p>
  <p><strong>A:</strong> As a customer, it’s your digital portal. It’s basically the same thing you probably have with your utility provider or bank. You log into a private environment, and you can see your account, manage your preferences, and more. This portal is, of course, more complex, but generally speaking, it is your digital access into your relationship with your supplier.</p>
  <p><strong>What sparked the creation of the portal, and why was it a priority?</strong></p>
  <p>The impetus for the project was customer feedback saying that it was challenging to do business with SAP at that time because it felt like dealing with multiple enterprises. We had acquired some new companies and they all had their own processes with their own tools, their own environment, and their own engagement. It was difficult for customers to see SAP as a unified solution.</p>
  <p>I took over the project when we were still calling it My Home. The goal all along has been nothing less than to change the way customers do business with SAP. <a href="/topics/crm-customer-experience">Customer experience</a> is so important, even more so in the cloud because there are many digital touchpoints. We wanted every interaction between us and the customer to improve their experience and provide them with better outcomes. That’s why we believe that the introduction of SAP for Me marks the beginning of a new customer experience.</p>
  <p><strong>What happens with other entry points now that SAP has streamlined down to just SAP.com, SAP Community, and SAP for Me?</strong></p>
  <p>The others become what we are calling secondary entry points. One example would be the Cloud Availability Center service. We are still in the process of determining exactly how these will be accessed because they contain great relevant content, but they are siloed from one another, which runs counter to our customer experience goal. In some cases, certain applications will be migrated or integrated into one of the three primary entry points. A few will be retired. Others will remain as a content provider but will be accessible through one of the main entry points. There are many applications in the support area, like the example with Cloud Availability Center, which we are already integrating successfully into SAP for Me.</p>
  <p><strong>Will SAP for Me also be the go-to place for engagement with SAP support?</strong></p>
  <p>Yes. Getting SAP support is an important element that SAP wants to enable customers and partners to do in SAP for Me. Therefore, it is planned to transition all support features from SAP ONE Support Launchpad to SAP for Me in a phased approach. As a first step, we have recently released the newly designed services and support and systems and provisioning dashboards. With this, more than one million support users can now perform all their support-related tasks by accessing the support applications directly via SAP for Me.</p>
  <p><strong>What are some of the benefits of SAP for Me?</strong></p>
  <p>Internally, we created an employee view so that our relevant employees can see exactly what the customer can see now, which is great for our colleagues. It allows us to answer customer questions easily and to find information much more quickly.</p>
  <p>For our customers, it empowers them to answer questions on their own, especially for certain recurring activities. For example, with regards to tenants, how many do I have on my list of licenses? And how much did I consume? These are standard questions, but it was difficult for a customer to find this out on their own previously, and it was time consuming for both parties when they regularly had to inquire with us. It’s also much easier for customers to know who to contact with specific questions, which, again, will increase efficiency for both our colleagues and our customers.</p>
  <p>And there are, of course, many more benefits, such as easily purchasing additional licenses for over 1,400 cloud solutions from SAP with your individually pre-negotiated terms and conditions and tracking details of each order including renewal periods and fees, license materials by order and contract, payment details, and addresses.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="explore-sap-for-me">Explore SAP for Me</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://me.sap.com/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="please-join-us-at-the-second-virtual-user-conference-on-december-7">Please join us at the <a href="https://events.sap.com/sap-4-me-second-virtual-user-conference/en/home?source=social-global-voicestorm-None&#x26;campaigncode=CRM-YD21-SOC-GETSOC1">second virtual user conference</a> on December 7!</h3>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="unified-view-and-digital-autonomy-the-future-of-our-customer-relationships-with-sap-for-me">Unified View and Digital Autonomy: The Future of Our Customer Relationships with SAP for Me</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/11/unified-view-digital-autonomy-sap-for-me-mobile-app">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Martin Gwisdalla is part of Global PR at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-for-me</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-one-support-launchpad</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unified View and Digital Autonomy: The Future of Our Customer Relationships with SAP for Me]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/unified-view-digital-autonomy-sap-for-me-mobile-app</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/unified-view-digital-autonomy-sap-for-me-mobile-app</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP for Me marks a new, simplified customer experience, especially with the launch of the SAP for Me mobile app. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a903832003837e34c273cbd6c0ea4f5745d5d107.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a903832003837e34c273cbd6c0ea4f5745d5d107.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1a903832003837e34c273cbd6c0ea4f5745d5d107.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Unified View and Digital Autonomy: The Future of Our Customer Relationships with SAP for Me" src="./media_1a903832003837e34c273cbd6c0ea4f5745d5d107.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="unified-view-and-digital-autonomy-the-future-of-our-customer-relationships-with-sap-for-me">Unified View and Digital Autonomy: The Future of Our Customer Relationships with SAP for Me</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>The digital age is empowering for many people who are now accustomed to accessing important information and taking required actions online. They can directly communicate with an unprecedented number of people through social media, as well as exchange views and information with global communities.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Whether it’s making a doctor’s appointment, depositing a check, enrolling in school, or buying a new car, people increasingly rely on digital tools to live their lives — and expect an intuitive online system to make that possible. Customers expect a consistent and seamless experience along every single touchpoint they have with a company.</p>
  <p>To meet this expectation, SAP now provides a single point of entry — <a href="https://me.sap.com/">SAP for Me</a> — that defines how customers will engage with the company in the future. This exciting shift in customer experience allows them to personalize their view based on their role and interests, get transparency across their complete SAP portfolio, engage with self-services, and actively influence products. This comprehensive portal marks a new, simplified customer experience with SAP, and with recent developments, including the release of a mobile version, it is now time for customers to begin exploring <a href="https://me.sap.com/">SAP for Me</a>.</p>
  <p>SAP for Me was introduced in response to customer feedback that SAP’s many tools and portals were proving challenging to navigate. Customers struggled to get an overarching picture of their portfolio and often required an intermediary to access basic information; for example, a customer would need to ask an account executive how many licenses they had purchased or how much they paid for certain contracts across different entities, rather than being able to access the information themselves.</p>
  <p>To solve this, SAP decided to streamline the number of entry points into the company down to three. One is <strong>sap.com</strong>, the “digital front door” through which anyone can meet the company. The second is <strong>SAP Community</strong>, which allows customers and partners to communicate directly. And the third is <strong>SAP for Me</strong>, which allows customers to engage with useful dashboards, personalized displays, and an updated look and feel for an intuitive experience that supports their business outcomes. Most vitally, it gives customers the power to do everything from monitoring their license consumption to accessing an overview of their portfolio KPIs to managing customer contacts. It puts the customer in the driver’s seat, giving them the autonomy they need to take control of their SAP experience in ways big and small.</p>
  <p>Today, customers can even access this portal straight from their mobile device. The SAP for Me mobile app provides the same functionalities of the SAP for Me portal, but accessible wherever and whenever the customer wants. The app will be expanded soon, with additional features and the ability to create and manage a new case, all from a phone.</p>
  <p>SAP for Me has been created based on customer feedback and demonstrates what is possible when customer needs drive innovation. SAP customer CONLOG, a metering solutions company with 50 years of experience and a reputation for innovation and customer centricity, has adopted SAP for Me to gain a simplified overview on business-critical incidents and direct options for action within the portal. That has enabled the company to resolve issues quickly, keeping the focus on their customers.</p>
  <p>“SAP for Me is a great and easy tool to manage all SAP products my company is utilizing,” says Lethu Ntuli, SAP Business Analyst at CONLOG. “It provides a simplified view of licensed materials with potential over-usage warnings, if applicable. With this view one can take necessary steps, using the same tool, to remedy the situation.”</p>
  <p>That is the goal of SAP for Me: to allow SAP customers to understand and access the full benefits of their SAP solutions, monitoring and acting easily and quickly to help ensure that their business can continue providing the same seamless experience for <em>their</em> customers. This portal provides comprehensive transparency with a personalized access point on the channel that works for our customers, be it in the office or on mobile. SAP customers now have the autonomy to manage, provision, or monitor their system environment on their own terms.</p>
  <p>With SAP for Me, customers are empowered to do what they need to achieve the business goals that matter to them—so why wait? The future of customer relationships with SAP is already here.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="explore-sap-for-me">Explore SAP for Me</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://me.sap.com/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="join-us-at-the-second-virtual-user-conference-on-december-7-2021-register-now">Join us at the <a href="https://events.sap.com/sap-4-me-second-virtual-user-conference/en/home?source=social-global-voicestorm-None&#x26;campaigncode=CRM-YD21-SOC-GETSOC1">second virtual user conference</a> on December 7, 2021. <a href="https://events.sap.com/sap-4-me-second-virtual-user-conference/en/home?source=social-global-voicestorm-None&#x26;campaigncode=CRM-YD21-SOC-GETSOC1">Register now</a>.</h3>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Oguzhan Genis is business product owner of SAP for Me.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-for-me</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Seamless Support Experience in the Post-Pandemic World]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/seamless-support-experience-post-pandemic-world</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/seamless-support-experience-post-pandemic-world</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[At SAP, end-to-end support is about having a seamless, unified approach to all aspects of the support experience. Read to learn more!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_161d736f1f8909faa946ca3de7493588f42e18e60.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_161d736f1f8909faa946ca3de7493588f42e18e60.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_161d736f1f8909faa946ca3de7493588f42e18e60.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="A Seamless Support Experience in the Post-Pandemic World" src="./media_161d736f1f8909faa946ca3de7493588f42e18e60.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="a-seamless-support-experience-in-the-post-pandemic-world">A Seamless Support Experience in the Post-Pandemic World</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-enterprise-support-the-proactive-support-you-need-to-succeed">SAP Enterprise Support: The proactive support you need to succeed</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://support.sap.com/en/offerings-programs/enterprise-support.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>For many companies, moving to the <strong>cloud is the “next normal”</strong> in business environments. It’s not about “if” anymore – it’s about “when” and “how.” This trend has dominated discussions in the enterprise technology space for a long time and has been further accelerated by <a href="/covid-19">the global pandemic</a>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In a <a href="https://www.cio.com/article/3611419/cios-say-public-cloud-migration-is-essential-for-survival.html">recent survey</a> of U.S.-based CIOs, 85% of respondents said that moving to the cloud was the foundation for a future-ready enterprise, enabling improved productivity and providing the speed and flexibility businesses need to respond quickly to changing conditions. The more insecure environments get – and the pandemic, climate change, and many other elements today contribute strongly to insecurity – the more cloud benefits like flexibility and less bundled commitments to technology will play a role.</p>
  <p>Moving to the cloud is not like flipping a switch. Having built up extensive and customized on-premise hardware and software landscapes over time, many companies will need time to move their business processes to a cloud-based environment, especially taking into account the more standardized nature of software as a service (SaaS). This will result in having many different software deployment and consumption models: some will be public cloud, some private cloud or on hyperscalers, some staying on-premise at least in the mid-term. Despite such mixed IT landscapes, customers expect a seamless end-to-end experience from their vendor – especially in support.</p>
  <p>At SAP, this expectation is nothing new. In fact, this has always been core to our support strategy. Even before the days of cloud, SAP strove to offer a comprehensive set of business solutions tightly integrated for end-to-end business processes, with seamless experiences on user interfaces, data, and support. This core principle still fits perfectly in the cloud world and provides enormous opportunity for customer value in landscapes that are hybrid or in transition.</p>
  <p>So, what does end-to-end support mean? At SAP, this is about having a <strong>unified approach to all aspects of support</strong>. The goal is one feature-rich, foundational support offering, one customer-facing support interface, one support infrastructure, and one support organization that maintains a strong global culture of service and expertise.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="say-hello-to-your-digital-companion-sap-for-me">Say hello to your digital companion, SAP for Me</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://me.sap.com/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Currently, SAP solutions are accompanied by our flagship support offering <a href="https://support.sap.com/en/offerings-programs/enterprise-support.html">SAP Enterprise Support</a>, which is embedded in cloud subscriptions and is the offering of choice for on-premise SAP software solutions. This can provide our customers with the confidence that they will receive the same high-quality of support for their entire landscape, no matter the SAP solution they happen to be using at any given moment. We understand that one end-to-end business process might touch several systems and SAP software solutions and, therefore, a support issue will not exist in a vacuum of a single product only. We have the expertise and culture of collaboration to look at problems holistically across an integrated SAP environment.</p>
  <p>Here are some recent <strong>examples of our continued expansion of customer value</strong>:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>In 2020 we launched <a href="https://support.sap.com/en/alm/sap-cloud-alm.html">SAP Cloud ALM</a>, SAP’s next-generation <strong>cloud-based application lifecycle management solution</strong> that includes best practices and mechanisms to manage and monitor integrated landscapes, not siloed by specific products. Developed to support the implementation and operation of SAP solutions, it is continually expanding its coverage of cloud and on-premise deployments.</li>
    <li>We are always striving to find new ways of making access to support easier for our customers. In 2020, SAP launched a new <strong>unified “digital front door”</strong> called <a href="https://me.sap.com/">SAP for Me</a>. The vision for this personalized portal is that customers and partners can access all information, insights, and tasks related to SAP. During the next year, many more support-related tasks and reports will also be made available on SAP for Me to help give customers an end-to-end view of their SAP assets, services, interactions, and more.</li>
    <li>In the last few years, we have introduced new ways for customers to get <strong>direct access to support experts and managers</strong>. It started with <a href="https://support.sap.com/en/my-support/product-support.html#section_519294480">Expert Chat</a> – here, SAP has recently delivered the <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/pulse/sap-customers-get-on-the-spot-support-million-times-heckmann">1,000,000th on-the-spot support</a>. Customers can start a chat directly with a technical support engineer or <a href="https://support.sap.com/en/my-support/product-support.html#section_1575600800">schedule a meeting</a> at their convenience. They can even schedule a <a href="https://support.sap.com/en/my-support/product-support.html#section_193743618">meeting with a support manager</a>.</li>
    <li>Sometimes it’s even better if you can <strong>get a solution automatically</strong>. As you would expect from an industry leader, SAP is exploring the next frontier of support innovation: artificial intelligence (AI). For example, the <a href="https://support.sap.com/en/my-support/product-support.html#section_1903672625">Incident Solution Matching</a> service analyzes a customer’s problem description while they are typing it into the support case and suggests potential solutions. <a href="https://support.sap.com/en/my-support/product-support.html#section_1255553798">Built-In Support</a>, with its digital support assistant, is already available in SAP S/4HANA Cloud and will be integrated into more products in time. We have launched the <a href="https://blogs.sap.com/2020/11/27/machine-translation-integration-to-last-communication-from-sap-support-for-customer-incidents">automatic translation of the last incident</a> and support assets like <a href="https://blogs.sap.com/2018/03/07/self-service-machine-translation-for-sap-notes-and-knowledge-base-articles-in-the-sap-one-support-launchpad/">SAP Notes or a SAP Knowledge Base Article</a>. And artificial intelligence can also help spot problems before they occur and provide recommendations to prevent future issues.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>Through it all, SAP provides the <strong>flexibility</strong> customers need to make the most of their business while saving time and resources. Whether a company is moving to the public cloud, balancing cloud and on-premise solutions, or just exploring cloud elements at its edges, we can provide the support it needs to be agile and resilient in today’s markets.</p>
  <p>The next generation of support is the baseline. It is seamless, end-to-end, proactive, multi-channeled, and intelligent in order to let our customers focus on what matters most to them: driving their business.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/built-in-support</category>
            <category>news-tag/expert-chat</category>
            <category>news-tag/incident-solution-matching</category>
            <category>product/sap-cloud-alm</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-enterprise-support</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-for-me</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Lowers Cost of Test and Demo Environment for Partners and Enhances Real-Time Partner Dashboard to Boost Partner Success]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/sap-lowers-cost-test-demo-environment-partners-enhances-dashboard</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/sap-lowers-cost-test-demo-environment-partners-enhances-dashboard</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP plans to offer partners significantly reduced subscription fees for its test and demonstration environment licenses.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-for-me</category>
            <category>product/sap-learning-hub</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-partner-demo-environment</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-partneredge</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>