<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[AHA! Moments in D&I: Disability Inclusion with Disability:IN]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/aha-moments-disability-inclusion</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/aha-moments-disability-inclusion</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Jill Houghton of Disability:IN talks to SAP's Supriya Jha about how leadership culture is key to disability inclusion. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-network-groups</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Equipping the Next Generation of Underrepresented Talent for a Career in Tech]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/equipping-next-generation-underrepresented-talent-tech</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/equipping-next-generation-underrepresented-talent-tech</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP’s digital skills initiative helps prepare underrepresented groups for a career in tech through a free SAP Certification course.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1516454e29028b1edfdf3049f7d0417f3f4530c3f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1516454e29028b1edfdf3049f7d0417f3f4530c3f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1516454e29028b1edfdf3049f7d0417f3f4530c3f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Equipping the Next Generation of Underrepresented Talent for a Career in Tech" src="./media_1516454e29028b1edfdf3049f7d0417f3f4530c3f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="equipping-the-next-generation-of-underrepresented-talent-for-a-career-in-tech">Equipping the Next Generation of Underrepresented Talent for a Career in Tech</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>“I just never saw myself in tech.”</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>This is what I heard during my discussion with the first cohort of SAP’s <a href="https://learning.sap.com/digital-skills">digital</a> <a href="https://learning.sap.com/digital-skills?campaigncode=CRM-YD24-ISM-2422141&#x26;source=blog-glo-Unrepped_Talent">skills</a> <a href="https://learning.sap.com/digital-skills">initiative</a>, a program that helps equip underrepresented and underserved groups for a career in the tech industry through participation in a free SAP Certification course.</p>
  <p>How could it be that in a time when companies need to find talent quickly to fill the need for technically skilled roles – a need that is becoming more urgent by the day – there is an entire population of determined, driven people who feel as though they do not belong in the tech industry?</p>
  <h2 id="the-current-state-of-diversity-in-technology">The Current State of Diversity in Technology</h2>
  <p>The numbers speak volumes: only <a href="https://ncwit.org/resource/bythenumbers/">27% of all computing-related jobs are held by women</a>. Only 3% of those jobs are held by Black women and 1% are held by Latina women. For me, it has always been impossible to ignore the lack of representation in the tech industry. I am acutely aware of when I am the only woman in the room – let alone the only Black woman.</p>
  <p>But this is changing. Companies have begun implementing diversity-forward hiring practices to try to minimize barriers for populations that have historically been overlooked. The percentage of <a href="https://www.naceweb.org/diversity-equity-and-inclusion/individuals-with-disabilities/ready-willing-but-still-underemployed/e619e772-a54b-4df6-858c-9ca50717a5a0">employers with diversity recruiting efforts</a> rose from 56% in 2016 to 88% in 2021. Though there is now targeted backlash, numerous employers remain committed to their diversity, equity, and inclusion (DE&#x26;I) goals for the workforce.</p>
  <p>These initiatives have proven to be important to younger generations. In a few years, millennials and Gen Z will make up the majority of our workforce – and they want to work for companies that align with their values. A 2022 survey from the <a href="https://www.naceweb.org/diversity-equity-and-inclusion/individuals-with-disabilities/ready-willing-but-still-underemployed/835bc35a-e4be-42fb-b838-d06086cb87bc">National Association of Colleges and Employers (NACE)</a> found that 76% of recent graduates indicated that <a href="/topics/diversity-and-inclusion">diversity, equity, and inclusion efforts</a> were “very important” or “extremely important” when considering their future employers.</p>
  <h2 id="helping-underserved-groups-break-into-tech">Helping Underserved Groups Break into Tech</h2>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="accelerate-your-career-with-our-digital-skills-initiative">Accelerate your career with our digital skills initiative</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://learning.sap.com/digital-skills?campaigncode=CRM-YD24-ISM-2422141&#x26;source=blog-glo-Unrepped_Talent">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>If we want diverse workforces, we must support and create targeted channels to source diverse talent. It is imperative that these groups – including women, people of color, veterans, and others – are given the resources to excel in high tech. I have seen firsthand how our digital skills initiative is making an impact on individuals and their communities, working to ensure that talent from all backgrounds can participate in this exciting era of technological innovation. At SAP, we offer training on products like <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/s4hana.html?campaigncode=CRM-YD24-ISM-2422141&#x26;source=blog-glo-Unrepped_Talent">SAP S/4HANA Cloud</a> and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp.html?campaigncode=CRM-YD24-ISM-2422141&#x26;source=blog-glo-Unrepped_Talent">SAP ERP</a>, whether through programs like the digital skills initiative or on <a href="https://learninghub.sap.com/?campaigncode=CRM-YD24-ISM-2422141&#x26;source=blog-glo-Unrepped_Talent">SAP Learning Hub</a>, helping anyone interested in jump-starting their career in tech.</p>
  <p>Without diverse perspectives, we leave out too many pieces of the puzzle to see the big picture. This deficit is particularly obvious in technology, given its influence on everything from how we shop to how we govern. It is unsustainable to expect lasting market viability from products that are developed by and marketed to one type of person. Put simply, employing diverse talent is essential to long-term success.</p>
  <h2 id="how-companies-can-recruit-diverse-talent">How Companies Can Recruit Diverse Talent</h2>
  <p>For companies that are looking for the next pool of employees to solve today’s business challenges, it is time to consider non-traditional avenues of talent, like graduates from SAP’s digital skills initiative. Each cohort comes equipped with SAP Certification, self-motivation, and a strong work ethic. This is a special opportunity to pull from a curated group of strong candidates, not just because of their new skills but because of demonstrated curiosity and drive that is not easy to find.</p>
  <p>SAP makes these trained and certified candidates available to recruiters at no charge. Want to get access to SAP-certified, ready-to-hire talent? Interested in adopting a cohort? <a href="https://learning.sap.com/digital-skills/hire-talent?campaigncode=CRM-YD24-ISM-2422141&#x26;source=blog-glo-Unrepped_Talent">Contact us</a> to see how you can start hiring and get involved.</p>
  <h2 id="register-for-the-digital-skills-initiative-as-a-participant">Register for the Digital Skills Initiative as a Participant</h2>
  <p>If you are interested in expanding your career opportunities by learning in-demand skills and achieving an SAP Certification free of charge, apply for the digital skills initiative using the <a href="https://community.sap.com/t5/beginner-corner-blog-posts/digital-skills-initiative-applicant-guide-for-self-study-candidates/ba-p/273119">applicant guide</a>. This is a fantastic opportunity for those who want to make a career switch to tech.</p>
  <p>To those who never pictured themselves in the tech industry, picture it. There is a place for you. Take this as a sign to invest in yourself and create a new path to success.</p>
  <h2 id="making-an-impact-on-future-generations">Making an Impact on Future Generations</h2>
  <p>When I talked with this first cohort of the digital skills initiative, I saw how they take great pride in their certification. For some, these new skills will prove to be life-changing.</p>
  <p>My goal is to support initiatives that aim to ensure that everyone, from all backgrounds, can pursue their interests in finding a career in tech. When we leave these doors closed, we not only rob those shut out of the opportunity, but all of us from the creativity, perspectives, and outcomes they could deliver.</p>
  <p>I am incredibly proud of SAP’s work in empowering people to pursue a career in technology. I believe that we are developing the future of innovation through programs like the digital skills initiative, and I cannot wait to see how similar programs will evolve in the future.</p>
  <p>If you are an NGO, university, or an SAP partner or customer, contact us at <a href="mailto:partners.digitalskills@sap.com">partners.digitalskills@sap.com</a> to learn more. If you are interested in applying to the digital skills initiative, <a href="https://groups.community.sap.com/t5/beginner-corner-discussions/creating-an-sap-account-and-getting-started-in-the-community/m-p/260744">create an SAP account</a> to start your journey.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Etosha Thurman is chief marketing and solutions officer for Intelligent Spend and Business Network at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>product/sap-learning-hub</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Helping Women-Owned Businesses Thrive in the Global Economy]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/helping-women-owned-businesses-thrive-weconnect-international</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/helping-women-owned-businesses-thrive-weconnect-international</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[WEConnect International looked to SAP Business Network and SAP Ariba to help achieve its mission of supporting women-ownedsuppliers.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1eed9a4483f7bc530c8c8f4393ca753b15c1d9c6b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1eed9a4483f7bc530c8c8f4393ca753b15c1d9c6b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1eed9a4483f7bc530c8c8f4393ca753b15c1d9c6b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Helping Women-Owned Businesses Thrive in the Global Economy" src="./media_1eed9a4483f7bc530c8c8f4393ca753b15c1d9c6b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="helping-women-owned-businesses-thrive-in-the-global-economy">Helping Women-Owned Businesses Thrive in the Global Economy</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>When Danielle Thomé was a teenager, she asked her father for a job. That’s not unusual, especially since her father was the founder of Projex Engenharia, a successful business in Brazil. But the business focused on civil and industrial construction, an industry where a 15-year-old girl didn’t fit the typical job description, despite her passion for civil engineering. Although Thomé would eventually take over her father’s business, her road to success was paved with many challenges.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“One of the biggest challenges I faced was the age-old problem of gender discrimination,” Thomé recalled years later. She is one of many women driven to lead businesses that reflect their life passions.</p>
  <p>Like other entrepreneurial women, she needed support. But where are the networks to help women turn their passions into successful businesses? Thomé found her network in an SAP customer. <a href="https://weconnectinternational.org/">WEConnect International</a> connects women-owned businesses to qualified buyers around the world. As a result of becoming WEConnect International certified – and a lot of hard work by Thomé and her team – Projex Engenharia’s revenue grew by a staggering 200% in just two years.</p>
  <h2 id="many-challenges-huge-potential-impact">Many Challenges, Huge Potential Impact</h2>
  <p>Women who start and lead businesses face unique challenges. Cultural and social norms, or simply being underestimated by investors, can impede their entrepreneurial efforts. <a href="https://hbr.org/2023/02/for-female-founders-only-fundraising-from-female-vcs-comes-at-a-cost">Harvard Business Review</a> observes that “women are massively under-represented among both venture-backed entrepreneurs and VC investors.” It adds that companies founded solely by women receive <a href="https://pitchbook.com/news/articles/the-vc-female-founders-dashboard">less than 3%</a> of all venture capital investments.</p>
  <p>Also, the pandemic exacerbated the imbalance in unpaid care work – managing the household or caring for children and aging parents – which disproportionally affects women in business.</p>
  <p>Women must also deal with the challenges other businesses face, including access to markets, information technology gaps, and the red tape involved with government programs designed to help new businesses.</p>
  <p>Yet despite these challenges, women-owned and women-led businesses offer the potential to make a significant impact on the global economy. The <a href="https://www.weforum.org/agenda/2018/01/this-is-why-women-must-play-a-greater-role-in-the-global-economy/">World Economic Forum (WEF)</a> observed that “societies with greater gender equality not only offer better socioeconomic opportunities for women, but also tend to grow faster and more equitably.”</p>
  <p>The WEF also reports that advancing women’s employment <a href="https://initiatives.weforum.org/accelerators-network/gender-parity">could add US$12 trillion to global GDP and boost some countries’ economic output by as much as 35%</a>.</p>
  <p>Yet despite a clear business case, the WEF sees global progress stagnating.</p>
  <h2 id="who-has-the-power-to-drive-change-all-of-us">Who Has the Power to Drive Change? All of Us.</h2>
  <p>Traditionally, the <a href="/topics/procurement">procurement</a> function within larger organizations has held the power to fill supply chain gaps and build networks of suppliers. Yet today, other voices are making themselves heard. Consumers are expressing preferences to buy from women and other diverse businesses. Around the world – for example in the United States, Australia, and Canada – government regulations are requiring increased diversity and inclusion.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-business-network-powers-transparency-resiliency-and-sustainability">SAP Business Network powers transparency, resiliency, and sustainability</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-network.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Additionally, the C-suite is reframing corporate policy to reflect more sophisticated approaches to selecting suppliers. In my role as customer officer, SAP Intelligent Spend &#x26; Business Network, I see business leaders prioritizing inclusive sourcing metrics within their procurement strategies to help ensure they have access to all the world’s best suppliers, not just the ones they always buy from.</p>
  <p>Concerned about supply chain risks, procurement leaders are increasingly adopting localization strategies. While seeking new local suppliers, they also focus on inclusive sourcing. Of course, finding diverse suppliers is not easy – even local ones. Many women-owned businesses are small entities, not well-known in the business community. They often lack access to communication technology that would help them create greater visibility for the business.</p>
  <p>How can we make it easier to connect enterprise buyers and women-owned businesses?</p>
  <h2 id="creating-connections-with-sap-technology">Creating Connections with SAP Technology</h2>
  <p>As president, CEO, and co-founder of <a href="https://weconnectinternational.org/">WEConnect International</a>, Elizabeth Vazquez is a leader in women’s economic empowerment and global supplier diversity and inclusion. Through WEConnect International, she helps women around the world grow their businesses to create wealth, hire more people, and contribute to the prosperity of their communities.</p>
  <p>Last week, she participated in panel discussions during the World Economic Forum Annual Meeting in Davos, Switzerland. The discussions focused on opportunities to direct more corporate spend to women-owned businesses, not only to do good but to close supply chain gaps.</p>
  <p>“Women-owned businesses are a valuable and under-utilized resource,” she said. “The women who run these businesses understand what their communities need most, and they are in a unique position to help solve them. In the process, they are creating entirely new industries.”</p>
  <p>WEConnect International recognizes that to compete in the global marketplace, women-owned businesses must be visible to potential customers. It developed the WECommunity platform, a global register of women-owned businesses that makes it easier for buyers to find women-owned suppliers.</p>
  <p>Unfortunately, the initial version of WECommunity relied on technology that delivered a poor user experience, making searching the register cumbersome. WEConnect International needed a scalable, global solution that offered smooth user experiences in multiple languages for buyers and suppliers.</p>
  <p>The <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/spend-management/supplier-lifecycle.html">SAP Ariba Supplier Lifecycle and Performance</a> solution and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-network.html">SAP Business Network</a> more than met these criteria. As an added advantage, many of the WECommunity member buyers were already transacting on SAP Business Network. SAP partner Premikati Inc., a women-owned business, was engaged to help deploy the SAP solutions.</p>
  <p>In its first year, the improved functionality of WECommunity produced dramatic outcomes:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Buyer membership increased by 91%, a $2 trillion increase in purchasing power.</li>
    <li>Over 6,000 women-owned businesses experienced revenue growth, creating 24,000 new jobs.</li>
    <li>Over 7,800 new registered women-owned businesses joined the database, a 95% growth.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>“By making it easier for women to register their businesses and for large buyers to find them, our online portal based on the SAP Ariba Supplier Lifecycle and Performance solution, SAP Business Network, and SAP Business Technology Platform helps women compete in a global marketplace,” Vazquez explained.</p>
  <h2 id="breaking-through-the-barriers">Breaking Through the Barriers</h2>
  <p>Remember Thomé, the teenage girl who wanted to work in her father’s construction business? Today, she is owner-director of Projex Engenharia, the business her father founded.</p>
  <p><a href="https://weconnectinternational.org/success-stories/danielle-thome/">As a noted in a recent profile</a>, Projex Engenharia earned the WEConnect International Women’s Business Enterprise Certification. Thomé leveraged the global network of women suppliers and large buyers to become a more confident and assertive leader.</p>
  <p>The relationship has also helped produce significant benefits for her business. In just six years, Projex Engenharia landed six large corporations as clients. This enabled the company to hire more people, ensure their safety and well-being, and support social, health, and environmental campaigns.</p>
  <p>SAP is committed to helping all customers achieve their diversity and equity goals. And it is gratifying to know that our technology has become a valuable tool in making this happen.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Megan O’Connor is customer officer for SAP Intelligent Spend &#x26; Business Network.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-spend</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/women-in-leadership</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Driving Economic Growth and Gender Equality Through the Power of Connection]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/weconnect-international-driving-economic-growth-gender-equality</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/weconnect-international-driving-economic-growth-gender-equality</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Innovation Award winner WEConnect International digitally transformed to drive change for gender parity and equitable opportunities.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>sap-award/sap-innovation-awards</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Making SAP Events More Sustainable]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/making-sap-events-more-sustainable</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/making-sap-events-more-sustainable</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP's Jenny Bittmann is on a mission to make customer events more sustainable. Read to learn what steps the company is taking to do so.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-footprint</category>
            <category>news-tag/circular-economy</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[AHA! Moments in D&I: “On the Trail, You Are Open to All People”]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/aha-moments-in-di-peter-lengler</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/aha-moments-in-di-peter-lengler</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Peter Lengler, member of the SAP Supervisory Board, People and Culture Committee, discusses what inclusion awareness means to him.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_114cd1e673570105a7a8224847ff5f416ec46f0ab.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_114cd1e673570105a7a8224847ff5f416ec46f0ab.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_114cd1e673570105a7a8224847ff5f416ec46f0ab.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="AHA! Moments in D&#x26;I: “On the Trail, You Are Open to All People”" src="./media_114cd1e673570105a7a8224847ff5f416ec46f0ab.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="aha-moments-in-di-on-the-trail-you-are-open-to-all-people">AHA! Moments in D&#x26;I: “On the Trail, You Are Open to All People”</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Peter Lengler, member of the SAP Supervisory Board, People and Culture Committee, talks about the process of learning to see the barriers that others face.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In the latest episode of the AHA! Moments in Diversity &#x26; Inclusion video series, SAP Chief Diversity &#x26; Inclusion Officer Supriya Jha and Lengler discuss what inclusion awareness means to him.</p>
  <p>As part of the <a href="https://www.sap.com/investors/en/governance/supervisory-board.html#committees">SAP Supervisory Board</a>, the People and Culture Committee is dedicated to fostering a culture of innovation, performance, diversity, organizational design, and integrity. It also maintains SAP’s network to universities and other stakeholders to support the company’s people strategy.</p>
  <h2 id="on-the-trail">On the Trail</h2>
  <p>The World Economic Forum estimates that more than 150 million people are homeless globally and, for Lengler, meeting one of them further cemented his passion for diversity and inclusion.</p>
  <p>During his 162 days on the Appalachian Trail, Lengler discovered that another hiker he met had been homeless for more than 10 years. Initially, he was a little apprehensive about this fact – and the hiker. However, he quickly discovered that sharing a common goal – in this case to complete the trail – meant that any preconceptions or concerns about this formerly homeless individual ceased to be relevant. They were to spend the next four weeks hiking the trail together.</p>
  <p>“On the trail,” Lengler explains, “you have the same goal, and you are open to all people there.”</p>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_185f5c43b6746d301d2ea2ceb663a4eab466197f6.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_185f5c43b6746d301d2ea2ceb663a4eab466197f6.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_185f5c43b6746d301d2ea2ceb663a4eab466197f6.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="On the Trail You Are Open to All People: AHA! Moments in D&#x26;I" src="./media_185f5c43b6746d301d2ea2ceb663a4eab466197f6.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://youtu.be/1eiCHx4B0iY">On the Trail You Are Open to All People: AHA! Moments in D&#x26;I</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="unlearning-ingrained-behavior-patterns">Unlearning Ingrained Behavior Patterns</h2>
  <p>Lengler reflects on those groups of individuals he refers to as “old white men clubs” who have never consciously suffered exclusion and have no understanding of the barriers that others face. Identifying unconscious biases and unlearning ingrained behavior patterns is critical to sustaining the success of diversity and inclusion initiatives.</p>
  <p>For Lengler, the important aspect of inclusion is not just to increase the number of employees from diverse backgrounds but to create a culture of true inclusion. Passionately, he explains that for him true inclusion means 100% acceptance for all team members, regardless of their backgrounds. Only team members who are 100% accepted and truly included in all aspects of team life will be able to bring their best selves to work and can be “open in their voice and their mind.”</p>
  <h2 id="the-aha-moment">The AHA! Moment</h2>
  <p>On the Appalachian Trail, Lengler experienced first-hand how a common goal and common hardship can bring people together. Above all else, someone who has different life experience or is in some way different from the rest of the team will bring another point of view and, says Lengler, “will look at the same problem in a different manner,” crystallizing his conviction that when you share your goal, “you can reach it together more easily instead of making it alone.”</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="its-time-to-run-a-world-where-our-differences-are-celebrated-equity-is-fostered-and-everyone-belongs">It’s time to run a world where our differences are celebrated, equity is fostered, and everyone belongs</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/our-values/diversity.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="diversity-and-inclusion-at-sap">Diversity and Inclusion at SAP</h2>
  <p>In its <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2023/04/4e7e324b-6e7e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">2022 Diversity and Inclusion report</a>, SAP states its mission to become “the most inclusive company in the world.” In the U.S., for example, more than 40% of employees are from underrepresented groups. SAP is on track to achieve long-term gender goals and has a five-generation workforce.</p>
  <p>One of the initiatives that the Global Diversity and Inclusion Office has launched to help further <a href="/topics/diversity-at-sap">SAP’s progress towards becoming the most inclusive company in the world</a> is the Inclusive Mindset Challenge. This challenge allows employees to learn about inclusion topics and the importance of becoming an ally for marginalized groups at their own pace. The challenge comprises a broad range of micro-learnings, such as menopause, transphobia, or sexism to name a few. In 2022, more than 11,000 employees completed this challenge. New challenges are added regularly; recent additions include indigenous inclusion and infuse D&#x26;I with AI.</p>
  <h2 id="sap-inclusion-month">SAP Inclusion Month</h2>
  <p>SAP has designated October 2023 as SAP Inclusion Month. All employees are invited to join the inclusion journey and to get involved in an Employee Network Group (ENG) journey, allyship journey, and, for leaders, the intentional inclusion journey.</p>
  <p>With more that 40,000 employees, ENGs are voluntary, employee-led diversity and inclusion initiatives representing groups such as visually impaired employees, caregivers, or Latinos.</p>
  <p>With the allyship inclusion journey, employees are invited to use their privilege and power to support marginalized groups. With the intentional inclusion journey, leaders learn about intentional inclusion practices that can help further advance SAP’s journey to become a truly inclusive workplace.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Top photo courtesy of SAP employee Celia Carillo.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-at-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-network-groups</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[On the Trail You Are Open to All People: AHA! Moments in D&I]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/videos/on-the-trail-you-are-open-to-all-people-aha-moments-in-di</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/videos/on-the-trail-you-are-open-to-all-people-aha-moments-in-di</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Peter Lengler, member of the SAP Supervisory Board, People and Culture Committee, talks about the process of learning to see the barriers that others face.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_185f5c43b6746d301d2ea2ceb663a4eab466197f6.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_185f5c43b6746d301d2ea2ceb663a4eab466197f6.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_185f5c43b6746d301d2ea2ceb663a4eab466197f6.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="On the Trail You Are Open to All People: AHA! Moments in D&#x26;I" src="./media_185f5c43b6746d301d2ea2ceb663a4eab466197f6.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="on-the-trail-you-are-open-to-all-people-aha-moments-in-di">On the Trail You Are Open to All People: AHA! Moments in D&#x26;I</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_185f5c43b6746d301d2ea2ceb663a4eab466197f6.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_185f5c43b6746d301d2ea2ceb663a4eab466197f6.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_185f5c43b6746d301d2ea2ceb663a4eab466197f6.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="On the Trail You Are Open to All People: AHA! Moments in D&#x26;I" src="./media_185f5c43b6746d301d2ea2ceb663a4eab466197f6.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1eiCHx4B0iY">On the Trail You Are Open to All People: AHA! Moments in D&#x26;I</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Peter Lengler, member of the SAP Supervisory Board, People and Culture Committee, talks about the process of learning to see the barriers that others face.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In the latest episode of the AHA! Moments for Diversity &#x26; Inclusion video series, SAP Chief Diversity &#x26; Inclusion Officer Supriya Jha and Lengler discuss what inclusion awareness means to him.</p>
  <p><a href="/2023/11/aha-moments-in-di-peter-lengler">Read the article to learn more.</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/video</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Actionable Strategies for Elevating Women in Supply Chain]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/elevating-women-in-supply-chain-actionable-strategies</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/elevating-women-in-supply-chain-actionable-strategies</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A recent discussion hosted by SAP and EY shed light on important trends, challenges, and strategies for advancing women in supply chain.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f9da2820936b7055a711bcac1c73b9837db4504d.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f9da2820936b7055a711bcac1c73b9837db4504d.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1f9da2820936b7055a711bcac1c73b9837db4504d.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Actionable Strategies for Elevating Women in Supply Chain" src="./media_1f9da2820936b7055a711bcac1c73b9837db4504d.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="actionable-strategies-for-elevating-women-in-supply-chain">Actionable Strategies for Elevating Women in Supply Chain</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Supporting and retaining women in <a href="/topics/supply-chain-management">supply chain</a> remains critical to not only the success of women in this space, but in many ways also to fostering sustainable and resilient supply chains.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>According to a <a href="https://www.gartner.com/en/newsroom/press-releases/2023-06-29-gartner-says-26-percent-of-supply-chain-csuite-roles-now-filled-by-women">study by Gartner</a>, women representation in C-suite supply chain roles has risen from 19% in 2022 to 26% in 2023. Encouragingly, there has also been an increase in the percentage of women in the supply chain workforce, from 39% to 41%. While these are considered positive shifts in the industry, there is a notable lag in the percentage of frontline roles held by women in this space, ranging from 26% to 34% across various leadership levels.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="design-risk-out-of-your-supply-chain-with-sap">Design risk out of your supply chain with SAP</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In a recent panel discussion hosted by the SAP North America Business Women’s Network and EY Women in SAP, women supply chain leaders shed light on some important trends, challenges, and strategies for advancing women in supply chain.</p>
  <p>The discussion was moderated by Lori Foster, managing director for EY SAP Consulting. On the panel, I was joined by Etosha Thurman, chief marketing and solutions officer for SAP Intelligent Spend &#x26; Business Network, Regenia Sanders, partner at EY Business Consulting, and Angelee Tango, manager for EY SAP Extended Warehouse Management. Opening remarks were provided by Yolanda Kirksey, SAP Alliance leader and director for SAP Ariba U.S. Go-to-Market for EY.</p>
  <p>A few key strategies emerged from the discussion for how organizations can help to elevate women in supply chain:</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>1. Support the choice to stay with flexibility</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>A consequence of the global pandemic was a moment of reassessment for women juggling full-time careers with responsibilities at home. In that moment, many women (and men) chose to shift their priorities outside of work or simply had to make that shift to address the needs at home. What we as business leaders can learn from observing this trend is the need to create environments that support women and accommodate work-life balance.</p>
  <p>An important point called out in this panel discussion is that work-life balance looks different for everyone. Organizations must set an expectation of respect and boundaries that allow for all employees to manage the many responsibilities they have outside of work — regardless of marital status, if they have children or grandchildren, or if they are a caregiver in another capacity. A culture supportive of pursuing career aspirations while maintaining a healthy balance in personal life empowers women to effectively set and maintain boundaries as well as seek help when needed.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>2. Recruit for top skills to succeed in supply chain roles</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The panel named skills like curiosity, customer focus, relationship building, change management, crisis management, and communication as both crucial factors for success in this field and areas in which women tend to excel, citing the <a href="https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1111/poms.13329">Production and Operations Management Society (POMS) study</a>. Collaboration was underscored by several panelists as essential. Tango shared, “From determining the technology we want to use to the final stage of implementation, the need to continuously evaluate requires everyone to be on board.”</p>
  <p>The panel suggested that having more women engaged in these transformative projects helping facilitate collaboration is a strategic way to support innovation that sticks. As Sanders stated, “Making sure [internal stakeholders’] input is being heard when gathering requirements is a critical difference-maker to having an organization that actually embraces technology versus being intimidated by it.”</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>3. Provide forums that encourage open discussion</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>At any stage in your career, it can be helpful to hear of the challenges other women supply chain professionals have faced and how they overcame them. What Foster shared on this topic stood out to me: “It’s easy for people to see where you are today, but not what you went through to get there.” That sense of mutual respect and understanding helps to build confidence.</p>
  <p>Role models also play an important role. Thurman spoke to the importance of representation: “Seeing people who look like you and can manage a life like you is important to how we move forward.”</p>
  <p>Of the many valuable individual takeaways from this discussion, a few specific pieces of advice resonated with me for women looking to elevate their careers in supply chain:</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>1. Set and hold boundaries where they make sense for you</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>You must be willing to reshape your own conceptions of how you need to be perceived and what your role needs to be. Instead of trying to meet this picture-perfect standard, work from an understanding of what you want and need so you can set and maintain reasonable boundaries with a career that requires significant flexibility.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>2. Know that you belong and operate in that way</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As a woman working in a male-dominated field, it is likely that you will experience moments where you or your contributions are slighted, discounted, or ignored. While we are working to change that behavior, when this happens it’s important to remember to focus on what you want to achieve. If you feel that you are not yet at a point in your career to remedy the situation directly, ask for help.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>3. Use your voice</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>There is an advantage to being different. If you are one woman in a room of 50 men and you can clearly articulate your point well, you will be remembered. As you build your brand, opportunities will follow. And when you have the chance to support other women in your field, lend your voice to advocate, guide, and champion the next generation of leaders.</p>
  <p>There is a lot that we can learn from each other, in and across industries. These leaders conveyed inspiring journeys in their supply chain careers where they have encountered and continue to navigate a wide spectrum of challenges, but also have found fulfillment in this line of work. This open discussion represented a significant stride toward acknowledging the challenges, opportunities, and collective efforts needed to empower and elevate women in supply chain.</p>
  <p>As these forums continue, my hope is that they will not only support and inspire women through a vast network of supply chain professionals, but also drive toward a more equitable and inclusive supply chain landscape.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Darcy MacClaren is chief revenue officer for SAP Digital Supply Chain.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-sap-news-on-linkedin-for-the-latest-updates">Connect with SAP News on LinkedIn for the latest updates</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news/">Follow now</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>news-tag/gender-equality</category>
            <category>news-tag/women-in-tech</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Leveraging SAP SuccessFactors Solutions: Five Ways User Experience Drives DEI&B Success]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/five-ways-sap-successfactors-ux-drives-deib</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/five-ways-sap-successfactors-ux-drives-deib</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP SuccessFactor's focus on UX helps businesses advance DEI&B by offering an interface that can address employee needs in the flow of work.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-employee-central</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-learning</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-performance-goals</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-workforce-analytics</category>
            <category>news-tag/ux</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[People, Pizza, Planet, and Profit: Driving Positive Outcomes by Investing in Employees]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/mod-pizza-driving-positive-outcomes-investing-in-employees</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/mod-pizza-driving-positive-outcomes-investing-in-employees</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[MOD Pizza's “pizza as a platform” mission provides employment opportunities regardless of employee background. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/people-sustainability</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How the “Broken Rung” Is Impacting Women in the Workplace and How HXM Technology Can Help]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/broken-rung-women-in-workplace-hxm-technology</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/broken-rung-women-in-workplace-hxm-technology</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Organizations are using SAP SuccessFactors solutions to address the "broken rung" and other systemic biases in the workplace.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d46530ef90cfa2cd40a0002001a263d2368e417e.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d46530ef90cfa2cd40a0002001a263d2368e417e.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1d46530ef90cfa2cd40a0002001a263d2368e417e.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="How the “Broken Rung” Is Impacting Women in the Workplace and How HXM Technology Can Help" src="./media_1d46530ef90cfa2cd40a0002001a263d2368e417e.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="how-the-broken-rung-is-impacting-women-in-the-workplace-and-how-hxm-technology-can-help">How the “Broken Rung” Is Impacting Women in the Workplace and How HXM Technology Can Help</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Representation of women in leadership has been increasing in recent years. However, only about 25% of C-suite leaders and 40% of manager-level positions are held by women today. According to psychologists, biased perceptions of women in the workplace may be partially to blame, preventing women from obtaining and being successful in leadership-level roles. The inability to access higher levels of leadership is termed the “broken rung,” and there is still a lot of work to do to repair it.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Recently, a group of psychologists at the annual Society for Industrial &#x26; Organizational Psychology conference met to present emerging research on the broken rung. Caitlynn Sendra, Ph.D., experience product scientist at SAP SuccessFactors, who hosted the session, explained that because of the roles men and women historically held in society, our stereotypes around men and women can carry over into today’s workplace, even if not intentionally. “Men are stereotypically thought to be agentic, direct, and task-focused – traits historically associated with leaders. On the other hand, women are stereotyped to be nurturing, communal, and community-focused,” explained Sendra. Although this has led women to be seen as less leader-like, Sendra presented original research on how this may actually give women leaders an advantage when it comes to influencing organizational culture.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-the-latest-research-from-the-sap-successfactors-growth--insights-team">Read the latest research from the SAP SuccessFactors Growth &#x26; Insights team</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/dg/hr-meta-trends-2023/index.html?campaigncode=CRM-YI23-HXM-2055448&#x26;source=ctabutton-glo-SAPNews">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Throughout the session, the researchers presented data on several different sources of potential bias around women leaders, including 360-degree reviews, “high-potential” programs, and feedback. For example, Dr. Martin Lanik, CEO of Pinsight, demonstrated that men are three times more likely than women to be identified as “high potential.” Additionally, Dr. Stefanie Mockler, co-founder of The Violet Group, showed data indicating that managers tended to “soften” their feedback to women. The message of the session was clear: businesses need to be proactive in removing this bias from people processes in order to level the playing field for women leaders.</p>
  <p>The session ended with a discussion about what <a href="/topics/human-resources">HR</a> leaders can do to help reduce bias towards women leaders. Providing training on bias awareness and reduction was one solution provided by the researchers. HR technology was also called out as a key piece of the puzzle.</p>
  <p>At SAP, we’re working with organizations of all sizes to help drive more equitable and inclusive HR strategies that empower equitable experiences for every employee, including women. With embedded features throughout <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm.html?campaigncode=CRM-YI23-HXM-2055448&#x26;source=text-glo-SAPNews">SAP SuccessFactors Human Experience Management (HXM) Suite</a>, our customers are provided with the tools they need to help detect and prevent unconscious bias while also gaining the insights required to make decisions that can cultivate a diverse and inclusive workforce.</p>
  <p>Here are three examples of how organizations are using SAP SuccessFactors solutions to help solve for the broken rung and other systemic biases in the workplace:</p>
  <h3 id="sanlam">Sanlam</h3>
  <p><a href="https://www.sap.com/asset/dynamic/2022/11/7c370ed5-4e7e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Sanlam</a> is one of the largest financial services groups in South Africa and believes building a diverse, future-ready workforce is key to becoming the unrivaled industry leader in Africa and to strengthening its position abroad. With 105,000 team members, including both permanent employees and contingent staff, Sanlam is committed to ensuring access and opportunity across its total workforce.</p>
  <p>With SAP SuccessFactors solutions, Sanlam is bridging the gap between permanent and contingent workers by providing a consistent experience for all workers. With visibility into the total workforce, management can identify skill gaps and offer all workers development opportunities that match future priorities. And with group-wide analytics, Sanlam’s leadership can set and actively track targets around race, gender, and disability.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="understand-what-your-people-need-how-they-work-and-what-motivates-them">Understand what your people need, how they work, and what motivates them</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm.html">Explore SAP SuccessFactors solutions</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“We have all the information we need at the drop of a hat,” said Ronel Pfotenhauer, SAP SuccessFactors portfolio product owner, Sanlam Life Insurance Limited. “For instance, we can report on the number of Black, African females with five years of experience and an MBA as potential candidates for a leadership role, with SAP SuccessFactors solutions acting as a type of internal recruitment portal.”</p>
  <h3 id="the-university-of-toronto">The University of Toronto</h3>
  <p>The University of Toronto’s mission is to build a community where academic and learning opportunities are given to every member of its community, including 12,000 full-time and 14,000 part-time employees across three campuses. Its recent work on the anti-Black racism task force and similar initiatives to do with anti-semitism and anti-Asian racism demonstrates the organization’s commitment to ensuring the principles of equity, diversity, and inclusion are deeply embedded in the fabric of everything it does.</p>
  <p>With SAP SuccessFactors solutions, the University of Toronto is bringing a consistent look and feel to the employee experience, providing comprehensive learning programs and empowering people leaders to create the conditions for all talent to thrive. <a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2022/12/cc9d1c23-5f7e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Watch this video to see how</a>.</p>
  <h3 id="mod-pizza">MOD Pizza</h3>
  <p><a href="https://www.sap.com/asset/dynamic/2023/07/623a5dca-807e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">MOD Pizza</a> is dedicated to making positive social impacts in the lives of its employees and the communities it serves. The company strives to create a more equitable world full of opportunities for those who face barriers to steady employment, such as people formerly incarcerated as well as individuals with intellectual or developmental disabilities. It calls its community of employees the MOD Squad, and the MOD Squad is 10,000 employees strong and growing along with the company.</p>
  <p>With SAP SuccessFactors solutions, MOD Pizza has redefined the value of HR data, processes, and experiences – putting the MOD Squad at the heart of its business success. All candidates and new hires are provided with a welcoming experience to help them feel supported and prepared. All employees are provided with on-demand digital training to encourage continuous learning and growth. And with multiple touchpoints to gather sentiment feedback, MOD Pizza can quickly identify areas for potential improvement.</p>
  <p>“SAP’s dedication to people sustainability struck a chord with us. This focus continues to show us that SAP solutions are the right choice for MOD Pizza because they’re designed to create a fair future full of opportunities for our employees,” said Tara Gambill, senior director of Enterprise Systems, MOD Pizza LLC.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Carrie Klauss is global director of Solution Marketing at SAP SuccessFactors.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-sap-news-delivered-to-your-inbox-every-week">Get the latest SAP news delivered to your inbox every week</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/nl/sap-news-center-newsletter/index.html">Sign up</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
            <category>news-tag/women-in-leadership</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Disability Pride Month: Creating Accessible Content]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/creating-accessible-content</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/creating-accessible-content</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Making content accessible and creating a culture of inclusion and belonging is everyone’s responsibility and benefits everyone. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/accessibility</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pride@SAP: Empowering Change and Championing Diversity and Inclusion Since 2001]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/pridesap-championing-diversity-inclusion</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/pridesap-championing-diversity-inclusion</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Diversity and inclusion are business priorities, and SAP is proud to stand up for LGBTQIA+ inclusion. Learn more about Pride@SAP.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-at-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>news-tag/pridesap</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proud at SAP: Interview with Robyn Arroyo]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/06/proud-at-sap-robyn-arroyo</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/06/proud-at-sap-robyn-arroyo</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Senior Compliance Lead Robyn Arroyo talks about her experiences at SAP and her involvement with Pride@SAP. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-at-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>news-tag/pridesap</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Accelerating Impact Together: Lessons from Diversity & Inclusion Leaders]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/accelerating-impact-together-bwn-global-leadership-summit</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/accelerating-impact-together-bwn-global-leadership-summit</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[At the fifth annual BWN Global Leadership Summit, leaders shared strategies to create workplace environments where everyone can thrive.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11dd914da134050498741203229d56c631625869d.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11dd914da134050498741203229d56c631625869d.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_11dd914da134050498741203229d56c631625869d.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Accelerating Impact Together: Lessons from Diversity &#x26; Inclusion Leaders" src="./media_11dd914da134050498741203229d56c631625869d.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="accelerating-impact-together-lessons-from-diversity--inclusion-leaders">Accelerating Impact Together: Lessons from Diversity &#x26; Inclusion Leaders</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>A panel of diversity and inclusion (D&#x26;I) leaders from Merck, Airbus, Schneider Electric, and SAP gathered at the fifth annual Business Women’s Network (<a href="/2022/04/business-womens-network-empowerment-connection">BWN</a>) Global Leadership Summit and shared the strategies their companies use to create workplace environments where everyone can thrive.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>“<a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/our-values/diversity.html">Diversity and inclusion</a>, in practice, is a matter of continuous learning. Change is rapid — in the world and in technology — and we need to be intentional in putting in the effort to consider diversity in everything that we do.”</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“Our ambition is to become the place to be for all, where everyone has a voice and belongs, regardless of abilities, nationality, background, gender, age, and any other factor,” said Caroline Sehn, Diversity, Equity &#x26; Inclusion lead at Merck. “We truly believe that it will help our success in innovation, technology, and creativity as diverse minds, as well as to become digital enablers for the business, building a workplace accessible and inclusive for all.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b56052fdcc53cded4a113a20a4b80e7631b35bc0.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b56052fdcc53cded4a113a20a4b80e7631b35bc0.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1b56052fdcc53cded4a113a20a4b80e7631b35bc0.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="BWN Global Leadership Summit 2023" src="./media_1b56052fdcc53cded4a113a20a4b80e7631b35bc0.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1500" height="1125">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p><em>L-R: Supriya Jha, Caroline Sehn, Julie Ashton-Howorth, Hoda Monsour, Célia Frey</em></p>
  <p>The rest of the panel agreed with the sentiment, and unanimously agreed that one of the best ways to ensure that D&#x26;I does not fall by the wayside is with data and key performance indicators (KPIs), as is standard practice with other business goals.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-how-sap-is-creating-a-unique-culture-where-everyone-can-be-their-authentic-selves-and-connect-with-each-other">Learn how SAP is creating a unique culture where everyone can be their authentic selves and connect with each other</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/our-values/diversity.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="degree-approach-to-di-at-airbus">360-Degree Approach to D&#x26;I at Airbus</h2>
  <p>Airbus is the largest aeronautics and space company in Europe and a worldwide leader in the aviation industry with more than 130,000 employees. Within the Digital organization, the percentage of women is 25%, a bit higher than the market average of 24%. A strong commitment to raise awareness of younger women and encourage them to pursue digital careers through activities such as special events and mentorship is coordinated in partnership with various associations such as Elles bougent in France.</p>
  <p>Célia Frey, vice president and head of Information Management for Programs, Customer Engagement &#x26; Services at Airbus, explained that the company thinks of diversity from five key perspectives: gender parity, LGBTI+ inclusion, equal opportunities for people with disabilities, accommodating generational gaps, and contributing to the economic and social development of underprivileged neighborhoods.</p>
  <p>On gender parity, for example, Airbus is committed to the United Nations objective of developing women in business and having women in 25% of executive positions in 2025, where the starting situation was 14%.</p>
  <p>Airbus also has a program called Generation A, which aims to bridge the gap between the multiple generations its employees span and a “support an employee” network called Balance for Business, which helps all employees balance work with life commitments and promote gender equity.</p>
  <h2 id="digitall-inclusive-and-diverse-place-for-all-at-merck">Digitall: Inclusive and Diverse Place for All at Merck</h2>
  <p>Merck KGaA, a leading science and technology company operating across healthcare, life science, and electronics sectors, <a href="/2023/02/merck-kgaa-darmstadt-germany-digitalization-joint-innovation">recently announced</a> a strategic partnership with SAP to jointly drive sustainable business practice innovation and digitalization. The company has a goal of gender parity by 2030. To reach this ambition, Merck IT has launched a campaign to help break down stereotypes around gender, nationality, age, family situations, and personal goals.</p>
  <p>Sehn says that Merck CIO Alessandro de Luca is refreshingly honest in acknowledging that IT used to be a male-dominated industry, but now and in the future will need all talents to drive innovation and digitalize the business. Merck IT offers agile work processes and good work life-balance with flexible working hours. There are also mentoring campaigns, talent development, and career training opportunities that enable employees to establish share learnings and establish support networks.</p>
  <h2 id="schneider-electrics-strategy-for-inclusion-and-care-by-design">Schneider Electric’s Strategy for Inclusion and Care by Design</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="explore-saps-employee-network-groups">Explore SAP's Employee Network Groups</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/our-values/diversity.html#engs">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As a leader in the digital transformation of energy management and automation, Schneider Electric also aims to be the most inclusive and caring company in the world. To execute on that vision, the company has created Inclusion and Care by Design, the philosophy to build inclusion and care into all process and elements of company culture.</p>
  <p>Julie Ashton-Howorth, group chief accounting officer at Schneider Electric, explained that all company processes — whether they involve employees or customers or both — feature end-to-end accountability that helps ensure every individual feels respected and safe to be their unique self.</p>
  <p>One of the things Schneider Electric has done to promote diversity in leadership is move away from a single headquarters model to a multi-hub structure that better serves the communities where the company operates. It also transparently shares its journey, progress, processes, and commitments, and co-creates with employees, customers, suppliers, and NGOs to be a truly responsible corporate citizen.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>“Diversity is being invited to the party.<br>Equity is ensuring everyone can get to the dance, regardless of their starting location.<br>Inclusion is being asked to dance together.”</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="di-center-of-excellence-at-sap">D&#x26;I Center of Excellence at SAP</h2>
  <p>SAP Chief Diversity and Inclusion Officer Supriya Jha explained that the company has invested internally and externally in programs that help existing and potential female employees grow and thrive in their careers. For example, there is a D&#x26;I center of excellence that reports to the SAP Executive Board monthly, and houses a data analytics team that monitors the internal and external KPIs related to female progression and provides insightful data to hiring, learning and development teams, and the SAP leadership team, so that they can take intentional steps to retain and advance women at SAP.</p>
  <p>While its ultimate goal is to attain gender parity, SAP is proud to have achieved a milestone goal of 35% women in its workforce and is seeing an increase in the number of women in managerial ranks from 25.5% in 2017 to 29.4% at the close of 2022. In addition, in 2023, SAP was reinstated to the Bloomberg Gender-Equality Index, which recognizes a commitment to advancing women in the workplace.</p>
  <p>All panelists acknowledged that there is more to be done to achieve gender parity and other diversity goals, but they felt positive. Sehn summarized the sentiment: “As the old Buddhist saying goes, ‘One candle can light thousands.’ We need to keep this in mind when we’re working together.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-sap-news-on-linkedin">Connect with SAP News on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/business-womens-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Organizations Are Using SAP SuccessFactors Solutions to Prepare for What’s Next]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/organizations-using-sap-successfactors-2023-hr-meta-trends</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/organizations-using-sap-successfactors-2023-hr-meta-trends</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Organizations are using SAP SuccessFactors solutions to get ahead – and stay ahead – of the curve. Read about our 2023 HR meta-trends.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/mental-health-well-being</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-work-zone</category>
            <category>news-tag/well-being-at-work</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP North America Commits to Mentoring Afghan Refugees]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/sap-north-america-tent-mentoring-afghan-refugees</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/sap-north-america-tent-mentoring-afghan-refugees</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP will work with Tent to mentor 50 Afghan refugees over the next three years and aid their transition into the American job market.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14f9bf1a1a14dd69b3b7557083ccbcfbf1d45bd7a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14f9bf1a1a14dd69b3b7557083ccbcfbf1d45bd7a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_14f9bf1a1a14dd69b3b7557083ccbcfbf1d45bd7a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP North America Commits to Mentoring Afghan Refugees" src="./media_14f9bf1a1a14dd69b3b7557083ccbcfbf1d45bd7a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-north-america-commits-to-mentoring-afghan-refugees">SAP North America Commits to Mentoring Afghan Refugees</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>SAP has committed to mentoring 50 Afghan refugees over the next three years to aid them in their transition into the American job market.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP will work with the <strong>Tent Partnership for Refugees</strong>, a <a href="https://www.tent.org/">non-profit organization founded by Hamdi Ulukaya</a>, the CEO and Chairman of Chobani. As a Turkish immigrant, Ulukaya saw firsthand the power of immigrants finding appropriate employment and how it benefits the refugee and the businesses who hire them.</p>
  <p>I’m excited to be a part of this for several reasons.</p>
  <p><strong>For me, working with Tent is a deeply personal cause</strong>. As a soldier in the US Army’s 75th Ranger Regiment, I deployed twice to Afghanistan during Operation Enduring Freedom. I saw a beautiful country full of incredible people torn apart and ravaged by war.</p>
  <p>In August 2021, I was also one of the thousands of people worldwide who worked feverishly to help evacuate as many Afghans from Kabul as we could. In those two frantic weeks, we did everything possible to save our friends. These men and women were not strangers, but people we had forged deep relationships with. They were some of the bravest and hardest-working men and women I have ever met.</p>
  <p>The men and women this program will mentor are incredibly intelligent and hard-working professionals. Their command of the English language is excellent. They bring technical skills and professional expertise to the table. Like so many before them, they are eager to embrace the American dream.</p>
  <p>But they are in the challenging position of rapidly learning a new culture after being ripped out of their homes — some literally in the middle of the night — while trying to do whatever they can to support their families, both here and, in many cases, back home in Afghanistan.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-what-life-looks-like-at-sap">Learn more about what life looks like at SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://jobs.sap.com/content/Life-At-SAP/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="tent-trains-corporate-mentors-to-help-refugees-find-the-right-employment">Tent Trains Corporate Mentors to Help Refugees Find the Right Employment</h2>
  <p>Led by Veterans@SAP and in partnership with <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/our-values/diversity.html#eng">Employee Network Groups</a> <a href="/2023/04/autism-acceptance-month-sascha-dietsch">Autism Inclusion Network</a>, Black Employees Network, Business Women’s Network, SAP Interfaith Alliance, Latinos@SAP, and Pan-Asians@SAP, this initiative will be working to help these Afghan mentees starting in May.</p>
  <p>Volunteers will provide mentorship, interview prep, resume review, coaching, and access to a more robust professional network as the refugees work to find new employment in the U.S. that is better matched to their skills and expertise. SAP is excited and honored to be a part of this important initiative.</p>
  <h2 id="help-tent-by-joining-the-cause">Help Tent by Joining the Cause</h2>
  <p>This is an opportunity to help these amazing human beings integrate into the American workforce, to enrich this nation through their talents and experiences. That is why Tent’s work is important. It’s why we are so excited to work with them.</p>
  <p>If you are so moved, consider <a href="https://www.tent.org/become-a-member/">becoming a member of Tent.org</a> as they continue their mission to help refugees and immigrants more easily transition into the American work force.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Tom Amenta is a field marketing specialist for Cloud ERP at SAP North America.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-network-groups</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sports and the Metaverse: A Revolutionary Convergence for Inclusion]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/sports-and-metaverse-revolutionary-convergence-inclusivity</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/sports-and-metaverse-revolutionary-convergence-inclusivity</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With the metaverse taking shape, corporations can now use intelligent software to create virtual sporting worlds for inclusivity. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>news-tag/esports</category>
            <category>news-tag/metaverse</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-hana-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-sports-one</category>
            <category>industry/sports-entertainment</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Let’s Meet in the Middle: Autism Acceptance Month]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/autism-acceptance-month-sascha-dietsch</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/autism-acceptance-month-sascha-dietsch</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP employee Sascha Dietsch shares his experience joining SAP as a neurodivergent individual. Read his story.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/autism-at-work</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-at-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Making the Coldplay Music Of The Spheres World Tour App Accessible for Blind and Visually Impaired People]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/accessibility-coldplay-app-music-of-the-spheres-world-tour</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/accessibility-coldplay-app-music-of-the-spheres-world-tour</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A blind Coldplay fan has supported SAP in making the tour app accessible for blind and visually impaired people. Learn more about how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/accessibility</category>
            <category>news-tag/coldplay</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-sponsorships</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[New Study Reveals Nearly 99% Fair Pay Across Race and Gender at SAP North America]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/equal-pay-at-sap-north-america</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/equal-pay-at-sap-north-america</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A recent study on equal pay at SAP North America supported the global analysis that 99% of employees are paid equally for equal work.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>news-tag/future-of-work</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-tag/people-sustainability</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How SAP Is Embracing Pay Equity on the Road to Equality]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/embracing-pay-equity-at-sap-road-to-equality</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/embracing-pay-equity-at-sap-road-to-equality</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[For 2023 and beyond, SAP is doubling down on its commitment to pay equity and transparency for its more than 109,000 people.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d9824118b7d7fe95b32de7fddbf82ac62b3982ae.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d9824118b7d7fe95b32de7fddbf82ac62b3982ae.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1d9824118b7d7fe95b32de7fddbf82ac62b3982ae.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="How SAP Is Embracing Pay Equity on the Road to Equality" src="./media_1d9824118b7d7fe95b32de7fddbf82ac62b3982ae.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="how-sap-is-embracing-pay-equity-on-the-road-to-equality">How SAP Is Embracing Pay Equity on the Road to Equality</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="new-study-reveals-nearly-99-equal-pay-across-race-and-gender-at-sap-north-america">New Study Reveals Nearly 99% Equal Pay Across Race and Gender at SAP North America</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2023/03/equal-pay-at-sap-north-america">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>With every new year, personal financial goals tend to be at the top of the resolution list. As the global employer to more than 109,000 people, we’re committed to doing our part by ensuring fair pay. For 2023 and beyond, we’re doubling down on that commitment.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>It is important to us because our business is built on trust with our colleagues. That trust leads to high performance and gives us a competitive edge for both talent retention and attraction.</p>
  <p>In January 2022, we published a fair pay statement, explaining our philosophy and principles around fair pay. It outlined our efforts to create a culture of equity and inclusion, and a promise to ensure our compensation practices are transparent. Our fair pay motto is “aggregate, don’t segregate.”</p>
  <p>In April, we reported that 99.8% of our employees around the world had transparency on their pay range. We also launched a new annual global statistical analysis and made pay equity adjustments.</p>
  <p>Even with such positive results, however, it’s still not a time for chest thumping. Among professionals who have a career focusing on diversity, equity, and inclusion (DE&#x26;I), we know how easy it is to regress. And we have no interest in going backwards. We must continue to raise the bar and push ourselves.</p>
  <p>Our current compensation results are not a coincidence and did not happen overnight. We have prioritized fair pay through implementing a global job architecture and global grades framework. We have pushed pay range transparency for employees. We’ve targeted salary adjustments to pay range minimums for those employees whose compensation was below the range. And since last year, we committed to annually reviewing internal pay leveraging statistics to ensure employees are paid appropriately.</p>
  <p>At SAP, “fair pay” is more than reducing the gender and ethnicity pay gap. For us, it means focusing on the processes, programs, and guidelines across the organization. We are pushing ourselves to examine the tools leaders use to ensure talent is treated fairly, and that employees with an exceptional work performance are rewarded accordingly.</p>
  <p>Fair pay also is about rewarding individuals based on their unique contribution and impact in their teams and the overall company.</p>
  <p>We are so committed to promoting pay equity that we’re sharing our insights with others.</p>
  <p>Business Beyond Bias features in our SAP SuccessFactors solutions work to help eliminate the inherent biases around age, race, ethnicity, differently abled, and LGBTQ+ communities in HR processes. Our software helps companies uncover unconscious bias in calibration and compensation decisions. It shows where an employee’s pay stands relative to the rest of their job family or group within the company. In addition, it allows you to pull in external market pay information into the compensation worksheet to provide additional data points for ensuring fair and equitable pay decisions.</p>
  <p>We’re moving toward a day when equitable pay for all people will no longer be an issue but a basic right for every individual. Until then, we’ll keep working on it.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Supriya Jha is chief diversity and inclusion officer at SAP.</em><br><em>Chetna Singh is senior vice president and global head of Total Rewards at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>news-tag/future-of-work</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-tag/people-sustainability</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bridging the Digital Gap for Women in Tech]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/iwd-2023-women-in-tech-bridging-digital-gap</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/iwd-2023-women-in-tech-bridging-digital-gap</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[For IWD 2023, learn more about how SAP is investing in programs that help existing and potential female employees thrive.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>non-sap-event/international-womens-day</category>
            <category>news-tag/women-in-tech</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Allyship for Women: AHA! Moments in D&I]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/videos/allyship-for-women-aha-moments-in-di</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/videos/allyship-for-women-aha-moments-in-di</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP’s Chief Diversity & Inclusion Officer Supriya Jha interviews Chris McLellan, head of SAP SuccessFactors Solution Advisory, to understand how he became an ally for diversity and inclusion in general and women in particular.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/video</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Empathy Is Our Superpower to Embrace Equity]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/international-womens-day-2023-empathy-is-our-superpower-to-embrace-equity</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/international-womens-day-2023-empathy-is-our-superpower-to-embrace-equity</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Ahead of International Women’s Day 2023, SAP employees share stories of fostering empathy and increasing equity for women in the workplace.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>non-sap-event/international-womens-day</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Conversations about Leadership with Women in the Chemical and Steel Industries]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/women-leadership-in-chemical-and-steel-industries</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/women-leadership-in-chemical-and-steel-industries</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Women leaders discuss taking career risks, rising above gender stereotypes, and forging new paths in historically male-dominated industries.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/business-womens-network</category>
            <category>industry/chemicals</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>industry/mining: industry/mill-products</category>
            <category>news-tag/women-in-leadership</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Inclusive Teams, Better Products]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/inclusive-teams-better-products</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/inclusive-teams-better-products</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Promoting inclusive teams and collaboration in your product development process can improve the experience for everyone. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-design</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Women Can Be the Key to Solving the Global Skills Gap in Tech]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/01/women-key-to-global-digital-skills-gap-in-tech</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/01/women-key-to-global-digital-skills-gap-in-tech</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The global lack of digitally skilled workers is increasing in the tech industry. Learn about SAP's initiative and how women are key.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/coursera</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills-gap</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-certification</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-community</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Milliken & Company Transforms HR in the Cloud]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/01/milliken-company-transforms-hr-cloud</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/01/milliken-company-transforms-hr-cloud</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Milliken & Company leveraged cloud HR solutions to create a sustainable workforce. Read to learn more about its transformation.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>topic/data-analytics</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-employee-central</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-recruiting</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Hispanic Promise]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/01/the-hispanic-promise-aha-moments</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/01/the-hispanic-promise-aha-moments</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP's Supriya Jha and activist Claudia Romo Edelman discuss the Hispanic Promise, a pledge to recruit, retain, and promote Hispanics.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>