<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/employee-network-groups/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[AHA! Moments in D&I: Disability Inclusion with Disability:IN]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/aha-moments-disability-inclusion</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/aha-moments-disability-inclusion</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Jill Houghton of Disability:IN talks to SAP's Supriya Jha about how leadership culture is key to disability inclusion. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-network-groups</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[AHA! Moments in D&I: “On the Trail, You Are Open to All People”]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/aha-moments-in-di-peter-lengler</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/aha-moments-in-di-peter-lengler</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Peter Lengler, member of the SAP Supervisory Board, People and Culture Committee, discusses what inclusion awareness means to him.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_114cd1e673570105a7a8224847ff5f416ec46f0ab.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_114cd1e673570105a7a8224847ff5f416ec46f0ab.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_114cd1e673570105a7a8224847ff5f416ec46f0ab.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="AHA! Moments in D&#x26;I: “On the Trail, You Are Open to All People”" src="./media_114cd1e673570105a7a8224847ff5f416ec46f0ab.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="aha-moments-in-di-on-the-trail-you-are-open-to-all-people">AHA! Moments in D&#x26;I: “On the Trail, You Are Open to All People”</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Peter Lengler, member of the SAP Supervisory Board, People and Culture Committee, talks about the process of learning to see the barriers that others face.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In the latest episode of the AHA! Moments in Diversity &#x26; Inclusion video series, SAP Chief Diversity &#x26; Inclusion Officer Supriya Jha and Lengler discuss what inclusion awareness means to him.</p>
  <p>As part of the <a href="https://www.sap.com/investors/en/governance/supervisory-board.html#committees">SAP Supervisory Board</a>, the People and Culture Committee is dedicated to fostering a culture of innovation, performance, diversity, organizational design, and integrity. It also maintains SAP’s network to universities and other stakeholders to support the company’s people strategy.</p>
  <h2 id="on-the-trail">On the Trail</h2>
  <p>The World Economic Forum estimates that more than 150 million people are homeless globally and, for Lengler, meeting one of them further cemented his passion for diversity and inclusion.</p>
  <p>During his 162 days on the Appalachian Trail, Lengler discovered that another hiker he met had been homeless for more than 10 years. Initially, he was a little apprehensive about this fact – and the hiker. However, he quickly discovered that sharing a common goal – in this case to complete the trail – meant that any preconceptions or concerns about this formerly homeless individual ceased to be relevant. They were to spend the next four weeks hiking the trail together.</p>
  <p>“On the trail,” Lengler explains, “you have the same goal, and you are open to all people there.”</p>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_185f5c43b6746d301d2ea2ceb663a4eab466197f6.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_185f5c43b6746d301d2ea2ceb663a4eab466197f6.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_185f5c43b6746d301d2ea2ceb663a4eab466197f6.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="On the Trail You Are Open to All People: AHA! Moments in D&#x26;I" src="./media_185f5c43b6746d301d2ea2ceb663a4eab466197f6.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://youtu.be/1eiCHx4B0iY">On the Trail You Are Open to All People: AHA! Moments in D&#x26;I</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="unlearning-ingrained-behavior-patterns">Unlearning Ingrained Behavior Patterns</h2>
  <p>Lengler reflects on those groups of individuals he refers to as “old white men clubs” who have never consciously suffered exclusion and have no understanding of the barriers that others face. Identifying unconscious biases and unlearning ingrained behavior patterns is critical to sustaining the success of diversity and inclusion initiatives.</p>
  <p>For Lengler, the important aspect of inclusion is not just to increase the number of employees from diverse backgrounds but to create a culture of true inclusion. Passionately, he explains that for him true inclusion means 100% acceptance for all team members, regardless of their backgrounds. Only team members who are 100% accepted and truly included in all aspects of team life will be able to bring their best selves to work and can be “open in their voice and their mind.”</p>
  <h2 id="the-aha-moment">The AHA! Moment</h2>
  <p>On the Appalachian Trail, Lengler experienced first-hand how a common goal and common hardship can bring people together. Above all else, someone who has different life experience or is in some way different from the rest of the team will bring another point of view and, says Lengler, “will look at the same problem in a different manner,” crystallizing his conviction that when you share your goal, “you can reach it together more easily instead of making it alone.”</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="its-time-to-run-a-world-where-our-differences-are-celebrated-equity-is-fostered-and-everyone-belongs">It’s time to run a world where our differences are celebrated, equity is fostered, and everyone belongs</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/our-values/diversity.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="diversity-and-inclusion-at-sap">Diversity and Inclusion at SAP</h2>
  <p>In its <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2023/04/4e7e324b-6e7e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">2022 Diversity and Inclusion report</a>, SAP states its mission to become “the most inclusive company in the world.” In the U.S., for example, more than 40% of employees are from underrepresented groups. SAP is on track to achieve long-term gender goals and has a five-generation workforce.</p>
  <p>One of the initiatives that the Global Diversity and Inclusion Office has launched to help further <a href="/topics/diversity-at-sap">SAP’s progress towards becoming the most inclusive company in the world</a> is the Inclusive Mindset Challenge. This challenge allows employees to learn about inclusion topics and the importance of becoming an ally for marginalized groups at their own pace. The challenge comprises a broad range of micro-learnings, such as menopause, transphobia, or sexism to name a few. In 2022, more than 11,000 employees completed this challenge. New challenges are added regularly; recent additions include indigenous inclusion and infuse D&#x26;I with AI.</p>
  <h2 id="sap-inclusion-month">SAP Inclusion Month</h2>
  <p>SAP has designated October 2023 as SAP Inclusion Month. All employees are invited to join the inclusion journey and to get involved in an Employee Network Group (ENG) journey, allyship journey, and, for leaders, the intentional inclusion journey.</p>
  <p>With more that 40,000 employees, ENGs are voluntary, employee-led diversity and inclusion initiatives representing groups such as visually impaired employees, caregivers, or Latinos.</p>
  <p>With the allyship inclusion journey, employees are invited to use their privilege and power to support marginalized groups. With the intentional inclusion journey, leaders learn about intentional inclusion practices that can help further advance SAP’s journey to become a truly inclusive workplace.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Top photo courtesy of SAP employee Celia Carillo.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-at-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-network-groups</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP North America Commits to Mentoring Afghan Refugees]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/sap-north-america-tent-mentoring-afghan-refugees</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/sap-north-america-tent-mentoring-afghan-refugees</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP will work with Tent to mentor 50 Afghan refugees over the next three years and aid their transition into the American job market.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14f9bf1a1a14dd69b3b7557083ccbcfbf1d45bd7a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14f9bf1a1a14dd69b3b7557083ccbcfbf1d45bd7a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_14f9bf1a1a14dd69b3b7557083ccbcfbf1d45bd7a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP North America Commits to Mentoring Afghan Refugees" src="./media_14f9bf1a1a14dd69b3b7557083ccbcfbf1d45bd7a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-north-america-commits-to-mentoring-afghan-refugees">SAP North America Commits to Mentoring Afghan Refugees</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>SAP has committed to mentoring 50 Afghan refugees over the next three years to aid them in their transition into the American job market.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP will work with the <strong>Tent Partnership for Refugees</strong>, a <a href="https://www.tent.org/">non-profit organization founded by Hamdi Ulukaya</a>, the CEO and Chairman of Chobani. As a Turkish immigrant, Ulukaya saw firsthand the power of immigrants finding appropriate employment and how it benefits the refugee and the businesses who hire them.</p>
  <p>I’m excited to be a part of this for several reasons.</p>
  <p><strong>For me, working with Tent is a deeply personal cause</strong>. As a soldier in the US Army’s 75th Ranger Regiment, I deployed twice to Afghanistan during Operation Enduring Freedom. I saw a beautiful country full of incredible people torn apart and ravaged by war.</p>
  <p>In August 2021, I was also one of the thousands of people worldwide who worked feverishly to help evacuate as many Afghans from Kabul as we could. In those two frantic weeks, we did everything possible to save our friends. These men and women were not strangers, but people we had forged deep relationships with. They were some of the bravest and hardest-working men and women I have ever met.</p>
  <p>The men and women this program will mentor are incredibly intelligent and hard-working professionals. Their command of the English language is excellent. They bring technical skills and professional expertise to the table. Like so many before them, they are eager to embrace the American dream.</p>
  <p>But they are in the challenging position of rapidly learning a new culture after being ripped out of their homes — some literally in the middle of the night — while trying to do whatever they can to support their families, both here and, in many cases, back home in Afghanistan.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-what-life-looks-like-at-sap">Learn more about what life looks like at SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://jobs.sap.com/content/Life-At-SAP/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="tent-trains-corporate-mentors-to-help-refugees-find-the-right-employment">Tent Trains Corporate Mentors to Help Refugees Find the Right Employment</h2>
  <p>Led by Veterans@SAP and in partnership with <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/our-values/diversity.html#eng">Employee Network Groups</a> <a href="/2023/04/autism-acceptance-month-sascha-dietsch">Autism Inclusion Network</a>, Black Employees Network, Business Women’s Network, SAP Interfaith Alliance, Latinos@SAP, and Pan-Asians@SAP, this initiative will be working to help these Afghan mentees starting in May.</p>
  <p>Volunteers will provide mentorship, interview prep, resume review, coaching, and access to a more robust professional network as the refugees work to find new employment in the U.S. that is better matched to their skills and expertise. SAP is excited and honored to be a part of this important initiative.</p>
  <h2 id="help-tent-by-joining-the-cause">Help Tent by Joining the Cause</h2>
  <p>This is an opportunity to help these amazing human beings integrate into the American workforce, to enrich this nation through their talents and experiences. That is why Tent’s work is important. It’s why we are so excited to work with them.</p>
  <p>If you are so moved, consider <a href="https://www.tent.org/become-a-member/">becoming a member of Tent.org</a> as they continue their mission to help refugees and immigrants more easily transition into the American work force.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Tom Amenta is a field marketing specialist for Cloud ERP at SAP North America.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-network-groups</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>