<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/learning/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Powering the AI Revolution with New Learning, Certifications, and Simplified Access to Talent]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/powering-ai-revolution-learning-certifications-talent</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/powering-ai-revolution-learning-certifications-talent</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Bring out your best with new learning opportunities, role-based SAP Certifications, and simplified access to talent. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_158ee9e4c4293f1933f13d07a2fb3eddc96c821de.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_158ee9e4c4293f1933f13d07a2fb3eddc96c821de.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_158ee9e4c4293f1933f13d07a2fb3eddc96c821de.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Powering the AI Revolution with New Learning, Certifications, and Simplified Access to Talent" src="./media_158ee9e4c4293f1933f13d07a2fb3eddc96c821de.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="powering-the-ai-revolution-with-new-learning-certifications-and-simplified-access-to-talent">Powering the AI Revolution with New Learning, Certifications, and Simplified Access to Talent</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Artificial intelligence (AI) is currently forcing the technology industry to undergo <a href="">a paradigm shift</a>, further accelerating the upheaval in business and society. We see AI embedded in tools we have been using for years, and we see software finding its way into every aspect of competition today. Against this background, it comes as no surprise that <a href="https://www2.deloitte.com/us/en/pages/consulting/articles/state-of-ai-2022.html">94% of business leaders see AI as critical to success over the next five years</a>. However, many report the lack of resources and talent to drive competitiveness with these new tools.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="taking-business-to-the-next-level-in-the-era-of-ai">Taking Business to the Next Level in the Era of AI</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/events/sapphire/news-guide.html">Read the news guide</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>To make it easier to develop relevant skills and secure business success in such a volatile environment, <a href="/2022/11/sap-coursera-partnership-digital-skills-underrepresented-groups">we embarked on a journey to upskill millions of people worldwide</a> in search of opportunity. After launching a digital skills initiative for those underserved in tech, forging new partnerships, offering the first role-based certifications to help meet real-life business needs, and making future-focused learning resources available to all, we are now taking our efforts to an even higher level – with more free, self-paced learning and engagement opportunities, new solution demos to experience the latest innovations in SAP Business AI, cloud ERP, and SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP), among others, a full portfolio of role-based certifications and a new certification model, as well as an extended digital skills initiative.</p>
  <h2 id="more-than-250-free-online-courses-now-available-for-all">More Than 250 Free Online Courses Now Available for All</h2>
  <p>From global talent shortages and changing job profiles to the digitalization of entire economies, many organizations see the gaps between skill supply and demand grow wider and wider while searching for ways to adapt to a business landscape where advancements like AI, machine learning, and a new era of Big Data come into play. In this ever-changing atmosphere, tens of thousands of organizations have <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company.html">deployed SAP solutions</a> to support them on their path to bring out their best, leading to skyrocketing demand for SAP talent.</p>
  <p>To help meet the increasing demand, we recently launched more than 50 new free, self-paced learning journeys – many of them touching on AI features embedded in our software – bringing the total number of digital courses on the <a href="https://learning.sap.com/?url_id=text-sapnewscenter-prdteng-Sapphire">SAP Learning site</a> to more than 250. By allowing everyone with an Internet connection to quickly learn a new skill for free, keep up with the latest innovations, and prepare for an in-demand SAP Certification, more professionals can advance in the competitive technology labor market, while customers can draw on a deeper bench of skills to accelerate digital transformation.</p>
  <h2 id="launching-role-based-certifications-for-all-key-roles">Launching Role-Based Certifications for All Key Roles</h2>
  <p>As organizations need to be more adaptive and dynamic, traditional university degrees become less important and skills-based hiring is on the rise when trying to fill positions. In fact, recent reports show that up to <a href="https://www.hiringlab.org/2024/02/27/educational-requirements-job-postings/">52% of job postings</a> in the U.S. in the beginning of the year did not state an educational requirement. Instead, role-based certifications and practical experience have become more determining factors for career paths and hiring.</p>
  <p>Recognizing the advantages role-based certifications can offer both individuals and organizations, we have further enhanced our certification program to better align with real-life business needs, now offering role-based certification for all key roles, including consultants, analysts, and architects. These role-based certifications come with a clear career path for individuals. Together with a <a href="https://learning.sap.com/get-certified?url_id=text-sapnewscenter-prdteng-Sapphire">new model to get and stay certified</a> with continuous assessments, this is our way to help ensure skill sets are sharp, focused on core competencies, and more sustainable and valid for longer periods of time.</p>
  <p>With these enhancements, we believe we have now taken an important next step to support professionals and organizations in the SAP ecosystem to bring out their best with ongoing and up-to-date knowledge of the latest skills, helping to maximize the ROI of SAP software, shorten deployment times, lower costs, speed innovation, and increase employee retention and satisfaction.</p>
  <h2 id="simplified-access-to-pre-trained-sap-talent">Simplified Access to Pre-Trained SAP Talent</h2>
  <p>However, we recognize that many people considered underrepresented in tech still do not have access to future-focused educational resources and with it, fulfilling careers. Launched in late 2022, <a href="https://learning.sap.com/digital-skills?url_id=text-sapnewscenter-prdteng-Sapphire">SAP’s digital skills initiative</a> was intended to equip 10,000 people from underrepresented and underserved groups for a career in the tech industry with free, self-paced learning resources and a free certification exam attempt to obtain an in-demand SAP Certification to show their expertise. Ever since its launch, the initiative has grown – and contributed to <a href="https://community.sap.com/t5/learner-stories/bg-p/learner-stories">amazing success stories</a>.</p>
  <p>Hearing that SAP professionals like <a href="https://community.sap.com/t5/sap-learning-blog-posts/breaking-barriers-and-fighting-sexism-lin-s-journey-from-a-salesgirl-to-an/ba-p/13588835">Lin Fan, a Chinese immigrant to Germany</a>, could overcome gender bias because of our digital skills initiative, makes me proud. “[The digital skills initiative and SAP Certification] indeed opened new doors and helped me get noticed by recruiters,” Fan said. “I got several interviews from major SAP consulting firms shortly after handing in my application. In the interviews, I highlighted what I learned and expressed my confidence in accepting challenges for rolling out SAP S/4HANA. In the end, I got an offer and gladly started a junior role at a consulting firm that actively implements SAP S/4HANA projects.”</p>
  <p>While Fan’s path is inspiring, she is not the only one who turned their life around with the help of SAP. Given the expectation-exceeding demand of now more than 14,500 candidates, we are overwhelmed by the positive uptake of the initiative. One of our recent graduates, <a href="https://community.sap.com/t5/learner-stories/breaking-down-barriers-hear-from-chelcie-scott-how-she-broke-into-tech-with/ba-p/13710541">Chelcie Scott, agreed to tell her story</a> on camera and shared how intimidating the tech industry appeared to the single mother at first. Thanks to her willpower and commitment, plus a little help from the digital skills initiative, she recently got certified and hired by an SAP partner. And as organizations are still struggling to find skilled employees, we have decided to extend SAP’s digital skills initiative, bringing candidates and organizations together. With simplified access to SAP-trained talent, we are helping customers and partners to recruit talent and expand their workforce faster while also allowing for greater diversity and innovation.</p>
  <p>At SAP, we recognize the challenges and opportunities that lie ahead for customers, partners, and individual learners within and outside of the SAP ecosystem. With these enhancements, we have taken the next step to help organizations equip their existing workforce with the right tools and resources to future-proof their skill set while also paving career growth for those who do not have a seat at the table yet but can bring a fresh set of perspectives to it.</p>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1bf4a81f181aead9f58c4d25e211885b7fc5988cc.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1bf4a81f181aead9f58c4d25e211885b7fc5988cc.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1bf4a81f181aead9f58c4d25e211885b7fc5988cc.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Break Down Barriers With the Help of SAP’s Digital Skills Initiative" src="./media_1bf4a81f181aead9f58c4d25e211885b7fc5988cc.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pEsE7dicrc4&#x26;feature=youtu.be">Break Down Barriers With the Help of SAP’s Digital Skills Initiative</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Andre Bechtold is SVP and head of Solution &#x26; Innovation Experience at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-sapphire-in-2024-innovations-to-bring-out-the-best-in-your-business">SAP Sapphire in 2024: Innovations to bring out the best in your business</h3>
        <p><em><a href="/topics/sap-sapphire">Get the latest news and coverage</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills-gap</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Building a Dynamic Organization with a Skills-Based Approach to Talent]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/building-dynamic-organization-skills-based-approach-to-talent</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/building-dynamic-organization-skills-based-approach-to-talent</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A skills-based approach to talent management can help organizations build a dynamic and resilient workforce. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/recruiting</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-learning</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-opportunity-marketplace</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-recruiting</category>
            <category>news-tag/talent-acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhancing Support Experiences with Support Accreditation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/enhancing-support-experiences-with-support-accreditation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/enhancing-support-experiences-with-support-accreditation</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The Support Accreditation course enables customers and partners to make the best use of SAP's offerings and tools. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c17ed9e9e6e8aba827d32e446eff7f7691e16f08.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c17ed9e9e6e8aba827d32e446eff7f7691e16f08.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1c17ed9e9e6e8aba827d32e446eff7f7691e16f08.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Enhancing Support Experiences with Support Accreditation" src="./media_1c17ed9e9e6e8aba827d32e446eff7f7691e16f08.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="enhancing-support-experiences-with-support-accreditation">Enhancing Support Experiences with Support Accreditation</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>The Support Accreditation course offered by SAP plays a vital role in educating partners, customers, and internal employees about <a href="/topics/support">SAP’s support services</a>. In this interview, Simone Engelhardt, SVP and head of Customer Engagement Support for Customer Services &#x26; Delivery at SAP, discusses the importance of support channels, the 24/7 support structure, service continuity, and best practices for interacting effectively with SAP support teams.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Feedback from participants highlights the training’s success in improving the understanding and utilization of support services. Ongoing updates help ensure the course remains relevant amidst evolving technology and business landscapes, with future developments likely to incorporate advancements in artificial intelligence (AI) and machine learning tools for support services.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Q: Can you provide an overview of the Support Accreditation training and its significance for anyone engaging with SAP’s support processes?</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><strong>Engelhardt:</strong> The Support Accreditation is a vital learning tool for our partners and customers as well as for our employees. It’s an informative course that can familiarize participants with SAP support services and help maximize their support experience. This is a unique opportunity to understand all the tools and resources available when interacting with SAP support and to learn efficient ways of engaging with our teams and resolving issues.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>In situations of urgency or escalation, customers might try to contact someone at SAP they personally know rather than follow the regular process. How does Support Accreditation address such situations and educate participants on the importance of following the proper channels?</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>That’s a great point. In urgent or escalated situations, individuals might feel tempted to bypass the usual channels and seek immediate remedies. However, these uninformed measures can result in delays. The Support Accreditation course emphasizes following the correct SAP support processes, which can ensure their issues are routed to the appropriately skilled support teams, leading to more efficient problem resolution.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Can you shed light on how the Support Accreditation training details the importance of our 24/7 support structure and how customers and partners can take advantage of it?</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The course thoroughly details our 24/7 support structure. We work to ensure that participants understand how, no matter their time zone, they can harness this around-the-clock support. It’s about making sure that our customers and partners know that they always have the backing of SAP, no matter when an issue arises.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-started-with-support-from-sap">Get started with support from SAP</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://learning.sap.com/learning-journey/getting-started-with-support-from-sap-support-accreditation">Explore the Support Accreditation course</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>How can customers and partners ensure that their issues are addressed efficiently even when their primary contacts at SAP are out of office?</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>We indeed cover this crucial aspect. The training delves into detail about the Customer Support organization, which aims to ensure service continuity even if specific account contacts at SAP are unavailable. Our course participants are made aware of the various support structures in place to assist them.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>The Support Accreditation training also covers the etiquette and best practices for interacting with SAP support. Can you talk more about this and why it’s important?</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Interacting with support teams forms a large part of managing SAP services, so etiquette and best practices in this area are covered in our course. We guide learners on the most effective ways to communicate with our teams, provide necessary information, and follow prescribed processes for optimal support assistance.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Do you have any insights related to the feedback from Support Accreditation participants? How has the course improved their understanding and utilization of our support services?</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Feedback from Support Accreditation participants has been overwhelmingly positive. Our learners report significantly improved knowledge about SAP support services and tools, and they’ve been successful in applying this knowledge to engage more effectively with SAP support. This has resulted in smoother, quicker issue resolutions, translating to improved satisfaction and service experiences.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>With technology and business requirements evolving, how will the Support Accreditation course adapt to these changes? What future developments can participants expect?</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The course isn’t static; it evolves with the technology landscape and business requirements. We continually update it to include new tools, offerings, or changes to existing processes. This helps ensure that the Support Accreditation training remains up-to-date and continues to be a valuable resource for our customers and partners. Future developments will certainly involve advancements in AI and machine learning tools in support services, so participants can be well prepared for the future of support services.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Recognized as a Strategic Challenger in 2024 Fosway 9-Grid™ for Learning Systems]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/sap-strategic-challenger-2024-fosway-9-grid-for-learning-systems</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/sap-strategic-challenger-2024-fosway-9-grid-for-learning-systems</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP was recently named a Strategic Challenger in the 2024 Fosway 9-Grid for Learning Systems. Read to learn more about the recognition.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1909b111011bdb2e7f1b173d6614d6bdebec89073.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1909b111011bdb2e7f1b173d6614d6bdebec89073.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1909b111011bdb2e7f1b173d6614d6bdebec89073.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Recognized as a Strategic Challenger in 2024 Fosway 9-Grid™ for Learning Systems" src="./media_1909b111011bdb2e7f1b173d6614d6bdebec89073.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-recognized-as-a-strategic-challenger-in-2024-fosway-9-grid-for-learning-systems">SAP Recognized as a Strategic Challenger in 2024 Fosway 9-Grid™ for Learning Systems</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>SAP was recently named a Strategic Challenger in the <a href="https://www.fosway.com/9-grid-2/learning-systems/">2024 Fosway 9-Grid<sup>TM</sup> for Learning Systems</a>, a multidimensional learning market analysis model. As a Strategic Challenger, SAP is recognized as demonstrating solid performance with solutions that have a rich and broad suite of capability compared to the market.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>With the widened availability of AI, the race for skills is impacting both people and organizations. While people are learning how to use AI to drive more efficiency within their individual roles, organizations are also under pressure to adopt AI technology that can deliver more personalized development opportunities and greater talent intelligence.</p>
  <p>Over the last year, SAP has made significant investments across <a href="http://sap.com/hr">SAP SuccessFactors solutions</a>, specifically in <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/corporate-lms.html">SAP SuccessFactors Learning</a>, to deliver these capabilities.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="boost-employee-skills-while-helping-ensure-compliance-with-sap-successfactors-learning">Boost employee skills while helping ensure compliance with SAP SuccessFactors Learning</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/corporate-lms.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>These investments are part of a broader strategy to help our customers focus on accelerated skills growth and build a <a href="/2023/09/new-integrated-learning-experience-sap-successfactors">future-ready workforce</a>. Recently, we released a redesigned <strong>integrated learning experience</strong> that can deliver an entirely new way for people to experience learning at work. The highly personalized experience can guide the learner to not only accomplish compliance trainings – what they “have to learn” – and organizational goals – what they “need to learn” – but also helps to drive an intrinsic culture of learning around what they “want to learn,” tapping into each individual’s needs, aspirations, interests, or preferences based on their growth profile.</p>
  <p>Furthermore, <strong>the AI-powered</strong> <strong><a href="/2023/10/skills-based-organization-talent-intelligence-hub">talent intelligence hub</a></strong> is now available across all SAP SuccessFactors solutions. It is a framework that helps organizations understand the skills their employees have today, the gaps that exist, and how to close those gaps. With this intelligence, SAP SuccessFactors Learning can continue to deliver even more personalized learning and development recommendations.</p>
  <p>“The level of innovation within the learning systems market continues to accelerate rapidly – specifically around AI and skills,” said David Wilson, founder and CEO of Fosway Group. “As a major vendor in this space, SAP continues to invest significantly in innovating its learning and talent capabilities, reflecting its focus on enhancing the value it delivers to learning buyers as well as its wider HCM audience.”</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d02d983db0796a8aed17039c36d19de9b713748b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d02d983db0796a8aed17039c36d19de9b713748b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1d02d983db0796a8aed17039c36d19de9b713748b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_1d02d983db0796a8aed17039c36d19de9b713748b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="768">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>Source: 2024 Fosway 9-GridTM for Learning Systems. Click to enlarge.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Both multinational and midsize companies leverage <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/corporate-lms.html">SAP SuccessFactors Learning</a>, along with our partner ecosystem, to help drive upskilling and reskilling and create a culture of continuous learning.</p>
  <p><a href="/2023/07/san-pablo-farmacia-employees-brand-ambassadors">San Pablo Farmacia</a>, a Mexico-based pharmacy retail chain, created an intuitive and engaging training experience that employees can consume at their convenience. By integrating the learning solution with other talent management applications, it can design personal training and development plans in line with its growth strategies and the individual needs of the entire workforce. The company delivered certified training to 1,800 employees without the need to transport its people to a training location and take them away from their pharmacy stores.</p>
  <p>Delta is also embracing AI to drive upskilling and personalized development opportunities. “We are incorporating disruptive technologies like our AI-driven skills ontology that automatically incorporates industry trends with embedded intelligence,” said Tim Gregory, managing director of HR Innovation and Workforce Technology at <a href="/2023/10/skills-based-organization-talent-intelligence-hub">Delta</a>. “We can say which skills are most important to Delta Air Lines and the employee can easily combine those with their current capabilities, strengths and styles, and aspirations to create a personal career path. All of the content is based on Delta-specific skills and personalized to each employee’s career goals.”</p>
  <p>Looking ahead, we will continue to deliver more learning-specific enhancements and new AI capabilities throughout 2024 across all SAP SuccessFactors solutions so leaders can hire the best talent and grow their personal skills with individualized plans while building up the compliance and strategic skills needed by the organization.</p>
  <p><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/corporate-lms.html">Learn more about SAP SuccessFactors Learning.</a></p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Vinita Venkatesh is vice president of Product Management for SAP SuccessFactors Learning.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-learning</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Learning Services: What Our Customers Really Need]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/learning-services-what-customers-need</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/learning-services-what-customers-need</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learning services and content must be continually kept up-to-date, especially in a cloud world where innovation and flexibility are key.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Equipping the Next Generation of Underrepresented Talent for a Career in Tech]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/equipping-next-generation-underrepresented-talent-tech</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/equipping-next-generation-underrepresented-talent-tech</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP’s digital skills initiative helps prepare underrepresented groups for a career in tech through a free SAP Certification course.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1516454e29028b1edfdf3049f7d0417f3f4530c3f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1516454e29028b1edfdf3049f7d0417f3f4530c3f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1516454e29028b1edfdf3049f7d0417f3f4530c3f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Equipping the Next Generation of Underrepresented Talent for a Career in Tech" src="./media_1516454e29028b1edfdf3049f7d0417f3f4530c3f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="equipping-the-next-generation-of-underrepresented-talent-for-a-career-in-tech">Equipping the Next Generation of Underrepresented Talent for a Career in Tech</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>“I just never saw myself in tech.”</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>This is what I heard during my discussion with the first cohort of SAP’s <a href="https://learning.sap.com/digital-skills">digital</a> <a href="https://learning.sap.com/digital-skills?campaigncode=CRM-YD24-ISM-2422141&#x26;source=blog-glo-Unrepped_Talent">skills</a> <a href="https://learning.sap.com/digital-skills">initiative</a>, a program that helps equip underrepresented and underserved groups for a career in the tech industry through participation in a free SAP Certification course.</p>
  <p>How could it be that in a time when companies need to find talent quickly to fill the need for technically skilled roles – a need that is becoming more urgent by the day – there is an entire population of determined, driven people who feel as though they do not belong in the tech industry?</p>
  <h2 id="the-current-state-of-diversity-in-technology">The Current State of Diversity in Technology</h2>
  <p>The numbers speak volumes: only <a href="https://ncwit.org/resource/bythenumbers/">27% of all computing-related jobs are held by women</a>. Only 3% of those jobs are held by Black women and 1% are held by Latina women. For me, it has always been impossible to ignore the lack of representation in the tech industry. I am acutely aware of when I am the only woman in the room – let alone the only Black woman.</p>
  <p>But this is changing. Companies have begun implementing diversity-forward hiring practices to try to minimize barriers for populations that have historically been overlooked. The percentage of <a href="https://www.naceweb.org/diversity-equity-and-inclusion/individuals-with-disabilities/ready-willing-but-still-underemployed/e619e772-a54b-4df6-858c-9ca50717a5a0">employers with diversity recruiting efforts</a> rose from 56% in 2016 to 88% in 2021. Though there is now targeted backlash, numerous employers remain committed to their diversity, equity, and inclusion (DE&#x26;I) goals for the workforce.</p>
  <p>These initiatives have proven to be important to younger generations. In a few years, millennials and Gen Z will make up the majority of our workforce – and they want to work for companies that align with their values. A 2022 survey from the <a href="https://www.naceweb.org/diversity-equity-and-inclusion/individuals-with-disabilities/ready-willing-but-still-underemployed/835bc35a-e4be-42fb-b838-d06086cb87bc">National Association of Colleges and Employers (NACE)</a> found that 76% of recent graduates indicated that <a href="/topics/diversity-and-inclusion">diversity, equity, and inclusion efforts</a> were “very important” or “extremely important” when considering their future employers.</p>
  <h2 id="helping-underserved-groups-break-into-tech">Helping Underserved Groups Break into Tech</h2>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="accelerate-your-career-with-our-digital-skills-initiative">Accelerate your career with our digital skills initiative</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://learning.sap.com/digital-skills?campaigncode=CRM-YD24-ISM-2422141&#x26;source=blog-glo-Unrepped_Talent">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>If we want diverse workforces, we must support and create targeted channels to source diverse talent. It is imperative that these groups – including women, people of color, veterans, and others – are given the resources to excel in high tech. I have seen firsthand how our digital skills initiative is making an impact on individuals and their communities, working to ensure that talent from all backgrounds can participate in this exciting era of technological innovation. At SAP, we offer training on products like <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/s4hana.html?campaigncode=CRM-YD24-ISM-2422141&#x26;source=blog-glo-Unrepped_Talent">SAP S/4HANA Cloud</a> and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp.html?campaigncode=CRM-YD24-ISM-2422141&#x26;source=blog-glo-Unrepped_Talent">SAP ERP</a>, whether through programs like the digital skills initiative or on <a href="https://learninghub.sap.com/?campaigncode=CRM-YD24-ISM-2422141&#x26;source=blog-glo-Unrepped_Talent">SAP Learning Hub</a>, helping anyone interested in jump-starting their career in tech.</p>
  <p>Without diverse perspectives, we leave out too many pieces of the puzzle to see the big picture. This deficit is particularly obvious in technology, given its influence on everything from how we shop to how we govern. It is unsustainable to expect lasting market viability from products that are developed by and marketed to one type of person. Put simply, employing diverse talent is essential to long-term success.</p>
  <h2 id="how-companies-can-recruit-diverse-talent">How Companies Can Recruit Diverse Talent</h2>
  <p>For companies that are looking for the next pool of employees to solve today’s business challenges, it is time to consider non-traditional avenues of talent, like graduates from SAP’s digital skills initiative. Each cohort comes equipped with SAP Certification, self-motivation, and a strong work ethic. This is a special opportunity to pull from a curated group of strong candidates, not just because of their new skills but because of demonstrated curiosity and drive that is not easy to find.</p>
  <p>SAP makes these trained and certified candidates available to recruiters at no charge. Want to get access to SAP-certified, ready-to-hire talent? Interested in adopting a cohort? <a href="https://learning.sap.com/digital-skills/hire-talent?campaigncode=CRM-YD24-ISM-2422141&#x26;source=blog-glo-Unrepped_Talent">Contact us</a> to see how you can start hiring and get involved.</p>
  <h2 id="register-for-the-digital-skills-initiative-as-a-participant">Register for the Digital Skills Initiative as a Participant</h2>
  <p>If you are interested in expanding your career opportunities by learning in-demand skills and achieving an SAP Certification free of charge, apply for the digital skills initiative using the <a href="https://community.sap.com/t5/beginner-corner-blog-posts/digital-skills-initiative-applicant-guide-for-self-study-candidates/ba-p/273119">applicant guide</a>. This is a fantastic opportunity for those who want to make a career switch to tech.</p>
  <p>To those who never pictured themselves in the tech industry, picture it. There is a place for you. Take this as a sign to invest in yourself and create a new path to success.</p>
  <h2 id="making-an-impact-on-future-generations">Making an Impact on Future Generations</h2>
  <p>When I talked with this first cohort of the digital skills initiative, I saw how they take great pride in their certification. For some, these new skills will prove to be life-changing.</p>
  <p>My goal is to support initiatives that aim to ensure that everyone, from all backgrounds, can pursue their interests in finding a career in tech. When we leave these doors closed, we not only rob those shut out of the opportunity, but all of us from the creativity, perspectives, and outcomes they could deliver.</p>
  <p>I am incredibly proud of SAP’s work in empowering people to pursue a career in technology. I believe that we are developing the future of innovation through programs like the digital skills initiative, and I cannot wait to see how similar programs will evolve in the future.</p>
  <p>If you are an NGO, university, or an SAP partner or customer, contact us at <a href="mailto:partners.digitalskills@sap.com">partners.digitalskills@sap.com</a> to learn more. If you are interested in applying to the digital skills initiative, <a href="https://groups.community.sap.com/t5/beginner-corner-discussions/creating-an-sap-account-and-getting-started-in-the-community/m-p/260744">create an SAP account</a> to start your journey.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Etosha Thurman is chief marketing and solutions officer for Intelligent Spend and Business Network at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>product/sap-learning-hub</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Invests in Partner Learning to Boost Availability of SAP Experts]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/sap-invests-in-partner-learning</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/sap-invests-in-partner-learning</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Learning is reimagining partner enablement with SAP Learning Journeys, subject matter experts, and opportunities to earn credentials.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Support Accreditation: A Consultant’s Hack for Maximizing SAP’s Support Offerings]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/support-accreditation-maximizing-sap-support-offerings</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/support-accreditation-maximizing-sap-support-offerings</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Support Accreditation is a course that enables customers and partners to make the best use of SAP's offerings and tools. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/real-time-support</category>
            <category>product/sap-cloud-alm</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Best Time to Be a Developer Is Now]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/best-time-to-be-a-developer-is-now</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/best-time-to-be-a-developer-is-now</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[There is a skyrocketing demand for developers. Resources for constant career growth and learning are critical. Learn what SAP is offering.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Turns Every Developer Into a Generative AI Developer at SAP TechEd in 2023]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/sap-teched-2023-generative-ai-developers</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/sap-teched-2023-generative-ai-developers</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[From SAP TechEd, SAP has unveiled new innovations in generative AI, vector database capabilities, and new learning opportunities.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1372d56f0d8353651580c6665a37ae494d4534f9d.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1372d56f0d8353651580c6665a37ae494d4534f9d.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1372d56f0d8353651580c6665a37ae494d4534f9d.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Turns Every Developer Into a Generative AI Developer at SAP TechEd in 2023" src="./media_1372d56f0d8353651580c6665a37ae494d4534f9d.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-turns-every-developer-into-a-generative-ai-developer-at-sap-teched-in-2023">SAP Turns Every Developer Into a Generative AI Developer at SAP TechEd in 2023</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>BANGALORE</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p>At the SAP TechEd event in 2023, <a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) announced a comprehensive series of generative AI capabilities and advancements aimed at empowering developers of all skill levels to supercharge their businesses in the age of AI.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h2 id="sap-unveils-innovations-in-generative-ai-application-development-and-vector-database-capabilities-as-well-as-new-learning-opportunities-for-developers-in-the-era-of-ai">SAP Unveils Innovations in Generative AI Application Development and Vector Database Capabilities as Well as New Learning Opportunities for Developers in the Era of AI</h2>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="enterprise-innovation-in-the-age-of-ai">Enterprise Innovation in the Age of AI</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/events/teched/news-guide.html">Read the news guide</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“Today’s dynamic technology and business landscape means every developer needs to be an AI developer,” said Juergen Mueller, Chief Technology Officer and member of the Executive Board of SAP SE. “The innovations we’re launching at SAP TechEd, from AI-infused pro-code tools to a one-stop shop to create generative AI extensions and applications on SAP Business Technology Platform, support the developers at the heart of the AI revolution and provide them with resources they need to transform the way businesses run.”</p>
  <p>As organizations aim to derive business value from generative AI, effective collaboration between professional and citizen developers is essential. SAP is launching the SAP Build Code solutions, which streamline cooperation with business experts who use the low-code <a href="/2022/11/sap-teched-sap-build-business-expertise-coursera-partnership">SAP Build</a> solutions launched at SAP TechEd in 2022. Uniquely built for SAP applications and the SAP ecosystem, SAP Build Code solutions offer AI-powered productivity tools for developers and are optimized for Java and JavaScript development. SAP Build Code also draws on the power of SAP’s new generative AI copilot Joule – the copilot that truly understands business – to further boost productivity, embedding code generation capabilities for data model, application logic and test script creation.</p>
  <p>Good data is the foundation of good AI, and SAP HANA Cloud continues to pioneer innovation in the data space by adding new vector database features to its multimodel offerings at no additional cost. Vector data stores manage unstructured data – such as text, images or audio – to provide long-term memory and better context to AI models. This makes it easy to find and retrieve similar objects quickly. For example, users can search for suppliers based on the language in their contracts to examine payment history and trace individual orders. These powerful new vector database features enhance interactions between large language models and an organization’s mission-critical data. The innovation helps put SAP developers at the forefront of delivering radically new levels of data insight within a secure, private framework that uses industry-specific customer data to reduce hallucinations.</p>
  <p>AI Foundation on SAP BTP, a new one-stop shop for developers to create AI- and generative AI-powered extensions and applications on SAP BTP, will further help increase developers’ impact and efficiency. AI Foundation includes everything developers need to start creating business-ready AI tools on SAP BTP – from ready-to-use AI services and access to the top large language models to vector database capabilities and AI runtime and lifecycle management.</p>
  <p>The rapid pace of technological innovation has driven up global demand for skilled developers – and SAP is increasing its learning opportunities in tandem. As part of a commitment to upskill two million professionals by 2025 and complement free AI learning content already available, SAP today launched <a href="https://learning.sap.com/certification/sap-certified-associate-back-end-developer-abap-cloud?url_id=text-sapnewscenter-prdteng-LSC-TechEd">new role-based certification</a> and free learning resources for back-end developers using the ABAP Cloud development model. The two new learning resources covering ABAP development tools on SAP BTP and SAP S/4HANA are available on the <a href="https://learning.sap.com/?url_id=text-sapnewscenter-prdteng-LSC-TechEd">SAP Learning site</a>. They are designed for agile and cloud-compliant business transformation, providing developers with skills to build cloud-ready extensions that are aligned with SAP’s clean core strategy. SAP <a href="/">has also joined</a> the Stanford HAI (Institute for Human-Centered AI) <a href="https://hai.stanford.edu/corporate-affiliate-program">Corporate Affiliate Program</a>. Researchers and engineers at SAP will work with the Stanford academic community, including research faculty and students, on the intersection of generative AI and business.</p>
  <p>For details on all the announcements made at SAP TechEd in 2023, please <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/events/teched/news-guide.html">visit our news guide here</a>.</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-teched-in-2023-join-us-live-in-bangalore-or-attend-virtually">SAP TechEd in 2023: Join us live in Bangalore or attend virtually</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/events/teched/bangalore.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>About SAP</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP’s strategy is to help every business run as an intelligent, sustainable enterprise. As a market leader in enterprise application software, we help companies of all sizes and in all industries run at their best: SAP customers generate 87% of total global commerce. Our machine learning, Internet of Things (IoT), and advanced analytics technologies help turn customers’ businesses into intelligent enterprises. SAP helps give people and organizations deep business insight and fosters collaboration that helps them stay ahead of their competition. We simplify technology for companies so they can consume our software the way they want – without disruption. Our end-to-end suite of applications and services enables business and public customers across 26 industries globally to operate profitably, adapt continuously, and make a difference. With a global network of customers, partners, employees, and thought leaders, SAP helps the world run better and improve people’s lives. For more information, visit <a href="http://www.sap.com">www.sap.com</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Note to editors:</strong><br>To preview and download broadcast-standard stock footage and press photos digitally, please visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/photos">www.sap.com/photos</a>. On this platform, you can find high resolution material for your media channels.</p>
  <p><strong>For customers interested in learning more about SAP products:</strong><br>Global Customer Center: +49 180 534-34-24<br>United States Only: 1 (800) 872-1SAP (1-800-872-1727)</p>
  <p><strong>For more information, press only:</strong><br>Joellen Perry, +1 (626) 265-0370, <a href="mailto:joellen.perry@sap.com">joellen.perry@sap.com</a>, PT<br>Stacy Ries, +1 (484) 619-0411, <a href="mailto:stacy.ries@sap.com">stacy.ries@sap.com</a>, ET<br>Marcus Winkler, +49 6227-767497, <a href="mailto:marcus.winkler@sap.com">marcus.winkler@sap.com</a>, CEST<br><a href="mailto:SAP%20Press%20Room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>This document contains forward-looking statements, which are predictions, projections, or other statements about future events. These statements are based on current expectations, forecasts, and assumptions that are subject to risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results and outcomes to materially differ. Additional information regarding these risks and uncertainties may be found in our filings with the Securities and Exchange Commission, including but not limited to the risk factors section of SAP’s 2022 Annual Report on Form 20-F.<br>© 2023 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.<br>Please consider our <a href="https://www.sap.com/corporate/en/legal/privacy.html">privacy policy</a>. If you received this press release in your e-mail and you wish to unsubscribe to our mailing list please contact <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a> and write Unsubscribe in the subject line.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-teched</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/abap-cloud</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-build</category>
            <category>product/sap-build-code</category>
            <category>product/sap-hana-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/stanford-hai</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Accelerate Your Skills Transformation with the New Integrated Learning Experience for SAP SuccessFactors]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/new-integrated-learning-experience-sap-successfactors</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/new-integrated-learning-experience-sap-successfactors</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The integrated learning experience for SAP SuccessFactors helps to address skills gaps and considers employees' whole self in skills growth.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills-gap</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning-management-system</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-learning</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Career Pathfinding on the AI Frontier: Become the Talent Behind the Tech]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/ai-careers-talent-behind-tech</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/ai-careers-talent-behind-tech</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The landscape of AI careers has exploded, with almost every industry needing people with AI skills at different levels.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/opensap</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Learning to Stay Ahead of the Curve: Why Teams Should Value Low-Code/No-Code Training]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/value-low-code-no-code-training</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/value-low-code-no-code-training</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Providing access to learning and development opportunities like low-code/no-code training opens new workforce opportunities. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/low-code-no-code</category>
            <category>product/sap-build</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Powering Business Transformation with Unprecedented Career Growth for SAP Professionals]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/powering-unprecedented-career-growth-sap-professionals</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/powering-unprecedented-career-growth-sap-professionals</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[We all are facing a changing work environment. Read to learn how SAP Learning supports the career growth of SAP professionals.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-certification</category>
            <category>product/sap-learning-hub</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Starts Pilot with Accenture and IBM to Co-Validate SAP Expertise for Advanced Professionals]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/accenture-ibm-pilot-co-validate-sap-expertise</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/accenture-ibm-pilot-co-validate-sap-expertise</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A new pilot to co-validate SAP expertise, with first partners Accenture and IBM, is paving the way for career growth and business success.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/accenture</category>
            <category>news-tag/ibm</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-certification</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-partner-connect</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Communicating the True Value of Learning and Development in 2023]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/communicating-value-of-learning-development-2023</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/communicating-value-of-learning-development-2023</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Leaders need to be strategic in providing learning opportunities. Learn why and how leaders and employees can benefit from the investment.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c348ed4ab53e7860823ae46dfe75ba57f60e11e8.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c348ed4ab53e7860823ae46dfe75ba57f60e11e8.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1c348ed4ab53e7860823ae46dfe75ba57f60e11e8.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Communicating the True Value of Learning and Development in 2023" src="./media_1c348ed4ab53e7860823ae46dfe75ba57f60e11e8.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="communicating-the-true-value-of-learning-and-development-in-2023">Communicating the True Value of Learning and Development in 2023</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>As we move quickly into the second quarter of 2023, leaders and workers alike are facing increasing pressure resulting from the current tumultuous economic period. In a business environment where every budget line is being questioned, IT leaders must maintain a strategic lens when providing <a href="/topics/training">learning</a> opportunities for their teams. They must be able to clearly articulate the value of technical training and development opportunities – or risk losing them.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In the midst of this uncertainty, keeping IT workers abreast of innovative technologies and the skills to implement them is a balancing act. To stay at the forefront of industry change, learning must be considered more than a priority – it needs to be a core pillar of every organization. IT upskilling is key in today’s landscape to drive employee satisfaction and organizational success. Here are three of the top reasons to invest in learning and development opportunities and how the benefits can be articulated to leadership to ensure they consider learning a top priority, too.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-digital-skills-you-need-with-sap-learning">Get the digital skills you need with SAP Learning</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://learning.sap.com/digital-skills?url_id=text-sapnewscenter-prdteng-DigitalSkills">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="invest-in-your-employees--and-they-just-might-stick-around">Invest in Your Employees – and They Just Might Stick Around</h2>
  <p>While layoffs seem to be dominating the headlines, employees are quitting their jobs at <a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2023/02/13/business/employee-retention-quitting-companies.html">three times</a> the rate of layoffs. Retaining strong talent remains a competitive pursuit, and organizations are feeling the impacts of this challenge. Now, <a href="http://workplaceintelligence.com/upskilling-study/">64% to 66% of employees</a> would consider leaving their current role because there aren’t enough opportunities for skill development or career advancement. The truth is that adequate training directly impacts retention. An important factor in how employees evaluate their organization is based on the opportunities they’re provided to learn the skills that will catapult them towards reaching their goals. Learning and development opportunities can equip employees with essential leadership skills that can elevate their current position and pave the way for internal advancement.</p>
  <p>By offering learning programs, and therefore showing the workforce that leaders are invested in their growth, executive teams will realize a multitude of benefits. Individuals will feel valued and excited by new challenges and upskilling opportunities, making them more likely to be happy with their current role. Beyond this, they’ll build a workforce that is equipped with the latest knowledge to drive meaningful outcomes for the organization.</p>
  <h2 id="fostering-creativity-innovation-and-curiosity">Fostering Creativity, Innovation, and Curiosity</h2>
  <p>The tech industry is evolving – fast. From generative artificial intelligence (AI) and machine learning to immersive-reality technologies, digital transformation has raised the bar on the skills required of teams today. Inspiring employees to lead innovative strategies can feel daunting when the workforce is not properly equipped with the latest knowledge to take on new initiatives. When employees do not feel prepared, they are less likely to be enthusiastic about taking on new responsibilities or raise their hand to lead a project that is outside of their comfort zone. In fact, <a href="https://www.gartner.com/en/publications/emerging-technology-roadmap-for-large-enterprisesB">64% of IT professionals</a> think the skills shortage is the biggest barrier to the adoption of game-changing technologies.</p>
  <p>To combat this hesitation and encourage workers to tackle new challenges, leaders must recognize that learning and development opportunities enable IT teams to feel prepared and excited to move forward on adopting new workplace technologies. This ultimately increases efficiency and allows more time and space for innovation and creativity.</p>
  <p>Steve Lucas, SAP S/4HANA Cloud application consultant at Sapphire Systems, has seen how learning, for instance with <a href="https://learning.sap.com/?url_id=text-sapnewscenter-prdteng">self-paced SAP Learning Journeys on the SAP Learning site</a>, can drive innovation firsthand. “Earning an SAP Certiﬁcation is important to not just my future but the future of my company. It ensures we’ll both meet our goals and remain at the forefront of SAP’s latest innovations,” he said.</p>
  <h2 id="tackling-the-persistent-skills-gap-challenge">Tackling the Persistent Skills Gap Challenge</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="explore-sap-learning-journeys-and-product-pages">Explore SAP Learning Journeys and product pages</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://learning.sap.com/?url_id=text-sapnewscenter-prdteng">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The skills gap remains top-of-mind for leaders across industries as technical roles continue to evolve and competition for top talent remains high. Due to the speed of innovation, over <a href="https://www.gartner.com/en/newsroom/press-releases/2021-02-03-gartner-hr-research-finds-fifty-eight-percent-of-the-workforce-will-need-new-skill-sets-to-do-their-jobs-successfully">58% of the workforce will need new skill sets</a> to do their jobs successfully in the coming years.</p>
  <p>While some employees may be able to make time outside of work hours for learning and development, many have competing personal priorities – meaning encouraging employees to seek upskilling opportunities outside of their nine-to-five may set them on a path of frustration and burnout. Instead, bring training programs directly to them and build a few uninterrupted hours into their workday so that employees can devote themselves to learning without navigating demanding tasks at the same time. This simple solution can mitigate burnout and ensure everyone is receiving the information they need to be successful in their roles – now and in the future.</p>
  <p>For example, learning programs like <a href="https://learning.sap.com/learning-journey/discover-the-foundations-of-sap-commerce-cloud-and-sap-s-4hana-cloud-integration?url_id=text-sapnewscenter-prdteng">SAP S/4HANA</a> or <a href="https://learning.sap.com/learning-journey/utilize-sap-build-for-low-code-no-code-applications-and-automations-for-citizen-developers?url_id=text-sapnewscenter-prdteng">low-code/no-code</a> basics can quickly and efficiently equip employees with the skills they need by educating them on the latest platforms and technology necessary to keep up with digital transformation efforts. These programs can also level the playing field among teams, increasing workers’ value and purpose within their current role.</p>
  <h2 id="the-return-on-learning-and-development-priceless">The Return on Learning and Development? Priceless.</h2>
  <p>While it’s true that that investing in learning and development is a commitment – both in budget and in resources – the benefits far outweigh the drawbacks. It’s easy to deprioritize learning when the time and money that goes into upskilling can seem like an optional expense, but in today’s workplace culture, it is essential. Companies who invest in learning and development opportunities will reap the benefits almost immediately and will equip their teams for a future of innovation, creativity, and equitable opportunities for growth, ultimately leading to higher retention, empowered employees, and a more secure workforce.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Jan Meyer is head of Learning Systems at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills-gap</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Vodafone Builds Its Future-Ready Workforce on Cloud HR Foundations]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/vodafone-builds-cloud-hr-foundations</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/vodafone-builds-cloud-hr-foundations</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Vodafone Group Plc implements SAP SuccessFactors solutions as its cloud HR foundation for improved efficiency and employee engagement.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fieldglass</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-learning</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-work-zone</category>
            <category>sap-event/successconnect</category>
            <category>news-tag/total-workforce-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Women Can Be the Key to Solving the Global Skills Gap in Tech]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/01/women-key-to-global-digital-skills-gap-in-tech</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/01/women-key-to-global-digital-skills-gap-in-tech</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The global lack of digitally skilled workers is increasing in the tech industry. Learn about SAP's initiative and how women are key.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/coursera</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills-gap</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-certification</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-community</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Three Steps to Prioritize Digital Skills for Sustainable Growth]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/three-steps-prioritize-digital-skills</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/three-steps-prioritize-digital-skills</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Businesses must have enough people with the right skills, at the right time, to help them accelerate their digital transformation.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/covid-19</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/people-sustainability</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Pledges to Equip Underrepresented Groups with Digital Skills, Announces Partnership with Coursera to Reach Millions of Learners Worldwide]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/sap-coursera-partnership-digital-skills-underrepresented-groups</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/sap-coursera-partnership-digital-skills-underrepresented-groups</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A Coursera partnership and global skills initiative are part of SAP's efforts to grow a more diverse ecosystem of tech professionals.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/sap-teched</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/coursera</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The SAP Partner Enablement Journey: Why SAP Partners Invest in Getting Certified]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/sap-partners-invest-in-certifications</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/sap-partners-invest-in-certifications</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Through SAP Certifications, SAP partners are better prepared to lead true business transformation with SAP Business Technology Platform.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_129d3bf60136cb2f67f5f6bed2adc45a4c2fdfeeb.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_129d3bf60136cb2f67f5f6bed2adc45a4c2fdfeeb.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_129d3bf60136cb2f67f5f6bed2adc45a4c2fdfeeb.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="The SAP Partner Enablement Journey: Why SAP Partners Invest in Getting Certified" src="./media_129d3bf60136cb2f67f5f6bed2adc45a4c2fdfeeb.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="the-sap-partner-enablement-journey-why-sap-partners-invest-in-getting-certified">The SAP Partner Enablement Journey: Why SAP Partners Invest in Getting Certified</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Business leaders typically spend considerable time and effort before investing in the services of a software provider or partner to help ensure they acquire the service quality and performance they need. Certification quickly conveys that proof of competency since such technical accreditation is considered a direct stamp of approval.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Acquiring new customers is one thing; retaining them is another. In both cases, continuously attaining the latest certifications – from trending topics to specialized capabilities – reassures customers and inspires them to make that first contact and keep coming back. Compared to their noncertified counterparts, certified consultants speed implementation times by up to 15% and deliver projects with less rework and higher customer satisfaction, according to <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/08/c00f44c1-f27d-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">IDC</a>.</p>
  <p>Another advantage of certification is the potential to attract, develop, and retain the strong talent pool that customers expect. <a href="https://home.pearsonvue.com/voc">Pearson VUE’s global survey</a> of more than 10,000 IT professionals indicated that the value of IT certification surpasses that of training alone. Benefits include a culture that promotes confidence in abilities, greater job satisfaction, increased respect among peers, more work autonomy and independence, promotion and advancement, and higher salary and wages.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-btp-accelerate-business-outcomes-with-integration-data-to-value-and-extensibility">SAP BTP: Accelerate business outcomes with integration, data to value, and extensibility</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="a-competency-framework-for-competitive-certification">A Competency Framework for Competitive Certification</h2>
  <p>When working with SAP, partners have the added benefit of fast access to the learning content needed to prepare for and attain certification. They are also rewarded with a visual badge that can be included in their marketing materials and on their Web sites.</p>
  <p>In addition, through the recently announced <a href="https://partneredge.sap.com/en/partnership/manage/competency.html">Competency Framework</a>, SAP partners can achieve competencies and specializations by certifying a required number of their consultants and developers, enabling them to reach essential, advanced, or expert competency tiers. These competencies and corresponding specializations are then visible on <a href="https://www.sap.com/partner/find.html">SAP Partner Finder</a> to help prospective customers make informed partner selections based on the desired solution expertise.</p>
  <p>SAP provides a broad set of certifications so partners can build specific skill sets and offer highly specialized consulting and implementation services. More than <a href="https://training.sap.com/certification/validity">100 certifications</a> cover a wide range of expertise and skill levels across an expansive set of SAP solutions and services. In fact, <a href="https://groups.community.sap.com/t5/sap-business-technology-platform/sap-certifications-for-business-technology-platform-you-bet/ba-p/2032">eight dedicated certifications</a> are available for <a href="/topics/business-technology-platform">SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP)</a>, including SAP Integration Suite, SAP Extension Suite, the SAP HANA Cloud database, the SAP Analytics Cloud solution, and low-code and no-code development applications and automations.</p>
  <p>Partners can promote their certifications by using <a href="https://training.sap.com/content/certification-verification">SAP Certification digital badges</a>. This real-time verification demonstrates that the partner’s certification is valid and contains a description of the SAP-backed expertise.</p>
  <p>Learning content for certification exams for SAP BTP is available free of charge on the <a href="https://learning.sap.com/">SAP Learning</a> site. And as SAP technologies, such as SAP BTP, continue to evolve and bring new capabilities, partners can keep skills current with <a href="https://learning.sap.com/ready-to-get-certified">certification training and exams</a> continuously updated for every cloud release from SAP.</p>
  <p>SAP partners can also attend <a href="https://partneredge.sap.com/en/library/news/products/tech_platform/btp/certification_academies.html">partner certification academies</a> for SAP BTP. The academies are online, interactive trainings delivered by SAP experts who guide you through the content of selected learnings for SAP BTP and help prepare partners to pass the associated certification exams. After completing an academy and passing the related certification, partners are equipped with the skills, knowledge, and tools needed to efficiently implement future projects on SAP BTP.</p>
  <h2 id="proven-proficiency-drives-true-transformation">Proven Proficiency Drives True Transformation</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="build-extend-integrate-and-market-solutions-as-an-sap-partner">Build, extend, integrate, and market solutions as an SAP partner</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/partner/become/partneredge-build.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Technology is advancing exponentially. This reality requires people of all experience levels to grow their knowledge and take stock of how these new skills might be applied to improve productivity and efficiency, resolve existing challenges, and produce transformative outcomes.</p>
  <p>The more we share and grow our knowledge of technologies, tools, and platforms, the more significant the impact of innovation and the faster we can achieve our goals. But most importantly, our partners are well-positioned to drive future growth, better experiences, and more sustainable and profitable outcomes.</p>
  <p>With <a href="https://learning.sap.com/certification">SAP Certification</a>, our partners have the power to innovate with SAP BTP, among other SAP technologies, in ways that lead to true business transformation with unparalleled skill, confidence, and trust.</p>
  <p>If you have not done so already, please join us on the journey with SAP BTP, attend the partner certification academies, and get certified today! You can also engage with your peers through <a href="https://groups.community.sap.com/t5/sap-business-technology-platform/gh-p/SAP-BTP">the partner community for SAP BTP</a> (login required). We look forward to driving successful business outcomes together.</p>
  <ul>
    <li><a href="https://partneredge.sap.com/en/library/education/partnership/licenses/e_ep_td_payg.html">Access to SAP BTP, including free tier services</a> (available to SAP partners only)</li>
    <li><a href="https://partneredge.sap.com/en/library/assets/products/tech_plat/dgl/33/96/SAP813396.html">Enablement path for SAP BTP</a> (available to SAP partners only)</li>
    <li><a href="https://partneredge.sap.com/en/library/assets/products/tech_plat/dgl/36/25/SAP813625.html">Top 10 SAP BTP partner enablement resources</a> (available to SAP partners only)</li>
    <li><a href="https://www.sap.com/partner/become/partneredge-build.html">Software partnership opportunities through SAP PartnerEdge – Build</a></li>
    <li><a href="https://learning.sap.com/learning-journey">SAP Learning Journey guides, including certifications</a></li>
    <li><a href="https://partneredge.sap.com/en/library/news/products/tech_platform/btp/certification_academies.html">Partner certification academies for SAP BTP</a> (available to SAP partners only)</li>
    <li><a href="https://partneredge.sap.com/en/partnership/manage/competency.html">The Competency Framework</a></li>
  </ul>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Pavel Penaz is global head of Partner Solution Adoption Strategy and Execution for SAP Business Technology Platform at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-certification</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-partneredge-build</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Four Culture Keys for Unlocking Lifelong Learning]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/four-culture-keys-lifelong-learning</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/four-culture-keys-lifelong-learning</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A thoughtful and data-driven learning and development strategy is essential to meet business priorities. Here are four culture keys to do so.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning-for-life</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-learning</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-work-zone</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Some Organizations Have Successfully Changed Their Learning and Talent Experience]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/organizations-successfully-changed-learning-culture</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/organizations-successfully-changed-learning-culture</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP customers have transformed their learning culture by leveraging SAP SuccessFactors Learning and SAP SuccessFactors Work Zone.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning-for-life</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-learning</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-opportunity-marketplace</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-work-zone</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Drive Key Business Outcomes through People Sustainability]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/drive-key-business-outcomes-people-sustainability</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/drive-key-business-outcomes-people-sustainability</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[HR has both the opportunity and responsibility to ensure that people are at the center of work. Learn more about people sustainability.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/mental-health-well-being</category>
            <category>news-tag/people-sustainability</category>
            <category>news-tag/well-being-at-work</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Building a Lifelong Learning Culture Is More Important Than Ever]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/building-a-lifelong-learning-culture</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/building-a-lifelong-learning-culture</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Continuous learning options and a culture of lifelong learning will be critical to develop the workforce of the future. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning-for-life</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning-management-system</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-learning</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ensuring Tech Employee Growth Through Constant Change]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/09/tech-employee-growth-learning-trends</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/09/tech-employee-growth-learning-trends</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Technological progress means constant change. These four learning trends show how employees can keep up and generate lasting growth.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/low-code-no-code</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Leaders Can Inspire Career Trajectory in the “Great Resignation”]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/09/leaders-inspire-career-trajectory-resignation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/09/leaders-inspire-career-trajectory-resignation</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[At this time in history, many people are reflecting on their career trajectory. Learn three areas strong leaders can have influence.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How SAP SuccessFactors Innovation Can Help You Tackle Your Toughest Challenges]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/sap-successfactors-innovation-tackle-2022-hr-trends</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/sap-successfactors-innovation-tackle-2022-hr-trends</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Take on 2022 HR trends like hybrid work, diversity and inclusion, well-being, and the race for talent with SAP Successfactors solutions.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-technologies</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/mental-health-well-being</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-employee-central</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-opportunity-marketplace</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-performance-goals</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-recruiting</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-work-zone</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Makes Strides in Continuous Learning]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/sap-makes-strides-in-continuous-learning</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/sap-makes-strides-in-continuous-learning</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Read how SAP Learning contributes to continuous learning and upskilling with innovative offerings and the value it brings to organizations.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rethinking Learning and Change Management with a Cloud Mindset]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/rethinking-learning-and-change-management-with-a-cloud-mindset</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/rethinking-learning-and-change-management-with-a-cloud-mindset</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With companies adopting a cloud mindset, needs and expectations for learning and change management shift. Read to find out how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-activate</category>
            <category>product/sap-enable-now</category>
            <category>product/sap-learning-hub</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>