<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/sap-training-and-adoption/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP's Vision for Supporting Business Transformation and the Workforce of the Future]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/vision-business-transformation-workforce-of-the-future</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/vision-business-transformation-workforce-of-the-future</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP has a vision for supporting the workforce of the future as humanity enters one of its most transformative phases. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/opensap</category>
            <category>non-sap-event/wef-davos</category>
            <category>product/sap-learning-hub</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-training-and-adoption</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-university-alliances</category>
            <category>news-tag/un-sdgs</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[People Drive Success: RISE with SAP Inspires and Empowers Employees]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/02/people-drive-success-rise-with-sap-training</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/02/people-drive-success-rise-with-sap-training</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[For a successful business transformation, put your people first with a holistic strategy for change management and training. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-enable-now</category>
            <category>product/sap-learning-hub</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-training-and-adoption</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Change Management in SAP Projects: How Employees Drive Transformation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/02/change-management-employees-drive-transformation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/02/change-management-employees-drive-transformation</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[For change management, involving employees from the outset makes them allies – and drivers of change and it pays off. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_105383b73d3e0296df42d30bce9178a41d71d960d.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_105383b73d3e0296df42d30bce9178a41d71d960d.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_105383b73d3e0296df42d30bce9178a41d71d960d.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Change Management in SAP Projects: How Employees Drive Transformation" src="./media_105383b73d3e0296df42d30bce9178a41d71d960d.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="change-management-in-sap-projects-how-employees-drive-transformation">Change Management in SAP Projects: How Employees Drive Transformation</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Unfamiliar systems, new processes, completely different ways of working: an SAP implementation may unsettle users. That’s why change management is crucial for the success of any IT project, especially in the course of a business transformation. However, if you involve employees correctly and from the start, you turn them into allies and drivers of change. And that’s when opportunity pays off.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Entire industries are repositioning themselves on their <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/intelligent-enterprise.html">intelligent enterprise</a> journey to meet the demand for different approaches to business that did not exist before. Technologies such as artificial intelligence (AI) are also fundamentally and increasingly changing the processes. The software for business transformation is being implemented under the leadership of the CIO, sometimes at a rapid pace.</p>
  <p>However, the software is ultimately and primarily used by employees who were not involved in the selection process. Many of these employees and managers initially stick to their usual processes and are concerned about what changes an implementation of something such as SAP S/4HANA will concretely mean for their everyday lives. It’s a human reaction, of course, but one whose consequences are often underestimated because work runs less efficiently, more errors can occur, and sometimes even shadow IT is created.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="listen-to-the-educationnewscast-podcast">Listen to the EducationNewscast podcast</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://blogs.sap.com/2021/04/21/educationnewscast-the-education-podcast-from-sap">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="the-human-factor-in-change-management">The Human Factor in Change Management</h2>
  <p>Oliver Kohnke emphasizes the importance of the human component in the change process. As Global Director of <a href="https://www.sap.com/services/advisory-development/education-consulting.html">Organizational Change Management</a> at SAP Learning Services, he also recommends supporting change management digitally – through virtual workshops or semi-automated surveys and evaluations. He shares two lessons: in IT change projects, especially in the cloud world, we see less degrees of freedom than in other change projects. Efficiency and humanity should not be mutually exclusive.</p>
  <p>It’s not just the IT experts who need to understand the new applications – it’s the entire management team and employees, according to Dr. Torben Mauch, head of Change Management at SAP partner Nagarro ES. He knows from experience that a business transformation is only an IT project at first glance. “Thinking in terms of departments and old processes is often a major obstacle,” says Mauch in the EducationNewscast podcast. Change management, he says, needs to do much more than just explain the purpose of an SAP implementation. It should get employees excited about the shared journey, actively involve them in shaping the new processes, and take concerns seriously as well as work to resolve them.</p>
  <p>Change affects an organization’s people as well as the organization itself. SAP calls this organizational change management. Ideally, it begins with a change assessment. In the planning phase of the implementation project, interviews and workshops with the most important project participants determine how the organizational structures, roles, and responsibilities within the company already fit with the vision. The next step is evaluating the people affected by the transformation and to what extent change management processes and competencies are in place.</p>
  <h2 id="crisp-communication-and-a-shared-future">Crisp Communication and a Shared Future</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="five-tips-for-effective-change-management-in-new-technology-projects">Five Tips for Effective Change Management in New Technology Projects</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/10/five-tips-effective-change-management-new-technology-projects">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Change agents are then called upon to realize the change management concept. They represent their respective areas in the company, come together in a change network, and exchange and reflect on information about the necessary changes at regular intervals. At least that’s how it went at Evonik, where the chemical company’s <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/s4hana-erp.html">SAP S/4HANA</a> migration affected about 15,000 users. “Because of this, we appointed coordinators from various business units and brought them to the table alongside representatives from communications,” explains Vali Maria Bluma, transformation office lead for Operations Excellence at Evonik. “With such a large undertaking, it is important to create clarity on the topic.”</p>
  <p>Bluma’s recommendation from this experience is to communicate all important innovations concisely and precisely using figures, data, and facts. This includes how many employees in which regions will be affected. The change agents become liaisons between the management level and the respective departments and are available as contacts and multipliers for both parties.</p>
  <p>Division managers often take on the role of a change agent. Anne Charlotte Luchtenveld, head of Talent and Development at Schülke &#x26; Mayr, is a case in point. She manages the HR transformation of the disinfectant manufacturer. She sees herself as a strategist, coach, and project manager all in one. “The most important component of a successful IT project is a well-positioned interdisciplinary team that is intrinsically motivated and given the necessary decision-making power and creative freedom,” says Luchtenveld. This clear structure leads to long-term success, she adds.</p>
  <p>“If the employer empowers the team and trusts them to work independently, employees are shown enormous appreciation. This has a positive effect on the working atmosphere and encourages employees,” explains Luchtenveld.</p>
  <h2 id="connect-training-with-digital-transformation">Connect Training with Digital Transformation</h2>
  <p>Anyone who manages people is familiar with the “can-may-will” model. Employees can only fully exploit their potential if they have the necessary skills, if the use of their competencies is actually welcomed and encouraged, and if they are motivated. Change management aims to ensure that employees are able and willing to do so. The ability requires a flexible training strategy. SAP Training and Adoption has developed a holistic approach that works to involve and empower employees equally.</p>
  <p>Furthermore, it is important that a transformation is seen as more than just a one-off activity, but as a continuous learning journey. Guido Schlief, head of SAP Services Middle and Eastern Europe, agrees that employees should always have access to information on software updates, new learning material, and background information in order to best meet the latest requirements.</p>
  <p><a href="/2021/10/five-tips-effective-change-management-new-technology-projects">Employees embrace the new software</a> because they recognize not only the benefits for the company, but also for their own work, resulting in adoption and acceptance. They transform from mere users and become “allies,” drivers of change.</p>
  <p>And that, in turn, increases the added value of the implementation.</p>
  <p>To gain knowledge from industry thought leaders and SAP customers on why focusing on transformation, training, and how to manage them both are key, <a href="https://event.on24.com/eventRegistration/EventLobbyServletV2?target=reg20V2.jsp&#x26;eventid=3655711&#x26;sessionid=1&#x26;key=1BE57F155CB3ED34E5F7B90F53B54FA4&#x26;groupId=3420588&#x26;sourcepage=register">register now for the Learning Transformation Insights webinar series</a>.</p>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div>The EducationNewscast podcast provides more inspiration and best practices around change management and training. The above quotes were originally in German. However, you can find English-only channels including all episodes <a href="https://blogs.sap.com/2021/04/21/educationnewscast-the-education-podcast-from-sap/">here</a>.</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>Thomas Jenewein is business development manager for SAP Training and Adoption.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-training-and-adoption</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Find and Create Top Talent with Up-to-Date Technology Certification]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/up-to-date-technology-certification-find-create-top-talent</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/up-to-date-technology-certification-find-create-top-talent</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP technology certifications can help a business perform better at a time when it's never been harder to find and retain the right talent.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a66c150959cdfb37047cddbd1fdf2dcedd03f3c1.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a66c150959cdfb37047cddbd1fdf2dcedd03f3c1.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1a66c150959cdfb37047cddbd1fdf2dcedd03f3c1.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Find and Create Top Talent with Up-to-Date Technology Certification" src="./media_1a66c150959cdfb37047cddbd1fdf2dcedd03f3c1.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="find-and-create-top-talent-with-up-to-date-technology-certification">Find and Create Top Talent with Up-to-Date Technology Certification</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>What do you look for in a job candidate? Skills, experience, and education are probably top priorities. But what if there was another option, a way you could know that a candidate will fulfill their role and support your business because they stay on top of the latest technology standards and trends?</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Now there is, with the right <a href="/2021/05/embrace-continued-learning-certification">certification</a>. Certification is a marker of foundational knowledge and continued learning. So when a candidate comes to you with a respected, up-to-date technology certification, you can trust that they are among the best at what they do.</p>
  <h2 id="win-the-competition-for-top-talent">Win the Competition for Top Talent</h2>
  <p>As the cloud becomes increasingly pervasive, more partners are looking for talented consultants who are certified and willing to stay current on this new and evolving technology. This makes for a significantly more competitive talent market. On top of that, candidates and employees have more needs and demands than ever.</p>
  <p>It’s never been harder to find and retain the right talent. Certification equips you with the tools needed to win the ongoing war for talent in two ways: hiring highly qualified employees and enhancing your existing workforce.</p>
  <p><strong>Find Top Talent</strong></p>
  <p>Certification provides at-a-glance insight into which candidates are highly skilled and motivated. For example, to receive a certification in SAP solutions, a candidate must pass a rigorous and comprehensive exam from SAP. Unlike a physician or certified accountant, technology experts do not need certification to practice in their field, so a technology certification speaks volumes about those who have received it. The certification says that a candidate has gone out of their way to educate themselves on the latest in SAP technology.</p>
  <p><strong>Create Your Own Top Talent</strong></p>
  <p>You may have some of the best in the business working for your company, but if they aren’t certified, how can your customers know your employees are a cut above the rest? Customers today increasingly look for certifications. This reassures them that your business can provide the up-to-date expertise they need. This is because up-to-date certification requires continuous learning to pass the latest exam.</p>
  <p>On top of that, customers are looking toward the cloud to solve their greatest business challenges and enable their digital transformations. Customers like cloud-based solutions because developers are constantly updating these solutions to meet customers’ needs. But this means that your business must do more to stay on top of these changes as cloud technology evolves.</p>
  <p>When your peers say that experience is what matters most when choosing a new job candidate, think twice. The basis for that experience – especially if it is cloud technology – is changing. A candidate who has recently taken an online exam and received a certification from a reputable certification organization has proven that they are committed to advancing their own knowledge and skills and staying current with the latest in technology.</p>
  <h2 id="sharpen-your-competitive-edge">Sharpen Your Competitive Edge</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-learning-hub-your-digital-solution-for-sap-software-skills">SAP Learning Hub: Your digital solution for SAP software skills</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/training-certification/education-courses/learning-hub.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The partner edition of SAP Learning Hub provides the tools, learning content, and practice your employees need to receive certifications from the SAP Global Certification program and to stay current. When a candidate or employee has access to SAP Global Certification and the partner edition of SAP Learning Hub, this means that they are:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Equipped with the latest digital learning content to stay current, available 24×7</li>
    <li>Up to date with comprehensive knowledge of SAP technologies, including cloud solutions from SAP</li>
    <li>Offered access to two certification exams</li>
    <li>Empowered to take “one-attempt” certification exams, a new offering that enables consultants to take an exam once and as needed</li>
    <li>Dedicated to a professional journey of self-improvement and enablement</li>
    <li>Motivated to learn more about technology</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="drive-business-success-with-validated-sap-solution-skills">Drive Business Success with Validated SAP Solution Skills</h2>
  <p>Certified experts in SAP solution skills can help your business perform better. Differentiate yourself with a skilled and trusted workforce that delivers valued outcomes. Increase efficiency and enhance customer satisfaction with up-to-date solution expertise. Certification affirms your experts’ knowledge and the fact that they are current on the latest in technology, which can boost your reputation.</p>
  <p>Today, there is more reason than ever for your employees to take and pass an SAP Global Certification online exam. The SAP PartnerEdge site will soon go live with a new and improved version of <a href="https://partneredge.sap.com/content/partnerfinder/search.html#/">SAP Partner Finder</a>, which matches SAP customers with partners that are prepared to meet their technology needs.</p>
  <p>All SAP partners will need to reenter their business information in the partner finder, and we have included new fields to help our customers and partners connect. The number of consultants who have earned certifications through the SAP Global Certification program, as well as their area of certification, will be listed.</p>
  <p>Get your business ready with a competitive differentiation through SAP Global Certification. You can help your employees receive their certification and stay current with the partner edition of SAP Learning Hub.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-the-power-of-partnership-with-sap">Learn more about the power of partnership with SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="http://www.sap.com/partner">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="find-out-more-about-the-partner-edition-of-sap-learning-hub-and-the-benefits-of-sap-global-certification-at-trainingsapcomcertification">Find out more about the partner edition of SAP Learning Hub and the benefits of SAP Global Certification at <a href="https://training.sap.com/certification/">training.sap.com/certification</a>.</h3>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>product/sap-learning-hub</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-training-and-adoption</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enabling an Innovative, Agile Culture with SAP Innovate to Win]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/sap-innovate-to-win-agile-culture</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/sap-innovate-to-win-agile-culture</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Newly expanded, the SAP Innovate to Win program helps customers build an internal culture around innovative and agility. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_185769a8bf884145887bfdb3c5602151d7f6c78db.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_185769a8bf884145887bfdb3c5602151d7f6c78db.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_185769a8bf884145887bfdb3c5602151d7f6c78db.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Enabling an Innovative, Agile Culture with SAP Innovate to Win" src="./media_185769a8bf884145887bfdb3c5602151d7f6c78db.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="enabling-an-innovative-agile-culture-with-sap-innovate-to-win">Enabling an Innovative, Agile Culture with SAP Innovate to Win</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>To become an intelligent enterprise in our increasingly digitized and rapidly evolving world, it is crucial to foster an engaged workforce that prioritizes innovation and agility. Employers foresee skills such as problem-solving, critical thinking, creativity, flexibility, and active learning increasing in demand moving forward, according to the World Economic Forum’s recent <a href="https://www.weforum.org/reports/the-future-of-jobs-report-2020">Future of Jobs Report</a>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP is committed to setting individuals and teams up for success by creating opportunities to develop and hone new capabilities and ways of thinking. As part of this mission, we’ve expanded <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/05/4a102369-e17d-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html?source=social-Global-SAPEDU-TWITTER-MarketingCampaign-Training_Enablement-unspecified-spr-4846849072&#x26;campaigncode=CRM-WX20-EDU-SOC">SAP Innovate to Win</a>, a service designed to help customers get enabled on innovation frameworks and mindsets and apply these to build an internal culture around innovative and agility.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="turn-learning-into-achieving-with-sap-training-and-adoption">Turn learning into achieving with SAP Training and Adoption</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/training-certification.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="empowering-new-ways-of-thinking">Empowering New Ways of Thinking</h2>
  <p>Available for companies of all sizes and from all industries, SAP Innovate to Win is an innovation enablement and coaching service that helps companies to tackle their individual business challenges. We piloted the program in the Middle East and North Africa region, and have now expanded to support enterprises around the globe with virtual, in-person, and hybrid format options.</p>
  <p>The customized service enables teams within organizations to adopt Design Thinking — defined by <a href="https://hpi.de/en/school-of-design-thinking/design-thinking/what-is-design-thinking.html">The HPI School of Design Thinking (HPI D-School)</a> as a human-centered, iterative, team-based mindset that leads to breakthrough innovations — and to build digital prototypes using SAP technologies. It also uniquely includes Business Model Innovation, Blue Ocean strategy, positive psychology, and creative coaching.</p>
  <p>The standard program is delivered in seven different modules over the course of six weeks. With an emphasis on learning by doing, users complete field work in between each module to apply their learnings. This culminates in the final module when they then pitch the concepts they’ve developed to be utilized in real-world situations. SAP also creates a “maturity assessment,” or checklist, to help teams stay on track to achieve their objectives.</p>
  <h2 id="supporting-it-and-business-professionals">Supporting IT and Business Professionals</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-more-detail-on-the-innovation-enablement-and-coaching-service-with-sap-innovate-to-win">Get more detail on the innovation enablement and coaching service with SAP Innovate to Win</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/05/4a102369-e17d-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html?source=social-Global-SAPEDU-TWITTER-MarketingCampaign-Training_Enablement-unspecified-spr-4846849072&#x26;campaigncode=CRM-WX20-EDU-SOC">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP Innovate to Win is also designed for different types of professionals. First, the programming can be geared to people specializing in IT who want to collaborate more efficiently with the business side of an organization. With SAP Innovate to Win, IT professionals are better equipped to communicate with different kinds of teams and move from conversations centered on tech requirements to those focused on outcomes.</p>
  <p>On the other hand, business professionals can leverage SAP Innovate to Win to build digital skills and IT-inspired mindsets. In doing so, both business and IT teams can speak the same language to foster an innovation culture across the broader company.</p>
  <h2 id="propelling-future-success">Propelling Future Success</h2>
  <p>As the <a href="https://hbr.org/2020/01/the-transformer-clo">Harvard Business Review</a> described, to achieve learning goals, there is now a greater focus on developing growth mindsets and capabilities, rather than role-specific training. With the coaching from SAP Innovate to Win, teams are prepared — and empowered — to creatively explore solutions to unique business challenges that arise down the line.</p>
  <p>We continue to see customers benefit from a personalized SAP Innovate to Win curriculum. Vicky Hasioti, SAP Innovate to Win program director, noted: “Through SAP Innovate to Win, we have already supported our customers to create more than 250 low-fidelity prototypes for new solutions and road maps in an effort to solve business challenges and improve their companies’ business models.”</p>
  <p>In one example, in the United Arab Emirates, Dubai Future Foundation utilized SAP Innovate to Win in a series of workshops. Yaqoob Al-Zaabi from the Strategy Department at Dubai Future Foundation said, “It’s been a surprisingly great experience! It really helped me think in ways that I have never thought before. It also gave me a sense of self-confidence to express myself and give feedback. The content was very clear and everything had a practical aspect and purpose which gave me actionable skills that I can take with me into my job.”</p>
  <p>With the expansion of SAP Innovate to Win, SAP will support more customers around the world in their journeys to cultivate thriving innovation cultures that ultimately generate greater value for stakeholders in the future.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning-for-life</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-training-and-adoption</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Getting Ahead of the Skills Curve]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/getting-ahead-skills-curve</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/getting-ahead-skills-curve</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Businesses can get ahead of the skills curve by aligning strategic workforce planning and business strategy. Read to learn more!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1be3fe31204da0bc2c881ee5a27f5a8d1f0bd6231.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1be3fe31204da0bc2c881ee5a27f5a8d1f0bd6231.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1be3fe31204da0bc2c881ee5a27f5a8d1f0bd6231.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Getting Ahead of the Skills Curve" src="./media_1be3fe31204da0bc2c881ee5a27f5a8d1f0bd6231.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="getting-ahead-of-the-skills-curve">Getting Ahead of the Skills Curve</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>What’s the uber skill? The ability to constantly learn, evolve, update, or even un-learn relevant skills. Today, training workforces to acquire that mindset of continuous learning is everything. We spoke with Stefan Haenisch, senior vice president of SAP Learning Strategic Initiatives at SAP, to dive deeper into his perspective, especially as he comes out of the World Economic Forum’s summer event, <a href="https://www.weforum.org/events/the-jobs-reset-summit-2021">The Jobs Reset Summit</a>, and recently published an <a href="https://www.weforum.org/agenda/2021/05/back-to-school-4-lessons-in-workforce-skilling/">article</a> for WEF about the critical lessons in workforce skilling and lifelong learning.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-the-skills-you-need-anytime-anywhere-with-sap-learning-hub">Learn the skills you need anytime, anywhere with SAP Learning Hub</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://learninghub.sap.com/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="q-in-your-article-for-the-world-economic-forum-you-discuss-the-importance-of-connecting-business-strategy-to-workforce-skills-can-you-share-what-this-looks-like-and-why-its-so-essential">Q: In your article for the World Economic Forum, you discuss the importance of connecting business strategy to workforce skills. Can you share what this looks like and why it’s so essential?</h3>
  <p><strong>A:</strong> Every company plots out its business strategy. But how often does it think about how this relates and aligns with its people strategy and strategic workforce planning and skill building?</p>
  <p>For example, if our strategy is to use <a href="https://insights.sap.com/what-is-artificial-intelligence/">artificial intelligence (AI)</a> to make our products smarter, we must simultaneously be asking ourselves how we can <a href="https://insights.sap.com/importance-upskilling/">upskill the workforce</a> on the required skills to drive this vision.</p>
  <p>Skill training shouldn’t be an afterthought. Instead, by connecting skills and strategy from the very beginning, companies can proactively adapt and more effectively position themselves for long-term success.</p>
  <h3 id="how-does-an-organization-develop-skills-for-the-future-when-things-are-changing-so-frequently-and-we-cant-possibly-know-what-the-world-will-look-like-in-the-next-couple-of-years">How does an organization develop skills for the future when things are changing so frequently and we can’t possibly know what the world will look like in the next couple of years?</h3>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="how-to-upskill-staff-from-strategy-to-practical-steps">How to Upskill Staff: From Strategy to Practical Steps</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://insights.sap.com/how-to-upskill-guide/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As we saw with <a href="http://news.sap.com/covid-19">the global pandemic</a>, things may go differently than predicted. Companies must embrace ambiguity and disruption when it comes to skills for the future. A recent article in the <a href="https://hbr.org/2020/01/the-transformer-clo">Harvard Business Review</a> noted, “If you focus on building individual micro skills, you may be missing the bigger picture.” Indeed, there are ‘expiration dates’ on technical skills as innovation emerges, so companies must establish a culture that encourages agility and experimentation in the workforce – and, not least, motivates continuous learning – in order to yield sustainable success. Soft skills like dealing with uncertainty, staying curious, as well as embracing and tolerating ambiguity are the foundation of employees being ready for the future. They can then quickly and continuously keep up the relevant hard skills.</p>
  <p><a href="https://www2.deloitte.com/content/dam/Deloitte/global/Documents/HumanCapital/gx-the-future-of-work-post-covid-19-poc.pdf">A recent report from Deloitte</a> asserts that the <a href="https://insights.sap.com/what-is-future-of-work/">future of work</a> in our technology-driven world is about “creating an environment where organizations can optimize human potential” and “empowering workers with agency and choice over what they do, unleashing their interests and passions.” What this means is that the ultimate skill is being able to continuously learn in a constantly changing business environment. Fostering agile, innovative mindsets and curiosity throughout the workforce – promoting not only the <em>need</em> to learn, but the <em>want</em> to learn – helps companies to think big and earn a competitive edge.</p>
  <h3 id="how-do-offerings-at-sap-help-support-strategic-workforce-planning-and-continuous-learning">How do offerings at SAP help support strategic workforce planning and continuous learning?</h3>
  <p>At SAP, we value ongoing learning as part of the foundation for success. In the fast-moving tech sector where skill demand changes faster than in other industries, we’re constantly evolving our learning offerings to support the hard and soft skills needed to help people stay competitive.</p>
  <p>Inside SAP, for example, we look at a long and successful track record in deploying skills management to effective resource management in our consulting business and are now evolving this to support dynamic and forward-looking workforce planning and development.</p>
  <p>Our customers can benefit from our experience as we are incorporating the best practices we learned in people and skills management into our SAP SuccessFactors solutions. When it comes to helping our customers and partners build and sustain SAP product skills, our digital learning offerings, <a href="https://open.sap.com/">openSAP</a> and <a href="https://learninghub.sap.com/">SAP Learning Hub</a>, work to provide easy-to-use, engaging content for learners to explore, build, and maintain relevant skills. Additionally, we help support career planning around the skills that learners are honing, working to provide the right learning journey targeted to each learner’s goals.</p>
  <p>Our mission is to create learning and development opportunity for all across the SAP ecosystem. We aim to empower everyone to successfully build SAP software skills using future-oriented content delivered in different formats to fit individual ways of learning. By better aligning strategic workforce planning and business strategy at the onset, as well as becoming laser-focused on a workplace culture that values agility and curiosity, businesses can get ahead of the skills curve.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning-for-life</category>
            <category>news-tag/opensap</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-certification</category>
            <category>product/sap-learning-hub</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-training-and-adoption</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Learning With SAP: What's New and What's to Come]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/06/learning-with-sap-new-to-come</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/06/learning-with-sap-new-to-come</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[What's new and next for learning with SAP? Chief Learning Officer Max Wessel discusses SAP's work to accelerate digital skills of the future.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning-for-life</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-certification</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-training-and-adoption</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Launches Free Student Offering: SAP Learning Hub, Edition for SAP Next-Gen]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/05/launch-sap-learning-hub-edition-for-sap-next-gen</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/05/launch-sap-learning-hub-edition-for-sap-next-gen</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The new SAP Learning Hub, edition for SAP Next-Gen, provides knowledge and opportunities to the next generation of talent.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>product/sap-learning-hub</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-next-gen</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-training-and-adoption</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-university-alliances</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The New Learning Toolbox for SAP S/4HANA Has Arrived]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/new-learning-toolbox-sap-s4hana</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/new-learning-toolbox-sap-s4hana</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Get a comprehensive overview of the new learning toolbox for SAP S/4HANA, including training, enablement, and courses.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1525efb65050c4567b3172aac225138d2da50bff0.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1525efb65050c4567b3172aac225138d2da50bff0.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1525efb65050c4567b3172aac225138d2da50bff0.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="The New Learning Toolbox for SAP S/4HANA Has Arrived" src="./media_1525efb65050c4567b3172aac225138d2da50bff0.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="the-new-learning-toolbox-for-sap-s4hana-has-arrived">The New Learning Toolbox for SAP S/4HANA Has Arrived</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>The past years have radically altered the manner in which the business world learns. Companies are compelled to become ever more agile and transformative and consequently there will have to be far greater emphasis on enabling workforces.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Meanwhile, a disrupted operating landscape with fresh business challenges requires us to rethink how we train our people. Naturally it makes little sense to be attempting to solve today’s challenges with yesterday’s tools.</p>
  <p>A new toolkit is needed.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="test-drive-sap-learning-hub-today-with-a-free-trial">Test drive SAP Learning Hub today with a free trial</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/td/sap-learning-hub.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="learning-and-enablement-gets-an-update">Learning and Enablement Gets an Update</h2>
  <p>Transforming business always starts with people. Education has therefore taken on ever greater strategic importance in today’s fast-evolving and automated environment, where workers are called upon to undertake new tasks and exhibit different skill sets at a moment’s notice.</p>
  <p>Learning can therefore no longer be considered a single event, but a continuous and ongoing process intrinsic to a modern way of daily life and work. As such, the manner in which training is delivered needs to be reexamined. Learning must be more accessible, easier to consume, and altogether more straightforward and efficient.</p>
  <h2 id="latest-generation-erp-requires-novel-learning-approaches">Latest Generation ERP Requires Novel Learning Approaches</h2>
  <p>The need for a new era of learning holds especially true when it comes to wiring your business up to Intelligent enterprise resource planning (ERP). Making the most out of a state-of-the-art, smart operating system necessitates pairing it with the requisite skilled personnel to run it. The Intelligent Enterprise requires smarter ways of learning.</p>
  <p>Knowledge unlocks the power of SAP S/4HANA, as demonstrated by the latest independent research findings from IDC. We understand that better training delivers considerable benefits. It:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Speeds up deployment timeframes</strong>: 70 hours or more of initial administrator training reduces deployment time by 1.5 months.</li>
    <li><strong>Is a performance enhancer</strong>: When users are well trained on SAP S/4HANA, organizations typically attain 14-times greater improvement in their KPIs.</li>
    <li><strong>Facilitates faster expansion and roll out</strong>: Not only are well trained organizations able to deploy SAP applications faster, but they also enjoy broader and faster deployments across the organization.</li>
    <li><strong>Increases customer satisfaction</strong>: Organizations are 104% more likely to be highly satisfied when users are well trained).</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="companies-like-porsche-and-attune-value-sap-s4hana-and-sap-learning-hub">Companies like Porsche and Attune Value SAP S/4HANA and SAP Learning Hub</h2>
  <p>Organizations are increasingly aware of the growing relevance of continuous learning in the workplace and are noticing the interlinkages between overall business performance and smooth enablement.</p>
  <p><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/01/9e76bbda-c77d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff.html">MHP/ Porsche</a></strong><br>“SAP Learning Hub is a main pillar of our learning strategy and it helps to ensure long-term and sustainable business success. A key outcome among others was the high adoption and certified expertise in SAP S/4HANA Cloud.”</p>
  <p><strong><a href="https://www.sap.cn/documents/2020/11/b8fcad38-be7d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff.html">Attune</a></strong><br>“As an SAP partner, SAP Learning Hub has been a key part of our learning and development strategy. It helps us stay ahead of the game and deliver exceptional value to our customer. One hundred percent of consultants were upskilled on SAP S/4HANA for fashion and vertical business, resulting in higher employee engagement and job satisfaction.”</p>
  <h2 id="sap-augments-learning-offering-for-sap-s4hana-to-reflect-emerging-trends">SAP Augments Learning Offering for SAP S/4HANA to Reflect Emerging Trends</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="book-training-for-sap-s4hana-today">Book training for SAP S/4HANA today</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://training.sap.com/content/sap-s4hana-training-overview">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>What’s new with SAP S/4HANA enablement? Content, scope, and style changes:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>A brand-new user experience (UX) interface for <a href="https://learninghub.sap.com/?sap-outbound-id=03E03105A4AD96CC886B985EC4186A834286EE13">SAP Learning Hub</a>: Customers now enjoy easier access and more personalized learning pathways.</li>
    <li>An expanded envelope for keeping up to date: The portfolio with stay current opportunities has been doubled and is now an integral part of SAP Learning Hub. On a quarterly basis, users can hone their skills with short video highlights, in-depth tutorials, hands-on practice in live training systems, and short 15-min assessments. It is complemented with expert-led live sessions and Q&#x26;A forums.</li>
    <li>Innovative learning approaches: SAP Blended Learning Academy now incorporates the concept of moderated communities while providing enablement for SAP S/4HANA. The learning experience is tailored toward two use cases, for consultancy and integration respectively. It also offers a more guided learning approach.</li>
    <li>Special focused training events, such as SAP S/4HANA transition days and SAP Skills Forum.</li>
    <li>Hundreds of tutorials have been added, including getting started, implementation, and configuration, as well as task tutorials available both in SAP Learning Hub and via the in-app learning Web assistant.</li>
  </ul>
  <p><a href="https://sapvideoa35699dc5.hana.ondemand.com/?entry_id=1_g67beyma&#x26;sap-outbound-id=03E03105A4AD96CC886B985EC4186A834286EE13">Take a video walk-through of the updates</a>.</p>
  <h2 id="solving-the-cloud-migration-skills-gap-learning-on-rise-with-sap">Solving the Cloud Migration Skills Gap: Learning on RISE with SAP</h2>
  <p>One major skills gap for many businesses relates to journeying into the cloud. SAP has been quick off the mark to plug this gap with a plethora of new learning options as part of RISE with SAP. These include:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Live content updates with many expert-led live sessions for RISE with SAP and SAP S/4HANA Cloud lines of business as well as across topics such as extensibility and integration.</li>
    <li>A dedicated RISE with SAP introduction e-learning course that clearly outlines the offering and components.</li>
    <li>An SAP S/4HANA Cloud sandbox available to all subscribers of SAP Learning Hub at no additional cost.</li>
    <li>Twenty SAP Learning Journey guides specific to public cloud offering SAP S/4HANA Cloud and a brand-new SAP Learning Journey to help SAP S/4HANA Cloud, private edition, customers onboard easily and quickly: <a href="https://help.sap.com/doc/221f8f84afef43d29ad37ef2af0c4adf/HP_2.0/en-US/f1e06ba89b8c48f299b0c61069fe31a4.html?zoom=0.7">RISE with SAP S/4HANA Cloud, Private Edition Onboarding Fundamentals Learning Journey</a>.</li>
    <li>Over 40 lines of business SAP Learning Journeys specific to SAP S/4HANA Cloud, private edition, and learners who need to upskill or freshly start their journey to this deployment of choice.</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="discover-more">Discover More</h2>
  <p>SAP is the natural learning and enablement partner for businesses that want to embrace the new world of continuous, flexible learning and those seeking to get the very most out of their Intelligent ERP.</p>
  <p>Find out more about our courses and training tools:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Test drive <a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/td/sap-learning-hub.html">SAP Learning Hub through a free trial</a></li>
    <li>Book an <a href="https://training.sap.com/content/sap-s4hana-training-overview">SAP S/4HANA training</a></li>
    <li>Check out the latest content, including webinars and podcasts, on the <a href="https://events.sap.com/eur/sap-s4hana-training-and-adoption-emea/en/home">SAP S/4HANA events page</a></li>
  </ul>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-learning-hub</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-training-and-adoption</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Transforming Learning for a Digitally Native Future]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/03/digitally-native-future-transform-learning</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/03/digitally-native-future-transform-learning</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[To support readiness for a digitally native future, SAP is simplifying access to learning for all. Learn how the company is staying dynamic.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning-for-life</category>
            <category>news-tag/moocs</category>
            <category>news-tag/opensap</category>
            <category>product/sap-learning-hub</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-training-and-adoption</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[openSAP Celebrates 5 Million Course Enrollments, Continues to Provide Learners with Innovative Learning Resources]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/03/5-million-opensap-enrollments-innovative-learning</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/03/5-million-opensap-enrollments-innovative-learning</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Mar 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is celebrating 5 million openSAP enrollments, helping ensure that the entire ecosystem has the right skills to thrive in a digital world.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e3f34c5bd39a32b2cff91dc65c9bfe018ae5b588.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e3f34c5bd39a32b2cff91dc65c9bfe018ae5b588.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1e3f34c5bd39a32b2cff91dc65c9bfe018ae5b588.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="openSAP Celebrates 5 Million Course Enrollments, Continues to Provide Learners with Innovative Learning Resources" src="./media_1e3f34c5bd39a32b2cff91dc65c9bfe018ae5b588.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="opensap-celebrates-5-million-course-enrollments-continues-to-provide-learners-with-innovative-learning-resources">openSAP Celebrates 5 Million Course Enrollments, Continues to Provide Learners with Innovative Learning Resources</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="explore-the-opensap-course-catalog">Explore the openSAP course catalog</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://open.sap.com/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced a milestone of five million course enrollments on its openSAP platform – a free online platform that offers innovative, expert-led massive open online courses (MOOCs) with accompanying microlearning and podcasts across a range of topics for learners of all abilities.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>openSAP was established in 2013 to provide individuals with essential knowledge and the opportunity to acquire the skills necessary to navigate the SAP software landscape, all with the flexibility to learn from anywhere at any time. Leveraging tried and trusted learning concepts, the online platform integrates features such as gamification and discussion forums to allow learners to interact with experts and peers in a way that is impactful and enjoyable. Hosted and run by the Hasso Plattner Institute (HPI), SAP can look back on many years of close collaboration and successful codevelopment with the institute led by Director and CEO Prof. Dr. Christoph Meinel.</p>
  <p>“In today’s digitally-driven age, it’s important to create a learning environment that is accessible for all,” said Professor Hasso Plattner, Chairman of the Supervisory Board of SAP SE. “With the <a href="/covid-19">COVID-19</a> pandemic upending all facets of life and forcing many to move to a remote working and learning environment, it has become more important than ever to lower the barriers to essential knowledge to provide learners with the right tools and resources to continue to achieve and further their skills. It is tremendous to see what we have achieved so far with openSAP, and we are excited to continue to be part of our customers’ learning journeys as we work to meet their evolving needs.”</p>
  <p>The online learning platform has recently seen accelerated growth, with the number of course enrollments doubling over the last three years. Enrollments in approximately 250 different courses average out to 20,000 enrollments per course, totaling 1.2 million learners across the board. While the platform continues to provide new courses on the latest topics and innovations, such as SAP S/4HANA, SAP Business Technology Platform, intelligent integration, digital transformation and machine learning, older courses are still relevant and consistently attract new enrollments.</p>
  <p>“With the tremendous need for reskilling through our current period of digital transformation, SAP continues to invest in lowering learning barriers through free offerings like openSAP,” said Maxwell Wessel, EVP and Chief Learning Officer, SAP. “Our goal is to ensure that everyone in our ecosystem – customers, partners, developers and employees – all have the right skills to thrive in a digital world and are equipped with the knowledge they need to prepare for the future.”</p>
  <p>The award-winning platform has garnered great recognition and learner satisfaction over the years:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Ninety-eight percent are very satisfied with the learning experience openSAP provides.</li>
    <li>Ninety-five percent say that the skills taught will help them in their future work.</li>
    <li>Ninety-nine percent plan to take additional courses on the openSAP platform in the future.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>To celebrate this achievement, SAP is offering its course <a href="https://open.sap.com/">SAP’s Integrated Intelligent Suite</a> on the openSAP platform for an additional five months (until the end of July) to provide more learners with the opportunity to acquire essential knowledge and earn a record of achievement.</p>
  <p>Today, SAP’s learning portfolio consists of various offerings to support continuous learning, performance and validation for everyone within the SAP ecosystem. As the learning environment continues to evolve, the portfolio will be enhanced and expanded by additional freely accessible offerings to meet learners’ changing needs.</p>
  <p>To start learning with openSAP, visit <a href="https://open.sap.com/">open.sap.com</a>.</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP on Twitter at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>About SAP</strong></p>
  <p>SAP’s strategy is to help every business run as an intelligent enterprise. As a market leader in enterprise application software, we help companies of all sizes and in all industries run at their best: 77% of the world’s transaction revenue touches an SAP system. Our machine learning, Internet of Things (IoT), and advanced analytics technologies help turn customers’ businesses into intelligent enterprises. SAP helps give people and organizations deep business insight and fosters collaboration that helps them stay ahead of their competition. We simplify technology for companies so they can consume our software the way they want – without disruption. Our end-to-end suite of applications and services enables business and public customers across 25 industries globally to operate profitably, adapt continuously, and make a difference. With a global network of customers, partners, employees, and thought leaders, SAP helps the world run better and improve people’s lives. For more information, visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/">www.sap.com</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Note to editors:</strong><br>To preview and download broadcast-standard stock footage and press photos digitally, please visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/photos">www.sap.com/photos</a>. On this platform, you can find high resolution material for your media channels. To view video stories on diverse topics, visit <a href="http://www.sap-tv.com">www.sap-tv.com</a>. From this site, you can embed videos into your own Web pages, share video via email links, and subscribe to RSS feeds from SAP TV.</p>
  <p><strong>For customers interested in learning more about SAP products:</strong><br>Global Customer Center: +49 180 534-34-24<br>United States only: 1 (800) 872-1SAP (1-800-872-1727)</p>
  <p><strong>For more information, press only:</strong><br>Martin Gwisdalla, SAP, +49 (6227) 7-67275, <a href="mailto:martin.gwisdalla@sap.com">martin.gwisdalla@sap.com</a>, CET<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>Any statements contained in this document that are not historical facts are forward-looking statements as defined in the U.S. Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995. Words such as “anticipate,” “believe,” “estimate,” “expect,” “forecast,” “intend,” “may,” “plan,” “project,” “predict,” “should” and “will” and similar expressions as they relate to SAP are intended to identify such forward-looking statements. SAP undertakes no obligation to publicly update or revise any forward-looking statements. All forward-looking statements are subject to various risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results to differ materially from expectations. The factors that could affect SAP’s future financial results are discussed more fully in SAP’s filings with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (“SEC”), including SAP’s most recent Annual Report on Form 20-F filed with the SEC. Readers are cautioned not to place undue reliance on these forward-looking statements, which speak only as of their dates.<br>© 2021 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.<br>Please consider our <a href="https://www.sap.com/corporate/en/legal/privacy.html">privacy policy</a>. If you received this press release in your e-mail and you wish to unsubscribe to our mailing list please contact <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a> and write Unsubscribe in the subject line.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/moocs</category>
            <category>news-tag/opensap</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-training-and-adoption</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How to Make the Most of Virtual Learning]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/make-most-virtual-learning-in-2021</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/make-most-virtual-learning-in-2021</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Last year was one of profound transformation within education. Get tips on how to make the most of virtual learning in 2021.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18d4e0f8c50e0fe6128ccf312c23bffbe5e8d0f7b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18d4e0f8c50e0fe6128ccf312c23bffbe5e8d0f7b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_18d4e0f8c50e0fe6128ccf312c23bffbe5e8d0f7b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="How to Make the Most of Virtual Learning" src="./media_18d4e0f8c50e0fe6128ccf312c23bffbe5e8d0f7b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="how-to-make-the-most-of-virtual-learning">How to Make the Most of Virtual Learning</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Last year was one of profound transformation within education. In 2020, learning institutions were compelled to go virtual almost overnight and students were suddenly exposed to new technological tools as well as the need to learn from home. Distance education became the norm.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="turn-learning-into-achieving-with-sap-training-and-adoption">Turn learning into achieving with SAP Training and Adoption</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/training-certification.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="welcome-to-the-next-new-world-of-learning">Welcome to the Next New World of Learning</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="try-ultra-personalized-and-flexible-learning-solutions">Try ultra-personalized and flexible learning solutions</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://events.sap.com/eur/next-learning/en/home">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>While certain institutions were already well-versed in modern digital learning, these changes have impacted practically every learner and teacher. Some of the key emerging trends include:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Displacement and decentralization of the classroom</li>
    <li>Adapting the home to a multifunctional space encompassing leisure, learning, and working</li>
    <li>The growing need for informal social experiences</li>
    <li>The rise of differentiated, engaging instruction</li>
    <li>A shift from passive to active learning</li>
    <li>The appearance of modern learners with significantly higher expectations for a flexible, on-demand, personalized educational experience</li>
  </ul>
  <p>To assist you with this transformative journey, SAP Community members and education experts from the SAP Training and Adoption team have joined forces to compile a set of learning hacks and practical tips.</p>
  <p><strong>1. Acclimatize to the New Mode of Instruction</strong></p>
  <p>To be effective, remote training requires many of the same core ingredients as traditional instruction: clear goals, reflection, documentation of the learning process, checking for understanding, and prompt feedback. For a well-designed learning experience, teachers therefore need to come up with ways to provide opportunities to practice, apply, reflect upon, and reinforce what is learned.</p>
  <p>Meanwhile, you, as the student, need to cultivate an appropriate, enabling ecosystem by:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Minimizing distractions in your physical and digital environments</li>
    <li>Gathering, ordering, and mastering your tech</li>
    <li>Ensuring you have the appropriate hardware and furniture</li>
    <li>Managing time</li>
    <li>Being organized and disciplined</li>
  </ul>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Efficient Learning Hacks:</strong> Did you know there are tools out there that can assist with productive learning? These include visual project management ‘<a href="https://asana.com/de/resources/what-is-kanban">Kanban</a>’ boards, ‘<a href="https://francescocirillo.com/pages/pomodoro-technique">Pomodoro</a>’ time keeping techniques, <a href="http://brain.fm/">brain.fm</a>, and <a href="https://open.spotify.com/genre/meditation-page">Spotify Genre Meditation</a> for decluttering the mind prior to a learning session.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><strong>2. Jump-Start Your Learning Experience</strong></p>
  <p>Nailing the details of your learning experience can pay back handsomely. In today’s learning landscape, we are overwhelmed with vast amounts of content to watch, read, and listen to, but knowing is different from doing. To get the very most out of online learning, make sure you organize your new knowledge in a way that you can easily access, reflect, retain, apply repeatedly, and adapt to new contexts.</p>
  <p>Order your freshly acquired knowledge to make it more meaningful:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Organize your notes digitally with note-taking tools like <a href="https://www.microsoft.com/de-de/microsoft-365/onenote/digital-note-taking-app?ms.url=onenotecom&#x26;rtc=1">OneNote</a> or <a href="https://evernote.com/">Evernote</a></li>
    <li>Break down learning to smaller, but regular chunks to make it a habit</li>
    <li>Document your progress with <a href="https://lucidspark.com/landing/create/online-sticky-notes?utm_source=google&#x26;utm_medium=cpc&#x26;utm_campaign=en_tier1_mixed_nb_search_exact_&#x26;km_CPC_CampaignId=11277231974&#x26;km_CPC_AdGroupID=111001787936&#x26;km_CPC_Keyword=sticky%20notes%20application&#x26;km_CPC_MatchType=e&#x26;km_CPC_ExtensionID=&#x26;km_CPC_Network=g&#x26;km_CPC_AdPosition=&#x26;km_CPC_Creative=470768448419&#x26;km_CPC_TargetID=kwd-350666602556&#x26;km_CPC_Country=9042015&#x26;km_CPC_Device=c&#x26;km_CPC_placement=&#x26;km_CPC_target=&#x26;mkwid=saB7mJ5UR_pcrid_470768448419_pkw_sticky%20notes%20application_pmt_e_pdv_c_slid__pgrid_111001787936_ptaid_kwd-350666602556&#x26;gclid=Cj0KCQiA9P__BRC0ARIsAEZ6irhCxhg_O21faDr00woC38bMb_pvWahFE8q2ZbyiqPMjoBB0uT2QkYYaAkBnEALw_wcB">Sticky Notes</a> and mind maps like <a href="https://www.mindmeister.com/">MindMeister</a></li>
    <li>Set up an online calendar so you don’t miss deadlines</li>
    <li>Hold regular retrospectives in the evenings or at the end of the week</li>
    <li>Factor in time for self-reflection and hands-on-practice</li>
  </ul>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Experiment:</strong> Each of us possesses an individual, unique learning preference in how we best acquire and process new information. Experiment to discover yours. If you study best with other people around, why not consider a co-working app like <a href="https://www.focusmate.com/">Focusmate</a> to boost your productivity?</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><strong>3. Take Your Learning Social</strong></p>
  <p>It’s long been recognized that high-flying students require opportunities not just to listen or read, but to actively process the information being presented. Social media-enabled communities or collaborative virtual classes allow for entirely new types of peer-to-peer learning journeys where fellow students solve issues together through problem-based discussion and reflection. This enables the learning to stick.</p>
  <p>Consider ramping up your interactions to increase information retention:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Participate in discussion forums and respond to peers’ posts</li>
    <li>Create a social network group to share ideas and knowledge</li>
    <li>Take advantage of video breakout study groups and form a learning circle with <a href="https://cogneon.github.io/lernos/en/">lernOS</a></li>
    <li>Gamify your learning and think of stories, personas, or how you can reinforce yourself and others</li>
    <li>Harness real-time, multi-player editors like <a href="https://etherpad.org/">Etherpad</a> or Wikis to write joint notes</li>
    <li>Brainstorm and sketch together with <a href="https://conceptboard.com/">Conceptboard</a> and <a href="https://www.mural.co/">Mural</a></li>
  </ul>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Discover:</strong> Ready to test-drive the exciting new mode of peer-to-peer, collaborative learning? <a href="https://www.sap.com/uk/training-certification/education-courses/learning-hub.html?video=be0d5ad5-597d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff">SAP Learning Rooms</a> bring you a uniquely interactive, virtual training experience that seamlessly blends social networking with study.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><strong>4. Embrace the Augmented Classroom</strong></p>
  <p>The beauty of virtual learning is it not only replicates the conventional classroom in a virtual setting, but actually improves upon, enriches, and augments traditional teaching techniques. With more control over your own learning, you are able to work at your own pace, channelling your energy to areas where your individual need is greatest.</p>
  <p>Inherently modular, virtual training also mobilizes a wider variety of resources to support a rich learning experience. This can include “micro-lectures” that bundle course material into coherent, bite-sized chunks to stimulate the senses from multiple directions. IBM has found that participants tend to learn five times more material in online learning settings that harness multimedia than in traditional face-to-face courses.</p>
  <p>Digital learning enhances your knowledge acquisition because it:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Balances both synchronous and asynchronous learning</li>
    <li>Caters to multiple learning styles and preferences simultaneously</li>
    <li>Introduces new forms of interactive educational discovery</li>
    <li>Places the student right at the heart of the learning process</li>
  </ul>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Reflect:</strong> Imagine that, instead of having to go to class, your learning environment came to you wherever and whenever you wanted it. <a href="https://training.sap.com/content/live-class-virtual-training">SAP Live Class</a> offers the same teachers, course materials, personal support, and face-to-face instructor engagement as a traditional classroom, but delivers it remotely to your very own home.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Acquiring new skills has never been so accessible, convenient, and individually tailored to you. SAP re-imagined the remote learning experience and has been at the forefront of pioneering these innovations. Let us guide you through the new world of SAP Learning and Adoption.</p>
  <p><a href="https://events.sap.com/eur/next-learning/en/home">Start your journey</a> and join us on February 26 to learn more about <em><a href="https://sap-se.zoom.us/webinar/register/WN_OTTDU2pLTTOLMvw8aUOCzw">Virtual Learning and Training Hacks</a></em>.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-training-and-adoption</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Training Courses in 2021: All About Choice]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/01/sap-training-courses-in-2021-learners-choice</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/01/sap-training-courses-in-2021-learners-choice</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[For SAP training courses in 2021, it's all about Learner’s Choice. Get started planning for professional development now.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ab9fa30908e5d36c712b28a30d64c57120dd0818.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ab9fa30908e5d36c712b28a30d64c57120dd0818.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1ab9fa30908e5d36c712b28a30d64c57120dd0818.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Training Courses in 2021: All About Choice" src="./media_1ab9fa30908e5d36c712b28a30d64c57120dd0818.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-training-courses-in-2021-all-about-choice">SAP Training Courses in 2021: All About Choice</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>With the new year upon us and the <a href="https://training.sap.com/">2021 SAP Training and Adoption course catalog</a> now available, it is a great time to start planning for professional development.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Using a wide range of filters, you can put together a personalized list of topics, dates, and prices according to <a href="https://training.sap.com/training-course-schedule">category, language, delivery method, and location</a>. And this year, it is all about <a href="https://training.sap.com/content/SAP-classroom-virtual-learners-choice">Learner’s Choice</a>.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-information-about-the-sap-training-and-adoption-portfolio">Get the latest information about the SAP Training and Adoption portfolio</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://training.sap.com/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="classroom-or-virtual">Classroom or Virtual</h2>
  <p><strong>Choose Your Topic: Classic or New</strong></p>
  <p>Besides a wide range of application training courses focused on <a href="https://training.sap.com/content/sap-s4hana-training-overview">SAP S/4HANA</a>, courses on SAP ERP Central Component are still available. Course offerings also include learning pathways for <a href="https://training.sap.com/content/sap-analytics-training">analytics</a> and <a href="https://training.sap.com/content/sap-cx-training-and-certification">customer experience</a>, as well as offerings such as <a href="https://training.sap.com/trainingpath/Cloud-SAP+Customer+Experience+%28C4HANA%29-Commerce+Cloud+-+Development">SAP Customer Experience solutions</a>, <a href="https://training.sap.com/trainingpath/Database+&#x26;+Technology-Implementation+&#x26;+Administration-SAP+Activate">SAP Activate</a>, <a href="https://training.sap.com/content/sap-user-experience-fiori">SAP Fiori</a>, <a href="https://training.sap.com/trainingpath/Database+&#x26;+Technology-Development-SAP+Fiori">SAPUI5</a>, <a href="https://training.sap.com/content/sap-logistic-supply-chain">digital supply chain</a>, and, of course, <a href="https://training.sap.com/content/sap-s4hana-training-overview">SAP S/4HANA Cloud</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Choose Your Venue: An SAP Training Center or Online on SAP Live Class</strong></p>
  <p>From this year, participants can choose how they join a class – in person at an SAP training center or online at an SAP Live Class. <a href="https://training.sap.com/content/SAP-classroom-virtual-learners-choice">Learner’s Choice</a> combines classroom training and virtual SAP Live Class sessions in one learning experience. The training shop shows Learner’s Choice events as classroom and SAP Live Class sessions for the same date and time.</p>
  <p><strong>Choose When: Scheduled Date or On Demand</strong></p>
  <p>If you cannot find a course date that suits your schedule, the <a href="https://training.sap.com/content/3toRun-request-training-schedule">3 to RUN</a> initiative enables scheduling a course on demand – simply bring two or more colleagues to the course with you. This applies for classroom and for virtual SAP Live Class sessions. SAP also offers <a href="https://training.sap.com/content/dach-zwischen">custom training sessions</a> for larger groups.</p>
  <p><strong>Choose How: Live Classroom Training, Self-Study, or a Blend</strong></p>
  <p>An expanded <a href="https://training.sap.com/content/blended-learning-academy">SAP Blended Learning Academy</a> program allows participants to prepare for certification as an SAP S/4HANA consultant alongside their day job. Besides the flexibility of blended learning, the live sessions held by instructors are offered throughout the learning period. And you can get in touch with instructors and peers at any time during the selected period.</p>
  <h2 id="learning-paths-to-guide-you">Learning Paths to Guide You</h2>
  <p>To view the various training curricula that SAP offers, take a look at <a href="https://help.sap.com/doc/221f8f84afef43d29ad37ef2af0c4adf/HP_2.0/en-US/317030086f83418a94dfe94173b46584.html">SAP Learning Journey guides</a>. These visual guides show course combinations for certain SAP solutions and how to progress to completion. Alternatively, you can take a look at the <a href="https://training.sap.com/content/sap-training-catalog">curricula in the course catalog</a>.</p>
  <p><a href="https://training.sap.com/">The training shop</a> is scheduled to get a makeover this year, with a new design to make it even easier to get started and access the courses.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-training-and-adoption</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>