<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/compliance/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[From CSRD Reporting to Sustainable Business Outcomes]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/from-csrd-reporting-to-sustainable-business-outcomes</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/from-csrd-reporting-to-sustainable-business-outcomes</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[By leveraging SAP Sustainability solutions, organizations can move beyond compliance, like CSRD reporting, and operationalize sustainability.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/compliance</category>
            <category>news-tag/esg</category>
            <category>news-tag/green-ledger</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-data-exchange</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-footprint-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-sustainability-solutions</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Business Ethics and Compliance: Foundation for Sustainable Development]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/ethics-and-compliance-at-sap-sustainable-development</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/ethics-and-compliance-at-sap-sustainable-development</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP’s Group Chief Compliance Officer discusses ethics and compliance at SAP and making the world run better for generations to come.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f4920e9368d5e4413dca1065881fd063f5d4624b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f4920e9368d5e4413dca1065881fd063f5d4624b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1f4920e9368d5e4413dca1065881fd063f5d4624b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Business Ethics and Compliance: Foundation for Sustainable Development" src="./media_1f4920e9368d5e4413dca1065881fd063f5d4624b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="business-ethics-and-compliance-foundation-for-sustainable-development">Business Ethics and Compliance: Foundation for Sustainable Development</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>It’s during times of great change and disruption that the strength and resilience of communities comes to the fore. The <a href="/covid-19">COVID-19</a> pandemic has impacted all aspects of life — from the way we work to the way we connect with friends and how we manage our health and our time. There have been many examples of true resilience and community spirit.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1202f47336218659019d191f987e05b7bb309b745.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1202f47336218659019d191f987e05b7bb309b745.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1202f47336218659019d191f987e05b7bb309b745.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_1202f47336218659019d191f987e05b7bb309b745.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2000" height="2800">
    </picture>However, it has also served to highlight the impact of unethical practices, such as bribery and corruption, on those people most in need of support.
  </p>
  <p>As SAP Group Chief Compliance Officer <a href="/2020/10/sap-chief-compliance-officer-trust-underpins-business">Vivianne Gordon-Pullar</a> points out, the way we conduct business today will define how future generations live, work, and thrive. By conducting only ethical business, we have the opportunity to make the world run better for generations to come.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-ethics-and-compliance-at-sap">Learn more about ethics and compliance at SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/purpose-and-sustainability/reporting-and-policies.html#ethics-compliance">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="q-how-important-are-integrity-and-ethics-in-business">Q: How important are integrity and ethics in business?</h2>
  <p><strong>A:</strong> Ethics have always been — and will always be — important in life and in business. Doing business ethically means doing business with integrity.</p>
  <p>Technological advancement and changing business models may prompt revised legislation and guidance, but the importance of ethical business remains critical in building a sustainable business. By making the right ethical choices, we can make a positive impact and strengthen democracy, economic development, and equality, as well as reduce poverty and social division.</p>
  <p>Consider SAP’s mission: we want to help the world run better and improve people’s lives. With our robust ethics and compliance framework, we strive to conduct our business ethically and in adherence to the laws in all the markets in which we work. Our purpose drives how we conduct our business, and it is this that defines our culture. We focus on ethical business because it matters — to us, to our people, our customers, partners, suppliers, and most importantly to the societies in which we work.</p>
  <h2 id="q-how-will-ethical-business-today-shape-the-future">Q: How will ethical business today shape the future?</h2>
  <p>Fundamentally, ethical business is about doing the right thing. Ethics, compliance integrity, trust: together these define good corporate citizens that deliver a positive impact on both business and the workplace, and on society as a whole.</p>
  <p>By adopting strong ethics and compliance we can shape a future that is respectful, fair, and lawful for generations to come. We want our children and theirs to be able to build on our culture of ethics and accountability so that they can thrive, and continue to advance and innovate to make the world a better place.</p>
  <h2 id="q-what-are-the-pressures-on-ethical-business">Q: What are the pressures on ethical business?</h2>
  <p>In today’s world, and amplified by the impact of the pandemic, people can find themselves with more responsibilities, expanding goals, and tightening deadlines. Together these factors can lead to an increase in pressure to compromise ethical values. No organization, geography, or sector can be complacent when it comes to ethical business and compliance.</p>
  <h2 id="q-how-has-a-culture-of-ethics-and-compliance-helped-sap-navigate-through-the-pandemic">Q: How has a culture of ethics and compliance helped SAP navigate through the pandemic?</h2>
  <p>Clearly the pandemic has raised new pressures on business, but our values and culture have remained strong and unswerving. The guiding principle is ethical business, which drives sustainable, long-term value and impact while protecting us, our customers, and partners from the risks and consequences of non-compliance.</p>
  <h2 id="q-why-is-the-united-nations-iacd-so-important">Q: Why is the United Nations’ IACD so important?</h2>
  <p>The IACD is important in driving awareness of the impact of bribery and corruption on society, highlighting how we all — including government officials, civil servants, law enforcement bodies, media representatives, the private sector, society, academia, and the public — have a responsibility and role to play in tackling corruption.</p>
  <p>We hear of the very high-profile corruption and fraud cases as they are covered in the media, quite often presented with a focus on the corporate perspective, but the impact of bribery and corruption on people’s lives is significant> Understanding the context and impact of bad choices helps us to be robust and uncompromising in rejecting unethical behavior.</p>
  <p>Understanding the very direct link between ethical business, driven by policies, trainings and defined processes, and a culture of compliance will help to turn the tide on this.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/compliance</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Using Mobile Technology with Hourly Employees: Balancing the Employee Experience and Wage Compliance Risks]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/mobile-technology-hourly-employee-experience-wage-compliance</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/mobile-technology-hourly-employee-experience-wage-compliance</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 13 Aug 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[There's value behind supporting deskless and hourly employees with mobile technology. But what wage compliance risks should be considered?]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/compliance</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/experience-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/mobile</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[New SAP Services Embed Sustainability into Business Decision-Making]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/embed-sustainability-services-into-decision-making</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/embed-sustainability-services-into-decision-making</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A new sustainability service package from SAP is the next step in the path to a greener, more resilient, safer future. Read to learn more!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/compliance</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-sustainability-solutions</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Business Imperative for Localized HR Systems]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/06/business-imperative-localized-hr-systems</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/06/business-imperative-localized-hr-systems</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Change is constant, especially today. Read to learn how SAP technology can help streamline and simplify localized HR efforts.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14c495a05fbfd40f2dfdcb9e0e752f87ece5687a5.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14c495a05fbfd40f2dfdcb9e0e752f87ece5687a5.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_14c495a05fbfd40f2dfdcb9e0e752f87ece5687a5.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="The Business Imperative for Localized HR Systems" src="./media_14c495a05fbfd40f2dfdcb9e0e752f87ece5687a5.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="the-business-imperative-for-localized-hr-systems">The Business Imperative for Localized HR Systems</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Things are changing faster than ever – it’s so obvious that it almost isn’t worth saying any more. Some changes are pretty great, like curbside pick-up for instance. Others are not so great, like learning to wear a mask when out in public. Navigating change is tough – for individuals, for government agencies, and for businesses. But when the changes are legal mandates imposed on businesses, it doesn’t matter if meeting the requirements is simple and straightforward or incredibly complex and arcane – businesses have to step up and prove compliance. If they can’t, they face a host of negative consequences like fines or hits to brand reputation.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Even before the <a href="http://news.sap.com/covid-19">pandemic</a>, we were seeing a rise in the number of government regulations around the world and a rise in the pace of changes to regulations. Throw in the uncertainty of the pandemic and pretty much every organization in nearly every country is looking at new rules for managing workforce health and safety. As the situation evolves and more data comes in about what works and what doesn’t, those rules are in continual flux.</p>
  <p>The good news is that this is a problem that technology can streamline and simplify, as long as the tech provider fully understands and embraces the scope and complexity of the problem. The other good news is that SAP has nearly 50 years of experience in solving the world’s most complex problems and <a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/dg/global-hr-payroll-regulatory-compliance/index.html">SAP SuccessFactors Human Experience Management Suite</a> works to provide embedded automated support for managing regulatory changes in more than 100 countries.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="streamline-core-processes-for-hr-with-sap-solutions">Streamline core processes for HR with SAP solutions</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/employee-central-hris.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="what-types-of-regulations"><strong>What Types of Regulations?</strong></h2>
  <p>Right now, we’re seeing rapid change in three main categories of regulation:</p>
  <p><strong>Employee Health and Safety</strong> Many industries, such as manufacturing, mining, and energy production, have long had robust health and safety programs designed to keep plant and field workers safe and productive. In the wake of the pandemic, those existing programs need to be extended to include office workers at corporate headquarters, while other ‘less hazardous’ industries such banking or retail suddenly find that they need far more robust workforce safety training and tracking.</p>
  <p><strong>Data Privacy and Security</strong><br>When the EU passed the General Data Privacy Rule in 2016, the rest of the world had no choice but to take notice, and many other countries also passed legislation outlining how personal information needed to be managed and used – or not. For employers, this has had a massive impact on how they manage personally identifiable information (PII) of their employees. They must appropriately manage and secure the data, obtain explicit consent from employees to store or process their data, and handle change audits and data purges in a manner that meets local laws.</p>
  <p><strong>Corporate Malfeasance</strong><br>After the 2008 global recession caused by unexamined banking processes, governments across the world have instituted financial transparency and reporting regulations designed to prevent financial instability.</p>
  <h2 id="how-can-hr-technology-help-manage-regulatory-compliance"><strong>How Can HR Technology Help Manage Regulatory Compliance?</strong></h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="experience-wins-with-sap-successfactors-hxm-suite">Experience wins with SAP SuccessFactors HXM Suite</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm/hxm-suite.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>HR technology can help streamline and optimize compliance by digitizing and automating compliance management, enabling monitoring of workforce qualifications, and offering learning solutions to bring workers up to speed. It also needs to provide embedded support that goes beyond mere translation and initial configuration. For an HR solution to be fully globalized, it needs to provide not only basic translation to local languages, but also the ability to display local currencies and local formatting for fields like name and address. In addition, it needs to provide ongoing updates for regulations, proactively pushing them forward so systems stay up-to-date.</p>
  <h2 id="the-sap-successfactors-difference"><strong>The SAP SuccessFactors Difference</strong></h2>
  <p><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm/core-hr-payroll.html">SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central and SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central Payroll</a> customers in over 100 countries are supported by more than 200 in-country product managers who analyze local legal requirements and prioritize software adaptations to support regulatory changes. More than 300 product developers are responsible for implementing statutory and legal changes into SAP SuccessFactors solutions. These changes are automatically shared, working to simplify and streamline the compliance process.</p>
  <p>For a deeper dive into the power of SAP’s localized HCM software, read the full report, <em><a href="https://www.sap.com/registration/protected/default-overlay.html?gated_asset_path=%2F%2Fwww.sap.com%2Fdocuments%2F2021%2F05%2Fb08304d0-e27d-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.rc.html&#x26;pdf-asset=b08304d0-e27d-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b&#x26;page=1">Fulfill Regulatory Requirements with a Localized Human Capital Management Approach</a></em>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Barbara Ocain is global executive advisor at SAP SuccessFactors.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/compliance</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-employee-central</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>