<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/sap-preferred-success-cloud-series/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2021 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Agile and Intelligent ERP Is a Myth No More with SAP Preferred Success]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/sap-preferred-success-sap-s4hana-cloud-agile-intelligent-erp</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/sap-preferred-success-sap-s4hana-cloud-agile-intelligent-erp</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With SAP Preferred Success and SAP S/4HANA Cloud, customers can can map their transition to the cloud. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1381148cc7bc7bd04a2ac63a702d499a37236c656.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1381148cc7bc7bd04a2ac63a702d499a37236c656.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1381148cc7bc7bd04a2ac63a702d499a37236c656.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Agile and Intelligent ERP Is a Myth No More with SAP Preferred Success" src="./media_1381148cc7bc7bd04a2ac63a702d499a37236c656.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="agile-and-intelligent-erp-is-a-myth-no-more-with-sap-preferred-success">Agile and Intelligent ERP Is a Myth No More with SAP Preferred Success</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>An enterprise resource planning (ERP) system that possesses the agility and intelligence to move a business forward provides distinct characteristics, ranging from realizing emerging opportunities faster to mitigating risk in real time and predicting future needs accurately. For hundreds of SAP customers, such a profound shift is best achieved with insight-driven, prescriptive, and personalized guidance.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Thinking about the technical and business challenges that executives face every day, two conclusions come to mind. First and foremost, ERP systems are fundamental platforms for digital transformation. And secondly, modernizing the technology to meet the demands of today’s fast-paced, ever-evolving market dynamics is a time-consuming, complex, and sustaining commitment.</p>
  <p>When companies are prepared to move their legacy processes to our intelligent ERP, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/s4hana-erp.html">SAP S/4HANA Cloud</a>, a wide variety of challenges inevitably arise. All organizations may not share the same goals. Shifting from a fully flexible model to one rooted in standardization may lead to confusion about the ability to adapt and modify the technology as needed. Complex discussions on integration, extensibility, data migration and management, regulatory compliance, and the cloud provider’s role may fall to the wayside among some business leaders.</p>
  <p>The <a href="https://www.sap.com/services/support-plans/preferred-success-cloud.html">SAP Preferred Success</a> offering enables our customers to productively overcome these challenges with targeted recommendations for optimizing and maximizing the value of their investment in SAP S/4HANA Cloud. The offering helps customers fully adopt the cloud mindset necessary for deployment and rapidly plan ongoing adoption of capabilities that bring specific value to their line-of-business priorities and align with their overall business goals.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-more-about-services-from-sap">Read more about services from SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/support.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="trusted-guide-to-agility-and-intelligence">Trusted Guide to Agility and Intelligence</h2>
  <p>By aligning expectations for SAP S/4HANA Cloud with desired business outcomes early in the life cycle, our customers can map their transition to the cloud and understand the importance of standardization with some adaptation of existing processes.</p>
  <p>But this standardization should also be liberating. This foundational concept simplifies support for operational processes and focuses the implementation on the capabilities and functions that truly differentiate our customers from their competitors. The initial phase of SAP Preferred Success allows our customers to fully understand how the modern ERP model fills existing gaps and continues to scale at the same pace that organizational change happens.</p>
  <p>More importantly, our customers can further build out their digital strategy by considering new capabilities and tools available that they didn’t know existed. For example, live virtual events and expert-led sessions give insight into a range of intelligent technologies embedded in SAP S/4HANA Cloud, including robotic process automation (RPA), machine learning, predictive analytics, and artificial intelligence (AI). This targeted content uncovers the connection between what SAP S/4HANA Cloud provides and what can be achieved as their ultimate vision.</p>
  <p>Although these experiences with SAP Preferred Success are early in the overall implementation of SAP S/4HANA Cloud, the information provided can be an eye-opener that impacts the entire digital transformation journey for years to come. Executives are better prepared to lead their workforce through every change along the path to go-live while knowing how to minimize costs and risk and focusing on value.</p>
  <p>Unlike some offerings, SAP Preferred Success stays engaged with SAP customers throughout the life of their deployment of SAP S/4HANA Cloud. Dedicated customer success managers help steer organizations through quarterly updates, determining which new capabilities are needed to further their digital strategy and address unique business needs. They recommend the capabilities that customers should consider enhancing or adopting and assist in the creation and completion of a minimally disruptive plan to implement relevant innovations. Adoption planning sessions are offered to dive into these new ideas, weigh their viability, and choose the best options to deliver a better technology or process experience.</p>
  <h2 id="continuous-support-for-scaled-digital-transformation">Continuous Support for Scaled Digital Transformation</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-to-know-sap-preferred-success">Get to know SAP Preferred Success</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/services/support-plans/preferred-success-cloud.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Many businesses are digitally transforming themselves with impressive speed. However, speed alone is not the key to a successful digital transformation. What’s needed is an agile and intelligent foundation that unlocks their true potential – whether navigating economic uncertainty, exploring new business models, ramping up toward a recovery, or paving the way to growth.</p>
  <p>While change doesn’t come without risks, SAP Preferred Success helps prepare SAP customers to navigate them all – with the agility and intelligence of SAP S/4HANA Cloud.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>For more real-life insights on SAP Preferred Success, read the rest of the series, “<a href="/topics/sap-preferred-success-cloud-series">Heading to the Cloud with SAP Preferred Success</a>” and discover how your entire company can accelerate cloud adoption and business outcomes with insight-driven, prescriptive, and personalized guidance and support.</p>
        <p><em>Chris Lewis is global director and product manager for SAP Preferred Success, SAP S/4HANA Cloud at SAP.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="subscribe-to-the-innovation-and-transformation-newsletter">Subscribe to the Innovation and Transformation Newsletter</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/nl/sap-innovation-and-transformation-newsletter/index.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-erp</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-preferred-success</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-preferred-success-cloud-series</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Preferred Success: Leading Organizations to the Future of Cloud Computing]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/sap-preferred-success-and-cloud-computing</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/sap-preferred-success-and-cloud-computing</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Together SAP Preferred Success and cloud computing are helping SAP customers are map and navigate unique paths to the cloud.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-preferred-success</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-preferred-success-cloud-series</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Preferred Success Reveals the Cloud’s Influence on Customer Experience]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/01/sap-preferred-success-and-customer-experience</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/01/sap-preferred-success-and-customer-experience</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With SAP Preferred Success and customer experience solutions, insight-driven, prescriptive, and personalized support is available.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16b1df8be771b3179df47340b63cf8aba4868fe6c.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16b1df8be771b3179df47340b63cf8aba4868fe6c.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_16b1df8be771b3179df47340b63cf8aba4868fe6c.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Preferred Success Reveals the Cloud’s Influence on Customer Experience" src="./media_16b1df8be771b3179df47340b63cf8aba4868fe6c.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-preferred-success-reveals-the-clouds-influence-on-customer-experience">SAP Preferred Success Reveals the Cloud’s Influence on Customer Experience</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>It’s no secret that “experience” is the new focus for many organizations – whether it is the experience of their customers or their own employees. Businesses now need to be conscious of experience more than ever.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Customers’ expectations evolve rapidly in today’s digital world, which only increases the pressure for businesses to meet them. So how do businesses provide a superior omnichannel experience for their customers now while remaining poised to adapt to the customer of the future? The answer is cloud. Investing in cloud solutions and technologies can help give businesses that competitive advantage they need.</p>
  <p>As the margin of error for businesses slims and customers increasingly prefer digital channels for their shopping experience, businesses need to use this competitive advantage to connect with their customers on multiple levels. They need to demonstrate their value as a trusted supplier, relevant brand, and committed partner. Maintaining this reputation is no easy feat given the endless number of options customers have at their fingertips and how quickly a poor experience can send a customer running to a competitor.</p>
  <p>To maintain the relationships with their customers, businesses need to understand them at a holistic level. They need to have deep insights into the behaviors and desired experiences of their customers to proactively create and engage opportunities and react quickly to challenges. For many SAP customers, cloud technology connects those customer data points and sets the foundation for more intelligent data capture, processing, and analysis. Before the pandemic, <a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/cx/b2b-value-chains-gch14/index.html?url_id=ctabutton-gl-FCEE-platforms-will-rule-in-B2B-experience-economy-blogpost">46% of B2B companies</a> were already planning to employ cloud-based technologies for 61% to 100% of their digital commerce solutions. And now, B2C businesses are following the same path to engage customers with restrictive in-person policies.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-to-know-sap-preferred-success">Get to know SAP Preferred Success</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/services/support-plans/preferred-success-cloud.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="taking-the-customer-experience-to-the-cloud--with-confidence">Taking the Customer Experience to the Cloud – with Confidence</h2>
  <p>When moving from an on-premise environment to a cloud landscape, most organizations quickly realize that the experience is unlike anything they’ve seen before. Challenges exist for both the business and IT teams. Organizations must adapt to a mindset of standardization over customization, more frequent releases containing new innovations designed to improve their business, and foundationally new products that they lack knowledge and experience administering.</p>
  <p>The <a href="https://www.sap.com/services/support-plans/preferred-success-cloud.html">SAP Preferred Success</a> offering can help organizations overcome those challenges to help ensure a successful transition to the cloud and adoption of optimal business processes, leading to better user experience. The offering orchestrates a success plan including a comprehensive portfolio of exclusive resources to optimize the consumption of cloud solutions and technology from SAP.</p>
  <p>The underlying goal of SAP Preferred Success is to help customers leverage cloud solutions the right way for their business. We work with our customers to help ensure their cloud investments play an integral role in helping them reach their desired and expected business outcomes.</p>
  <p>Through an extensive community of users, business peers, and product experts, customers receive guidance on the latest functions. A dedicated customer success manager (CSM) acts as the partner for success for customers. The CSM helps ensure milestones and goals are being met through close collaboration with customer teams and by orchestrating the necessary resources for success.</p>
  <p>Each phase and milestone – such as an implementation or a new release – is supported by SAP Preferred Success. Customers’ goals and key initiatives are integrated into the approach to help ensure the delivery of the expected outcomes and the overall digital transformation strategy.</p>
  <h2 id="driving-continuous-value-that-resonates">Driving Continuous Value that Resonates</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-more-about-services-and-support-from-sap">Read more about services and support from SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/support.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Without question, today’s competitive landscape is full of challenges primarily centered around the experience of customers. But don’t forget that a slew of new opportunities is emerging and quickly becoming a point of differentiation in a rapidly evolving digital marketplace.</p>
  <p>It’s a juggling act to handle all this change. Beyond just implementing new technology, businesses need to commit to a fundamental and permanent shift in their digital strategies, processes, and mindsets to serve customers better. And with SAP Preferred Success by their side, they have the insight-driven, prescriptive, and personalized support they need to build the right customer experience.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>Get more real-life insights on SAP Preferred Success through the series, <a href="/topics/sap-preferred-success-cloud-series">Heading to the Cloud with SAP Preferred Success</a>, and learn how your entire company can accelerate cloud adoption and business outcomes with insight-driven, prescriptive, and personalized guidance and support.</p>
        <table>
          <thead>
            <tr>
              <th>Quote</th>
            </tr>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td>Stay in the conversation by following SAP Services and Support on <a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/sapsupportinfo">YouTube</a>, <a href="https://twitter.com/SAPDigitalSvcs">Twitter</a>, <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/138840">LinkedIn</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/SAPDigitalBusinessServices">Facebook</a>.</td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
              <td>Timothy Curcio is global director of SAP Customer Experience solutions for SAP Preferred Success, Customer Engagement and Experience, at SAP.</td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="subscribe-to-the-innovation-and-transformation-newsletter">Subscribe to the Innovation and Transformation Newsletter</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/nl/sap-innovation-and-transformation-newsletter/index.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-preferred-success</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-preferred-success-cloud-series</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Preferred Success Opens the Door to Talent Businesses Need Now]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/01/sap-preferred-success-and-sap-fieldglass-talent-businesses-need</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/01/sap-preferred-success-and-sap-fieldglass-talent-businesses-need</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Preferred Success and SAP Fieldglass solutions can help organizations capitalize on a well-managed, dynamic, flexible external workforce.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f1525d4b569e23fd8bb241e9c0ce8b91aaa49e83.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f1525d4b569e23fd8bb241e9c0ce8b91aaa49e83.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1f1525d4b569e23fd8bb241e9c0ce8b91aaa49e83.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Preferred Success Opens the Door to Talent Businesses Need Now" src="./media_1f1525d4b569e23fd8bb241e9c0ce8b91aaa49e83.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-preferred-success-opens-the-door-to-talent-businesses-need-now">SAP Preferred Success Opens the Door to Talent Businesses Need Now</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>The workforce you need today isn’t the same as it was yesterday – and it will undoubtedly be different tomorrow. To <a href="https://insights.sap.com/importance-upskilling/">stay competitive</a>, organizations are capitalizing on a well-managed, dynamic, and flexible external workforce. And SAP Preferred Success can help reveal yours with the visibility and insight of SAP Fieldglass solutions.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>While navigating an economy that is reshaping customer demand, business models, and industries in unpredictable ways, executives are just as concerned about their company’s recovery readiness. Just days before the onset of the <a href="/covid-19">pandemic</a>, <a href="https://www.economist.com/business/2020/03/24/the-coronavirus-crisis-thrusts-corporate-hr-chiefs-into-the-spotlight">The Economist</a> revealed that four-fifths of CEOs worried about skill gaps, up from half in 2012.</p>
  <p>As the marketplace continues to evolve, concern over skill shortages is intensifying. In response, businesses are relying more on contingent talent, comprising 42 percent of the average workforce spend according to <a href="https://www.fieldglass.com/resources/research/contingent-workforce-insights-2019/download">Oxford Economics</a>. Sometimes, we even hear organizational managers say that their company couldn’t conduct business as usual without the support of independent contractors, freelancers, temporary staff, and service providers.</p>
  <p>Despite the importance of external workers, most CEOs and senior leaders do not have fast, easy access to information on them. This reality is not as uncommon as you may think. In fact, this lack of visibility that limits compliance, governance, cost control, and resource optimization prompts many companies to implement <a href="https://www.fieldglass.com/">SAP Fieldglass</a> solutions. And with the assistance of the <a href="https://www.sap.com/services/support-plans/preferred-success-cloud.html">SAP Preferred Success</a> offering, our customers are aligning their workforce practices with business needs in real time.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-to-know-sap-preferred-success">Get to know SAP Preferred Success</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/services/support-plans/preferred-success-cloud.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="uncovering-workforce-value-outside-the-payroll">Uncovering Workforce Value Outside the Payroll</h2>
  <p>Every business wants the best talent – on the payroll or not – that can help see them through times of disruption, uncertainty, and prosperity. They need knowledgeable people who can get the job done efficiently, timely, and with an edge that further differentiates the brand. And most importantly, executives expect high-quality outcomes at a fair price and the ability to quickly identify talent that could be a valuable candidate for an open role or leadership position.</p>
  <p>Bringing these expectations to life requires a system of checks and balances when managing workers hired outside the payroll. This capability involves workflow automation that serves as a single point for compliance auditing, assignment administration, communication, and delivery of work items. External workforce information should also be integrated seamlessly with modern enterprise resource planning (ERP) software to trigger invoicing and payment; cost analysis; and HR processes such as onboarding, badging, security checks, technology access, and laptop distribution.</p>
  <p>Our customers find that SAP Fieldglass solutions are well-suited to support such a digital transformation. But to optimize their adoption of the vendor management system, they often want insight-driven, prescriptive, and personalized support to determine <a href="https://www.fieldglass.com/solutions/contingent-workforce-management">contingent workforce</a> goals that complement their business strategies and address talent management disparities.</p>
  <p>SAP Preferred Success gives the guidance that our customers seek. With a comprehensive portfolio of exclusive success plans and support expertise, organizations can identify opportunities for cost savings, process automation, and adoption of business networks to allow qualified contingent workers to bid against each other. Tailored functional learning, change management, and enhanced support capabilities are also offered to help implement new solutions, establish new processes and refine existing ones, and foster business-wide adoption.</p>
  <p>Perhaps as its most critical advantage, SAP Preferred Success offers continuous support throughout our customers’ transformation journey. We give organizations the freedom to fully understand emerging trends and consider how they relate to their business needs, workforce capabilities, and digital strategies. These developments may include recently passed labor regulations, rising demand for new skills, evolving market forces, and shifts in business direction.</p>
  <p>Semiannually, SAP Fieldglass solutions are updated to fulfill the changing landscape of external workforce management. However, we also understand that our customers must also strategically choose capabilities based on current requirements and scale the technology as the contingent workforce fluctuates. Access to the latest release notes, solutions road maps, and real-life best practices allows our customers to make informed decisions that meet their unique needs.</p>
  <h2 id="bringing-to-life-a-connected-ecosystem-of-the-right-talent">Bringing to Life a Connected Ecosystem of the Right Talent</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-more-about-services-and-support-from-sap">Read more about services and support from SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/support.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>For many of our customers, the experience of evolving their external talent management with SAP Preferred Success brings a new perspective on the value of independent contractors, freelancers, temporary staff, and service providers.</p>
  <p>Every workshop, design-thinking session, update release, and process change allows them to make connections between business goals, defined success metrics, and the role of external employees. This level of visibility enables them to look beyond the day-to-day minutia to think about their entire workforce on and off the payroll – opening the door to the talent they need.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>Get more real-life insights on SAP Preferred Success through the series, <a href="/topics/sap-preferred-success-cloud-series">Heading to the Cloud with SAP Preferred Success</a>, and learn how your entire company can accelerate cloud adoption and business outcomes with insight-driven, prescriptive, and personalized guidance and support.</p>
        <table>
          <thead>
            <tr>
              <th>Quote</th>
            </tr>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td>Stay in the conversation by following SAP Services and Support on <a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/sapsupportinfo">YouTube</a>, <a href="https://twitter.com/SAPDigitalSvcs">Twitter</a>, <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/groups/138840">LinkedIn</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/SAPDigitalBusinessServices">Facebook</a>.</td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
              <td>John Wagner, Jr., is global practice lead for SAP Preferred Success, Intelligent Spend Management, at SAP. Nick Geiger is director of Customer Adoption, Americas, for SAP Fieldglass.</td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="subscribe-to-the-innovation-and-transformation-newsletter">Subscribe to the Innovation and Transformation Newsletter</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/nl/sap-innovation-and-transformation-newsletter/index.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-spend</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-preferred-success</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-preferred-success-cloud-series</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>