<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-topic/spend-management/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[New Supply Chain and External Workforce Innovations Reduce Organizational Inefficiencies]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/supply-chain-external-workforce-innovations</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/supply-chain-external-workforce-innovations</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[At SAP Sapphire, we introduced supply chain and external workforce innovations to help reduce inefficiency and improve decision-making.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/automation</category>
            <category>news-tag/external-workforce-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fieldglass</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA["Source from Ukraine" Initiative: The S Stands for Solidarity]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/source-from-ukraine-initiative-s-for-solidarity</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/source-from-ukraine-initiative-s-for-solidarity</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The "Source from Ukraine" initiative aims to activate procurement spend to support Ukrainian suppliers in rebuilding their businesses.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/csr</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/ukraine</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP's “Source from Ukraine” Initiative Boosts Business and Social Responsibility]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/source-from-ukraine-initiative-boosts-business-social-responsibility</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/source-from-ukraine-initiative-boosts-business-social-responsibility</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The "Source from Ukraine" initiative aims to activate procurement spend to support Ukrainian suppliers in rebuilding their businesses.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1be90b8393bfeb6a3a3bdc9a317fa62a7be1e9acb.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1be90b8393bfeb6a3a3bdc9a317fa62a7be1e9acb.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1be90b8393bfeb6a3a3bdc9a317fa62a7be1e9acb.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP’s “Source from Ukraine” Initiative Boosts Business and Social Responsibility" src="./media_1be90b8393bfeb6a3a3bdc9a317fa62a7be1e9acb.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="saps-source-from-ukraine-initiative-boosts-business-and-social-responsibility">SAP’s “Source from Ukraine” Initiative Boosts Business and Social Responsibility</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>SAP’s “Source from Ukraine” initiative, launched in March 2023, has a clear goal: to increase spend with Ukrainian companies while also generating business benefits for SAP. This shows SAP’s deep understanding of social responsibility as an integral part of its commitment to a sustainable future.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The initiative aims to activate <a href="/topics/procurement">procurement</a> spend as a means to support Ukrainian suppliers in rebuilding their businesses. Beyond sourcing for quality goods and services, SAP has a focus on integrating ESG (environmental, social, and governance) principles into decision-making as is standard with its procurement policy.</p>
  <p>It highlights SAP’s commitment not only to sourcing products from Ukraine, but also to promoting social change.</p>
  <h2 id="built-in-sustainability">Built-In Sustainability</h2>
  <p>In implementing the initiative to attract more suppliers from Ukraine, SAP initially focused on the IT sector and conducted a rigorous selection process. So far, suppliers, including industry leaders like Softserve, Unicsoft, and Luxoft, have been selected. SAP’s commitment extends beyond services to include product areas, where notable Ukrainian companies producing innovative environmentally sustainable products have been discovered.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-is-powering-equitable-access-to-economic-opportunity-education-and-employment-and-the-circular-economy">SAP is powering equitable access to economic opportunity, education and employment, and the circular economy</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/our-values/csr.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>At SAP Spend Connect Live in Vienna, Austria, held in October 2023, Ukrainian manufacturers Rekava, Mol’far Tea, and Releaf Paper showcased their sustainable and innovative products. Rekava, for example, specializes in producing biodegradable candles made from recycled coffee grounds, while Mol’far focuses on minimalism and ethical environmental practices in tea production. Releaf Paper is the world’s first manufacturer of paper made from fallen leaves, promoting sustainable products such as paper bags. By supporting these unique Ukrainian companies, SAP is not only contributing to the economic reconstruction of the country, but also sustainability efforts.</p>
  <p>One of SAP’s tier one suppliers, ABC Premium, has taken an important step by offering Rekava candles within its purchasing catalog, available to SAP employees on the SAP Ariba Buying solution.</p>
  <h2 id="strong-alliances-for-reconstruction">Strong Alliances for Reconstruction</h2>
  <p>At the outset of the project, the NGO Impact Ukraine helped SAP connect with Ukrainian suppliers. It focuses on microfinance, procurement, and recruitment from Ukraine. The collaboration is facilitated by the voluntary engagement of professionals from the technology, healthcare, and finance sectors. With Impact Ukraine’s support, SAP and other organizations can further advance their goals regarding procurement from Ukraine.</p>
  <p>SAP’s commitment to promoting innovation, sustainability, and economic growth through partnerships with Ukrainian companies not only fulfills its aspirations for procurement with purpose, but also contributes to making the world a better place.</p>
  <h2 id="helping-the-world-run-better">Helping the World Run Better</h2>
  <p>The “Source from Ukraine” initiative builds on global efforts to integrate social enterprises and diverse suppliers into SAP purchasing opportunities. Beyond SAP’s own internal purchasing efforts, the SAP Corporate Social Responsibility (SAP CSR) team is also investing in social and sustainable procurement ecosystems alongside public, private, and social sector partners like the European Commission, Deloitte, World Economic Forum’s Global Alliance for Social Entrepreneurship, and Social Enterprise World Forum’s People and Planet First verification.</p>
  <p>Consider that US$5.3 trillion in annual commerce is transacted on <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-network.html">SAP Business Network</a>. If we can help create a small shift in procurement spend to organizations prioritizing people and planet like Releaf Paper, we could collectively increase investment in sustainable development in a way that is not possible through corporate philanthropy alone. To join our efforts, please e-mail: <a href="mailto:csr-global@sap.com?subject=Please%20Share%20More%20Collective%20Social%20Procurement%20Investments%20and%20How%20to%20Get%20Involved">csr-global@sap.com</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Elena Parker is chief revenue officer for Intelligent Spend and Business Network, MEE, at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-sap-news-delivered-to-your-inbox-once-a-week">Get the latest SAP news delivered to your inbox once a week</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/nl/sap-news-center-newsletter/index.html">Sign up today</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/csr</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/ukraine</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ardent Partners Positions SAP Fieldglass as a Market Leader for Vendor Management Systems]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/ardent-partners-sap-fieldglass-vms-market-leader</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/ardent-partners-sap-fieldglass-vms-market-leader</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Ardent Partners positioned SAP Fieldglass as a Market Leader for vendor management systems (VMS). Read to learn more about the recognition.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/external-workforce-management</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fieldglass</category>
            <category>news-tag/total-workforce-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Three Key Actions Procurement Can Take to Increase Supply Chain Visibility]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/three-actions-procurement-increase-supply-chain-transparency</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/three-actions-procurement-increase-supply-chain-transparency</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Procurement’s transparency into the supply chain is paramount for informed decision-making and mitigating risk. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-spend</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>topic/spend-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Companies Are Using AI to Better Analyze and Manage Their Spend]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/how-companies-use-ai-spend-management</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/how-companies-use-ai-spend-management</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence (AI) can digitalize spend management and procurement functions, making them more efficient and resilient. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>product/sap-ariba-category-management</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-spend</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>topic/spend-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Ariba and SAP Business Network Seamlessly Integrated into SAP for Me]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-ariba-business-network-integrated-sap-for-me</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-ariba-business-network-integrated-sap-for-me</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP for Me, the central access point to solution support for customers, is now available for SAP Ariba solutions and SAP Business Network.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f7e35b0ca7f6abf5c3e5f984222aa27df64caab8.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f7e35b0ca7f6abf5c3e5f984222aa27df64caab8.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1f7e35b0ca7f6abf5c3e5f984222aa27df64caab8.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Ariba and SAP Business Network Seamlessly Integrated into SAP for Me" src="./media_1f7e35b0ca7f6abf5c3e5f984222aa27df64caab8.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-ariba-and-sap-business-network-seamlessly-integrated-into-sap-for-me">SAP Ariba and SAP Business Network Seamlessly Integrated into SAP for Me</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><a href="https://me.sap.com/">SAP for Me</a> is our digital companion for our customers, providing them with a personalized one-stop shop across their SAP product portfolio. And now it’s available to SAP Ariba and SAP Business Network customers and partners.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP for Me provides a central access point to solution support. The portal offers a user-friendly interface with improved functionalities that can enable better and faster interaction with SAP support experts and can provide immediate guidance to solutions for daily business tasks. It aims to make detached information a thing of the past on the customer and partner journey to an intelligent enterprise.</p>
  <p>Since November 6, 2023, an English-language experience has been available for customers and partners to begin their exploration before the migration. And as of today, SAP Ariba and SAP Business Network knowledge-related content on SAP for Me is available in over 20 languages.</p>
  <p>SAP for Me provides an integrated and comprehensive platform to help meet the diverse needs of its users. The Services &#x26; Support dashboard features an SAP Ariba card that helps direct users to multiple resources on the legacy SAP Ariba Connect <a href="https://connectsupport.ariba.com/sites#Home-show">platform</a>, including SAP Ariba and SAP Business Network release readiness information, product documentation, announcements, and specific content related to adoption and deployment.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="say-hello-to-your-digital-companion">Say hello to your digital companion</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://me.sap.com/">Check out SAP for Me</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>When getting started with SAP for Me, know that:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>SAP Ariba Connect S-user authorizations are automatically carried over to SAP for Me – no additional access authorization is needed to use SAP for Me.</li>
    <li>The portal gives access to personalized content in the most used languages – English, German, Japanese, Simplified Chinese, French, Portuguese, and Spanish.</li>
    <li>SAP for Me offers intuitive cards that categorize and bucket information for your convenience. Support-relevant cards are mainly located in the Services &#x26; Support and Systems &#x26; Provisioning dashboards.</li>
    <li>The availability, maintenance, and subscriptions for SAP Ariba solutions and SAP Business Network can be found in the availability section of Systems &#x26; Provisioning.</li>
    <li>You can get a holistic view of licenses, orders, and consumption status.</li>
    <li>SAP for Me is also available on mobile devices. The mobile app will be enhanced with additional features and the ability to create and manage a new case.</li>
    <li>The get support application is your primary touchpoint with support.</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="get-support-easier-and-faster">Get Support, Easier and Faster</h2>
  <p>The get support application helps guide customers through technical product issues in real time or reaching SAP experts through an AI-enabled framework. It can provide an integrated and personalized support experience to help simplify and streamline the case creation process. AI can automatically recommend solutions during the interaction, predict the right product categorization, and recommend the most suitable support channel, like Expert Chat, SAP Community, or Ask an Expert Peer, when available for the selected product.</p>
  <h2 id="access-sap-support-on-the-go">Access SAP Support on the Go</h2>
  <p>With the SAP for Me mobile app, support interaction can be possible anywhere and anytime to complete tasks and access information directly on a smartphone. The mobile app can be downloaded from the Apple Store and Google Play Store.</p>
  <p>In conclusion, SAP for Me puts customer and partner interests into focus. While partners can manage their pipeline and customer success, the portal also serves as the central entry point for all support-related topics and questions for customers. It allows access to relevant information, self-services, and consumption status connected to any purchased product portfolio.</p>
  <p>The SAP for Me migration for SAP Ariba solutions and SAP Business Network is a significant milestone as we tap into the next generation of AI opportunities to create an effective experience for our customers while delivering a seamless consistency in the look, feel, and delivery of critical <a href="/topics/support">support services</a>.</p>
  <p>SAP for Me is made for you. Follow SAP for Me on LinkedIn and bookmark SAP for Me on SAP Community to stay updated.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Rohan Patel is global head of Support for SAP Procurement.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="follow-sap-news-on-linkedin-to-stay-informed">Follow SAP News on LinkedIn to stay informed</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news">Connect with us</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-for-me</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Is on the Cutting Edge of How to Best Manage Company Spend]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-cutting-edge-company-spend-management</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-cutting-edge-company-spend-management</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP has been on the cutting edge of how to best manage company spend. Read about some recent updates to SAP spend management solutions.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11441be6b25f7c09e02cd28d0b0aa9997b84c22a1.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11441be6b25f7c09e02cd28d0b0aa9997b84c22a1.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_11441be6b25f7c09e02cd28d0b0aa9997b84c22a1.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Is on the Cutting Edge of How to Best Manage Company Spend" src="./media_11441be6b25f7c09e02cd28d0b0aa9997b84c22a1.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-is-on-the-cutting-edge-of-how-to-best-manage-company-spend">SAP Is on the Cutting Edge of How to Best Manage Company Spend</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>As a pioneer of spend management software, SAP has been on the cutting edge of how to best comprehensively manage company spend and supplier relationships.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Like at home, identifying every dollar you spend and getting the most out of it is more critical than ever for your business. And as we continue to roll out SAP Business AI technology, the teams behind SAP solutions are working on ways to help you reduce the time spent on mundane tasks so you can focus on executing your strategy, unlocking spend potential, and unleashing efficiency.</p>
  <p>The first quarter of 2024 was among the most productive in my 18 years at SAP. We debuted new AI capabilities in various SAP spend management solutions. Check out some of these highlights:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>SAP Ariba Category Management</strong>: We’ve incorporated <a href="https://community.sap.com/t5/spend-management-blogs-by-sap/generative-ai-powered-content-recommendations-in-sap-ariba-category/ba-p/13640447?campaigncode=CRM-YD24-ISM-2422141&#x26;source=blog-glo-JCollierQ124">generative AI-enabled features</a> that can assist category managers by generating recommendations in the solution’s category segmentation, market dynamics, and cost structure tools.</li>
    <li><strong>Scoutbee Discovery</strong>: SAP partnered with Scoutbee, a leading AI-powered supplier intelligence and discovery platform, to launch <a href="https://store.sap.com/dcp/en/product/display-2001012892_live_v1/scoutbee-discovery?campaigncode=CRM-YD24-ISM-2422141&#x26;source=blog-glo-JCollierQ124">Scoutbee Discovery</a>. This SAP endorsed app can rapidly identify qualified suppliers that meet specific criteria and can help advance strategic business imperatives. <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/events/7176993552332140544/comments/">Watch the recording</a> of me participating in a recent LinkedIn Live with the Scoutbee team.</li>
    <li><strong>Concur Request:</strong> Now, this service uses generative AI to help provide <a href="https://www.concur.com/blog/article/sap-concur-delivers-enriched-travel-and-expense-experiences-at-fusion-2024?campaigncode=CRM-YD24-ISM-2422141&#x26;source=blog-glo-JCollierQ124">intelligent cost estimates</a> for trip planning.</li>
    <li><strong>ExpenseIt</strong>: Users can upload receipt images to the ExpenseIt solution, which taps AI to help <a href="https://www.concur.com/blog/article/sap-concur-delivers-enriched-travel-and-expense-experiences-at-fusion-2024?campaigncode=CRM-YD24-ISM-2422141&#x26;source=blog-glo-JCollierQ124">automatically create a new expense</a> with several key fields prepopulated. Plus, ExpenseIt can now itemize hotel folios using generative AI.</li>
    <li><strong>Generative AI search</strong>: A new capability within Concur Support allows SAP Concur customers to type questions in natural language and get quick answers using generative AI, <a href="https://www.concur.com/blog/article/sap-concur-delivers-enriched-travel-and-expense-experiences-at-fusion-2024?campaigncode=CRM-YD24-ISM-2422141&#x26;source=blog-glo-JCollierQ124">without submitting a support ticket</a>.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>SAP’s market-leading spend and business network solutions are getting even smarter, working to unlock greater value for our customers. We have many resources devoted to spend management and that’s why we continue to deliver innovation in spend management.</p>
  <p>And we are only getting started. By the end of 2024, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-network.html?campaigncode=CRM-YD24-ISM-2422141&#x26;source=blog-glo-JCollierQ124">SAP Business Network</a> is planning the following enhancements:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Generative AI RFI/RFP responses in SAP Business Network Discovery</strong>: With generative AI-enabled responses for postings in SAP Business Network Discovery, suppliers will be able to respond to RFIs promptly and more accurately, helping to save time and reduce costs associated with manual labor and resource allocation.</li>
    <li><strong>Catalog enrichment using ChatGPT recommendations</strong>: This feature can enable suppliers to generate and improve product descriptions and overall catalog quality based on prompts and keyword recommendations from ChatGPT.</li>
    <li><strong>Intelligent error simplification using generative AI</strong>: This feature uses machine learning and a large language model to interpret and categorize invoice rejection reasons, allowing suppliers to reduce the number of failing invoices, improve rapid invoice submission and payment, and optimize cash flow.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>For more on how AI is transforming business networks, read <a href="/2024/04/business-networks-accelerate-ai-value">this recent article</a> from my colleague Joern Keller.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="eliminate-the-mundane-and-elevate-the-strategic-in-spend-management-with-generative-ai">Eliminate the mundane and elevate the strategic in spend management with generative AI</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/spend-management/innovations.html#ai">Discover SAP solutions</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="but-what-are-our-customers-saying">But What Are Our Customers Saying?</h2>
  <p>Each quarter, G2 highlights the top rated solutions in the industry, chosen by the source that matters most: customers. Spring 2024 is no different, and once again our suite of spend and business network solutions scored extremely well.</p>
  <ul>
    <li><a href="https://www.g2.com/products/sap-sap-fieldglass/reviews">SAP Fieldglass</a> is a G2 Spring Leader in Vendor Management.</li>
    <li><a href="https://www.g2.com/products/sap-ariba/reviews">SAP Ariba</a> is a G2 Spring Leader in Procure to Pay, Purchasing, Strategic Sourcing, Supplier Relationship Management, and Contract Lifecycle Management.</li>
    <li><a href="https://www.g2.com/products/sap-concur/reviews">SAP Concur</a> is a G2 Spring Leader in Expense, Travel &#x26; Expense, and Invoicing.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>What’s more, G2 recently announced its <a href="https://www.g2.com/best-software-companies">2024 Best Software Award winners</a>, with SAP Fieldglass and SAP Concur receiving high honors:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>SAP Fieldglass came in at No. 26 in G2’s Best Software Awards across all products and No. 12 in G2’s Best Software Awards for best midmarket products.</li>
    <li>SAP Concur came in at No. 4 in G2’s Best Software Awards for the account and software product category.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>My colleagues are also getting their flowers. Etosha Thurman, chief marketing and solutions officer of Intelligent Spend and Business Network, and Steve Seide, global head of Adoption for Intelligent Spend and Business Network, were named Top Procurement Pros in the <a href="https://issuu.com/supplydemandchainfoodlogistics/docs/sdc0324_digital?fr=sNGVkZTcxMzY1NTY">Supply &#x26; Demand Chain Executive 2024 Pros to Know awards</a>. A big congratulations also goes out to Darcy MacClaren, CRO for SAP Digital Supply Chain, who received a Pros to Know Lifetime Achievement award.</p>
  <h2 id="driving-success-for-our-customers">Driving Success for Our Customers</h2>
  <p>Hearing me spotlight our direct and indirect procurement, external workforce, and travel and expense management solutions is one thing. Seeing them in action is something way more powerful. Here are a few recent customer success stories to take in:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>American Eagle Outfitters</strong> (AEO), a leading global specialty retailer offering high-quality on-trend clothing, accessories, and personal care products through its portfolio of brands, needed to evaluate indirect purchasing processes and vendor relationships to maximize efficiency. See how <a href="https://www.sap.com/asset/dynamic/2023/10/2ed3b1af-917e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.htm?campaigncode=CRM-YD24-ISM-2422141&#x26;source=blog-glo-JCollierQ124l">SAP Business Network for Procurement and SAP Ariba solutions</a> helped simplify processes and deliver compliant purchasing protocols across the company.</li>
    <li>Power provider to over 900,000 electric customers, <strong>Oklahoma Gas &#x26; Electric Company</strong> (OG&#x26;E) faced challenges with the complexity of third-party and cross-department management of contingent workers. After transitioning SAP Fieldglass solutions to internal management, OG&#x26;E <a href="/2024/02/oge-and-brightspeed-manage-employees-contingent-workers">gained the visibility</a> to make more informed financial decisions, like supplier negotiations.</li>
    <li><a href="https://www.sap.com/idea-place/sap-innovation-awards/entries/2024-award.html#winners?campaigncode=CRM-YD24-ISM-2422141&#x26;source=blog-glo-JCollierQ124">2024 SAP Innovation Award winner</a> <strong>Vestas Wind Systems</strong>, the world’s largest manufacturer of wind turbines, launched a large-scale quality initiative powered by SAP Business Network to help mitigate product defects in a highly complex supply chain. Now, using SAP Business Network, suppliers complete predefined quality tests and document them before confirming or sending an order. This enables Vestas employees to be warned in advance of any quality issues further up the supply chain, so they can <a href="/2024/02/vestas-powering-quality-in-supply-chain">take corrective action</a>.</li>
    <li>Most <strong>KUKA</strong> employees are based in Germany, where tax regulation is complex and submitting hotel and entertainment expenses is anything but simple. The KUKA team worked together to develop a simple process using SAP Concur solutions, connected to SAP ERP, that allows employees to create hotel and entertainment expenses <a href="https://www.concur.com/en-us/casestudy/kuka?campaigncode=CRM-YD24-ISM-2422141&#x26;source=blog-glo-JCollierQ124">seven times faster</a> with fewer errors and fewer rejected expense reports.</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="join-us-at-sap-sapphire">Join Us at SAP Sapphire!</h2>
  <p>SAP Sapphire &#x26; ASUG Annual Conference is June 3-5 in Orlando, Florida, this year and I can’t wait to meet with customers, partners, and my fellow colleagues. This is the best event in the industry in my opinion and you don’t want to miss out. Join us by registering on the <a href="https://www.sap.com/events/sapphire.html?campaigncode=CRM-YD24-ISM-2422141&#x26;source=blog-glo-JCollierQ124">SAP Sapphire event website</a>, where you can also save your spot at the SAP Sapphire Virtual and SAP Sapphire Barcelona events. See you there!</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Jeff Collier is chief revenue officer for SAP Intelligent Spend and Business Network.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>product/sap-ariba-category-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-spend</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-concur</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fieldglass</category>
            <category>topic/spend-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Solutions from SAP and Icertis Empower Enterprises with Contract Intelligence Innovation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-icertis-contract-intelligence-innovation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-icertis-contract-intelligence-innovation</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP and Icertis are working to improve contract intelligence for enterprises, reducing revenue leakage and increasing efficiency. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/icertis</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[RISE with SAP: Extending Procurement’s Digital Transformation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/rise-with-sap-sap-business-network-procurement</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/rise-with-sap-sap-business-network-procurement</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The combination of RISE with SAP and SAP Business Network for Procurement empowers procurement teams to digitally transform. Learn how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/enterprise-resource-planning</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Procurement Teams Can Drive Innovation in Services Procurement]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/how-procurement-drives-innovation-in-services-procurement</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/how-procurement-drives-innovation-in-services-procurement</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A new study conducted by Art of Procurement and sponsored by SAP examines the current state of services procurement. Read about its findings.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fieldglass</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cloud-Based Visibility Equips Trading Partners to Counter Supply Chain Disruption]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/cloud-based-business-networks-equip-trading-partners</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/cloud-based-business-networks-equip-trading-partners</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Enterprises rely increasingly on cloud-based business networks to extend visibility, facilitate collaboration, and stay ahead of disruption.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17eccb1dbc9662324e6f79b18766a0335800c285f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17eccb1dbc9662324e6f79b18766a0335800c285f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_17eccb1dbc9662324e6f79b18766a0335800c285f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Cloud-Based Visibility Equips Trading Partners to Counter Supply Chain Disruption" src="./media_17eccb1dbc9662324e6f79b18766a0335800c285f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="cloud-based-visibility-equips-trading-partners-to-counter-supply-chain-disruption">Cloud-Based Visibility Equips Trading Partners to Counter Supply Chain Disruption</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>With geopolitical conflict and climate change roiling global shipping corridors from the <a href="https://www.arabnews.com/node/2463151/business-economy">Suez Canal</a> to <a href="https://www.reuters.com/business/panama-canal-does-not-plan-transit-restrictions-least-until-april-2024-02-07">Panama</a> and <a href="https://apnews.com/article/persian-gulf-oman-strait-hormuz-3a906e909be2ce63c87c1b208ed05baa">elsewhere</a>, enterprises rely increasingly on cloud-based business networks and artificial intelligence (AI) applications to extend visibility, facilitate collaboration, and ensure they stay one step ahead of the looming threat of disruption.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Meanwhile, as legislation to bolster transparency in supply chains <a href="https://www.bundesregierung.de/breg-en/service/archive/supply-chain-act-1872076">takes</a> <a href="https://minister.homeaffairs.gov.au/jasonwood/Pages/modern-slavery-act-delivers-transparency-in-supply-chains.aspx">hold</a> <a href="https://oag.ca.gov/SB657">around</a> <a href="https://laws.justice.gc.ca/eng/acts/F-10.6">the</a> <a href="https://www.consilium.europa.eu/en/press/press-releases/2023/12/14/corporate-sustainability-due-diligence-council-and-parliament-strike-deal-to-protect-environment-and-human-rights">world</a>, the digital platforms through which trading partners carry out interconnected operational processes have become indispensable for managing risk, advancing sustainability objectives, and verifying adherence to ethical business practices – even as volatility in international commerce gathers pace.</p>
  <p>After rebounding from several years of logjammed seaports, idled factories, and quarantined workers, many businesses find that though COVID-19 has receded, disruption stubbornly persists. Yet visibility across all aspects of the supply chain – from sourcing raw materials and managing logistics capacity to securing working capital solutions and managing dispersed physical assets – remains paramount in the quest to ensure business continuity, instill operational resilience, and deepen competitive advantage.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-business-network-powers-transparency-resiliency-and-sustainability">SAP Business Network powers transparency, resiliency, and sustainability</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-network.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>To help provide businesses with the 360-degree visibility and collaborative capabilities they require across complex trading relationships, SAP Business Network can connect people, processes, and systems across multiple enterprises to help digitize transactions, harness data-driven insights, and create transparent, resilient, and sustainable supply chains. Through <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-network/solutions.html#active_tab_item_1602592051931">SAP Business Network for Procurement</a>, trading partners can gain process efficiencies, improve supply assurance, and achieve business process and regulatory compliance by increasing operational transparency. With <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-network/solutions.html#active_tab_item_1602592257238">SAP Business Network Supply Chain Collaboration</a>, companies can achieve supply chain visibility by enabling plan-driven automation, optimizing capacity and inventory, and streamlining workflow. Aided by <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-network/solutions.html#active_tab_item_1602592296240">SAP Business Network for Logistics</a>, shippers and carriers can work together in unison, track and trace goods in transit, and achieve transparency throughout the supply chain by optimizing logistics processes, increasing on-time deliveries, and mitigating third-party risk. Relying on <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-network/solutions.html#active_tab_item_1660146110353">SAP Business Network Asset Collaboration</a>, owners, operators, and service providers can strengthen joint processes and the flow of shared information through a single, consistent version of asset master data to help streamline asset maintenance processes and reduce maintenance costs. With the benefit of <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-network/solutions.html#active_tab_item_1660146142567">SAP Business Network for Finance</a>, trading partners can enhance payment security, free up working capital through early-payment discounts, and leverage access to capital bound up in outstanding receivables.</p>
  <p>By linking together the routine business processes of trading partners, cloud-based networks establish the breadth of data necessary to apply predictive and generative AI applications to yield meaningful insights and outcomes. Through large language models and other forms of machine learning, cloud-based applications create new content with characteristics resembling that which precedes it. With every successive effort, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/spend-management/innovations.html#ai">generative AI</a> sharpens its ability to tailor desired content.</p>
  <p>As the world’s largest platform for business-to-business commerce, SAP Business Network can present an ideal setting for generative AI, in that it helps bring together an extremely large volume of trading partners across hundreds of millions of transactions representing US$5.3 trillion in commerce annually. Later this year, generative AI capabilities in SAP Business Network will be able to help detect errors and present automatic summaries when businesses create invoices. AI will also enable the network to help enrich catalog content and discovery posting responses for suppliers.</p>
  <p>SAP Business Network has accumulated significant structured content over many years to help generate broad operational insights for trading partners. When buyers, suppliers, carriers, and financing solution providers share operational data with each other in real time, the mutual value they create can be exponential rather than additive, enabling all participants in commerce to plan ahead with confidence, continuity, and enduring resilience.</p>
  <p>For further information on SAP Business Network and how we are equipping enterprises large and small with the digital tools needed to counter disruption, visit <a href="https://www.sap.com/businessnetwork">sap.com/businessnetwork</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Jörn Keller is executive vice president and chief product officer of SAP Business Network.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="stay-in-touch-and-follow-sap-news-on-linkedin">Stay in touch and follow SAP News on LinkedIn</h3>
        <p><em><a href="">Join us on LinkedIn</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/asset-management</category>
            <category>industry/travel-transportation</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-network-for-logistics</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Guided Sourcing Makes Achieving Strategic Goals Easier]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/guided-sourcing-makes-achieving-strategic-goals-easier</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/guided-sourcing-makes-achieving-strategic-goals-easier</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The guided sourcing capability for SAP Ariba Sourcing offers a wide range of benefits that can optimize and streamline procurement.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>product/sap-ariba-category-management</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>product/sap-ariba-sourcing</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Business Network Digitalizes Procurement for VAT E-Invoicing Mandates]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/sap-business-network-digitalizes-procurement-e-invoicing</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/sap-business-network-digitalizes-procurement-e-invoicing</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With VAT e-invoicing mandates on the rise, buyers and suppliers can join SAP Business Network for trusted, simplified procurement automation.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/financial-management</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/accounting</category>
            <category>news-tag/digitalization</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Total Workforce Management Evolution: How OG&E and Brightspeed Manage Employees and Contingent Workers]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/oge-and-brightspeed-manage-employees-contingent-workers</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/oge-and-brightspeed-manage-employees-contingent-workers</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[OG&E and Brightspeed highlight the importance of strategic planning and the effective use of technological tools in managing the workforce.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/contingent-workforce-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fieldglass</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>news-tag/total-workforce-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Cares About Your Company’s Spend]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/sap-cares-about-your-companys-spend</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/sap-cares-about-your-companys-spend</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP spend management and business network solutions continue evolving and improving with time – and 2024 will be no different.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>product/sap-ariba-category-management</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc-marketscape</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-spend</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-concur</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fieldglass</category>
            <category>news-tag/trustradius</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP’s Source-to-Pay Solution Strategy Focuses on Customer Success]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/sap-source-to-pay-strategy-focuses-customer-success</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/sap-source-to-pay-strategy-focuses-customer-success</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Within the source-to-pay landscape, SAP delivers integrated solutions to help manage all forms of spend. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>product/sap-ariba-category-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/icertis</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fieldglass</category>
            <category>product/sap-spend-control-tower</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Helping Women-Owned Businesses Thrive in the Global Economy]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/helping-women-owned-businesses-thrive-weconnect-international</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/helping-women-owned-businesses-thrive-weconnect-international</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[WEConnect International looked to SAP Business Network and SAP Ariba to help achieve its mission of supporting women-ownedsuppliers.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1eed9a4483f7bc530c8c8f4393ca753b15c1d9c6b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1eed9a4483f7bc530c8c8f4393ca753b15c1d9c6b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1eed9a4483f7bc530c8c8f4393ca753b15c1d9c6b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Helping Women-Owned Businesses Thrive in the Global Economy" src="./media_1eed9a4483f7bc530c8c8f4393ca753b15c1d9c6b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="helping-women-owned-businesses-thrive-in-the-global-economy">Helping Women-Owned Businesses Thrive in the Global Economy</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>When Danielle Thomé was a teenager, she asked her father for a job. That’s not unusual, especially since her father was the founder of Projex Engenharia, a successful business in Brazil. But the business focused on civil and industrial construction, an industry where a 15-year-old girl didn’t fit the typical job description, despite her passion for civil engineering. Although Thomé would eventually take over her father’s business, her road to success was paved with many challenges.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“One of the biggest challenges I faced was the age-old problem of gender discrimination,” Thomé recalled years later. She is one of many women driven to lead businesses that reflect their life passions.</p>
  <p>Like other entrepreneurial women, she needed support. But where are the networks to help women turn their passions into successful businesses? Thomé found her network in an SAP customer. <a href="https://weconnectinternational.org/">WEConnect International</a> connects women-owned businesses to qualified buyers around the world. As a result of becoming WEConnect International certified – and a lot of hard work by Thomé and her team – Projex Engenharia’s revenue grew by a staggering 200% in just two years.</p>
  <h2 id="many-challenges-huge-potential-impact">Many Challenges, Huge Potential Impact</h2>
  <p>Women who start and lead businesses face unique challenges. Cultural and social norms, or simply being underestimated by investors, can impede their entrepreneurial efforts. <a href="https://hbr.org/2023/02/for-female-founders-only-fundraising-from-female-vcs-comes-at-a-cost">Harvard Business Review</a> observes that “women are massively under-represented among both venture-backed entrepreneurs and VC investors.” It adds that companies founded solely by women receive <a href="https://pitchbook.com/news/articles/the-vc-female-founders-dashboard">less than 3%</a> of all venture capital investments.</p>
  <p>Also, the pandemic exacerbated the imbalance in unpaid care work – managing the household or caring for children and aging parents – which disproportionally affects women in business.</p>
  <p>Women must also deal with the challenges other businesses face, including access to markets, information technology gaps, and the red tape involved with government programs designed to help new businesses.</p>
  <p>Yet despite these challenges, women-owned and women-led businesses offer the potential to make a significant impact on the global economy. The <a href="https://www.weforum.org/agenda/2018/01/this-is-why-women-must-play-a-greater-role-in-the-global-economy/">World Economic Forum (WEF)</a> observed that “societies with greater gender equality not only offer better socioeconomic opportunities for women, but also tend to grow faster and more equitably.”</p>
  <p>The WEF also reports that advancing women’s employment <a href="https://initiatives.weforum.org/accelerators-network/gender-parity">could add US$12 trillion to global GDP and boost some countries’ economic output by as much as 35%</a>.</p>
  <p>Yet despite a clear business case, the WEF sees global progress stagnating.</p>
  <h2 id="who-has-the-power-to-drive-change-all-of-us">Who Has the Power to Drive Change? All of Us.</h2>
  <p>Traditionally, the <a href="/topics/procurement">procurement</a> function within larger organizations has held the power to fill supply chain gaps and build networks of suppliers. Yet today, other voices are making themselves heard. Consumers are expressing preferences to buy from women and other diverse businesses. Around the world – for example in the United States, Australia, and Canada – government regulations are requiring increased diversity and inclusion.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-business-network-powers-transparency-resiliency-and-sustainability">SAP Business Network powers transparency, resiliency, and sustainability</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-network.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Additionally, the C-suite is reframing corporate policy to reflect more sophisticated approaches to selecting suppliers. In my role as customer officer, SAP Intelligent Spend &#x26; Business Network, I see business leaders prioritizing inclusive sourcing metrics within their procurement strategies to help ensure they have access to all the world’s best suppliers, not just the ones they always buy from.</p>
  <p>Concerned about supply chain risks, procurement leaders are increasingly adopting localization strategies. While seeking new local suppliers, they also focus on inclusive sourcing. Of course, finding diverse suppliers is not easy – even local ones. Many women-owned businesses are small entities, not well-known in the business community. They often lack access to communication technology that would help them create greater visibility for the business.</p>
  <p>How can we make it easier to connect enterprise buyers and women-owned businesses?</p>
  <h2 id="creating-connections-with-sap-technology">Creating Connections with SAP Technology</h2>
  <p>As president, CEO, and co-founder of <a href="https://weconnectinternational.org/">WEConnect International</a>, Elizabeth Vazquez is a leader in women’s economic empowerment and global supplier diversity and inclusion. Through WEConnect International, she helps women around the world grow their businesses to create wealth, hire more people, and contribute to the prosperity of their communities.</p>
  <p>Last week, she participated in panel discussions during the World Economic Forum Annual Meeting in Davos, Switzerland. The discussions focused on opportunities to direct more corporate spend to women-owned businesses, not only to do good but to close supply chain gaps.</p>
  <p>“Women-owned businesses are a valuable and under-utilized resource,” she said. “The women who run these businesses understand what their communities need most, and they are in a unique position to help solve them. In the process, they are creating entirely new industries.”</p>
  <p>WEConnect International recognizes that to compete in the global marketplace, women-owned businesses must be visible to potential customers. It developed the WECommunity platform, a global register of women-owned businesses that makes it easier for buyers to find women-owned suppliers.</p>
  <p>Unfortunately, the initial version of WECommunity relied on technology that delivered a poor user experience, making searching the register cumbersome. WEConnect International needed a scalable, global solution that offered smooth user experiences in multiple languages for buyers and suppliers.</p>
  <p>The <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/spend-management/supplier-lifecycle.html">SAP Ariba Supplier Lifecycle and Performance</a> solution and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-network.html">SAP Business Network</a> more than met these criteria. As an added advantage, many of the WECommunity member buyers were already transacting on SAP Business Network. SAP partner Premikati Inc., a women-owned business, was engaged to help deploy the SAP solutions.</p>
  <p>In its first year, the improved functionality of WECommunity produced dramatic outcomes:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Buyer membership increased by 91%, a $2 trillion increase in purchasing power.</li>
    <li>Over 6,000 women-owned businesses experienced revenue growth, creating 24,000 new jobs.</li>
    <li>Over 7,800 new registered women-owned businesses joined the database, a 95% growth.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>“By making it easier for women to register their businesses and for large buyers to find them, our online portal based on the SAP Ariba Supplier Lifecycle and Performance solution, SAP Business Network, and SAP Business Technology Platform helps women compete in a global marketplace,” Vazquez explained.</p>
  <h2 id="breaking-through-the-barriers">Breaking Through the Barriers</h2>
  <p>Remember Thomé, the teenage girl who wanted to work in her father’s construction business? Today, she is owner-director of Projex Engenharia, the business her father founded.</p>
  <p><a href="https://weconnectinternational.org/success-stories/danielle-thome/">As a noted in a recent profile</a>, Projex Engenharia earned the WEConnect International Women’s Business Enterprise Certification. Thomé leveraged the global network of women suppliers and large buyers to become a more confident and assertive leader.</p>
  <p>The relationship has also helped produce significant benefits for her business. In just six years, Projex Engenharia landed six large corporations as clients. This enabled the company to hire more people, ensure their safety and well-being, and support social, health, and environmental campaigns.</p>
  <p>SAP is committed to helping all customers achieve their diversity and equity goals. And it is gratifying to know that our technology has become a valuable tool in making this happen.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Megan O’Connor is customer officer for SAP Intelligent Spend &#x26; Business Network.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-spend</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/women-in-leadership</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[What Does 2024 Have in Store for Spend Management and Supply Chain Professionals?]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/spend-management-supply-chain-2024-predictions</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/spend-management-supply-chain-2024-predictions</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP professionals share their 2024 predictions for spend management and supply chain. Read to learn what they said about the coming year.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18efa0d05f945b26c1dda8d2694f972656f97e05a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18efa0d05f945b26c1dda8d2694f972656f97e05a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_18efa0d05f945b26c1dda8d2694f972656f97e05a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="What Does 2024 Have in Store for Spend Management and Supply Chain Professionals?" src="./media_18efa0d05f945b26c1dda8d2694f972656f97e05a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="what-does-2024-have-in-store-for-spend-management-and-supply-chain-professionals">What Does 2024 Have in Store for Spend Management and Supply Chain Professionals?</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>When we look back on 2023, we’ll remember it as a year when economic conditions put the spotlight back on cost containment. At the same time, spend management professionals continued to face unexpected supply chain risks and environmental, social, and governance (ESG) requirements created more pressure to comply with government regulations and consumer demands.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>It was also the year when business leaders worldwide decided enough is enough. They began taking steps to future proof their supply chains. And we can’t forget that 2023 was the year when generative <a href="/topics/ai">AI</a> came to dominate every conversation about technology.</p>
  <p>Now it’s time to look ahead. Where will world events, business developments, and technology innovations take spend management in 2024? What strategies and technology will business leaders employ to bring greater resilience and efficiency to their supply chains?</p>
  <p>Here are predictions for 2024, from SAP’s intelligent spend and business network leaders.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>“In 2023, generative AI was like a bolt of lightning that compelled every business and technology leader to sit up and take notice. We’re no longer asking <em>if</em> businesses will adopt AI technology, but rather <em>how quickly</em> they can deploy it and realize its benefits. In 2024, businesses leaders will look beyond the industry buzz for solutions that deliver real-life, AI-based use cases. They’ll also see firsthand that AI is only as effective as the quality and availability of data. With the huge number of data and transactions running through our <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/spend-management/solutions.html?campaigncode=CRM-Y123-ISM-1980086&#x26;source=blog-glo-2024ISBNPredictions">systems</a> and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-network.html?campaigncode=CRM-Y123-ISM-1980086&#x26;source=blog-glo-2024ISBNPredictions">business network</a>, SAP is uniquely positioned to help organizations access the data they need, visualize it, and take decisive action to drive their success.”</p>
        <p>– <em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/muhammad-s-alam/">Muhammad Alam</a>, President and Chief Product Officer,</em><br><em>SAP Intelligent Spend and Business Network,</em><br><em>and General Manager for SAP Business Network</em></p>
        <p>“As we enter 2024, procurement organizations will continue to focus on cost containment and supply continuity in order to bring value to their businesses. These have traditionally been the primary value drivers and, in today’s economic environment, I see this continuing. The opportunity will be maintaining the expanded voice earned with stakeholders during the volatile, crisis-riddled past few years, given the resurgence of hyper focus on cost containment. I believe that the scope of procurement will not contract back to a sole focus on supply stability and cost containment. In fact, I think procurement’s remit will continue to evolve to lead broader supply chain risk management, given the growing variety and number of risks faced such as geopolitical tensions, sustainability expectations, the need for more diverse sources of supply, and lingering labor availability concerns. The challenge facing procurement will be how to tackle all of this successfully. What we’ll see is the use of innovation like generative AI, spend analysis, and category management solutions to not only provide relevant, real-time business insights, but, importantly, to increase the efficiency and productivity of procurement teams, giving more capacity to focus on the strategic work stakeholders now expect.”</p>
        <p>– <em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/etoshathurman/">Etosha Thurman</a>, Chief Marketing and Solutions Officer,</em><br><em>Intelligent Spend and Business Network, SAP</em></p>
        <p>“The more things change, the more they stay the same. Or do they? Last year we were talking about how businesses needed to grapple with economic, political, and environmental uncertainty. That hasn’t changed. What’s different is how quickly new strategies and technologies have emerged to help businesses deal with these challenges. In 2024, I expect business leaders to continue pursuing supply chain resilience and to look for solutions such as AI that enable them to make big leaps. There will also be a continued focus on cost savings. With economic concerns looming as central banks raise funds rates to counter inflation, I foresee leaders being asked to deliver higher margins for their enterprises. To do this, traditional cost-focused sourcing and procurement cost compliance will be essential.”</p>
        <p>– <em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/jeffcollier/">Jeff Collier</a>, Chief Revenue Officer,</em><br><em>Intelligent Spend and Business Network, SAP</em></p>
        <p>“As enterprises continue on their journey to digitalize procurement processes, the need for an even more intuitive user experience will increase. Procurement professionals are looking for ways to spend more time on value-adding tasks and are looking to generative AI and analytics to support them at the point of decision. Moving into 2024 and beyond, we expect the demand for these technologies to increase, as well as for new use cases to arise. At SAP, we are already evaluating further ways to embed generative AI and analytics into solutions throughout our SAP Ariba portfolio to help make our customers’ business lives easier than ever.”</p>
        <p>– <em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/salvatore-lombardo-a579662/">Salvatore Lombardo</a>, SVP, Chief Product Officer,</em><br><em>SAP Ariba Procurement Solutions, SAP</em></p>
        <p>“As technology evolves, pragmatic business leaders are looking for ways to leverage these new developments to help streamline and simplify their processes. Managing a workforce that can be comprised of up to 40% external workers demands tools that can simplify the user experience and offer broad visibility to both external and full-time workers. I predict that in 2024 we will see more organizations lean into total workforce management strategies to address this need for greater visibility across full-time and external workers, allowing businesses to align the skills they have with the work they need to complete. Along with a more holistic approach to managing their workforce, these same companies can leverage innovative AI tools designed to offer efficiencies and improve the user experience. In 2024, SAP Fieldglass customers will be able to leverage powerful AI tools, including AI-enhanced statement of work creation, translation capabilities, and our new <a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2023/10/e8cd2e18-937e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">job description builder</a> powered by generative AI. These offerings are just the beginning, with many more use cases to come.”</p>
        <p>– <em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/vishbaliga/">Vish Baliga</a>, Chief Technology Officer,</em><br><em>SAP Fieldglass Solutions, SAP</em></p>
        <p>“In my conversations with customers and prospects about their plans for 2024, they consistently voice concerns about supply chain disruption and economic uncertainty. Meanwhile, most seem to appreciate that artificial intelligence is vital to maintaining their competitive edge, yet many are unsure how to distinguish the actual value from the ample hype. In 2024, we will see more of the value that AI can deliver to organizations with capabilities to support their value chains. These include generative and predictive AI capabilities to help forecast disruptions, recommend alternate sources of raw materials, detect errors in invoices, extract pertinent data from requests for information, predict shipment and delivery times, and complete catalogue details. Trading partners need the ability to enter into additional collaborative relationships, such as those between buyers and suppliers spanning SAP Business Network Supply Chain Collaboration and material traceability and freight collaboration solutions. Also in 2024, we see network convergence taking center stage to give organizations a shared onboarding experience across all network applications, as well as a set of common data federation services to support data residency requirements.”</p>
        <p>– <em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/joernkeller/">Joern Keller</a>, Executive Vice President and Chief Product Officer,</em><br><em>SAP Business Network</em></p>
        <p>“In 2024, generative AI will deliver trillions in economic benefits. It will help companies realize greater top-line growth, be more productive, and safeguard supply chains. At the same time, resiliency will continue to be a major focus. The combination of AI and business networks will drive game-changing resiliency and productivity by facilitating improved demand forecasting and more efficient inventory management. These technologies will empower businesses to respond proactively to market changes, allowing them to source new suppliers quickly. In times of supply chain disruptions or demand surges, the nimblest companies will benefit most. Business networks will help them anticipate challenges with real-time information sharing and enhanced supply chain visibility. And there’s more good news for midmarket and smaller companies: as enterprise adoption of these technologies may begin to lag behind due to complex and unique use cases, segments like the midmarket and smaller companies will start to gain the competitive edge, building more resilient, predictable, and sustainable supply chains at scale.”</p>
        <p>– <em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/valerie-blatt-3790091/">Val Blatt</a>, Global Head, SAP Business Network</em><br><em>Customer Success and Go-to-Market, SAP</em></p>
        <p>“We’ll see business digitalization efforts go a level deeper – and become substantially more integrated – in 2024. Continued adoption of AI, automation, and virtual forms of payment will drive streamlined processes in travel, expense, and invoice. Instead of using a company credit card, employees will be able to expand their use of virtual payments for all business expenses, including travel. In turn, we’ll start to see two types of transactions emerge: trusted and exceptions. Most transactions will use trusted payment methods, and AI will quickly validate them as compliant, enabling near-immediate reimbursement. Exceptions will trigger AI-driven, automated audits to ensure compliance. In both cases, payments will be issued faster with more ease, and employees will have more time to focus on what matters most to them and the organization.”</p>
        <p>– <em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/cajseattle/">Christopher Juneau</a>, Head of SAP Concur Market Strategy,</em><br><em>SAP Concur</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-more-predictions-from-sap-concur">Get more predictions from SAP Concur</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.concur.com/blog/article/sap-concur-predictions-for-2024">Read the 2024 predictions blog</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“After another year of significant disruption caused by economic and geopolitical uncertainty, supply chain optimization has risen up the agenda as companies seek to better manage their working capital. Embedded finance has emerged as a solution, promising to reshape the way we do business and interact. Embedded finance has the power to expedite transactions, facilitate financing between trading partners, and lower trade barriers. By harnessing embedded finance, companies have the potential to optimize processes and access financing solutions seamlessly through B2B platforms. Ultimately, this will result in more streamlined payments, faster credit decisions, and expanded access to working capital.”</p>
  <p>– <em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/dweinblatt/">Danielle Weinblatt</a>, Chief Product Officer, Taulia</em></p>
  <p>“As organizations, especially midmarket companies, continue to navigate today’s dynamic business environment, they are realizing the need to work with solution partners to create more value for their customers and themselves. A strong relationship between organizations and their partner ecosystems is critical to success, and I expect we will continue to see more businesses, both large and small, looking to establish these relationships. With the cost of managing sustainable supply chains continuing to increase, companies should turn to their partner ecosystems to leverage their expertise, skills, and services. This approach can help unify a company’s operations to provide a greater experience for its buyers and sellers, enabling stronger collaboration, greater visibility and transparency, risk mitigation, and more efficient operations.”</p>
  <p>– <em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/clausgruenewald/">Claus Gruenewald</a>, Head of Intelligent Spend and</em><br><em>Business Network Partner Ecosystem, SAP</em></p>
  <h2 id="one-more-prediction">One More Prediction</h2>
  <p>Recent times have shown that unexpected disruptions aren’t the only reason businesses struggle in times of crisis. It’s also about their readiness to deal with disruption, to adapt, and to come out stronger when the crisis subsides. Many business leaders have learned this lesson. They’re taking action to ensure – to the best of their ability – that their businesses are prepared for what comes next.</p>
  <p>Of course, that’s easier said than done. Sometimes it feels like we need a crystal ball to see into the future. Or, to use a more common term, we need “visibility.” Visibility into market trends. Visibility into world events. Visibility into every corner of the supply chain.</p>
  <p>Here’s a prediction you can take to the bank: in 2024, SAP will continue to design and deliver <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/spend-management/solutions.html?campaigncode=CRM-Y123-ISM-1980086&#x26;source=blog-glo-2024ISBNPredictions">spend management</a> and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-network.html?campaigncode=CRM-Y123-ISM-1980086&#x26;source=blog-glo-2024ISBNPredictions">business network</a> solutions that can drive efficiency, leverage AI in ways that are relevant, reliable, and responsible, and create greater visibility for every size business.</p>
  <p>Mike Conners is a communications specialist for the SAP Spend Management Communications team.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-sap-news-delivered-to-your-inbox-once-a-week">Get the latest SAP news delivered to your inbox once a week</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/nl/sap-news-center-newsletter/index.html">Sign up</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-concur</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fieldglass</category>
            <category>topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/taulia</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[IDC MarketScape Positions SAP as a Leader in Cloud-Enabled Sourcing Applications]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/idc-marketscape-sap-a-leader-cloud-enabled-sourcing-applications</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/idc-marketscape-sap-a-leader-cloud-enabled-sourcing-applications</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is once again a Leader in the IDC MarketScape: Worldwide SaaS and Cloud-Enabled Sourcing Applications 2023 Vendor Assessment.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_133a48d9e5374e4e14271c30ea75c355e2eada374.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_133a48d9e5374e4e14271c30ea75c355e2eada374.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_133a48d9e5374e4e14271c30ea75c355e2eada374.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="IDC MarketScape Positions SAP as a Leader in Cloud-Enabled Sourcing Applications" src="./media_133a48d9e5374e4e14271c30ea75c355e2eada374.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="idc-marketscape-positions-sap-as-a-leader-in-cloud-enabled-sourcing-applications">IDC MarketScape Positions SAP as a Leader in Cloud-Enabled Sourcing Applications</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>SAP’s tireless efforts to build solutions that address today’s toughest challenges and deliver real business value is paying big dividends for our customers. Now, we have more recognition to prove it.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="optimize-cost-manage-risk-and-ensure-negotiated-savings-are-realized-with-strategic-sourcing-solutions">Optimize cost, manage risk, and ensure negotiated savings are realized with strategic sourcing solutions</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/spend-management/solutions.html#active_tab_item_1602592051931">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Based on an IDC analysis and customer feedback, SAP has been positioned in the Leaders Category of the <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2023/11/6a569cf4-987e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">IDC MarketScape: Worldwide SaaS and Cloud-Enabled Sourcing Applications 2023 Vendor Assessment</a>.*</p>
  <p>For those of us at SAP who have been working to deliver <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/spend-management/solutions.html#active_tab_item_1602592051931">sourcing applications</a> that help organizations work more strategically and efficiently, this is another milestone as we continue to advance up the leader board. More significantly, it is gratifying to know that this positioning is not just based on the IDC MarketScape’s detailed examination of our solutions. It’s also based on the word of our customers.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <picture>
          <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d697d7aa950dc39987b1ea9b4b23aceb728196db.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
          <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d697d7aa950dc39987b1ea9b4b23aceb728196db.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
          <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1d697d7aa950dc39987b1ea9b4b23aceb728196db.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
          <img loading="lazy" alt="IDC MarketScape Worldwide SaaS and Cloud-Enabled Sourcing Applications, 2023" src="./media_1d697d7aa950dc39987b1ea9b4b23aceb728196db.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="1013">
        </picture>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>IDC MarketScape vendor analysis model is designed to provide an overview of the competitive fitness of ICT suppliers in a given market. The research methodology utilizes a rigorous scoring methodology based on both qualitative and quantitative criteria that results in a single graphical illustration of each vendor’s position within a given market. The Capabilities score measures vendor product, go-to-market and business execution in the short-term. The Strategy score measures alignment of vendor strategies with customer requirements in a 3-5-year timeframe. Vendor market share is represented by the size of the icons.<br><em>Source:</em> <em><a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2023/11/6a569cf4-987e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">IDC MarketScape: Worldwide SaaS and Cloud-Enabled Sourcing Applications 2023 Vendor Assessment</a>, IDC #US51215923e, November 2023</em></p>
  <p>According to the IDC MarketScape’s assessment report, “SAP Ariba is a mature, established, and trusted brand…users expressed that the integration with SAP ERP and SCM products is a compelling feature.”</p>
  <p>The report highlights these SAP strengths:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Integrated sourcing functionality leverages capabilities across spend analytics, supplier identification, SAP Business Network, analytics/reporting dashboards, and contract management to serve as a “force multiplier” and provides a view to total cost impact of sourcing decisions.</li>
    <li>Milestone/project view extends functionality beyond simple sourcing events and provides all impacted stakeholders with the ability to follow progress, achieve milestones, assess the sourcing strategy, and provide input.</li>
    <li>Complex sourcing capabilities are strong, providing the ability to plan and execute large and compliant global sourcing events that come with a myriad of deliverables and complex pricing. Client references noted and appreciated the ability to scale and support sourcing events often involving many thousands of line items.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>The IDC MarketScape report says, “Consider SAP when you need a trusted, enterprise-grade sourcing application that can be utilized for large, complex, and global sourcing activities while also leveraging the capabilities of the full SAP Ariba solutions.”</p>
  <h2 id="continuing-our-commitment-to-customer-focused-innovation">Continuing Our Commitment to Customer-Focused Innovation</h2>
  <p>I believe one of the reasons SAP continues to advance its leadership position is our commitment to steady innovation. However, this is not just innovation for innovation’s sake. We carefully study the day-to-day role that sourcing and procurement professionals play today and, importantly, how that role is evolving. With these insights, we build solutions that are designed to help sourcing and procurement teams play an increasingly valuable role within their organizations.</p>
  <p>In just the past year, we have introduced a slew of innovations:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/spend-management/category-management-software.html">SAP Ariba Category Management</a></strong> empowers category managers to use data insights strategically to help identify trends, develop and implement strategies, and evaluate success relative to tangible business metrics. Just a few weeks ago at SAP Spend Connect, we announced enhancements to SAP Ariba Category Management with the power of generative AI to help procurement professionals build comprehensive and effective category strategies faster. We also highlighted <a href="/2023/09/joule-new-generative-ai-assistant">Joule</a>, which will be embedded across the SAP portfolio and available in SAP Spend Management solutions in 2024. Integration with large language models through SAP Business AI empowers procurement professionals to jump-start category strategy development and planning. Generative AI enables us to enhance our market analysis tool, offering valuable, visual insights into supply and demand, risk, opportunity, and top suppliers. <a href="https://sapvideoa35699dc5.hana.ondemand.com/?entry_id=1_caxgkqyw">Watch a demo here</a>.</li>
    <li>The next evolution of the <strong>guided buying capability</strong> in SAP Ariba solutions provides a personalized buying experience for today’s professional and casual buyers. It leverages AI to offer suggestions for specific work roles, and intelligent recommendations to help weigh the sustainability and environmental impact of a purchase. Much of this functionality is available today with more to come in future releases. <a href="https://sapvideoa35699dc5.hana.ondemand.com/?entry_id=1_ut29oylb">Watch a demo here</a>.</li>
    <li><strong>SAP Spend Control Tower</strong> delivers comprehensive spend analysis capabilities. To make it easier for procurement professionals to make timely, informed decisions, new dashboards in SAP Ariba Sourcing and SAP Ariba Buying embed near real-time insights where they are most useful — within key process workflows. These capabilities are available today and built on a new architecture that helps create the foundation for future innovation. Beginning in the first quarter of 2024, <a href="https://sapvideoa35699dc5.hana.ondemand.com/?entry_id=1_xqw6unwv">SAP Spend Control Tower</a> can help uncover cost-saving opportunities with advanced AI features and the ability to see across all spend — in cloud ERP, SAP Ariba, SAP Fieldglass, and SAP Concur solutions.</li>
    <li>With <strong>risk-aware procurement</strong> with AI-infused risk assessment in source-to-settle solutions, SAP has embedded AI-powered supplier risk assessment capabilities into its source-to-settle solutions to help business users make smarter decisions faster. This can make it possible to assess risk profiles within the sourcing, contracting, and buying solutions as an integral part of these processes to determine third-party risk. Supplier risk assessment capabilities are available today in SAP Ariba Sourcing, SAP Ariba Contracts, and SAP Ariba Buying.</li>
    <li>Supporting the <strong>future of supplier management</strong>, at SAP Spend Connect Live we provided a sneak preview of a feature we refer to as “the new supplier 360,” which can deliver instant access to risk data, AI-powered sustainability information, and operational evaluation to help track metrics like price variance. <a href="https://sapvideoa35699dc5.hana.ondemand.com/?entry_id=1_ai4bz2p8">Watch a demo here</a>.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>Want to read more about these innovations? <a href="/2023/10/procurement-news-sap-spend-connect-live">Check out our announcement from SAP Spend Connect Live 2023</a> that provides additional detail.</p>
  <h2 id="why-sap-is-a-leader">Why SAP is a Leader</h2>
  <p>With our steady stream of innovations designed to help businesses solve their biggest sourcing challenges, I am not surprised that SAP is once again a Leader in the <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2023/11/6a569cf4-987e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">IDC MarketScape: Worldwide SaaS and Cloud-Enabled Sourcing Applications 2023 Vendor Assessment</a>. Of course, we don’t intend to stop here.</p>
  <p>Looking ahead, we know that sourcing professionals are looking for an intuitive user experience that allows them to focus on strategic, value-added tasks. And as we have seen recently, they are eager to use generative AI, analytics, and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/spend-management/innovations.html#ai">practical AI use cases</a> to support them.</p>
  <p>Of course, AI is only as effective as the quality and availability of data. A huge amount of data and transactions run through SAP’s <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/spend-management/solutions.html">systems</a> and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-network.html">business network</a>. This makes us uniquely qualified to help organizations — large and small — access the data they need, interpret it, and take decisive action.</p>
  <p>As we have already shown, SAP is in the best position to deliver the broad-based use cases that businesses will need to stay competitive as conditions evolve.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Baber Farooq is senior vice president and head of Market Strategy for SAP Procurement Solutions.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-sap-news-on-linkedin-for-the-latest-stories">Connect with SAP News on LinkedIn for the latest stories</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news/">Follow now</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><em>*“IDC MarketScape: Worldwide SaaS and Cloud-Enabled Sourcing Applications 2023 Vendor Assessment” November 2023, IDC #US51215923e</em></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc-marketscape</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Supporting Midmarket Business with a Strong Partner Ecosystem]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/supporting-midmarket-business-strong-partner-ecosystem</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/supporting-midmarket-business-strong-partner-ecosystem</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP solutions help midmarket companies build relationships with partners that can enable continued growth and scale. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/sme</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-partneredge</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[What’s New in Intelligent Spend Management Solutions from SAP]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/whats-new-intelligent-spend-management-from-sap</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/whats-new-intelligent-spend-management-from-sap</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Intelligent spend management solutions from SAP are evolving with AI, being adopted by customers, and receiving recognition. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-spend</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-concur</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fieldglass</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-spend-connect-live</category>
            <category>topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/trustradius</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pushing the Boundaries of Procurement Customer Support with Innovations]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/procurement-customer-support-innovations</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/procurement-customer-support-innovations</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In this interview, SAP's Rohan Patel gives insight into how SAP support can benefit procurement customers. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1560e17ebf571c1cad896fad5b3fe9c897622bb2c.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1560e17ebf571c1cad896fad5b3fe9c897622bb2c.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1560e17ebf571c1cad896fad5b3fe9c897622bb2c.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Pushing the Boundaries of Procurement Customer Support with Innovations" src="./media_1560e17ebf571c1cad896fad5b3fe9c897622bb2c.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="pushing-the-boundaries-of-procurement-customer-support-with-innovations">Pushing the Boundaries of Procurement Customer Support with Innovations</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>In today’s environment, customers are reevaluating how they use and source software solutions to run their business. The move from on-premise only solutions to the cloud is SAP’s reality as a cloud vendor.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“Customers undergo a cloud transformation because they want to accelerate their time to realize business value and they want to take advantage of innovations faster,” says Rohan Patel, global vice president, Customer Support and Innovation, Product Support – Procurement, SAP. “That’s what helps them maintain a competitive edge. And they want to do this while decreasing overall cost and minimizing risk.”</p>
  <p>This is where <a href="https://support.sap.com/en/offerings-programs/strategy.html">Real-Time Support</a> from SAP can add real value. In this conversation, Patel gives insight into how SAP support can benefit procurement customers.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Q: How are you supporting procurement customers on their journey to the cloud?</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><strong>A:</strong> Support in the old, on-premise world is what I like to call ‘break-fix’ support. When something failed, the IT department submitted a ticket for support, the problem was fixed, and communication ended until another issue arose. Being a break-fix support provider doesn’t work in the cloud environment. Support requires speed and foresight. Support today identifies problems and optimizes products before customers even notice something’s not working as it should.</p>
  <p>SAP’s strategy is predictive and proactive. We want continuous dialogue with customers to provide insights and guidance that are a value-add so we’re there long before something breaks. Success in the cloud requires adoption outside of the traditional IT environment. Business end users and lines of business, like procurement, supply chain, and HR, expect easy-to-use support portals that are intuitive and quickly anticipate user needs.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-creates-support-programs-to-drive-an-innovative-and-consistent-experience">SAP creates support programs to drive an innovative and consistent experience</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://support.sap.com/en/offerings-programs/strategy.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Can you share some examples of how SAP is using data to enhance predictive support?</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The tools we use not only help us deliver a great experience to our customers, they also continue to improve the SAP solution itself. Consider the cloud health monitoring tools within <a href="https://support.sap.com/en/alm/sap-cloud-alm.html">SAP Cloud ALM</a>, our application lifecycle management solution that helps streamline the way our customers implement and operate their cloud and hybrid environments across the entire business.</p>
  <p>These tools can analyze what’s happening at the customer experience layer – for example, how long it takes a specific page to load, how long a user needs to complete a task, and any delays that could frustrate users, hinder adoption, and slow business outcomes. We act proactively at the engineering and cloud operations layer to help continuously improve that user experience.</p>
  <p>We also use knowledge and data to improve the support experience, such as with <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-network.html">SAP Business Network</a>, which has millions of active trading partners. This business-to-business network of companies connecting, transacting, and partnering with numerous shared processes and information expands the SAP footprint well beyond the four walls of traditional operations.</p>
  <p>Equally important is that our consumers today aren’t just IT support users, but rather work in departments throughout the clients’ operations. We’ve taken steps to help meet the needs of all those different user types. We can provide quick, easy-to-understand guidance and answers to their questions using intuitive, personalized, and real-time channels driven by both humans and artificial intelligence (AI). This recommendation engine can provide guided answers based on who the users are, what they’re doing in the application, or what questions they ask. Users can quickly get useful and relevant content for answering their questions. The data from those guided-answer experiences is then fed into the product road map to help make the entire user experience more optimal and eliminate problems before they happen.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>What have procurement customers seen in 2023 from SAP support?</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Our procurement coverage in 2023 hits two themes: harmonization and Real-Time Support. Let me begin with the harmonization perspective. We’re taking significant steps to create a customer support experience that’s consistent across all SAP solutions – most notably a single entry point to SAP support with <a href="https://me.sap.com/">SAP for Me</a>. SAP Fieldglass solutions went live on SAP for Me case management in March 2023, and SAP Ariba solutions and SAP Business Network will soon follow. The SAP for Me portal can give users the information and answers they need, specific to the solution they’re using. Earlier this year, procurement support went live on <a href="https://community.sap.com/">SAP Community</a>, where our business and IT users can access blog posts, tips, and connect with experts. Even customers and partners can provide an additional layer of insights and guidance, especially to a specific industry.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-real-time-support">Learn more about Real-Time Support</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://support.sap.com/en/offerings-programs/strategy.html">Explore now</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>This year we have been working to bring our Real-Time Support concept to reality for procurement. When I talk about Real-Time Support, I mean support that is always on, continuously evolves, and adapts to customer needs. This can be direct access to support experts for business-critical processes when and where customers need it. It’s the live support channels such as <a href="https://support.sap.com/en/my-support/product-support.html?anchorId=section_519294480">Expert Chat</a>, Ask an Expert Peer, context-sensitive help, <a href="https://support.sap.com/en/my-support/product-support.html?anchorId=section_1255553798">support built into our software</a>, and <a href="/2022/05/artificial-intelligence-future-of-customer-support-experiences">AI-driven self-service access</a> to a vast knowledge base and user community.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>What do you see in the future of support for procurement?</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>I envision a day when customers don’t need to see or hear from us because we’re already working behind the scenes to give our customers a seamless, reliable, and delightful experience. The ultimate vision is preventative support with the help of AI and machine learning – in other words, self-healing IT systems.</p>
  <p>Of course, there will always be times when customers need us. In those times, SAP is prepared to offer as simple of a support experience as possible, such as with <a href="https://support.sap.com/en/my-support/product-support.html?anchorId=section_1255553798">Built-In Support</a> and direct access to experts or a quick call to solve an issue the moment it occurs. We also continuously look to disrupt ourselves by using new technologies such as ChatGPT to enable self-help or self-guidance and provide the best possible customer experience.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>What sets the SAP support experience apart in the industry?</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP mindfully takes steps that help give customers the best support experience possible. We can provide a cohesive array of support channels, self-service tools, and cloud health and integration monitoring. Even with these successes in hand, SAP will continuously push the boundaries of customer support with new innovations, help ensure support interactions are delightful, and offer Real-Time Support that can bring ambition to life.</p>
  <p>Follow Rohan Patel on <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/rohan-patel-1897941/">LinkedIn</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Regina Postman is part of Customer Support and Innovation Communications at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="follow-sap-news-on-linkedin">Follow SAP News on LinkedIn</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news">Connect with us</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/product-support</category>
            <category>news-tag/real-time-support</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fieldglass</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-for-me</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[With AI, Business Networks Set to Transform Core Operational Processes]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/with-ai-business-networks-transform-processes</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/with-ai-business-networks-transform-processes</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[As the world’s largest platform for business-to-business commerce, SAP Business Network presents an ideal setting for generative AI.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-spend</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Future of Procurement Is Already a Reality at SAP Spend Connect Live]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/procurement-news-sap-spend-connect-live</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/procurement-news-sap-spend-connect-live</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[At SAP Spend Connect Live, we announced a series of procurement innovations focused on streamlining procurement processes. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>product/sap-ariba-buying</category>
            <category>product/sap-ariba-contracts</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-concur</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fieldglass</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-spend-connect-live</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Announces Winners of the SAP Global Intelligent Spend and Business Network Partner Excellence Awards for 2023]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/2023-sap-global-intelligent-spend-business-network-partner-excellence-awards</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/2023-sap-global-intelligent-spend-business-network-partner-excellence-awards</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Six SAP Global Intelligent Spend and Business Network Partner Excellence Awards were presented at SAP Spend Connect Live in Vienna.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-concur</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fieldglass</category>
            <category>sap-award/sap-global-lob-partner-excellence-awards</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-spend-connect-live</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Latest Innovations in Spend Management Revealed at SAP Spend Connect Live]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/innovations-ai-spend-management-sap-spend-connect-live</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/innovations-ai-spend-management-sap-spend-connect-live</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[As shown at SAP Spend Connect Live, SAP has made it a mission to enable the use of generative AI in spend management. Read to find out how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-spend</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-concur</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fieldglass</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-spend-connect-live</category>
            <category>topic/spend-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Unveils New Generative AI Innovations That Boost Productivity and Effectiveness in Spend Management]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/sap-spend-connect-live-generative-ai-innovations-spend-management</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/sap-spend-connect-live-generative-ai-innovations-spend-management</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[From SAP Spend Connect Live in Vienna, SAP has introduced new business AI and UX innovations for spend management and business network.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>product/sap-ariba-category-management</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>product/sap-ariba-buying</category>
            <category>product/sap-ariba-contracts</category>
            <category>product/sap-ariba-sourcing</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-concur</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-spend-connect-live</category>
            <category>product/sap-spend-control-tower</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Sneak Peek at All Things Procurement at SAP Spend Connect Live in Vienna]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/procurement-at-sap-spend-connect-live-2023</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/procurement-at-sap-spend-connect-live-2023</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[At SAP Spend Connect Live 2023, hear about innovations that will drive the future of procurement. Read about what to expect at the event.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-spend-connect-live</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No Breaks for SAP Spend Management Solutions]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/no-breaks-sap-spend-management</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/no-breaks-sap-spend-management</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP spend management solutions continue to help our customers and gain recognition from trusted review sites. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-spend</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-concur</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fieldglass</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-spend-connect-live</category>
            <category>topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/trustradius</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>