<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/sap-event/sap-global-partner-summit/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[RISE with SAP Showcased at the SAP Global Partner Summit and SAPPHIRE NOW]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/06/rise-with-sap-at-sap-global-partner-summit-sapphire-now</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/06/rise-with-sap-at-sap-global-partner-summit-sapphire-now</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Partners focus on expanded opportunity from RISE with SAP, following the 2021 SAP Global Partner Summit and SAPPHIRE NOW.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ff8d1fee33090d2ef3e69393d2fede693578997b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ff8d1fee33090d2ef3e69393d2fede693578997b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1ff8d1fee33090d2ef3e69393d2fede693578997b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="RISE with SAP Showcased at the SAP Global Partner Summit and SAPPHIRE NOW" src="./media_1ff8d1fee33090d2ef3e69393d2fede693578997b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="rise-with-sap-showcased-at-the-sap-global-partner-summit-and-sapphire-now">RISE with SAP Showcased at the SAP Global Partner Summit and SAPPHIRE NOW</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>This year, we were excited to host more than 7,000 viewers from all over the world for the 2021 SAP Global Partner Summit conference. Due to the <a href="/covid-19">pandemic</a>, the event was once again virtual, giving participants a fully digital experience broadcasted from New York City.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Hosted by Katie Linendoll, the summit provided viewers with insights and information from SAP executives, industry insiders, partner-business colleagues, and partners from around the world. Attendees heard about market dynamics, SAP’s strategy, how SAP continues to evolve the partner business, and the many opportunities with <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/rise.html">RISE with SAP</a>, <a href="https://www.sap.com/sea/industries/industry-cloud.html">industry cloud</a>, and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">SAP Business Technology Platform</a>.</p>
  <p>Over the past year, SAP experienced much growth across its cloud portfolio – with its highest growth in cloud in the last 10 years occurring in the first quarter of 2021. SAP partners recognize the great opportunity in the cloud and were able to leverage RISE with SAP and SAP Business Technology Platform to drive customers’ business transformations in the cloud and capitalize on that opportunity.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="rise-with-sap-transform-your-business-in-the-way-that-works-best-for-you">RISE with SAP: Transform your business in the way that works best for you</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/rise.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="partners-focus-on-growth-opportunity">Partners Focus on Growth Opportunity</h2>
  <p>Don Dickinson, founder and president of <a href="https://www.dickinson-assoc.com/">Dickinson + Associates</a>, shared this sentiment during the SAP Global Partner Summit primetime show, noting growth potential with RISE with SAP combined with SAP Business Technology Platform, particularly after a year that drove so many customers to <a href="https://insights.sap.com/digitization-vs-digitalization/">digitalization</a>.</p>
  <p>“[RISE with SAP] allows you to innovate on SAP Business Technology Platform on an ongoing basis once you get past that migration…and it offers improved best practices that have been built in,” he said. “This is a huge opportunity, coming out of the pandemic with a workforce that is ready to transform businesses.”</p>
  <p>Some partners have taken it a step further by working with SAP to launch cloud offerings for their specific industries. Ginger Smith, director of Strategic Partnerships at Honeywell, discussed the recent launch of <a href="https://store.sap.com/en/product/display-0000059571_live_v1/Honeywell%20Forge%20Real%20Estate%20Operations">Honeywell Forge Real Estate Operations with SAP</a> and how working with partners helps in bringing their platform to another level. After starting out with a few focus areas in real estate, Honeywell started expanding into indoor air quality and space utilization. Looking forward, Honeywell will leverage the SAP partnership to introduce its next iteration of the solution.</p>
  <h2 id="trust-is-key">Trust Is Key</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-more-news-and-coverage-from-sapphire-now">Read more news and coverage from SAPPHIRE NOW</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/topics/sapphire-now">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Throughout the event, it was encouraging to see so many partners finding success with SAP and with each other, thanks to the SAP partner ecosystem. During the primetime show, SAP Chief Partner Officer Karl Fahrbach discussed how SAP partners value simplicity, speed, trust, and transparency. He noted that trust is key to any relationship, particularly the one between SAP and its partners.</p>
  <p>This was echoed by the yearly Partner Enablement Experience survey, which seeks partner feedback on the SAP ecosystem. “If you look at the survey results, you’ll see that we’re doing very well in that partners are trusting SAP, but I think what is important to note is that SAP is trusting partners as well,” Fahrbach said. “When we commit to provide transparency of our road map – because we expect to deliver the Intelligent Enterprise with partner intellectual property and partner products – that means that we trust our partners.”</p>
  <p>The SAP Global Partner Summit event recapped some of the major highlights of the partner ecosystem, including the successes of our partners and SAP’s programs and engagements, and RISE with SAP over the past several months. Building on this momentum, at SAPPHIRE NOW, attendees learned about new RISE with SAP capabilities that will position SAP partners for success in the future.</p>
  <h2 id="rise-with-sap-offering-extended-at-sapphire-now">RISE with SAP Offering Extended at SAPPHIRE NOW</h2>
  <p>On the heels of the SAP Global Partner Summit event, SAP kicked off its global SAPPHIRE NOW conference. Throughout the event, attendees could see the value of SAP’s partner ecosystem, with sessions from partners including NTT Data, Accenture, and Siemens, as well as customer sessions featuring partners like Deloitte, Skillsoft, Blackline, and many more.</p>
  <p>SAPPHIRE NOW showcased the RISE with SAP transformation packages for specific industries, which build on the January introduction of the RISE with SAP offering. Since January, SAP partners, like Dickinson + Associates, have taken RISE with SAP to new heights, working to achieve revenue for their businesses and create value for their customers.</p>
  <p>The RISE with SAP transformation packages for specific industries provide business transformation as a service with five initial industry-tailored cloud solutions for retail, consumer products, automotive, utilities, and industrial machinery and components. Partners complement the RISE with SAP industry packages by applying their industry know-how to create personalized solutions for the industries they specialize in. This broadens the reach of SAP and its partners, leaving no industry untouched or unsupported by our joint expertise.</p>
  <p>Recently, Accenture launched <a href="https://www.accenture.com/us-en/about/events/sapphire-now">SOAR with Accenture</a>, a curated collection of RISE with SAP-compatible resources and services that enable business transformation across industries. SOAR with Accenture bundles business transformation capabilities and assets to help companies plan for, implement, and manage RISE with SAP projects. We are working with Accenture to develop a portfolio of ground-breaking industry solutions that span multiple industries, including utilities, oil and gas, defense, and manufacturing – among others.</p>
  <p>Tata Consultancy Services (TCS), one of our strategic partners, recently launched <a href="https://www.tcs.com/enterprise-navigator">TCS Enterprise Navigator™</a>, a consulting-led framework that takes a holistic and measurable approach to modernize processes and enhance user experience. Designed to help organizations build a future-ready digital foundation that allows them to enhance innovation and easily adapt to changing market dynamics, the consulting framework brings smart capabilities such as strategic insights and value realization, organization change management, and pre-configured business and industry solutions, supported by emerging technologies, such as AI and advanced analytics. The set of pre-configured industry and business solutions, <a href="https://www.tcs.com/tcs-crystallus">TCS Crystallus™</a>, powered by assets and accelerators bundled together as a business reference suite, complements the RISE with SAP offering and helps companies in their digital transformation journey by leveraging SAP digital core technologies and SAP Business Technology Platform. TCS Crystallus can be adopted for various industry segments including life sciences, hi-tech, professional services, and travel and transportation, and delivers faster time to market, competitive advantage, business agility and minimal business disruption.</p>
  <p>RISE with SAP highlights the best that the SAP partner ecosystem has to offer, as it demonstrates how partners and SAP work together to provide great solutions for customers. At SAP, we are continuously innovating on top of the solutions we offer to partners to achieve partner success because we know that, ultimately, partner success will bring customer success. As we move forward, we will continue putting our partners at the center of our strategy with the RISE with SAP offerings, and we will work closely with our partners to achieve our joint goals.</p>
  <p>If you missed important sessions of either event, join us on demand for the <a href="https://events.sap.com/sap-global-partner-summit/en/home">SAP Global Partner Summit</a> event or <a href="https://reg.sapevents.sap.com/flow/sap/sapphirenow2021/event/page/home">SAPPHIRE NOW</a>.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-global-partner-summit</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Why Partners Rise with SAP]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/05/why-partners-rise-sap-global-partner-summit</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/05/why-partners-rise-sap-global-partner-summit</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 May 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[At the 2021 SAP Global Partner Summit, SAP is announcing updates to help partners drive customer in the post-pandemic business landscape.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_124f2695176516da3f135c78e53d2015319efbdc6.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_124f2695176516da3f135c78e53d2015319efbdc6.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_124f2695176516da3f135c78e53d2015319efbdc6.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Why Partners Rise with SAP" src="./media_124f2695176516da3f135c78e53d2015319efbdc6.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="why-partners-rise-with-sap">Why Partners Rise with SAP</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Disruption spurs innovation. For businesses to thrive in a rapidly changing business environment, organizations must continuously adapt by reexamining what value they can provide customers. The <a href="/covid-19">pandemic</a> greatly accelerated this need to transform.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>This presents a unique opportunity for SAP and our partner ecosystem to guide customers through their digital transformations. Together, we help customers remain agile by managing their business processes end-to-end in the cloud. As a result of the combined value we deliver to customers, partners and SAP will generate significant cloud growth and recurring revenue.</p>
  <p>To help partners maximize this opportunity, SAP launched a new Partner Success organization, which will drive more proactive engagement from our partner experience managers. They will work with partners on their business plans and priorities. We continue to collect and act on partner feedback for our <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/rise.html">RISE with SAP</a> offering while focusing on improving partner profitability in migrating customers to the cloud.</p>
  <p>SAP is also introducing a new commercial offer and enhancing existing offerings to help partners drive customer success in the post-pandemic business landscape. Here are some details.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="join-the-sap-global-partner-summit-now">Join the SAP Global Partner Summit now</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://events.sap.com/sap-global-partner-summit/en/home">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="enhancing-partner-flexibility-to-support-cloud-adoption">Enhancing Partner Flexibility to Support Cloud Adoption</h2>
  <p>At the beginning of the third quarter of 2021, SAP plans to launch <strong>SAP PartnerEdge Cloud Choice, flex model</strong>, a new revenue share and go-to-market model that provides partners more flexibility to win cloud customers and rewards partners for driving customer adoption. The flex model splits the customer life cycle into two stages, creating opportunities to better compensate partners for delivering effective sales activities <em>and</em> ongoing customer engagement. We are also improving partner cash flow by paying upfront commissions for sales activities and increasing commission rates on renewals. This new model will be available in both the large enterprise and midmarket.</p>
  <h2 id="identifying-the-right-partner-quickly-and-easily">Identifying the Right Partner, Quickly and Easily</h2>
  <p>By the third quarter of 2021, SAP will roll out a new <strong>Partner Finder</strong> to provide greater exposure for partners. This will feature a simple, intuitive, and visual search function for customers to identify the right partner for a specific business or industry without needing an in-depth knowledge of SAP technology or the ecosystem.</p>
  <p>Customers will enjoy a more seamless experience that includes the possibility for partners to provide direct links to <a href="https://urldefense.com/v3/__https:/store.sap.com/dcp/en/?campaigncode=CRM-YD21-SOC-0STORPZ&#x26;source=ppc-SAPSTOREPS-GL-202121&#x26;gclid=EAIaIQobChMIm_7R9uiP8AIVmLd3Ch0Z_g8nEAAYASAAEgJ85PD_BwE__;!!HhhKMSGjjQV-!v_7qQHXHacqE5C74Cg_Il3rk-hqqQ50oeED2UvGqykCDyEm5VuJcTdmcHmBj_SBaAPdyCQ$">SAP Store</a> and <a href="https://urldefense.com/v3/__https:/www.sap.com/partner/find/qualified-packaged-solutions/finder.html?sort=title_asc__;!!HhhKMSGjjQV-!v_7qQHXHacqE5C74Cg_Il3rk-hqqQ50oeED2UvGqykCDyEm5VuJcTdmcHmBj_SB3dkzyYA$">SAP-qualified partner-packaged solutions</a>. On the main page, customers can also learn more about available SAP solutions and certified consultants and even ask the partners to be contacted, which will be a new source of demand generation for our partners. At the end of May, partners will receive an invitation to access the new partner profile editor to maintain their profile in the new Partner Finder, which they will need to complete to be visible to customers and prospects.</p>
  <h2 id="highlighting-partner-contributions-to-customer-success">Highlighting Partner Contributions to Customer Success</h2>
  <p>We are likewise transforming the annual <strong>SAP Pinnacle Award</strong> program to align to our strategy and priorities for creating customer value in the cloud. We will publicly recognize those partners that have delivered superior customer value in close collaboration with SAP and provide partners with the means to market this achievement accordingly. Customers that want to work with the best of the best in the ecosystem will be able to immediately recognize the partner for unique and outstanding contributions to customer success.</p>
  <h2 id="partner-led-customer-success-through-sap-btp-and-industry-cloud">Partner-Led Customer Success Through SAP BTP and Industry Cloud</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-the-power-of-partnership-with-sap">Learn more about the power of partnership with SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/partner.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP aims to foster a best-in-class ecosystem that delivers outstanding cloud implementations to drive customer outcomes and innovation. To achieve this, SAP is investing significantly to train and educate partner consultants and developers with the most relevant and up-to-date learning content so they can develop solutions on <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">SAP Business Technology Platform</a> (SAP BTP).</p>
  <p>With this additional training, SAP partners will be prepared to develop industry cloud offerings, combining partner-built solutions and innovations with integration services, industry content, accelerators, and industry reference architectures. With SAP BTP as its foundation, SAP’s industry cloud helps deliver lower costs for software innovation and faster time to innovation.</p>
  <p>As more partners developing on SAP technologies, we can help customers improve their integrated end-to-end business processes and run apps and data on a unified platform.</p>
  <p>According to a <a href="https://partneredge.sap.com/en/library/education/solutions/ind/industry_cloud/e_ep_forrester_study.html">study from Forrester Consulting</a> commissioned by SAP, partners can expect to close between 50% and 150% more deals in their first year, when compared to a similar solution, using a process model and integration technology within SAP’s industry cloud, in addition to selling bigger deals, closing deals faster, extending contract durations, and improving margins by leveraging SAP BTP.</p>
  <p>SAP is also committed to helping ensure that affordable training accompanies the release of new cloud updates and solutions. SAP is investing to help partners increase their SAP-certified consultants. In total, we aim to grow to 150,000 trained and certified SAP consultants within the SAP ecosystem by the end of 2021.</p>
  <h2 id="empowering-partner-sales-success-with-new-test-and-demo-opportunities">Empowering Partner Sales Success with New Test and Demo Opportunities</h2>
  <p>Since <a href="/2020/06/software-demonstration-environments-customer-partner-success">June 2020</a>, SAP has provided partners with free access to <a href="/2021/02/sap-lowers-cost-test-demo-environment-partners-enhances-dashboard">SAP Partner Demo Environment, shared option</a>. This integrated, pre-configured software demonstration environment expedites sales conversations. SAP is steadily expanding live demo offerings – with more than 50 live scenarios to date – to help partners position the value of the Intelligent Enterprise vision, including SAP BTP, RISE with SAP, and industry cloud.</p>
  <p>Additionally, the SAP Demo Store site has been expanded and offers partners more than 430 demo scenarios. SAP is also offering partners further price reductions for additional core cloud solutions. Since January 2021, we have offered reduced subscription fees for dedicated test, demo, and development systems of RISE with SAP, SAP Digital Supply Chain solutions, and the the database and data management and HR and people management portfolios. Reduced pricing on other cloud solutions is planned for later this year.</p>
  <h2 id="delivering-new-sap-for-me-dashboards">Delivering New SAP for Me Dashboards</h2>
  <p><a href="https://me.sap.com/">SAP for Me</a> is quickly becoming the single point of access for partners to get key actionable insights and data in a digital format. We extended the scope of <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nlJ3Q09DCxs">SAP for Me</a> and added new dashboards and functionalities for SAP PartnerEdge program members. This includes dynamic cards that sales professionals can use to facilitate end-to-end deal execution and that partner contacts can use to have a partner-level view of SAP certifications and partnership insights.</p>
  <p>Before the end of the year, partners will have access to additional insights, such as customer project information, a partner solutions dashboard, and cloud product adoption and renewals. This will give partners a complete overview of their customers’ information and relationship with SAP.</p>
  <p>I look forward to a gradually improving global demand in the second half of 2021 and am confident that the initiatives and opportunities we are creating for our partners will enhance the experience of both partners and customers and drive success — now and in the future.</p>
  <h2 id="additional-reading">Additional Reading</h2>
  <ul>
    <li><strong><a href="/">SAP Ecosystem and SAP Business Technology Platform: Delivering the Intelligent Enterprise for Customers</a></strong>, by Juergen Mueller, chief technology officer and member of the Executive Board of SAP SE</li>
    <li><strong><a href="/2021/02/unified-technology-platform-partners-enable-customer-success">How Partners Enable Customer Success Through a Unified Technology Platform</a></strong>, by Jagdish Sahasrabudhe, CTO of the Global Partner Organization at SAP</li>
  </ul>
  <p>Learn more on how to partner with SAP at <a href="https://www.sap.com/partner.html">sap.com/partner</a> and <strong><a href="https://events.sap.com/sap-global-partner-summit/en/home">join the 2021 SAP Global Partner Summit</a></strong>. Existing partners can find details on <a href="https://partneredge.sap.com/en/partnership/licenses/shared_demo.html">SAPPartnerEdge.com</a>.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>Follow SAP on Twitter at <a href="https://twitter.com/SAPPartnerEdge">@SAPPartnerEdge</a> and <a href="https://twitter.com/SAPPartners4U">@SAPPartners4U</a>,<br>as well as on <a href="https://www.facebook.com/SAPPartnerEdge">Facebook</a>, <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-partneredge/">LinkedIn</a>, and <a href="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCAb6QuwIS4HCCxYoCEWjBog">YouTube</a></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Karl Fahrbach is global partner officer at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-global-partner-summit</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-partner-demo-environment</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-partneredge</category>
            <category>sap-award/sap-pinnacle-awards</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-store</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Ecosystem and SAP Business Technology Platform: Delivering the Intelligent Enterprise for Customers]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2021/05/sap-ecosystem-and-sap-btp-customers-intelligent-enterprise</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2021/05/sap-ecosystem-and-sap-btp-customers-intelligent-enterprise</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 May 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Together, the SAP ecosystem and SAP BTP can help meet the current and future needs of all customers and partners. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1805cb6700c6bf79354428f1f119fe5187b2ad02f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1805cb6700c6bf79354428f1f119fe5187b2ad02f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1805cb6700c6bf79354428f1f119fe5187b2ad02f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Ecosystem and SAP Business Technology Platform: Delivering the Intelligent Enterprise for Customers" src="./media_1805cb6700c6bf79354428f1f119fe5187b2ad02f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-ecosystem-and-sap-business-technology-platform-delivering-the-intelligent-enterprise-for-customers">SAP Ecosystem and SAP Business Technology Platform: Delivering the Intelligent Enterprise for Customers</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>While SAP continues to deliver innovative products, it is the broad ecosystem of more than 22,000 partners, together with the SAP Services team, that helps customers realize business value and achieve tangible return on their investments.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>While this has always been the case for implementation of SAP applications, the opportunity is even greater for partners to extend, integrate, and build with SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP).</p>
  <p>Let’s look at it in more detail.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="join-the-sap-global-partner-summit-now">Join the SAP Global Partner Summit now</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://events.sap.com/sap-global-partner-summit/en/home">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="what-is-sap-business-technology-platform">What Is SAP Business Technology Platform?</h2>
  <p>The <a href="/covid-19">COVID-19</a> pandemic and subsequent pressures on the global supply chain demonstrate even more urgently how important it is for companies of all sizes to digitally transform their business. Today’s businesses need to be able to adapt quickly to volatile markets and changing business requirements. For this, they need a modern technology platform that enables integrated applications and processes, helps users create value from data, and supports easy extensibility and ecosystem access while offering development agility and speed.</p>
  <p>SAP BTP is the unified, business-centric, and open business and technology platform for the entire SAP ecosystem. It is the unified foundation for the Intelligent Enterprise, integrates and extends SAP’s intelligent suite, and is central to the industry cloud as well as partner applications.</p>
  <p>In a nutshell, what SAP BTP offers is all about business centricity:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Integration</strong> that connects applications, data, and business processes across SAP and third-party solutions, including hyperscaler technology</li>
    <li><strong>Data to value</strong>, with actionable insights and automation across enterprise data and processes</li>
    <li><strong>Extensibility and ecosystem access</strong>, thanks to rapid configuration, plug-and-play extensions, and business content from partners</li>
    <li><strong>Development agility and speed,</strong> with intuitive tooling and interfaces that create an engaging developer and user experience</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="what-is-in-it-for-partners">What Is In It for Partners?</h2>
  <p>Let’s step back for a second and look at the market potential. SAP solutions touch 77% of the world’s transactions. Because of that reach, we can offer <a href="https://www.sap.com/corporate/en/documents/2017/04/4666ecdd-b67c-0010-82c7-eda71af511fa.html">a more fully integrated set of business processes</a>, such as lead-to-cash, design-to-operate, source-to-pay, and recruit-to-retire. And within those processes are hundreds of specific components or sub-processes supported by SAP partners.</p>
  <p>So when our partners build on, integrate with, or extend SAP technology using SAP BTP, they have a unique opportunity to help customers by delivering solutions that reach across business processes, often tapping into data sources across various master data domains. Connecting and enriching the business processes increases the value and impact that each sub-process brings to an organization.</p>
  <p>Let me give you an example: Within the <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2020/03/66bf6ef3-8b7d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff.html">design-to-operate business process</a>, partners are adding value with solutions that extend the core SAP offering, including supplier certification, sustainability ratings, as well as search and data lookup. With those, customers are creating new revenue streams as a service business models using SAP BTP.</p>
  <p>SAP BTP offers opportunities for all types of SAP partners. It enables partners to stay competitive and innovative while keeping service practices, software sales, and margins secure. Software partners can build and sell complementary applications that extend and integrate with SAP’s end to end business processes. Value-added resellers can package data, analytics, workflow, and other automation content as accelerators to differentiate their businesses and drive new revenue streams. Services partners can continue to maintain ABAP practices, develop custom extensions on SAP BTP, build integrations to customer’s non-SAP systems, and deliver specific data-to-value business requirements.</p>
  <p>A good example is <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2020/09/3c1db458-ad7d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff.html">Taronga Conservation Society Australia</a>’s work with SAP and SAP partners Bourne Digital and Bluetree, each of which played an essential role in Taronga’s digital transformation journey. As a strategic advisor for the customer, SAP provided expert guidance and support to identify the right technology and approach according to its strategic objectives. From the beginning of the SAP Analytics Cloud journey, SAP experts helped develop a proof of concept and integration approach in partnership with Bluetree. Bourne Digital helped design and implement the <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2020/07/b65da1a9-a07d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff.html">Stax application</a> using SAP Workflow Management and other services in SAP BTP, leveraging design thinking and agile development to quickly deliver an easy-to-use application in a short time frame.</p>
  <p>Recently, in a commissioned survey conducted on behalf of SAP, <a href="https://d.dam.sap.com/s/p/a/kpPjvf5/Forresters%20Industry%20Cloud%20TEI%20Study%20-%20An%20SAP%20Partner%20Opportunity%20Analysis_Apr2021.pdf">The Partner Solution Opportunity For SAP’s Industry Cloud Portfolio</a>, Forrester Consulting concluded that partners benefit greatly from building solutions as part of <a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/industry-cloud.html">SAP’s industry cloud</a>. The integrated industry portfolio puts partners’ offerings front and center alongside SAP-built solutions. SAP BTP also provides a framework, technologies, and additional features such as artificial intelligence (AI) and analytics that help ensure interoperability with SAP while enabling the creation of replicable industry-specific solutions.</p>
  <h2 id="what-is-the-role-of-the-partner-ecosystem-in-rise-with-sap">What Is the Role of the Partner Ecosystem in RISE with SAP?</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="accelerate-business-outcomes-with-sap-business-technology-platform">Accelerate business outcomes with SAP Business Technology Platform</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>We cannot speak about the importance of SAP BTP for our partner ecosystem without addressing our latest offering: <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/rise.html">RISE with SAP</a>.</p>
  <p>RISE with SAP is about helping customers transform their businesses to an intelligent enterprise that is flexible, resilient, and built for continuous innovation. For many customers this transition will include a journey to the cloud at a pace that supports their business and industry requirements.</p>
  <p>SAP BTP, as the platform for the Intelligent Enterprise, is one part of the RISE with SAP offering. It helps partners and customers further innovate in the cloud with in-app extensions to fill small gaps, side-by-side innovations to extend the core, and integrations to bring the business processes together.</p>
  <h2 id="what-lies-ahead">What Lies Ahead?</h2>
  <p>To meet the current and future needs of our customers and partners, we want to firmly establish SAP BTP as the unified, business-centric, and open business and development platform for the entire SAP ecosystem. Partners that adopt the platform can develop more efficiently, provide foundational functionality, and commercialize products faster. Lower entry burdens will encourage our partners to develop applications that run on SAP BTP.</p>
  <p>Going forward, all SAP line-of-business and industry solutions will be built on SAP BTP. Partners can efficiently innovate and extend core solutions, create integrations, and deliver new content.</p>
  <p>Let’s deliver innovation together — faster and with less complexity.</p>
  <h2 id="want-to-learn-more">Want to Learn More?</h2>
  <p>For all the news from the SAP Global Partner Summit, see “<a href="/">Why Partners RISE with SAP</a>,” by Karl Fahrbach, global partner officer at SAP. And read “<a href="/2021/02/unified-technology-platform-partners-enable-customer-success">How Partners Enable Customer Success Through a Unified Technology Platform</a>,” by Jagdish Sahasrabudhe, CTO of the Global Partner Organization at SAP.</p>
  <p>Visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/partner">sap.com/partner</a> for more information on how to partner with SAP. Partners can find details on <a href="https://partneredge.sap.com/en/library/education/partnership/licenses/e_ep_td_cloud.html">SAPPartnerEdge.com</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Juergen Mueller is chief technology officer and a member of the Executive Board of SAP SE.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/blog/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/blog/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/blog/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/blog/article-read-more</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/executive-blog</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-global-partner-summit</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>