<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-topic/corporate/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Enters into Agreement to Acquire WalkMe, Driving Business Transformation by Enhancing the Customer Experience and Enriching SAP Business AI Offerings]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-enters-agreement-to-acquire-walkme</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-enters-agreement-to-acquire-walkme</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is entering into an agreement to acquire WalkMe, a leader in digital adoption platforms. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17c02c58752a8aaaec6051673cfe2308da8b06446.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17c02c58752a8aaaec6051673cfe2308da8b06446.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_17c02c58752a8aaaec6051673cfe2308da8b06446.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Enters into Agreement to Acquire WalkMe, Driving Business Transformation by Enhancing the Customer Experience and Enriching SAP Business AI Offerings" src="./media_17c02c58752a8aaaec6051673cfe2308da8b06446.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-enters-into-agreement-to-acquire-walkme-driving-business-transformation-by-enhancing-the-customer-experience-and-enriching-sap-business-ai-offerings">SAP Enters into Agreement to Acquire WalkMe, Driving Business Transformation by Enhancing the Customer Experience and Enriching SAP Business AI Offerings</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) and WalkMe Ltd. (NASDAQ: WKME) announced today that the companies have entered into a definitive agreement under which SAP will acquire WalkMe, a leader in digital adoption platforms (DAPs).</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>WalkMe’s solutions help organizations navigate constant technology change by providing users with advanced guidance and automation features that enable them to execute workflows seamlessly across any number of applications. This results in higher adoption of the underlying application and as such drives value realization.</p>
  <p>The Executive and Supervisory Boards of SAP SE and the board of directors of WalkMe have approved the transaction for US $14.00 per share in an all-cash transaction, representing an equity value of approximately US $1.5 billion. The offer price represents a 45% premium to WalkMe’s closing share price on June 4, 2024.</p>
  <p>The envisioned combination complements SAP’s Business Transformation Management portfolio around SAP Signavio and SAP LeanIX solutions to help customers on their transformation journeys.</p>
  <p>“Applications, processes, data and people are the four key elements of a successful business transformation,” said Christian Klein, CEO and member of the Executive Board of SAP SE. “By acquiring WalkMe, we are doubling down on the support we provide our end users, helping them to quickly adopt new solutions and features to get the maximum value out of their IT investments.”</p>
  <h2 id="walkme-focus-on-analyzing-adoption-and-business-transformation">WalkMe: Focus on Analyzing Adoption and Business Transformation</h2>
  <p>“We are thrilled to join forces with SAP. This acquisition marks a significant milestone in our journey, providing us with the resources and customer base necessary to enhance our product offerings and expand our market reach,” said Dan Adika, CEO of WalkMe. “By leveraging SAP’s extensive ecosystem, we are poised to unlock substantial growth opportunities and deliver even greater value to our customers. Together, we look forward to a future filled with innovation and exceptional service.”</p>
  <p>WalkMe helps organizations boost enterprise productivity and lower risk by enabling consistent, effective and efficient use of software and the workflows it enables. Its DAP works on top of an organization’s application landscape, detects where people encounter friction and provides the tailored support and automation they need to complete the job to be done, right in the flow of work, across any application. Importantly, WalkMe will continue to fully support non-SAP applications.</p>
  <p>Soon, WalkMe will launch the WalkMe<sup>X</sup> copilot, which will use WalkMe’s contextual awareness and AI to suggest the best next step for any workflow, anywhere. WalkMe<sup>X</sup> has the capability to always be on, serving as an overlay to any application, including copilots from different vendors that companies use in their landscapes. Integrating the strength of WalkMe’s adoption capabilities with SAP’s copilot Joule will boost AI assistant and productivity gains for all SAP customers. Additionally, integrating distinctive e-learning features in the SAP Enable Now solution with WalkMe will form the center of SAP’s people-centric transformation approach going forward.</p>
  <p>The acquisition is subject to customary closing conditions, including the receipt of WalkMe shareholder approval and necessary regulatory clearances, and is expected to close in the third quarter of 2024. The impact of the transaction on SAP’s non-IFRS earnings per share for fiscal 2024 is expected to be immaterial.</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>About WalkMe</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>WalkMe (NASDAQ: WKME), headquartered in Tel Aviv, Israel, pioneered DAP innovations and solutions so companies can effectively navigate the constant change brought on by technology. With WalkMe, organizations drive enterprise productivity and reduce risk by ensuring consistent, responsible, and efficient adoption of software and the workflows it powers. Our AI-driven platform sits on top of an organization’s tech stack, identifies where people experience friction, and delivers the personalized guidance and automation needed to get the job done, right in the flow of work. Customers like IBM, Nestle, ThermoFisher Scientific, and the U.S. Dept. of Defense trust WalkMe to create the people-centric experiences required to boost the effectiveness of their workflows and maximize software ROI.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>About SAP</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As a global leader in enterprise applications and business AI, SAP (NYSE:SAP) stands at the nexus of business and technology. For over 50 years, organizations have trusted SAP to bring out their best by uniting business-critical operations spanning finance, procurement, HR, supply chain, and customer experience. For more information, visit <a href="http://www.sap.com">www.sap.com</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Note to editors:</strong><br>To preview and download broadcast-standard stock footage and press photos digitally, please visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/photos">www.sap.com/photos</a>. On this platform, you can find high resolution material for your media channels.</p>
  <p><strong>For customers interested in learning more about SAP products:</strong><br>Global Customer Center: +49 180 534-34-24<br>United States Only: 1 (800) 872-1SAP (1-800-872-1727)</p>
  <p><strong>For more information, financial community only:</strong><br>Anthony Coletta, +49 6227-7-60437, <a href="mailto:investor@sap.com">investor@sap.com</a>, CEST</p>
  <p><strong>For more information, press only:</strong><br>Joellen Perry, +1 650-445-6780, <a href="mailto:joellen.perry@sap.com">joellen.perry@sap.com</a>, PT<br>Daniel Reinhardt, +49 6227-7-40201, <a href="mailto:daniel.reinhardt@sap.com">daniel.reinhardt@sap.com</a>, CEST<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p><strong>For WalkMe Investor Relations:</strong><br>John Streppa, <a href="mailto:investors@walkme.com">investors@walkme.com</a></p>
  <p><strong>Additional Important Information and Where to Find It</strong> In connection with the proposed transaction, WalkMe will prepare a proxy statement to be delivered to its shareholders and furnished to the Securities and Exchange Commission (the “SEC”). INVESTORS AND SECURITY HOLDERS ARE STRONGLY ADVISED TO READ THE PROXY STATEMENT WHEN IT BECOMES AVAILABLE AND OTHER RELEVANT DOCUMENTS FILED OR FURNISHED TO THE SEC IN CONNECTION WITH THE PROPOSED TRANSACTION OR INCORPORATED BY REFERENCE THEREIN, BECAUSE THE PROXY STATEMENT AND SUCH OTHER RELEVANT DOCUMENTS WILL CONTAIN IMPORTANT INFORMATION ABOUT THE PROPOSED TRANSACTION AND THE PARTIES TO THE PROPOSED TRANSACTION. This press release is not a substitute for the proxy statement or any other document that may be filed or furnished by WalkMe with the SEC.</p>
  <p>The proxy statement and other related documents filed or furnished to the SEC regarding the proposed transaction may be obtained for free from the SEC’s website (<a href="http://www.sec.gov/">www.sec.gov</a>), WalkMe’s website at <a href="http://www.walkme.com">www.walkme.com</a> or by directing such request to WalkMe’s Investor Relations.</p>
  <p><strong>Forward-Looking Statements</strong><br>This press release contains “forward-looking statements” within the meaning of the “safe harbor” provisions of the Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995 and other applicable securities laws. All statements other than statements of historical fact, including statements regarding the proposed acquisition of WalkMe by SAP, the expected timing for completing the proposed transaction and the terms thereof, future financial and operating results, benefits and synergies of the transaction, future opportunities for the combined businesses and any other statements regarding events or developments that may occur in the future, may be “forward-looking statements” for purposes of federal and state securities laws. These forward-looking statements involve a number of risks and uncertainties that could significantly affect the financial or operating results of SAP, WalkMe or the combined company. Words such as “expects,” “anticipates,” “intends,” “plans,” “believes,” “estimates,” “predicts,” “seeks,” “targets,” “would,” “will,” “should,” “may” and variations of such words and similar expressions are intended to identify such forward-looking statements. Such statements are based on management’s expectations as of the date they are first made, are not guarantees of future performance and involve certain risks, uncertainties and assumptions that are difficult to predict. Neither SAP nor WalkMe can give any assurances that the expectations in such forward-looking statements will be attained and, therefore, actual outcomes and results may differ materially from what is expressed or forecasted in such forward-looking statements. For example, these forward-looking statements could be affected by factors including, without limitation, risks associated with the ability to consummate the proposed transaction, the satisfaction of the conditions to the consummation of the proposed transaction, including the receipt of certain regulatory approvals, and the timing of the closing of the proposed transaction; the occurrence of any event, change or other circumstance that could give rise to the termination of the proposed transaction; the potential that WalkMe shareholders may not approve the transaction; the ability to successfully integrate operations and employees; the ability to realize anticipated benefits and synergies of the proposed transaction as rapidly or to the extent anticipated by financial analysts or investors; the potential impact of the announcement of the proposed transaction on operating results, business generally and business relationships, including with employees, customers, suppliers and competitors; unanticipated restructuring costs may be incurred or undisclosed liabilities assumed; actual or threatened legal proceedings that have been or may be instituted against SAP or WalkMe in connection with the proposed transaction or otherwise; the ability and costs related to retaining key personnel and clients; risks related to diverting management’s attention from ongoing business operations; delays, challenges, costs, fees, expenses and charges related to the proposed transaction; actions by competitors; general adverse economic, political, social and security conditions in the regions and industries in which SAP and WalkMe operate, including relating to Israel’s ongoing war with Hamas and other terrorist organizations in the Middle East and general hostilities; exposure to inflation, currency rate and interest rate fluctuations and risks associated with doing business locally and internationally, as well as fluctuations in the market price of SAP and WalkMe’s traded securities; natural catastrophes, any pandemic, epidemic or outbreak of infectious disease, warfare, protests and riots, and terrorist attacks; and those additional risks and factors discussed in reports filed or furnished with the SEC by SAP and WalkMe, including SAP’s and WalkMe’s most recent Annual Reports on Form 20-F and in any subsequent reports on Form 6-K, each of which is on file with or furnished to the SEC and available at the SEC’s website at <a href="http://www.sec.gov/">www.sec.gov</a>. Reports filed or furnished with the SEC by SAP are also available on SAP’s website at <a href="http://www.sap.com/investors/en.html">www.sap.com/investors</a> and by WalkMe on WalkMe’s website at <a href="http://www.walkme.com">www.walkme.com</a>. Moreover, other risks and uncertainties of which SAP or WalkMe are not currently aware or may not currently consider material may also affect each of the companies’ forward-looking statements and may cause actual results and the timing of events to differ materially from those anticipated. The forward-looking statements made in this press release are made only as of the date hereof or as of the dates indicated in the forward-looking statements, even if they are subsequently made available by SAP or WalkMe on their respective websites or otherwise. Neither SAP nor WalkMe undertakes any obligation to update or supplement any forward-looking statements to reflect actual results, new information, future events, changes in its expectations or other circumstances that exist after the date as of which the forward-looking statements were made.</p>
  <p>© 2024 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE and affiliated entities in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p>Please consider our <a href="https://www.sap.com/corporate/en/legal/privacy.html">privacy policy</a>. If you receive this press release in your e-mail and you wish to unsubscribe to our mailing list please contact <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a> and write Unsubscribe in the subject line.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/investor-relations</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>product/sap-leanix</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-signavio</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Generative AI Innovations Take Center Stage at SAP Sapphire in 2024]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-sapphire-generative-ai-center-stage</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-sapphire-generative-ai-center-stage</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A series of generative AI innovations and partnerships announced at SAP Sapphire showcase how SAP is taking business to the next level.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_183c39d6e19efd7774c87954a8bbf7838320ef779.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_183c39d6e19efd7774c87954a8bbf7838320ef779.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_183c39d6e19efd7774c87954a8bbf7838320ef779.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Generative AI Innovations Take Center Stage at SAP Sapphire in 2024" src="./media_183c39d6e19efd7774c87954a8bbf7838320ef779.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="generative-ai-innovations-take-center-stage-at-sap-sapphire-in-2024">Generative AI Innovations Take Center Stage at SAP Sapphire in 2024</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>SAP CEO Christian Klein kicked off SAP Sapphire this week with an upbeat keynote that highlighted the company’s latest business AI innovations, products, and partnerships, which he said will change how people work.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="taking-business-to-the-next-level-in-the-era-of-ai">Taking Business to the Next Level in the Era of AI</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/events/sapphire/news-guide.html">Read the news guide</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“This year is a very special Sapphire,” Klein said. “We are entering a new phase of AI, with endless possibilities for us all.”</p>
  <p>Klein and Chief Marketing and Solutions Officer Julia White used the keynote to outline how AI will deliver real business benefits for different corporate functions and “Bring Out Your Best,” this year’s event theme.</p>
  <h2 id="delivering-on-an-ai-promise">Delivering on an AI Promise</h2>
  <p>Klein emphasized how SAP has delivered on its promise to infuse generative AI throughout its business portfolio, has enabled customers to exploit the potential of business AI, and has positioned the Joule copilot as the new front end for SAP applications.</p>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11a9e312c5b8efe848ea7622ac6bcc8c38c9e5913.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11a9e312c5b8efe848ea7622ac6bcc8c38c9e5913.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_11a9e312c5b8efe848ea7622ac6bcc8c38c9e5913.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Sapphire Opening Keynote: Bring Out the Best in Your Business | 2024" src="./media_11a9e312c5b8efe848ea7622ac6bcc8c38c9e5913.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://youtu.be/gOVQhhm5yO0?si=wkpDopYq0gPK6kWn">SAP Sapphire Opening Keynote: Bring Out the Best in Your Business | 2024</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Together, the two also announced the next evolution and new capabilities in both RISE with SAP and GROW with SAP. Since it was launched over three years ago, more than 6,000 customers have selected RISE with SAP. During his keynote, Klein announced that RISE with SAP will now include a dedicated enterprise architect to guide customers through the RISE with SAP Methodology as well as an integrated tool chain to help manage the process, system, and data landscape holistically across the RISE with SAP life cycle.</p>
  <p>Meanwhile White, broadcasting live from the central showcase on the SAP Sapphire show floor, announced that cloud ERP offering GROW with SAP will now include SAP Sales Cloud and Concur Expense at no additional charge. Whether its managing your finances or managing your expenses, GROW with SAP has you covered, she said.</p>
  <h2 id="ai-momentum">AI Momentum</h2>
  <p>Building on SAP’s business AI momentum, Klein and White also announced a series of expanded partnerships to help companies make the most out of this decisive AI moment. The expanded partnerships include deals with Amazon Web Services (AWS) and Google Cloud. Klein also announced the integration of Microsoft 365 Copilot with Joule, delivering what he described as a “truly differentiated employee experience.”</p>
  <p>Together onstage with customers and SAP Chief AI Officer Philipp Herzig, they showcased how SAP is infusing generative AI throughout the application portfolio and enabling customers to thrive in the AI era.</p>
  <p>“The business AI innovations we’re announcing will not only change how people work with SAP solutions, but how people work overall,” said Klein ahead of his keynote address.</p>
  <h2 id="new-joule-capabilities">New Joule Capabilities</h2>
  <p>Klein announced Joule for consulting capabilities and Joule for ABAP developer capabilities, which will help SAP’s 6-million-strong consultant and developer community to accelerate projects by 30% and implement SAP solutions faster than ever before.</p>
  <p>During his keynote he described business AI as being “an inflection point” and added, “Today’s AI announcements and partnerships build on our commitment to deliver revolutionary technology that drives real-world results, helping customers unleash the agility and ingenuity they need to succeed in today’s fast-moving business landscape.”</p>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16cdfc9fd1fdbbf5cdc9cd5193401b9dfcafd1805.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16cdfc9fd1fdbbf5cdc9cd5193401b9dfcafd1805.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_16cdfc9fd1fdbbf5cdc9cd5193401b9dfcafd1805.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Why Joule Will Change the Way You Work" src="./media_16cdfc9fd1fdbbf5cdc9cd5193401b9dfcafd1805.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://youtu.be/a9j2Q6VVCfM?si=9cdzuqQ27TZ_J3uj">Why Joule Will Change the Way You Work</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“SAP is the only tech company who can infuse AI capabilities right into your business processes and workflows,” he said, saluting the achievements of the 40,000 SAP employees in the Product Development organization.</p>
  <h2 id="shout-out-to-sap-developers">Shout Out to SAP Developers</h2>
  <p>“No other tech company can offer a more powerful platform to transform enterprises to rewrite how business is run.” SAP developers have transformed SAP’s portfolio “from an ERP system that enabled transactions in real time, to a system with modular applications and embedded AI so that you can run intelligent, connected, and sustainable enterprises.”</p>
  <p>“We promised this to you, and we delivered,” Klein told audiences online and the 14,000 customers and partners attending SAP Sapphire in person this week in Orlando. “Now we are using the power of generative AI across our stack to once again revolutionize how businesses run and end users will work in the future.”</p>
  <p>After announcing generative AI copilot Joule in September 2023, Klein confirmed that it will become the new front-end and UX for SAP applications and “will turn your words into action.” Joule is ready for prime time, he declared, “and going forward, it will be embedded out of the box for all our cloud customers.”</p>
  <h2 id="joule-key-to-higher-productivity">Joule: Key to Higher Productivity</h2>
  <p>He predicted that Joule will also become the biggest productivity engine for every SAP end user, and that by the end of the year, 80% of the most used tasks will be managed via Joule and the 300 million end users of SAP products will be 20% more productive.</p>
  <p>While AI is a powerful technology facilitating huge opportunities for business and employees, the SAP CEO emphasized that it is also crucial to offer responsible AI. To that end, he announced that SAP is among the first tech companies to adhere to UNESCO’s AI principles.</p>
  <p>Klein wrapped up the keynote by emphasizing that SAP does not view AI as an end in itself, but rather as a tool to help the world run better and improve people’s lives. “You have my commitment that we will continue to listen to your needs, we will continue to deliver great innovations and we will continue to deliver great outcomes for your company.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-news-and-coverage-from-sap-sapphire-in-2024">Get the latest news and coverage from SAP Sapphire in 2024</h3>
        <p><em><a href="/topics/sap-sapphire">Read more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA["Source from Ukraine" Initiative: The S Stands for Solidarity]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/source-from-ukraine-initiative-s-for-solidarity</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/source-from-ukraine-initiative-s-for-solidarity</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The "Source from Ukraine" initiative aims to activate procurement spend to support Ukrainian suppliers in rebuilding their businesses.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/csr</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/ukraine</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP's “Source from Ukraine” Initiative Boosts Business and Social Responsibility]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/source-from-ukraine-initiative-boosts-business-social-responsibility</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/source-from-ukraine-initiative-boosts-business-social-responsibility</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The "Source from Ukraine" initiative aims to activate procurement spend to support Ukrainian suppliers in rebuilding their businesses.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1be90b8393bfeb6a3a3bdc9a317fa62a7be1e9acb.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1be90b8393bfeb6a3a3bdc9a317fa62a7be1e9acb.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1be90b8393bfeb6a3a3bdc9a317fa62a7be1e9acb.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP’s “Source from Ukraine” Initiative Boosts Business and Social Responsibility" src="./media_1be90b8393bfeb6a3a3bdc9a317fa62a7be1e9acb.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="saps-source-from-ukraine-initiative-boosts-business-and-social-responsibility">SAP’s “Source from Ukraine” Initiative Boosts Business and Social Responsibility</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>SAP’s “Source from Ukraine” initiative, launched in March 2023, has a clear goal: to increase spend with Ukrainian companies while also generating business benefits for SAP. This shows SAP’s deep understanding of social responsibility as an integral part of its commitment to a sustainable future.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The initiative aims to activate <a href="/topics/procurement">procurement</a> spend as a means to support Ukrainian suppliers in rebuilding their businesses. Beyond sourcing for quality goods and services, SAP has a focus on integrating ESG (environmental, social, and governance) principles into decision-making as is standard with its procurement policy.</p>
  <p>It highlights SAP’s commitment not only to sourcing products from Ukraine, but also to promoting social change.</p>
  <h2 id="built-in-sustainability">Built-In Sustainability</h2>
  <p>In implementing the initiative to attract more suppliers from Ukraine, SAP initially focused on the IT sector and conducted a rigorous selection process. So far, suppliers, including industry leaders like Softserve, Unicsoft, and Luxoft, have been selected. SAP’s commitment extends beyond services to include product areas, where notable Ukrainian companies producing innovative environmentally sustainable products have been discovered.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-is-powering-equitable-access-to-economic-opportunity-education-and-employment-and-the-circular-economy">SAP is powering equitable access to economic opportunity, education and employment, and the circular economy</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/our-values/csr.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>At SAP Spend Connect Live in Vienna, Austria, held in October 2023, Ukrainian manufacturers Rekava, Mol’far Tea, and Releaf Paper showcased their sustainable and innovative products. Rekava, for example, specializes in producing biodegradable candles made from recycled coffee grounds, while Mol’far focuses on minimalism and ethical environmental practices in tea production. Releaf Paper is the world’s first manufacturer of paper made from fallen leaves, promoting sustainable products such as paper bags. By supporting these unique Ukrainian companies, SAP is not only contributing to the economic reconstruction of the country, but also sustainability efforts.</p>
  <p>One of SAP’s tier one suppliers, ABC Premium, has taken an important step by offering Rekava candles within its purchasing catalog, available to SAP employees on the SAP Ariba Buying solution.</p>
  <h2 id="strong-alliances-for-reconstruction">Strong Alliances for Reconstruction</h2>
  <p>At the outset of the project, the NGO Impact Ukraine helped SAP connect with Ukrainian suppliers. It focuses on microfinance, procurement, and recruitment from Ukraine. The collaboration is facilitated by the voluntary engagement of professionals from the technology, healthcare, and finance sectors. With Impact Ukraine’s support, SAP and other organizations can further advance their goals regarding procurement from Ukraine.</p>
  <p>SAP’s commitment to promoting innovation, sustainability, and economic growth through partnerships with Ukrainian companies not only fulfills its aspirations for procurement with purpose, but also contributes to making the world a better place.</p>
  <h2 id="helping-the-world-run-better">Helping the World Run Better</h2>
  <p>The “Source from Ukraine” initiative builds on global efforts to integrate social enterprises and diverse suppliers into SAP purchasing opportunities. Beyond SAP’s own internal purchasing efforts, the SAP Corporate Social Responsibility (SAP CSR) team is also investing in social and sustainable procurement ecosystems alongside public, private, and social sector partners like the European Commission, Deloitte, World Economic Forum’s Global Alliance for Social Entrepreneurship, and Social Enterprise World Forum’s People and Planet First verification.</p>
  <p>Consider that US$5.3 trillion in annual commerce is transacted on <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-network.html">SAP Business Network</a>. If we can help create a small shift in procurement spend to organizations prioritizing people and planet like Releaf Paper, we could collectively increase investment in sustainable development in a way that is not possible through corporate philanthropy alone. To join our efforts, please e-mail: <a href="mailto:csr-global@sap.com?subject=Please%20Share%20More%20Collective%20Social%20Procurement%20Investments%20and%20How%20to%20Get%20Involved">csr-global@sap.com</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Elena Parker is chief revenue officer for Intelligent Spend and Business Network, MEE, at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-sap-news-delivered-to-your-inbox-once-a-week">Get the latest SAP news delivered to your inbox once a week</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/nl/sap-news-center-newsletter/index.html">Sign up today</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/csr</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/ukraine</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Alexandra Steiger to Join SAP as Global Head of Investor Relations]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/alexandra-steiger-to-join-global-head-sap-investor-relations</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/alexandra-steiger-to-join-global-head-sap-investor-relations</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Alexandra Steiger will join SAP as global head of Investor Relations on July 1, reporting to SAP Executive Board Member and CFO Dominik Asam.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_12c0f62a0c1bea8cebafaf88b1a2478cf4d11b899.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_12c0f62a0c1bea8cebafaf88b1a2478cf4d11b899.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_12c0f62a0c1bea8cebafaf88b1a2478cf4d11b899.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Alexandra Steiger to Join SAP as Global Head of Investor Relations" src="./media_12c0f62a0c1bea8cebafaf88b1a2478cf4d11b899.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="alexandra-steiger-to-join-sap-as-global-head-of-investor-relations">Alexandra Steiger to Join SAP as Global Head of Investor Relations</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced that Alexandra Steiger will join SAP as new global head of Investor Relations on July 1, 2024, reporting to Dominik Asam, member of the Executive Board and CFO of SAP SE.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>With over a decade of experience in the finance industry, Steiger has held roles at renowned institutions such as Goldman Sachs and UBS. She currently serves as executive director within Global Investment Research at Goldman Sachs, focusing on the U.S. Internet sector, including companies such as Alphabet, Meta and Amazon.</p>
  <p>“I am very happy Alexandra is joining SAP,” said Asam. “We will benefit from her leadership and the wealth of expertise she brings from her previous responsibilities. In her new role, she can build on the strong foundation laid by Anthony Coletta and the entire Investor Relations team.”</p>
  <p>Prior to her assignment at Goldman Sachs, Steiger was an executive director within UBS Equity Research, covering select U.S. Internet and Interactive Entertainment companies. She received a bachelor’s degree in International Business Administration from the University of Maastricht and a master’s degree in International Management CEMS from the Erasmus University Rotterdam and University of St. Gallen.</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="http://news.sap.com/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Media Contacts:</strong><br>Joellen Perry, +1 (626) 265-0370, <a href="mailto:joellen.perry@sap.com">joellen.perry@sap.com</a>, PT<br>Daniel Reinhardt, SAP, +49 6227-7-40201, <a href="mailto:daniel.reinhardt@sap.com">daniel.reinhardt@sap.com</a>, CET<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>Top image courtesy of SAP employee Laurentia-Iulia Pavel</p>
  <p>This document contains forward-looking statements, which are predictions, projections, or other statements about future events. These statements are based on current expectations, forecasts, and assumptions that are subject to risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results and outcomes to materially differ. Additional information regarding these risks and uncertainties may be found in our filings with the Securities and Exchange Commission, including but not limited to the risk factors section of SAP’s 2023 Annual Report on Form 20-F.<br>© 2024 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/investor-relations</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>news-tag/investor-relations</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Olaf Scholz Leads Farewell Tributes to Hasso Plattner]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/hasso-plattner-olaf-scholz-farewell-tributes</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/hasso-plattner-olaf-scholz-farewell-tributes</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[German Chancellor Olaf Scholz led the farewell tributes to SAP co-founder and former Chairman of the Supervisory Board Hasso Plattner.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-history</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pekka Ala-Pietilä Elected Chairman of SAP Supervisory Board — Strong Shareholder Support]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/pekka-ala-pietila-elected-chairman-sap-supervisory-board-2024-agm</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/pekka-ala-pietila-elected-chairman-sap-supervisory-board-2024-agm</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[At SAP's Annual General Meeting, Pekka Ala-Pietilä was elected as a new member of the company’s Supervisory Board. Read the 2024 AGM news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_199662acda1c93822a3bb96f83087091d36c8067e.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_199662acda1c93822a3bb96f83087091d36c8067e.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_199662acda1c93822a3bb96f83087091d36c8067e.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Pekka Ala-Pietilä Elected Chairman of SAP Supervisory Board — Strong Shareholder Support" src="./media_199662acda1c93822a3bb96f83087091d36c8067e.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="pekka-ala-pietilä-elected-chairman-of-sap-supervisory-board--strong-shareholder-support">Pekka Ala-Pietilä Elected Chairman of SAP Supervisory Board — Strong Shareholder Support</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>MANNHEIM</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced that at the company’s Annual General Meeting of Shareholders (AGM), Pekka Ala-Pietilä (67) was elected as a new member of the company’s Supervisory Board. Ala-Pietilä’s election was supported by 95.50% of shareholders. Subsequently, Ala-Pietilä was also elected the new Chairman of the SAP Supervisory Board, completing the handover from former Chairman of the Board, Prof. Dr. h. c. mult. Hasso Plattner.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“I am happy to pass the baton to Pekka Ala Pietilä to accompany SAP’s ongoing successful transformation,” said Plattner. “Pekka profoundly understands SAP and the technology industry and will strongly support the company in expanding its leadership in cloud ERP and business AI.”</p>
  <p>Ala-Pietilä added, “I am grateful to the SAP shareholders and Supervisory Board for the opportunity to rejoin Europe’s most important software company and I’m looking forward to help SAP broaden this strong position.”</p>
  <p>As announced in 2023, SAP Co-Founder and former Chairman of the Board Hasso Plattner left the SAP Supervisory Board after the 2024 AGM.</p>
  <p>During Plattner’s tenure as Chairman of the Supervisory Board (May 2003 to May 2024), SAP’s market capitalization increased from c. €30 billion to c. €200 billion, making SAP Germany’s most valuable listed company. Plattner’s innovative and competitive spirit has been a foundation of SAP’s success for more than 50 years, from the company’s first pioneering innovations in ERP to its strategic shift as an enterprise cloud and business AI leader. He will continue to serve as an advisor to SAP, ensuring his knowledge and experience remain available to the company.</p>
  <p>Aicha Evans (55), Gerhard Oswald (70) and Dr. Friederik Rotsch (51) were re-elected as members of the Supervisory Board with 93.39%, 89.82% and 92.45% of the vote respectively. Prof. Dr. Ralf Herbrich (50) was elected with 99.29% of the vote as successor to Punit Renjen, who left the SAP Supervisory Board at the end of the 2024 AGM.</p>
  <p>The AGM also supported all other proposals of the Executive Board and Supervisory Board. That included approving the actions of the Executive Board and Supervisory Board for fiscal 2023, 99.51% and 99.44% support respectively, and approving the adaptation of the compensation of the Chairman of the Supervisory Board. An overview of the resolutions of the Annual General Meetings 2024 and of previous years can be found <a href="https://www.sap.com/investors/en/calendar/agm.html">here</a>.</p>
  <p>For 2023, SAP shareholders will receive a dividend of €2.20 per share. This is an increase of €0.15, or seven percent compared to the dividend paid for 2022. The total payout to shareholders will thus amount to around €2.6 billion. The dividend is expected to be paid out from May 21, 2024.</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-financial-news-and-information-about-sap-and-company-performance">Get the latest financial news and information about SAP and company performance</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/investors/en.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>About SAP</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As a global leader in enterprise applications and business AI, SAP (NYSE: SAP) stands at the nexus of business and technology. For over 50 years, organizations have trusted SAP to bring out their best by uniting business-critical operations spanning finance, procurement, HR, supply chain, and customer experience. For more information, visit <a href="https://www.sap.com.">www.sap.com.</a></p>
  <p><strong>Note to editors:</strong><br>To preview and download broadcast-standard stock footage and press photos digitally, please visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/photos">www.sap.com/photos</a>. On this platform, you can find high resolution material for your media channels. To view video stories on diverse topics, visit <a href="http://www.sap-tv.com">www.sap-tv.com</a>. From this site, you can embed videos into your own Web pages, share video via email links, and subscribe to RSS feeds from SAP TV.</p>
  <p><strong>For customers interested in learning more about SAP products:</strong><br>Global Customer Center: +49 180 534-34-24<br>United States Only: 1 (800) 872-1SAP (1-800-872-1727)</p>
  <p><strong>For more information, financial community only:</strong><br>Anthony Coletta, +49 6227-7-60437, <a href="mailto:investor@sap.com">investor@sap.com</a>, CET</p>
  <p><strong>For more information, press only:</strong><br>Joellen Perry, +1 (650) 445-6780, <a href="mailto:joellen.perry@sap.com">joellen.perry@sap.com</a>, PT<br>Daniel Reinhardt, +49 6227-7-40201, <a href="mailto:daniel.reinhardt@sap.com">daniel.reinhardt@sap.com</a>, CET<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>This document contains forward-looking statements, which are predictions, projections, or other statements about future events. These statements are based on current expectations, forecasts, and assumptions that are subject to risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results and outcomes to materially differ. Additional information regarding these risks and uncertainties may be found in our filings with the Securities and Exchange Commission, including but not limited to the risk factors section of SAP’s 2023 Annual Report on Form 20-F.<br>© 2024 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/investor-relations</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/annual-general-meeting</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The End of an Era: Hasso Plattner Steps Down]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/the-end-of-an-era-hasso-plattner-steps-down</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/the-end-of-an-era-hasso-plattner-steps-down</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Hasso Plattner steps down from the SAP Supervisory Board on May 15, the last SAP co-founder to leave the company.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_185023c2d1a7a517fd9b3ea922005aa6bdc72da1f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_185023c2d1a7a517fd9b3ea922005aa6bdc72da1f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_185023c2d1a7a517fd9b3ea922005aa6bdc72da1f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="The End of an Era: Hasso Plattner Steps Down" src="./media_185023c2d1a7a517fd9b3ea922005aa6bdc72da1f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="the-end-of-an-era-hasso-plattner-steps-down">The End of an Era: Hasso Plattner Steps Down</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>SAP co-founder Dietmar Hopp once said about co-founder Hasso Plattner: “It’s hard to quantify his legacy. All I can say is that without him, SAP would never have been so successful.” At the 2024 Annual General Meeting of Shareholders on May 15, Plattner will step down from the SAP Supervisory Board after 21 years as its chairman.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>One need only look at the key milestones in Plattner’s 52-year career at SAP to gain a vivid picture of his legacy. Together with Dietmar Hopp and his fellow co-founders, Plattner created the market for real-time business software, helped steer SAP through more than five decades of fast-moving IT history, and drove SAP’s global expansion – transforming it from a single-product company to the world’s No. 1 provider of enterprise applications.</p>
  <p>Over the years, he worked tirelessly to open new horizons for the company and its employees, identifying technological trends and channeling his pioneering spirit into revolutionizing far more than just data management.</p>
  <h2 id="1973-the-early-days">1972-1973: The Early Days</h2>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10d76b7bedbfa9b44f37a7f18de5326417b0bb92d.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10d76b7bedbfa9b44f37a7f18de5326417b0bb92d.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_10d76b7bedbfa9b44f37a7f18de5326417b0bb92d.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_10d76b7bedbfa9b44f37a7f18de5326417b0bb92d.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="937" height="950">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>Hasso Plattner (sitting) explains the real-time screen application to colleagues from IBM and ICI</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Having created Germany’s first real-time software application with a user interface, Hasso Plattner and Dietmar Hopp founded a company they named Systemanalyse Programmentwicklung (“System Analysis Program Development”) on April 1, 1972, together with their IBM colleagues Claus Wellenreuther, Klaus Tschira, and Hans-Werner Hector.</p>
  <p>In 1973, the entrepreneurs launched RF, their first financial accounting system. The “R” in the name stood for “real time.” Developed under Plattner’s leadership, RF laid the foundation for a series of software modules in a system that would later be known as SAP R/1.</p>
  <p>“Before I worked on RF,” Plattner once said, “I knew nothing about financial accounting; afterwards, I could hold seminars about it for CFOs. And not because I’d read stacks of books or was very smart, but because I’d learned from customers how to build this kind of system. I worked side by side with our customers at their offices every day.”</p>
  <h2 id="the-formative-years">1976: The Formative Years</h2>
  <p>Systemanalyse Programmentwicklung was renamed “SAP.” Each of the founders and their employees – numbering about 30 at this point – was a developer, salesperson, and consultant all rolled into one.</p>
  <p>Hasso Plattner and Dietmar Hopp were constantly competing to be the best at programming and selling their products. Plattner recalls that it made him really mad once when Hopp sold more than he did. Wherever their tasks and skills converged, they would engage in a private, “take-no-prisoners” contest to outdo each other.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1975b69486811901685732531d50d62d6c7fdad0f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1975b69486811901685732531d50d62d6c7fdad0f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1975b69486811901685732531d50d62d6c7fdad0f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_1975b69486811901685732531d50d62d6c7fdad0f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="683">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>Dietmar Hopp (left) and Hasso Plattner: ambitious and always encouraging each other to achieve top performance (in the anniversary year 2022)</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Nevertheless, both men also knew how to harness their ambition and fondness for friendly competition to the benefit of their fledgling business.</p>
  <h2 id="conversion-and-ipo">1988: Conversion and IPO</h2>
  <p>SAP GmbH was converted to a stock corporation, SAP AG, and in October 1988 it listed on the stock exchanges in Frankfurt and Stuttgart, providing the company with the funding it needed to expand into even more markets.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_167fffe8a69b999710d7e69376bd52661f180a797.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_167fffe8a69b999710d7e69376bd52661f180a797.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_167fffe8a69b999710d7e69376bd52661f180a797.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_167fffe8a69b999710d7e69376bd52661f180a797.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="745">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>The initial public stock offering (IPO) was the beginning of a steep stock rise</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="sap-r3">1991: SAP R/3</h2>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_19fecf579dec3857a050cd97a1fe28061e163a3d6.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_19fecf579dec3857a050cd97a1fe28061e163a3d6.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_19fecf579dec3857a050cd97a1fe28061e163a3d6.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_19fecf579dec3857a050cd97a1fe28061e163a3d6.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="690">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>SAP R/3 made the company a global player. Plattner in 1991 at a Hewlett Packard (HP) event.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>At SAP’s 25th anniversary celebrations in 1997, Plattner recounted an incident in late January 1991, which he described as “probably the most dramatic situation” in the company’s history: “A year before the final delivery date for R/3, we realized during testing that its performance on our mainframe was completely unsatisfactory and that the test conditions were unacceptable. Six weeks before we had planned to present R/3 at the CeBIT trade fair in Hanover, we had all but given up on the project.</p>
  <p>We called an emergency meeting at which everyone remained standing, such was the urgency of the matter at hand. We decided to halt work on the mainframe systems and, in a last-ditch attempt, to switch to the new, more powerful Unix workstations, which we’d previously only used in development.</p>
  <p>The presentation of R/3 on Unix was a huge hit. A year and a half later, we began shipping our new client-server software to customers. That was the start of R/3, a business application for network-based computers.”</p>
  <h2 id="heading-stateside">1992: Heading Stateside</h2>
  <p>In the early 1990s, when everyone else’s attention was focused on getting SAP R/3 to market quickly, sales of SAP R/2 in Germany were a cause of concern for Dietmar Hopp. As Plattner recalls: “Dietmar and I were standing in his office, and he said to me, ‘It’s not looking good. The only option I can see is for you to pack the system up and take it to America.’” They agreed to continue promoting the SAP R/2 mainframe software in Germany while going all-in on SAP R/3 in the U.S.</p>
  <p>At the Sapphire customer conference held in Orlando in September 1992, Plattner announced that SAP would deliver the SAP R/3 system within six weeks to anyone who ordered it there and then. By October, computer manufacturer Convex had signed a contract for the new product, giving SAP its first SAP R/3 customer in the United States. And when, not long after that, oil giant Chevron – one of the country’s largest companies – also opted for R/3, SAP’s new software, originally built with the midmarket in mind, was well on track to becoming a global success story.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c3a355f706212ed652d74e2c55b05a54184af9e5.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c3a355f706212ed652d74e2c55b05a54184af9e5.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1c3a355f706212ed652d74e2c55b05a54184af9e5.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_1c3a355f706212ed652d74e2c55b05a54184af9e5.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="675">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>The computer manufacturer Convex was the first SAP R/3 customer in the U.S.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="a-very-special-partnership">1993: A Very Special Partnership</h2>
  <p>SAP entered into an alliance with the world’s largest software company: Microsoft. Bill Gates, who had flown into Munich to sign the contract in person, told the audience at the press conference announcing the partnership: “We are delighted that SAP, one of the leading providers of standard software, supports Microsoft’s client-server operating system. We believe that many businesses will see this move by SAP as a compelling reason to opt for Windows NT.”</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_19013199f514f4625702a74f7a59abba1a235561d.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_19013199f514f4625702a74f7a59abba1a235561d.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_19013199f514f4625702a74f7a59abba1a235561d.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_19013199f514f4625702a74f7a59abba1a235561d.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="725">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>The beginning of a long and fruitful partnership: Microsoft founder Bill Gates and Hasso Plattner</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>And when, in 2010, Plattner received the Transatlantic Partnership Award, Gates had this to say about his friend and colleague: “I’ve known Hasso for more than three decades. His knowledge, energy, and vision never cease to impress me.”</p>
  <h2 id="sap-celebrates-its-25th-anniversary">1997: SAP Celebrates Its 25th Anniversary</h2>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f8825a0550d086c89bdd5146f9375a6a696e143e.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f8825a0550d086c89bdd5146f9375a6a696e143e.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1f8825a0550d086c89bdd5146f9375a6a696e143e.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_1f8825a0550d086c89bdd5146f9375a6a696e143e.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="737">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>SAP turns 25 and celebrates with the Prime Minister of Baden-Württemberg, Erwin Teufel (left) and Federal Chancellor Helmut Kohl (right) in between Hopp, Tschira, and Plattner</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Plattner was appointed co-CEO, alongside Dietmar Hopp. In his speech at SAP’s 25th anniversary celebrations, he spoke about what had helped the company prosper: “Product focus is one pillar of SAP’s success. When a product sells well, the employees share in that sense of achievement. That feeling is just as important to them as the pay they take home each month. Our employees identify with the product – that’s why they have always gone the extra mile. No matter how different our views at times were, we always managed to regroup and we never lost sight of the product. For the past 25 years, the founders and employees of SAP remained true to the original product vision and never veered off course.”</p>
  <h2 id="sap-conquers-new-york">1998: SAP Conquers New York</h2>
  <p>On August 3, 1998, the company debuted on the New York Stock Exchange (NYSE), the world’s largest exchange. CEO Hasso Plattner described SAP’s Wall Street listing as “a strategic necessity and logical milestone in the history of SAP.”</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b14f26dbcde1cfb4a3f4ac26bff81202b5d0ecc2.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b14f26dbcde1cfb4a3f4ac26bff81202b5d0ecc2.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1b14f26dbcde1cfb4a3f4ac26bff81202b5d0ecc2.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_1b14f26dbcde1cfb4a3f4ac26bff81202b5d0ecc2.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="683">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>By having its shares listed on the New York Stock Exchange “Big Board,” SAP gained new prominence in its most important market</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>That same year, Plattner founded the Hasso Plattner Institute (HPI) for Software System Engineering in Potsdam, near Berlin. “The institute here in Potsdam is my contribution to training internationally competitive junior managers who help shape and advance the digital world,” he said.</p>
  <p>Dietmar Hopp and Klaus Tschira transitioned from the Executive Board to the Supervisory Board, and Plattner became co-CEO alongside Henning Kagermann.</p>
  <h2 id="the-mysapcom-revolution">1999: The mySAP.com Revolution</h2>
  <p>In May, Plattner announced the mySAP.com strategy, which set the company and its product portfolio on an entirely new path. Using the latest Web technology, mySAP.com connected e-commerce solutions with the company’s existing ERP applications.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_125b1f1928a1388f8384b736978c6a213389e62e9.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_125b1f1928a1388f8384b736978c6a213389e62e9.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_125b1f1928a1388f8384b736978c6a213389e62e9.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_125b1f1928a1388f8384b736978c6a213389e62e9.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="669">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>To be successful in the increasingly important Internet business, Plattner relied on the mySAP.com strategy</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>According to Plattner, success on the Internet was key to the company’s survival. At the Sapphire conference in Philadelphia in September 1999, a live demo of mySAP.com — with a prelude by Plattner playing Queen’s “I Want to Break Free” live on electric guitar — was enough to convince customers to adopt SAP’s Web strategy.</p>
  <p>And, true to form, Plattner was already thinking about where the technology would go next, predicting that e-commerce and the hosting of applications on SAP servers would be “the future of software sales.”</p>
  <h2 id="from-executive-board-to-supervisory-board">2003: From Executive Board to Supervisory Board</h2>
  <p>Plattner stepped down from the Executive Board and was elected chairman of the Supervisory Board.</p>
  <p>Speaking at the Annual General Meeting of Shareholders in May, he said: “This rising star of the 90s is now playing in the same league as IBM, Microsoft, and Oracle.”</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1fbc111a4f8322bcafea8f5269955b9d4807255cb.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1fbc111a4f8322bcafea8f5269955b9d4807255cb.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1fbc111a4f8322bcafea8f5269955b9d4807255cb.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_1fbc111a4f8322bcafea8f5269955b9d4807255cb.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="681">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>With Plattner’s withdrawal from the Executive Board, Kagermann (left) becomes the sole CEO</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Though no longer its CEO, Plattner continued to channel his passion and his eye for technological trends into driving SAP forward, but now in his new role as chief software advisor on the Supervisory Board. That same year, he helped found the Hasso Plattner Institute of Design (“d.school”) at Stanford University, providing funds to support its work on design thinking, a new approach to finding creative solutions to complex problems.</p>
  <h2 id="the-in-memory-database">2006: The In-Memory Database</h2>
  <p>It was in 2006 that Plattner and students at HPI began work on a revolutionary technology. The result was SAP HANA (<strong>H</strong> igh-Performance <strong>AN</strong> alytic <strong>A</strong> ppliance), an entirely new, column-oriented, in-memory database management system.</p>
  <p>“It’s not so easy for a big company to break out and do something radically different,” said Plattner. “The university context gives you the freedom to do it.”</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1eabfa710ea44e5ed2f80b5f5cc8b2fe2887a2033.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1eabfa710ea44e5ed2f80b5f5cc8b2fe2887a2033.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1eabfa710ea44e5ed2f80b5f5cc8b2fe2887a2033.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_1eabfa710ea44e5ed2f80b5f5cc8b2fe2887a2033.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="680">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>Plattner loves to pass on his knowledge to young people</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="2013-sap-hana-drives-growth">2011-2013: SAP HANA Drives Growth</h2>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1041d63cb46cf4ee98f676d9a1ce51d3e4799346d.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1041d63cb46cf4ee98f676d9a1ce51d3e4799346d.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1041d63cb46cf4ee98f676d9a1ce51d3e4799346d.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_1041d63cb46cf4ee98f676d9a1ce51d3e4799346d.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="681">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>Plattner talks about the importance of SAP HANA at the SAPPHIRE NOW conference in Orlando in 2012</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Five years later, the first SAP HANA customers began implementing the new database, which generated the kind of demand not seen since the market launch of SAP R/3.</p>
  <p>By the end of 2013, the entire SAP Business Suite had moved to SAP HANA. In the three years since its launch, SAP HANA had garnered nearly €1.2 billion in revenues, making it one of the fastest-growing products in the history of enterprise software.</p>
  <p>In an interview with German daily <em>Handelsblatt</em> in 2020, Plattner said: “SAP HANA is so superior in practice that there is no alternative. And quite honestly, it saved SAP’s life, because it let us massively accelerate our ERP system without a lot of changes, while physically downsizing it at the same time. That meant a huge cost saving for our customers.”</p>
  <h2 id="the-foundation">2015: The Foundation</h2>
  <p>Plattner reinforced his commitment to promoting education and culture by setting up the Hasso Plattner Foundation.</p>
  <p>Among the many causes the foundation has supported over the years are programs to promote healthcare and health education in South Africa. The German city of Potsdam also has much to thank Plattner for: The Hasso Plattner Institute is the largest investment in Potsdam and the one that bears his signature most strongly. The Barberini Museum that he rebuilt completes the inner cityscape of Potsdam and provides a home for his impressive Impressionist collection — the largest outside of France. With the Kunsthaus MINSK, he saved one of the few architectural icons of the GDR era and created a home for his GDR art collection.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17f549db93ae704dcec772e0a2339218fe1ce372d.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17f549db93ae704dcec772e0a2339218fe1ce372d.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_17f549db93ae704dcec772e0a2339218fe1ce372d.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_17f549db93ae704dcec772e0a2339218fe1ce372d.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="576">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>Celebrities at the opening of the Barberini Museum in Potsdam in 2017</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>On being asked why he chooses to get involved with causes and projects of this kind, Plattner explained: “I owe the resources and skills for life to my parents and, above all, to my studies at the public technical university in Karlsruhe. That’s why I want to give something back in the area of education, so that others can also benefit from it.”</p>
  <h2 id="learn-from-our-customers">2022: Learn from Our Customers</h2>
  <p>In an interview to mark SAP’s 50th anniversary, Plattner shared some advice: “I recommend a return to the approach we used in the early days of SAP – of sending SAP teams out to the customer. Instead of implementing our standard systems, they should find out how people actually use the tools they get from SAP and other vendors. That will give us our starting point. There are so many interesting companies out there. We can learn from them and with them. We have to step outside SAP and do something with the customers.”</p>
  <p>And in a comment directed to SAP employees, he said: “Treat the customers well – once we have them, we have to keep them. That’s one of SAP’s strengths. And never think it’s done. You have to carry on. The job is never done!”</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a34e8e4286e56c3ddf02ae86fe48f85adf8d6b14.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a34e8e4286e56c3ddf02ae86fe48f85adf8d6b14.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1a34e8e4286e56c3ddf02ae86fe48f85adf8d6b14.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_1a34e8e4286e56c3ddf02ae86fe48f85adf8d6b14.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="578">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>“Treat the customers well” – Plattner’s wish to employees on SAP’s 50th birthday</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="2024">2024</h2>
  <p>Plattner will step down from the Supervisory Board on May 15, the last of the SAP co-founders to leave the company.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="explore-more-of-saps-more-than-50-year-history-of-success-that-began-with-five-entrepreneurial-programmers">Explore more of SAP’s more than 50-year history of success that began with five entrepreneurial programmers</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/history.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-history</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Extends Contract with CEO Christian Klein]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/sap-extends-contract-ceo-christian-klein</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/sap-extends-contract-ceo-christian-klein</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP has extended the contract of CEO and Member of the Executive Board Christian Klein for three years, until the end of 2028. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Global Line of Business Partner Excellence Awards: 2024 Winners and Finalists]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-global-lob-partner-excellence-awards-2024-winners-finalists</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-global-lob-partner-excellence-awards-2024-winners-finalists</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Global LoB Partner Excellence Awards celebrate partners' contributions to our cloud ambitions. Here are the 2024 finalists and winners.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>sap-award/sap-global-lob-partner-excellence-awards</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Information About Upcoming Merger of Hybris Gesellschaft mit beschränkter Haftung into SAP SE]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/information-about-upcoming-merger-of-hybris-gesellschaft-mit-beschraenkter-haftung-into-sap-se</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/information-about-upcoming-merger-of-hybris-gesellschaft-mit-beschraenkter-haftung-into-sap-se</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[0]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15b655c0ab7d21f5ade2aaaa7940105f194180d83.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15b655c0ab7d21f5ade2aaaa7940105f194180d83.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_15b655c0ab7d21f5ade2aaaa7940105f194180d83.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Information About Upcoming Merger of Hybris Gesellschaft mit beschränkter Haftung into SAP SE" src="./media_15b655c0ab7d21f5ade2aaaa7940105f194180d83.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="information-about-upcoming-merger-of-hybris-gesellschaft-mit-beschränkter-haftung-into-sap-se">Information About Upcoming Merger of Hybris Gesellschaft mit beschränkter Haftung into SAP SE</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Publication of SAP SE, Walldorf,<br>pursuant to Sec. 62 para. 3 sent. 2 half sent. 1 UmwG<br><br>– Information about upcoming merger –</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <ol>
    <li>It is intended to merge Hybris Gesellschaft mit beschränkter Haftung (local court of München, HRB 124384) as transferring company in the course of a simplified group merger into SAP SE as acquiring company. Therefore, the assets of Hybris Gesellschaft mit beschränkter Haftung in its entirety together with all rights and obligations are transferred to SAP SE with effectiveness as of 1 January 2024, 0:00 a.m. (“effective merger date”). From the effective merger date to the date of the expiry of Hybris Gesellschaft mit beschränkter Haftung pursuant to Sec. 20 para. 1 No.2 UmwG<br>all acts and businesses undertaken by Hybris Gesellschaft mit beschränkter Haftung shall be deemed to have been undertaken for the account of SAP SE.</li>
    <li>SAP SE is the sole shareholder of Hybris Gesellschaft mit beschränkter Haftung. A merger resolution of the acquiring company SAP SE is not necessary pursuant to Sec. 62 para. 1 sent. 1 UmwG. A resolution of the general meeting of Shareholders of SAP SE on the approval of the merger agreement is also not required because SAP SE as the acquiring company holds the share capital of Hybris Gesellschaft mit beschränkter Haftung in full. Since SAP SE holds all shares in Hybris Gesellschaft mit beschränkter Haftung, the preparation of a merger report, a merger audit and an audit report is not required pursuant to Secs. 8 para. 3 sent. 3 no. 1 a), 9 para. 2, 12 para. 3, 60 UmwG.</li>
    <li>The stakeholders of SAP SE with a combined holding of one-twentieth of the share capital of the company are herewith advised of their right to request the convention of a general meeting to decide on the approval of the merger (Sec. 62 para. 2 sent. 1, para. 3 sent. 3 UmwG).</li>
    <li>A resolution of the shareholder’s meeting of Hybris Gesellschaft mit beschränkter Haftung on the approval of the merger agreement is not required pursuant to section 62 para. 4 sent. 1 UmwG because SAP SE is the sole shareholder of Hybris Gesellschaft mit beschränkter Haftung.</li>
    <li>As of the date of this announcement, the following documents can be assessed by the links below:
      <ol>
        <li><a href="https://www.sap.com/docs/download/investors/2024/hybris-gmbh/hybris-merger-agreement-draft.pdf">The draft merger agreement between SAP SE and Hybris Gesellschaft mit beschränkter Haftung</a>.</li>
        <li>The annual financial statements and, where required, the annual reports of the companies who are parties to the merger for the fiscal years 2021, 2022, 2023:</li>
        <li><a href="https://www.sap.com/docs/download/investors/2021/sap-2021-rechnungslegung-hgb.pdf">2021 SAP SE Statutory Financial Statements and Review of Operations (HGB)</a><br><a href="https://www.sap.com/docs/download/investors/2022/sap-2022-rechnungslegung-hgb.pdf">2022 SAP SE Statutory Financial Statements and Review of Operations (HGB)</a><br><a href="https://www.sap.com/docs/download/investors/2023/sap-2023-rechnungslegung-hgb.pdf">2023 SAP SE Statutory Financial Statements and Review of Operations (HGB)</a><br><a href="https://www.sap.com/docs/download/investors/2024/hybris-gmbh/hybris-gmbh-jahresabschluss-2021-signed.pdf">2021 Hybris Gesellschaft mit beschränkter Haftung Financial Statements</a><br><a href="https://www.sap.com/docs/download/investors/2024/hybris-gmbh/hybris-gmbh-jahresabschluss-2022-signed.pdf">2022 Hybris Gesellschaft mit beschränkter Haftung Financial Statements</a><br><a href="https://www.sap.com/docs/download/investors/2024/hybris-gmbh/hybris-gmbh-jahresabschluss-2023-signed.pdf">2023 Hybris Gesellschaft mit beschränkter Haftung Financial Statements</a></li>
      </ol>
    </li>
  </ol>
  <p><strong>SAP SE, April 26, 2024</strong></p>
  <p><strong><em>The Board of Directors</em></strong></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/investor-relations</category>
            <category>content-type/statement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-investor-relations</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Announces Q1 2024 Results]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-announces-q1-2024-results</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-announces-q1-2024-results</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP has announced Q1 2024 financial results, with unabated growth momentum of the cloud ERP suite. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/investor-relations</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/earnings</category>
            <category>news-tag/investor-relations</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-investor-relations</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[AHA! Moments in D&I: Disability Inclusion with Disability:IN]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/aha-moments-disability-inclusion</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/aha-moments-disability-inclusion</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Jill Houghton of Disability:IN talks to SAP's Supriya Jha about how leadership culture is key to disability inclusion. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-network-groups</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Disability Inclusion: AHA! Moments in D&I]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/videos/disability-inclusion-aha-moments-in-di</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/videos/disability-inclusion-aha-moments-in-di</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In the latest episode of the AHA! Moments in Diversity & Inclusion video series, SAP Chief Diversity & Inclusion Officer Supriya Jha talks to Jill Houghton of Disability:IN.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/video</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP to Release First Quarter 2024 Results]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-to-release-first-quarter-2024-results</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-to-release-first-quarter-2024-results</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP will release its full results for the first quarter of 2024 on Monday, April 22, at 10:05 p.m. CEST/ 4:05 p.m. EDT.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/statement</category>
            <category>news-tag/earnings</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Pinnacle Awards: 2024 Finalists and Winners Announced]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-pinnacle-awards-2024-finalists-and-winners</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-pinnacle-awards-2024-finalists-and-winners</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Pinnacle Awards recognize top-performing and innovative partners. Learn more about the SAP Pinnacle Awards 2024 finalists and winners.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11764e94c92ed4681b4c79ee2e132a07bdde6ab9c.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11764e94c92ed4681b4c79ee2e132a07bdde6ab9c.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_11764e94c92ed4681b4c79ee2e132a07bdde6ab9c.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Pinnacle Awards: 2024 Finalists and Winners Announced" src="./media_11764e94c92ed4681b4c79ee2e132a07bdde6ab9c.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-pinnacle-awards-2024-finalists-and-winners-announced">SAP Pinnacle Awards: 2024 Finalists and Winners Announced</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>The SAP Pinnacle Awards, our most prestigious global partner recognition program, shine a spotlight on our top-performing partners that demonstrate excellence in unlocking innovative new ways for customers to run their businesses.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP’s ecosystem plays a key role in our vision to enable every organization and every industry to become a network of intelligent, sustainable enterprises. Through their unique industry expertise, implementation methodologies, complementary solutions, and commitment throughout the Customer Value Journey, partners help customers thrive and succeed with SAP.</p>
  <p>Across 26 categories in the areas of Customer Success, Intelligent Enterprise Realization, Sustainability, and Social Impact, partners are recognized for their outstanding contributions, exponential growth, and simplification. Through delivering cloud innovations that help customers achieve their goals, these partners exemplify dedication to teamwork and embody our vision for partnering excellence.</p>
  <p>Twenty-five of the 2024 winners and finalists were selected from <a href="/topics/ecosystem">SAP’s wide-ranging partner base</a>, using system-generated data on core metrics and key performance indicators. A steering committee of global SAP representatives reviewed, vetted, and ranked the achievements according to our internal criteria, which aligned with SAP’s communicated business strategies.</p>
  <p>The only exception is the Social Impact category, which recognized a partner’s lasting societal impact by leveraging SAP innovation with concrete results. Partner nominations were evaluated and ranked by a panel of jurors consisting of SAP internal and third-party representatives.</p>
  <p>Winners and finalists for all categories will receive a communication package to help them promote their success to their customers, prospects, and the media, including logos for online and physical marketing vehicles. To increase their global exposure, SAP will list the winners and finalists on its Web site for an entire year, in addition to running a comprehensive campaign that promotes these winners and finalists to joint prospects and customers.</p>
  <p>Congratulations to the <a href="https://www.sap.com/partners/pinnacle-awards.html">winners and finalists</a>! We look forward to celebrating your success at SAP Partner Connect and SAP Sapphire.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Karl Fahrbach is chief partner officer at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-pinnacle-awards-showcase-partners-that-have-excelled-in-helping-customers-become-best-run-businesses">SAP Pinnacle Awards showcase partners that have excelled in helping customers become best-run businesses</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/partners/pinnacle-awards.html">Check out this year’s winners and finalists</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>sap-award/sap-pinnacle-awards</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Driving Progress in Sustainability, Adoption, and AI: The 2024 SAP Innovation Award Winners]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2024/04/2024-sap-innovation-award-winners</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2024/04/2024-sap-innovation-award-winners</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The 2024 SAP Innovation Award winners have utilized SAP solutions and AI to achieve remarkable results. Learn more about the winners.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/executive-blog</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>sap-award/sap-innovation-awards</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Extends Contract with Chief Technology Officer Juergen Mueller]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-extends-contract-with-cto-juergen-mueller</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-extends-contract-with-cto-juergen-mueller</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP has extended the contract of CTO Juergen Mueller for three years through 2027. Mueller joined the company in 2013 and the Board in 2019.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d4256f3133f0b4e05056896b40ac385c7299de26.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d4256f3133f0b4e05056896b40ac385c7299de26.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1d4256f3133f0b4e05056896b40ac385c7299de26.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Extends Contract with Chief Technology Officer Juergen Mueller" src="./media_1d4256f3133f0b4e05056896b40ac385c7299de26.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-extends-contract-with-chief-technology-officer-juergen-mueller">SAP Extends Contract with Chief Technology Officer Juergen Mueller</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced that it has extended the contract of Dr. Juergen Mueller, Chief Technology Officer (CTO) of SAP SE, for another three years until the end of 2027. Mueller joined SAP in 2013 and has been a member of the Executive Board of SAP SE since 2019.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As CTO, he leads the Technology &#x26; Innovation Board area at SAP and has successfully established SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP) as the platform for SAP and as an external business unit. In his mandate as CTO, he will prepare SAP for its accelerated cloud growth. In addition to SAP BTP, he is responsible for architecture decisions and innovations across SAP as well as Business Transformation Management with SAP Signavio and SAP LeanIX. Global security and cloud compliance are also part of his responsibility.</p>
  <p>“I would like to thank the Supervisory Board for their trust and am thrilled to continue shaping SAP’s technology strategy and driving innovation for our customers around the world,” Mueller said. “Together with our teams, I will continue working with the clear goal of being the number one enterprise application and business AI company.”</p>
  <p>“In recent years, Juergen Mueller and his team have successfully developed SAP BTP and established it as the platform of choice for our customers,” said Professor Hasso Plattner, chairman of the Supervisory Board of SAP SE. “We thank Juergen Mueller for his successful work to date and are convinced that he will continue to ensure SAP’s innovation capabilities in the future.”</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="http://news.sap.com/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Media Contact:</strong><br>Marcus Winkler, +49 6227 767497, <a href="mailto:marcus.winkler@sap.com">marcus.winkler@sap.com</a>, CEST<br><a href="http://www.news-sap.com/press-room/">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>This document contains forward-looking statements, which are predictions, projections, or other statements about future events. These statements are based on current expectations, forecasts, and assumptions that are subject to risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results and outcomes to materially differ. Additional information regarding these risks and uncertainties may be found in our filings with the Securities and Exchange Commission, including but not limited to the risk factors section of SAP’s 2023 Annual Report on Form 20-F.<br>© 2024 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP's Adoption Revolution: When Expectations and Outcomes for Cloud Transformation Meet]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2024/04/cloud-transformation-adoption-revolution-expectations-outcomes-meet</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2024/04/cloud-transformation-adoption-revolution-expectations-outcomes-meet</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The new Customer Services & Delivery Board area at SAP will make it easier and faster for customers to adopt cloud solutions.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/executive-blog</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Chief Investor Relations Officer to Leave End of June]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/sap-chief-investor-relations-officer-anthony-coletta-to-leave-end-of-june</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/sap-chief-investor-relations-officer-anthony-coletta-to-leave-end-of-june</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Anthony Coletta will remain in his current role until the end of June 2024; the company is in the process of finding a successor.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/investor-relations</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>news-tag/investor-relations</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-investor-relations</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Women Shape AI at SAP]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/how-women-shape-ai-at-sap</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/how-women-shape-ai-at-sap</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Women working in AI at SAP describe their roles, responsibilities, and how to build a successful career in the space. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c71f389e8850fb7895355ea5b6b7c031021581a5.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c71f389e8850fb7895355ea5b6b7c031021581a5.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1c71f389e8850fb7895355ea5b6b7c031021581a5.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="How Women Shape AI at SAP" src="./media_1c71f389e8850fb7895355ea5b6b7c031021581a5.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="how-women-shape-ai-at-sap">How Women Shape AI at SAP</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Although women comprise about 35% of the workforce at SAP, when it comes to shaping AI it seems they are punching above their weight.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Here, five SAP employees share about their roles, motivations, and tips for anyone wanting to step into AI. The women – Khawla Mallat, Camila Lombana Diaz, Xin Chen, Nadine Hoffmann, and Puntis Palazzolo – span four countries and three areas: Data Science Engineering, Product Management, and AI Ethics.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-business-ai-revolutionary-technology-real-world-results">SAP Business AI: Revolutionary technology, real-world results</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <table>
          <thead>
            <tr>
              <th>Text Large</th>
            </tr>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td><strong>Data Science Engineering</strong></td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
        <p><strong>Dr. Khawla Mallat, Security and Quantum Exploration Team, SAP France</strong></p>
        <p>“Be ready to be challenged all times,” says Mallat, if you want to build a career in AI.</p>
        <p>Unlike most data scientists at SAP, Mallat does not work directly on the product but is firmly anchored in researching and addressing “some of the technical challenges related to AI, namely fairness, explainability, privacy, and security.”</p>
        <table>
          <thead>
            <tr>
              <th>Lightbox</th>
            </tr>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td>
                <p>
                  <picture>
                    <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1bd271968479d2d41e43558e1d7ef16cac75424e4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
                    <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1bd271968479d2d41e43558e1d7ef16cac75424e4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
                    <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1bd271968479d2d41e43558e1d7ef16cac75424e4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
                    <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_1bd271968479d2d41e43558e1d7ef16cac75424e4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="291" height="300">
                  </picture>
                </p>
                <p><em>Photo courtesy of Khawla Mallat</em></p>
              </td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
        <p>Prior to joining SAP two years ago, Mallat was confronted with the unintended prejudices of face analysis systems. Certain demographic groups, explains Mallat, used to be inadvertently omitted or underrepresented in the underlying data sets, leading to shortcomings in the face analysis capabilities. Such cases highlight the broader issue of bias in other AI applications. In areas like HR, she continues, removing personal details in data sets might seem to solve the bias issues, but AI can still infer these details. This leads to potentially biased outcomes and the lack of explainability in AI models makes identification of such biases difficult. Letting data sets like this take root and grow into powerful data models not subject to scrutiny will only magnify the inherent bias or discrimination.</p>
        <p>Today Mallat’s passion for addressing such unfairness aligns well with her role of identifying the inherent risks of AI, educating teams about them, and defining technological solutions to mitigate them.</p>
        <p>“We need to adopt an interdisplinary approach to AI, with experts from ethics, legal compliance, and domain experts, for example, and abstract ourselves from the role of data scientists to succeed,” says Mallat.</p>
        <p>“I love working in AI,” she continues. “Everything is progressing at an incredible pace so if you want to work in AI, you have to have a certain thirst for knowledge. And, regardless of your role, you must take AI ethics – regulations and regulatory frameworks – seriously because these have huge implications not only for SAP but for individuals and societies in general.”</p>
        <table>
          <thead>
            <tr>
              <th>Text Large</th>
            </tr>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td><strong>AI Ethics</strong></td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
        <p><strong>Camila Lombana Diaz, Responsible AI, Germany</strong></p>
        <p>“AI is a mirror of our capacities as humans. And the biggest responsibility for those working in AI is, what do we want to see in that mirror?” explains Lombana Diaz, AI ethics research expert in the AI Ethics/Responsible AI team located in the SAP Business AI growth area.</p>
        <p>Lombana Diaz’s responsibilities include maturing and applying the SAP AI Global Ethics policy, creating and delivering enablement content, defining AI personas and processes, and giving guidance to make responsible AI an operational reality for development, as exemplified in SAP’s AI ethics handbook.</p>
        <table>
          <thead>
            <tr>
              <th>Lightbox</th>
            </tr>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td>
                <p>
                  <picture>
                    <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_116dec50e3ea9328d01378970e5e7ed4ce2f96acd.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
                    <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_116dec50e3ea9328d01378970e5e7ed4ce2f96acd.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
                    <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_116dec50e3ea9328d01378970e5e7ed4ce2f96acd.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
                    <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_116dec50e3ea9328d01378970e5e7ed4ce2f96acd.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="360" height="200">
                  </picture>
                </p>
                <p><em>Photo courtesy of Camila Lombana Diaz</em></p>
              </td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
        <p>When she joined SAP eight years ago, initially as a UX designer and then a strategic designer, machine learning and AI were core topics. But it became increasingly clear to her that “understanding the human implications of AI for a responsible and ethical AI demands a human-centric perspective.”</p>
        <p>Even though SAP is committed to the ethical development of AI – developers must now complete AI ethics assessment tasks and a steering committee scrutinizes all high-risk use cases – Lombana Diaz emphasizes the need to remain focused on the inherent risks and unintentional harms that AI may present. Part of her role is an ongoing assessment of the technology, identifying risks and limitations and communicating them to different teams.</p>
        <p>As AI continues to evolve at speed, so do the roles. Lombana Diaz is passionate about seeing AI beyond the confines of a technology-centric perspective. “AI is now an omnipresent technology shaping our daily lives; hence, we need individuals working in the field who challenge AI technology to be community centric. AI ethics is a space for experimental, open, curious, collaborative, and human-centered individuals,” and, she concludes, “the time to step into AI and build a career is <em>now</em> because, unlike the technology, the business of AI, the legal and ethical aspects, are still being shaped.”</p>
        <table>
          <thead>
            <tr>
              <th>Text Large</th>
            </tr>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td><strong>Data Science Engineering</strong></td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
        <p><strong>Dr. Xin Chen, SAP HANA Machine Learning, China</strong></p>
        <p>“I have always enjoyed working at SAP since joining nine years ago. I like the work environment and the colleagues here and I really want to encourage others to join us here in AI,” says Chen, data science researcher on the SAP HANA Machine Learning team.</p>
        <table>
          <thead>
            <tr>
              <th>Lightbox</th>
            </tr>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td>
                <p>
                  <picture>
                    <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1fd4656c3221d9e4aa5efe44771ca3b23d71d87db.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
                    <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1fd4656c3221d9e4aa5efe44771ca3b23d71d87db.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
                    <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1fd4656c3221d9e4aa5efe44771ca3b23d71d87db.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
                    <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_1fd4656c3221d9e4aa5efe44771ca3b23d71d87db.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="360" height="200">
                  </picture>
                </p>
                <p><em>Photo courtesy of Dr. Xin Chen</em></p>
              </td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
        <p>The team works on a toolbox providing different kinds of machine learning algorithms for regression, classification, clustering, and so on for the SAP HANA predictive analysis library.</p>
        <p>Part of Chen’s role is investigating research papers on the latest machine learning algorithms and, together with the team, deciding which algorithms would be beneficial to customers. Once the machine learning algorithms are implemented, Chen and the team evaluate feedback from customers and deliver enhancements.</p>
        <p>Recently Chen and her team researched machine learning algorithms investigating notions of fairness. “Fairness is a very hot topic just now,” she says. “In mathematics, there are different notions of fairness, but it is still a complex and evolving topic.”</p>
        <p>And Chen’s advice to would-be AI developers? “Critical thinking will become even more important to understand what solutions to offer, to make judgements on your own innovations, and to know if the generated output is right or wrong,” she says, reflecting on how this skill will become ever more important for future AI developers.</p>
        <table>
          <thead>
            <tr>
              <th>Text Large</th>
            </tr>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td><strong>Product Management</strong></td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
        <p><strong>Nadine Hoffmann, SAP Business AI, Germany</strong></p>
        <p>“I translate and I want to fascinate,” says Hoffmann, global AI product manager in the SAP Business AI growth area.</p>
        <p>Even after more than 20 years at SAP, disruptive ideas and mindset shifts still energize Hoffmann. To be an expert in new technologies, and to be energized and enthused by the constant volume and speed of them, is critical to being successful in the AI product management teams of today because product management is the glue between partners, customers, the field, and development.</p>
        <table>
          <thead>
            <tr>
              <th>Lightbox</th>
            </tr>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td>
                <p>
                  <picture>
                    <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b4e988730056885c9e500b8c6a21150a3fcc626a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
                    <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b4e988730056885c9e500b8c6a21150a3fcc626a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
                    <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1b4e988730056885c9e500b8c6a21150a3fcc626a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
                    <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_1b4e988730056885c9e500b8c6a21150a3fcc626a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="360" height="200">
                  </picture>
                </p>
                <p><em>Photo courtesy of Nadine Hoffmann</em></p>
              </td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
        <p>“On the one hand,” says Hoffmann, “SAP has data scientists, software engineers, and researchers taking our software to the next level. And on the other, there are experts defining the legal and ethical guardrails.” Product management must be fluent in both “technical software speak” and “customer speak” to understand desires, pain points, and business processes.</p>
        <p>Pivoting between these and aligning customer speak with technical software speak is akin to being a translator, Hoffmann says. Our software will only meet the requirements of customers if there is a common understanding between the teams responsible for the technological development, the legal teams responsible for ethical and legal compliance, and the customer.</p>
        <p>Regardless of the latest innovation, Hoffmann says success in product management is “not only about convincing teams and partners about the ease and positiveness of a technology, but also infusing them with a fascination about it so that they become passionate advocates and are intrinsically motivated to find out more by themselves.”</p>
        <table>
          <thead>
            <tr>
              <th>Text Large</th>
            </tr>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td><strong>Data Science Engineering</strong></td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
        <p><strong>Puntis Palazzolo, AI Strategist &#x26; Ethics Lead, SAP SuccessFactors, U.S.</strong></p>
        <p>“The ethical challenges presented by AI have transcended the scope of individual enterprises, extending beyond entities like SAP. It is crucial that we collaborate with others to collectively address AI’s emerging concerns,” says Palazzolo, who leads the SAP SuccessFactors Data Science team.</p>
        <p>The team acts as a consulting service on AI use cases for product teams in SAP SuccessFactors, analyzing the problem, developing code and algorithms, and building proof-of-concepts. Successful AI use cases are then integrated into SAP SuccessFactors solutions.</p>
        <table>
          <thead>
            <tr>
              <th>Lightbox</th>
            </tr>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td>
                <p>
                  <picture>
                    <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14ad04a2a505c656213cdec94acc2bd3275077a33.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
                    <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14ad04a2a505c656213cdec94acc2bd3275077a33.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
                    <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_14ad04a2a505c656213cdec94acc2bd3275077a33.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
                    <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_14ad04a2a505c656213cdec94acc2bd3275077a33.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="240" height="300">
                  </picture>
                </p>
                <p><em>Photo courtesy of Puntis Palazzolo</em></p>
              </td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
        <p>Much of the data in SAP SuccessFactors solutions is sensitive customer data. With the dramatic increase in generative AI use cases, safeguarding customer data must take precedence, Palazzolo says. “Generative AI is a powerful technology that introduces new challenges, such as hallucinations and automated decision-making. In high-risk sectors like HR, we need to explain how we reach certain decisions, especially when we are impacting people’s lives.”</p>
        <p>Palazzolo joined SAP 11 years ago and has been based in Palo Alto, California, since 2013, where she represents SAP on <a href="https://mlcommons.org/">MLCommons</a> – a collaboration of academia and companies, such as Google and NVIDIA, dedicated to developing safe practices and industry-standard benchmarks to improve AI models.</p>
        <p>Her advice to current and would-be AI practitioners? Follow your passion, be ethical, and make your voice heard while we still have time.</p>
        <p>“Legislators alone cannot write AI regulations for us because they do not have a full understanding of its complexities,” she says. “We cannot solve all the problems by ourselves, but we must make our voices heard to shape the future of AI.”</p>
        <p>Alexa MacDonald is an SAP News editor.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="follow-sap-news-on-linkedin-to-stay-in-touch">Follow SAP News on LinkedIn to stay in touch</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news">Connect with us</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-employee-profile</category>
            <category>news-tag/women-at-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/women-in-tech</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Wait Is Over: Here Are the 2024 SAP Innovation Award Finalists]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/2024-sap-innovation-award-finalists</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/2024-sap-innovation-award-finalists</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The 2024 SAP Innovation Award finalists have utilized cloud solutions from SAP and AI to achieve remarkable results. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>sap-award/sap-innovation-awards</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Celebrating the Winners of the Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award 2023]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/celebrating-hasso-plattner-founders-award-winners-2023</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/celebrating-hasso-plattner-founders-award-winners-2023</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP announced the 2023 winners of the Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award, the company’s most prestigious employee recognition.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_13403df4d72b3f7d91e84c8c6f66e21dcbf1a8636.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_13403df4d72b3f7d91e84c8c6f66e21dcbf1a8636.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_13403df4d72b3f7d91e84c8c6f66e21dcbf1a8636.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Celebrating the Winners of the Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award 2023" src="./media_13403df4d72b3f7d91e84c8c6f66e21dcbf1a8636.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="celebrating-the-winners-of-the-hasso-plattner-founders-award-2023">Celebrating the Winners of the Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award 2023</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Last week, to a virtual audience of nearly 50,000 employees, the Executive Board of SAP SE announced the 2023 winners of the Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award, the company’s most prestigious employee recognition.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Three teams were selected for outstanding and innovative projects in the categories Go-to-Market, Operational Excellence, and Products and Technology.</p>
  <p>In 2023, 115 nominations involved more than 750 employees from 35 countries. Eight teams consisting of 81 employees from around the world made it to the final round.</p>
  <p>In honor of the three winning teams, SAP will make donations to three charities selected by the team members. The €30,000 total donation – €10,000 per team – will be split between <a href="https://bettershelter.org/">Better Shelter</a>, <a href="https://wck.org/">World Central Kitchen</a>, and <a href="https://www.embraceglobal.org/">Embrace Global</a>.</p>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_134b71501074e5b151cb81e7d9d054b44ff8f3a67.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_134b71501074e5b151cb81e7d9d054b44ff8f3a67.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_134b71501074e5b151cb81e7d9d054b44ff8f3a67.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Meet the 2023 Hasso Plattner Founders&#x27; Award Winners" src="./media_134b71501074e5b151cb81e7d9d054b44ff8f3a67.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://youtu.be/qzsiBITdf8Y">Meet the 2023 Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award Winners</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="go-to-market-winner">Go-to-Market Winner</h3>
        <h2 id="reimagined-rise-with-sap-business-case-with-sap-signavio-and-sap-value-lifecycle-manager-integration">Reimagined RISE with SAP Business Case with SAP Signavio and SAP Value Lifecycle Manager Integration</h2>
        <p>When shifting to a cloud-first approach, it can be a challenge to pitch the cloud to customers due to the comprehensiveness of the solution spanning across the entire value chain of an enterprise.</p>
        <p>To apply a more streamlined and dependable method for crafting compelling value propositions, the Value Advisory team at SAP implemented the SAP Signavio portfolio of cloud-based business process management solutions within their practice to demonstrate value to customers through data-driven insights.</p>
        <p>The team created a system where business metrics from <a href="https://vlm.cfapps.eu10.hana.ondemand.com/home">SAP Value Lifecycle Manager</a> and process performance data from <a href="https://www.signavio.com/">SAP Signavio solutions</a> were merged and applied to business KPIs to identify cases of suboptimal performance. This allows customers to more easily see the connection between business outcomes and the process capabilities, supported by data.</p>
        <p>The approach offers a robust and repeatable performance diagnostic that can be used to identify, clarify, verify, and amplify value throughout the customer value journey, helping customers better understand the value of the cloud and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/rise.html">RISE with SAP</a>. The innovation helps build customer trust and intimacy while also helping our business operate at scale. To date, this process-driven value management has impacted more than 190 customers.</p>
        <p>“Our future focus involves enhancing usability and capabilities to comprehensively cover the customer value journey,” Nitin Singh, team leader and Value Advisory principal, says. “We extend our sincere gratitude to our leaders for fostering a culture of innovation, our colleagues for experimenting and navigating challenges with us, and prior colleagues whose work paved the way for this journey. We genuinely stand on the shoulders of giants.”</p>
        <h3 id="operational-excellence-winner">Operational Excellence Winner</h3>
        <h2 id="plutus-rate-optimization-and-management">Plutus: Rate Optimization and Management</h2>
        <p>Cloud services are a critical part of SAP’s recent evolution, with the company dedicating extensive time and resources to seamlessly integrate all essential services into the cloud. This effort aims to enhance customer experiences – and Plutus serves as the cornerstone of these endeavors.</p>
        <p>Plutus, which leverages <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform.html">SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP)</a>, is a one-stop solution for major hyperscalers. It’s crafted to empower lines of business by providing smarter and more efficient advice for optimizing cloud services. Plutus can centralize the management of cost optimization and intelligently navigate users through cloud expenses, providing top-notch recommendations and comprehensive end-to-end management. It caters to users’ needs from guidance to execution, helping to ensure cost savings every step of the way.</p>
        <p>The Plutus team used cutting-edge technologies to create a 24/7, fully integrated, user-centric cloud service hub and a smooth user interface platform that can operate across various channels. Plutus provides simplified financial operations processes by offering an intuitive interface across all platforms, working to eliminate pricing disparities and provide reliable cost-saving solutions. These efforts strongly emphasize SAP’s commitment to advancing global digital sustainability through innovative enterprise solutions.</p>
        <p>The solution uses machine learning to provide smart recommendations. The team also plans to integrate a versatile digital chatbot based on generative AI to help ensure seamless and comprehensive user support in the future.</p>
        <p>Plutus allows for a new approach to SAP’s cloud cost optimization strategy, unlocking new avenues for significant cost savings and margin improvements. To date, Plutus has generated over US$920 million in net savings for SAP, with projections reaching $1 billion in Q1 2024. It has also achieved and maintained remarkable, best-in-industry cloud utilization and coverage rates – exceeding 97% and 90%, respectively.</p>
        <p>“Winning the Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award reflects our dedication to teamwork and innovation,” Donghua Chen, Plutus team lead, says. “Our journey to this point has required a lot of hard work. But as we celebrate this achievement, we remain committed to continually analyzing cloud usage to maximize savings for SAP through rate optimization.”</p>
        <h3 id="products--technology-winner">Products &#x26; Technology Winner</h3>
        <h2 id="cap-and-capgpt--sap-cloud-application-programming-model-and-generative-ai">CAP and capGPT – SAP Cloud Application Programming Model and Generative AI</h2>
        <p>The SAP Cloud Application Programming Model (CAP) was started in 2018 as a project to address the lack of guidance for developers building apps on what is now SAP BTP. At first, developers could choose from a huge number of technologies, which made integration with the platform services a relatively high effort.</p>
        <p>As a development framework, CAP automatically solves about 80% of the problems backend developers face – such as multitenancy, expandability, or business features such as localization and translatability. But thanks to CAP’s domain-driven approach, it is no longer necessary to always change the coding in each of those cases. And for special use cases that CAP doesn’t cover, the coding can be easily added to build in this functionality. To help safeguard customers’ investments, CAP offers the possibility to interchange components, such as runtime or the database, without changing the actual implementation.</p>
        <p>CAP, as a centerpiece of Golden Path and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/developer-tools.html">SAP Build Code</a>, is now an integral part of the consumption experience of SAP BTP. Today, thousands of internal and external developers use CAP to build business applications on SAP BTP, driving higher developer productivity and easier SAP BTP service adoption.</p>
        <p>“This award is a great testament to the hard work and dedication of the whole CAP unit and a recognition of the impact we have both internally as well as for our customers and partners,” Ole Lilienthal, team lead, says.</p>
        <p>To make prototyping even easier, in spring 2023, SAP software architect David Kunz applied ChatGPT’s large language model to writing code for business apps.</p>
        <p>capGPT, as the new functionality is called, allows users to write in natural language what they want their app prototype to be able to do. In as little as 30 seconds, they can receive all the code – which previously had to be written by hand – and access the prototype to test it. This can not only save experienced developers an amazing amount of time, but can also enable non-developers to create prototypes of the apps they need. capGPT can also generate user interfaces in addition to backend applications. It will soon be available to customers through integration into SAP Build Code as part of AI-development assistant Joule.</p>
        <p>“Seeing capGPT go from an idea to a Hasso Plattner Founders’ Award winner within a year is a true testament that everything is possible at SAP,” Kunz says. “I feel very proud and I’m energized to continue to push the limits of what generative AI can enable.”</p>
        <p>Photo courtesy of SAP employee Fateh Kassab</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-sap-news-on-linkedin">Connect with SAP News on LinkedIn</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news">Follow us to stay in touch</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>sap-award/hasso-plattner-founders-awards</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP CSR's eBook Celebrates a Year of Global Impact]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/sap-csr-ebook-celebrates-global-impact</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/sap-csr-ebook-celebrates-global-impact</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The impact of SAP CSR in 2023 is a testament to the power of collective action and shared vision. Read to find out how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1aa60aead41f035043e44cbfe1f53c8c65e859485.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1aa60aead41f035043e44cbfe1f53c8c65e859485.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1aa60aead41f035043e44cbfe1f53c8c65e859485.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP CSR’s eBook Celebrates a Year of Global Impact" src="./media_1aa60aead41f035043e44cbfe1f53c8c65e859485.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-csrs-ebook-celebrates-a-year-of-global-impact">SAP CSR’s eBook Celebrates a Year of Global Impact</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Reflecting on the past year, one event stands out vividly in my memory: the Social Enterprises World Forum (SEWF) in Amsterdam, the Netherlands. For those unfamiliar, imagine a global assembly where more than 1,500 entrepreneurs from 82 countries dedicated to societal and environmental missions come together. These enterprises prioritize people and the planet, reinvesting their profits to advance their respective causes. Witnessing the energy and innovation in Amsterdam was a powerful reminder of why SAP has emphasized social entrepreneurship for the second consecutive year.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>It makes me proud to think about the 676 SAP colleagues who, in 2023, participated in our pro bono consulting programs, offering their expertise to these visionary social entrepreneurs. As in previous years, this collaboration has proven mutually beneficial, with 74% of our employees reporting a positive, lasting impact on their careers. Furthermore, 96% of the supported organizations and 77% of their beneficiaries have seen significant improvements. These numbers speak volumes about the shared value of our engagement.</p>
  <p>But the 2023 SEWF wasn’t just a personal highlight; it marked the beginning of another significant milestone. We announced our investment in the <strong>Social Enterprise People and Planet First Verification</strong> with Good Market and SEWF. This initiative aims to set a global standard for recognizing organizations prioritizing social and environmental impacts. Social enterprises can now also identify themselves on SAP Business Network, the world’s largest B2B commerce platform. This breakthrough can make it easier for these businesses to explore new business-to-business opportunities while also helping SAP customers achieve their goals of being more environmentally and socially responsible. Saying it’s a win-win situation is a bit cliché, but in this case it’s actually true.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-is-powering-equitable-access-to-economic-opportunity-education-and-employment-and-the-circular-economy">SAP is powering equitable access to economic opportunity, education and employment, and the circular economy</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/our-values/csr.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Working with SEWF shows how much we believe in working together and driving towards collective impact. I’ve said it before and I’ll say it again: we can’t do this by ourselves. Working with others is the key to driving the kind of systemic change our world needs. This idea is a big part of what we stand for at SAP, and is at the heart of our corporate social responsibility (<a href="/topics/csr">CSR</a>) strategy.</p>
  <p>This idea of working together really comes to life in our collaboration with <strong>UNICEF and Generation Unlimited</strong>. In 2023 – the fourth year of our partnership – we set out to make a real difference by not just developing the skills of young people but also finding jobs in the SAP ecosystem. Launching the SAP Educate to Employ program is a big step in that direction. Helping 25 young people get jobs with SAP in each of our pilot countries – Nigeria, Kenya, South Africa, and the Philippines – might not sound like a lot, but it’s a huge deal for each of those young people. For them, it’s a gateway to a sustainable livelihood, offering them not just gainful employment but a chance to build a career, achieve financial stability, and make meaningful contributions to their communities and the broader world. It’s about unlocking their potential and enabling them to participate in the digital and green economy. By the end of the year, we saw amazing results. While more than 2,500 had already passed the aptitude test, over 1,000 young people in Africa finished our “Boost Your Career with SAP Skills” course and more than 500 got through the first big part of their training.</p>
  <p>But, what’s a year recap without some high-level numbers? Let’s dive into some impressive <strong>numbers from 2023</strong>. More than 20,000 of our SAP colleagues volunteered over 140,000 hours. Our initiatives reached over 2.8 million young people – almost half girls – and supported over 41,000 teachers. Our partner network reached 1 billion people in over 140 countries. These stats are just the tip of the iceberg, showing our big reach and impact together with our partners.</p>
  <p>Building on this, our signature partnerships with Africa Code Week, Meet and Code, and Latin Code Week have always been at the heart of our achievements. As we handed over these initiatives in 2023, we took a moment to reflect and evaluate Africa Code Week and Latin Code Week outcomes more deeply. For instance, by empowering 14.6 million participants with the education, knowledge, and ICT skills needed to participate in the digital future, <strong>Africa Code Week</strong> has increased the likelihood that beneficiaries will realize higher earnings during their working lives. Common Good Marketplace estimates that Africa Code Week catalyzed up to US$1 billion in social value for program participants between 2015 and 2022 based on future increased income.</p>
  <p>As we close the chapter on 2023 and look ahead, the journey we’ve embarked upon at SAP CSR is a testament to the power of collective action and shared vision. The stories, numbers, and outcomes shared in our eBook reflect our commitment to making a meaningful difference. <a href="https://d.dam.sap.com/a/Gnggenc/SAP%20CSR%20in%20Review%202023.pdf?rc=10">Read the full eBook.</a></p>
  <p>Thank you to everyone who has been a part of this journey. Your passion, dedication, and commitment are what drive us forward.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Alexandra van der Ploeg is global head of Corporate Social Responsibility at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="follow-sap-news-on-linkedin-to-stay-up-to-date">Follow SAP News on LinkedIn to stay up-to-date</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news">Connect with us</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>non-sap-event/africa-code week</category>
            <category>news-tag/csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/generation-unlimited</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/social-entrepreneurship</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Releases Integrated Report 2023 and Files Annual Report 2023 on Form 20-F with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/sap-releases-integrated-report-2023-and-files-annual-report-2023-on-form-20-f</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/sap-releases-integrated-report-2023-and-files-annual-report-2023-on-form-20-f</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP SE today announced that it has filed the SAP Annual Report on Form 20-F as well as the 2023 SAP Integrated Report. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/investor-relations</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/investor-relations</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-investor-relations</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Proposes Dividend of €2.20 per Share and Announces Candidates for Shareholder Representative Elections]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/sap-proposes-dividend-and-announces-candidates-for-shareholder-representative-elections</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/sap-proposes-dividend-and-announces-candidates-for-shareholder-representative-elections</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP believes that its shareholders should benefit appropriately from the profit the Company made in 2023. The Company’s dividend policy is to pay a dividend ...]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1006f89343a6bddbfaa0b7d16f4c78618586e373b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1006f89343a6bddbfaa0b7d16f4c78618586e373b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1006f89343a6bddbfaa0b7d16f4c78618586e373b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Proposes Dividend of €2.20 per Share and Announces Candidates for Shareholder Representative Elections" src="./media_1006f89343a6bddbfaa0b7d16f4c78618586e373b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="196" height="130">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-proposes-dividend-of-220-per-share-and-announces-candidates-for-shareholder-representative-elections">SAP Proposes Dividend of €2.20 per Share and Announces Candidates for Shareholder Representative Elections</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong> — The Supervisory Board and Executive Board of <a href="http://www.sap.com">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) recommend that shareholders approve a dividend of €2.20 per share for fiscal year 2023. If approved by shareholders and assuming the same level of treasury shares as at December 31, 2023, the total amount distributed in dividends would be approximately €2.568 billion (2022: €2.393 billion), representing a pay-out ratio of 43.1% (2022: 139.6%).</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP believes that its shareholders should benefit appropriately from the profit the Company made in 2023. The Company’s dividend policy is to pay a dividend totaling 40% or more of profit after tax.</p>
  <p>The following dates are relevant for the dividend payment:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Record date for dividend payment: May 15, 2024</li>
    <li>Ex-dividend date: May 16, 2024</li>
    <li>Payment date: May 21, 2024</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="elections-of-shareholder-representatives-to-the-sap-supervisory-board">Elections of Shareholder Representatives to the SAP Supervisory Board</h2>
  <p>As announced on February 11, 2024, the <a href="/2024/02/pekka-ala-pietila-proposed-by-sap-supervisory-board-as-designated-successor-to-chairman-hasso-plattner">Supervisory Board has nominated Pekka Ala-Pietilä</a> to stand for election at the 2024 Annual General Meeting of Shareholders (AGM) as shareholder representative on the SAP Supervisory Board.</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Dr. h. c. mult. Pekka Ala-Pietilä</strong> (67), Helsinki, Finland, Chairman of the Board of Directors of Sanoma Corporation, Helsinki, Finland. In case of election, his term would expire in 2026. The Supervisory Board intends to elect him as chair.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>Further, the Supervisory Board is announcing the nomination of the following candidate to stand for election:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Prof. Dr. Ralf Herbrich</strong> (49), Falkensee, Germany, Managing director, professor for artificial intelligence and sustainability, Hasso Plattner Institute for Digital Engineering gGmbH, Potsdam, Germany. In case of election, his term would expire in 2028.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>Additionally, three candidates have been nominated to stand for re-election:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Aicha Evans</strong> (54), Los Gatos, CA, USA, Chief Executive Officer and member of the Board of Directors, Zoox, Inc., Foster City, California, USA. In case of re-election, her term would expire in 2028.</li>
    <li><strong>Gerhard Oswald</strong> (70), Walldorf, Germany, Managing director, Oswald Consulting GmbH, Walldorf, Germany; Associate lecturer, Technical University of Munich, Munich, Germany. In case of re-election, his term would expire in 2026.</li>
    <li><strong>Dr. Friederike Rotsch</strong> (51), Königstein im Taunus, Germany, Group General Counsel, Deutsche Bank AG, Frankfurt, Germany. In case of re-election, her term would expire in 2028 and she would continue in the role of Lead Independent Director (LID).</li>
  </ul>
  <p>These nominations are in alignment with the Profile of Skills and Expertise, the Supervisory Board’s Diversity Policy, and the objectives set by the Supervisory Board for its own composition.</p>
  <p><strong>Note to holders of SAP ADRs (American Depositary Receipts):</strong><br>One SAP ADR represents one SAP SE share. The final dividend amount per ADR is dependent upon the euro/US dollar exchange rate. Since SAP SE pays cash dividends on the ordinary shares in euro, the exchange rate fluctuations will affect the US dollar amounts received by holders of ADRs. The final dividend payment by SAP SE to the depositary bank is scheduled for May 21, 2024. The depositary bank will then convert the dividend payment from euro into US dollars as promptly as practicable.</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>About SAP</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP’s strategy is to help every business run as an intelligent, sustainable enterprise. As a market leader in enterprise application software, we help companies of all sizes and in all industries run at their best: SAP customers generate 87% of total global commerce. Our machine learning, Internet of Things (IoT), and advanced analytics technologies help turn customers’ businesses into intelligent enterprises. SAP helps give people and organizations deep business insight and fosters collaboration that helps them stay ahead of their competition. We simplify technology for companies so they can consume our software the way they want – without disruption. Our end-to-end suite of applications and services enables business and public customers across 26 industries globally to operate profitably, adapt continuously, and make a difference. With a global network of customers, partners, employees, and thought leaders, SAP helps the world run better and improve people’s lives. For more information, visit <a href="http://www.sap.com">www.sap.com</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Note to editors:</strong><br>To preview and download broadcast-standard stock footage and press photos digitally, please visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/photos">www.sap.com/photos</a>. On this platform, you can find high resolution material for your media channels.</p>
  <p><strong>For customers interested in learning more about SAP products:</strong><br>Global Customer Center: +49 180 534-34-24<br>United States Only: 1 (800) 872-1SAP (1-800-872-1727)</p>
  <p><strong>For more information, financial community only:</strong><br>Anthony Coletta, +49 (6227) 7-60437, <a href="mailto:investor@sap.com">investor@sap.com</a>, CET<br>Follow SAP Investor Relations on <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-investor-relations">LinkedIn</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>For more information, press only:</strong><br>Joellen Perry, +1 (650) 445-6780, <a href="mailto:joellen.perry@sap.com">joellen.perry@sap.com</a>, PT<br>Daniel Reinhardt, +49 (6227) 7-40201, <a href="mailto:daniel.reinhardt@sap.com">daniel.reinhardt@sap.com</a>, CET<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>This document contains forward-looking statements, which are predictions, projections, or other statements about future events. These statements are based on current expectations, forecasts, and assumptions that are subject to risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results and outcomes to materially differ. Additional information regarding these risks and uncertainties may be found in our filings with the Securities and Exchange Commission, including but not limited to the risk factors section of SAP’s 2022 Annual Report on Form 20-F.<br>© 2024 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/investor-relations</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Further Strengthens Focus on AI with Dedicated Growth Area]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/sap-further-strengthens-ai-focus-dedicated-growth-area</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/sap-further-strengthens-ai-focus-dedicated-growth-area</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Philipp Herzig is the new SAP chief artificial intelligence officer (CAIO), leading a unit overseeing SAP Business AI. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pekka Ala-Pietilä Proposed by SAP Supervisory Board as Designated Successor to Chairman Hasso Plattner]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/pekka-ala-pietila-proposed-by-sap-supervisory-board-as-designated-successor-to-chairman-hasso-plattner</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/pekka-ala-pietila-proposed-by-sap-supervisory-board-as-designated-successor-to-chairman-hasso-plattner</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Pekka Ala-Pietilä has been nominated to stand for election as a new member of the Supervisory Board and successor to Hasso Plattner.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/investor-relations</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/investor-relations</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-investor-relations</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Kicking Off AI with SAP Sports One]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/ai-sap-sports-one-soccer-scouting-fc-bayern</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/ai-sap-sports-one-soccer-scouting-fc-bayern</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is expanding the SAP Sports One solution with with AI-powered scouting reporting. Learn more about the new features.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-sponsorships</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-sports</category>
            <category>product/sap-sports-one</category>
            <category>industry/sports-entertainment</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Announces Q4 and FY 2023 Results]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/sap-announces-q4-and-fy-2023-results</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/sap-announces-q4-and-fy-2023-results</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP SE announced today its financial results for the fourth quarter and fiscal year ended December 31, 2023.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1984fd48fa7c554f5d115cbe32c6e61bafdde4738.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1984fd48fa7c554f5d115cbe32c6e61bafdde4738.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1984fd48fa7c554f5d115cbe32c6e61bafdde4738.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Announces Q4 and FY 2023 Results" src="./media_1984fd48fa7c554f5d115cbe32c6e61bafdde4738.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-announces-q4-and-fy-2023-results">SAP Announces Q4 and FY 2023 Results</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> announced today its financial results for the fourth quarter and fiscal year ended December 31, 2023.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <ul>
    <li>SAP exceeds non-IFRS operating profit and cash flow outlook for FY 2023</li>
    <li>Cloud revenue up 20% and up 23% at constant currencies for FY 2023, underpinned by 25% cloud revenue growth at constant currencies in the fourth quarter</li>
    <li>Current cloud backlog of €13.7 billion, up 25% and up 27% at constant currencies</li>
    <li>IFRS cloud gross profit up 23%, non-IFRS cloud gross profit up 23% and up 27% at constant currencies in FY 2023</li>
    <li>IFRS operating profit down 5%, non-IFRS operating profit up 9% and up 13% at constant currencies in FY 2023</li>
    <li>2024 outlook anticipates accelerating cloud revenue growth</li>
    <li>Planned transformation program including restructuring in 2024 reflects focus on scalability of operations and Business AI</li>
    <li>2025 non-IFRS operating profit and free cash flow ambition updated to reflect updated non-IFRS definition as well as approximately half a billion Euro of incremental efficiency gains from the program</li>
  </ul>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div>SAP has delivered: We met or exceeded our outlook for 2023 in all key metrics. Based on a stellar order entry, our current cloud backlog expanded by 27% – an all-time high. We are confident about the company’s prospects in 2024. From this position of strength, SAP is opening the next chapter: with the planned transformation program, we are intensifying the shift of investments to strategic growth areas, above all Business AI. Going forward, this will empower us to keep leading with innovation while increasing the scalability of the operating model.</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>Christian Klein, CEO</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div>2023 was a year of inflection. We kept our promise and achieved double-digit non-IFRS operating profit growth despite an adverse macro environment. In 2024, we will focus on putting the right gradient of earnings growth in place to deliver on our raised ambition for 2025 and sustain growth and financial performance beyond.</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>Dominik Asam, CFO</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="https://www.sap.com/docs/download/investors/2023/sap-2023-q4-statement.pdf">Read the Quarterly Statement</a></p>
  <p><strong>Press Contacts:</strong><br>Joellen Perry, +1 (650) 445-6780, <a href="mailto:joellen.perry@sap.com">joellen.perry@sap.com</a>, PT<br>Daniel Reinhardt, +49 (6227) 7-40201, <a href="mailto:daniel.reinhardt@sap.com">daniel.reinhardt@sap.com</a>, CET</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/investor-relations</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/earnings</category>
            <category>news-tag/investor-relations</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-investor-relations</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>