<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/product/sap-litmos/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Francisco Partners Has Completed Acquisition of Litmos]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/francisco-partners-acquisition-of-litmos-complete</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/francisco-partners-acquisition-of-litmos-complete</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP SE and Francisco Partners (FP) have announced that the Litmos acquistion has been completed. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>product/sap-litmos</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Francisco Partners to Acquire Litmos from SAP]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/sap-litmos-acquisition-francisco-partners</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/sap-litmos-acquisition-francisco-partners</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Francisco Partners will acquire SAP Litmos, an established leader in the learning management system market. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>product/sap-litmos</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Join SAP for Litmos LIVE 2021]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/sap-litmos-live-learning-summit</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/sap-litmos-live-learning-summit</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Litmos LIVE brings together industry leader to discuss learning and development’s most pressing issues, top trends, and future outlook.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_167b315a253efec8ed028385d83bd1e0f3ae2f799.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_167b315a253efec8ed028385d83bd1e0f3ae2f799.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_167b315a253efec8ed028385d83bd1e0f3ae2f799.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Join SAP for Litmos LIVE 2021" src="./media_167b315a253efec8ed028385d83bd1e0f3ae2f799.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="join-sap-for-litmos-live-2021">Join SAP for Litmos LIVE 2021</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>SAP is excited to invite participants to <strong>Litmos LIVE</strong>, a global, corporate learning summit being held May 5. The gathering will bring together industry-leading analysts, thought leaders, and practitioners to discuss learning and development’s most pressing issues, top trends, and future outlook.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>This 100% virtual event is packed into a single day, with five tracks and 25 sessions. Attendees have the opportunity to pick and choose among live sessions as well as come back to those that have been recorded.</p>
  <p>On another exciting front, the SAP Litmos team has worked with with colleagues at <a href="https://www.litmos.com/litmos-live#agenda-keynote">SAP SuccessFactors and Qualtrics</a> for an insightful keynote on employee experience and diversity and inclusion, and have packed the program with many other timely talks by learning thought-leaders from Brandon Hall Group, Fosway Group, and Talented Learning.</p>
  <p>To provide a few other quick highlights from the agenda, attendees can join our head of Customer Experience for an open-forum <strong>Ask Me Anything</strong> session in the <a href="https://www.litmos.com/litmos-live#litmos-product-training">SAP Litmos product training track</a> and spend time with senior instructional designers for training on the most popular features, such as interface customization and in-solution content creation.</p>
  <p>We’ve assembled a <a href="https://www.litmos.com/litmos-live#featured-features">featured features track</a> for sessions on content and authoring, integrations, and a glimpse into the SAP Litmos road map, and are humbled to include some fantastic <a href="https://www.litmos.com/litmos-live#super-user-stories">customer</a> and <a href="https://www.litmos.com/litmos-live#litmos-extended-enterprise">partner</a> speakers who will tell their success stories. We’re still adding sessions and speakers to the <a href="https://www.litmos.com/litmos-live">agenda</a>, so check back for the latest schedule as the event nears. <strong><a href="https://vshow.on24.com/clients/SAP/2964750/?partnerref=sapblog">Register now</a></strong> to stay in the loop and receive reminders and other important communications.</p>
  <p>SAP Litmos develops e-learning solutions for top-performing companies. An established leader in the market since 2007, SAP Litmos offers one of the world’s easiest-to-use learning management system (LMS), SAP Litmos Training, and a comprehensive course library, SAP Litmos Training Content. Thousands of companies trust the solutions to centralize and deliver transformative training to employees, customers, and partners. SAP Litmos solutions are used by more than 24 million people in 150 countries, across 35 languages. Find more information at <a href="http://www.litmos.com">www.litmos.com</a>.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="register-now-for-litmos-live">Register now for Litmos LIVE</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://vshow.on24.com/clients/SAP/2964750/?partnerref=sapblog">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="register-today-for-litmos-live"><a href="https://vshow.on24.com/clients/SAP/2964750/?partnerref=sapblog">Register today for Litmos LIVE</a>.</h3>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Jennifer Kling is vice president of Marketing for SAP Litmos at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>product/sap-litmos</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Empowering Organizations with Virtual, Collaborative Learning]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/virtual-collaborative-learning-integrations</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/virtual-collaborative-learning-integrations</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[President of SAP SuccessFactors Jill Popelka discusses the need for collaborative learning integrations in virtual workplaces. Learn more!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1443c0a691083fd5ae2b2bff4cfedb4d993d2b6ab.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1443c0a691083fd5ae2b2bff4cfedb4d993d2b6ab.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1443c0a691083fd5ae2b2bff4cfedb4d993d2b6ab.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Empowering Organizations with Virtual, Collaborative Learning" src="./media_1443c0a691083fd5ae2b2bff4cfedb4d993d2b6ab.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="empowering-organizations-with-virtual-collaborative-learning">Empowering Organizations with Virtual, Collaborative Learning</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>With the need for greater collaboration in virtual environments, <a href="/2021/01/expanding-microsoft-sap-partnership">SAP recently introduced</a> several new integrations between Microsoft Teams and SAP solutions, including SAP SuccessFactors Learning. I spoke to SAP SuccessFactors President Jill Popelka to learn more about these integrations and hear her thoughts on why learning is becoming even more important and how SAP is innovating in this area.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><strong>Q: It goes without saying that the way we work has changed drastically over the last year. How has this impacted learning?</strong></p>
  <p><strong>A:</strong> Learning has never been more important. While learning has traditionally been essential for standard compliance and basic role training, it plays an increasingly critical role in helping companies drive the people and culture transformation required to adopt new business models and deliver new innovations. In fact, <a href="https://www2.deloitte.com/us/en/insights/focus/human-capital-trends.html">45 percent of executives</a> believe that building an organizational culture that celebrates growth, adaptability, and resilience is the most important action they can take to transform work.</p>
  <p>As companies continue to face unanticipated change and disruption, employees are being asked to take on additional tasks, expand responsibilities, and even work on new teams. Organizations need to support their people every step of the way, which includes delivering personalized, relevant learning opportunities that will empower them to be successful.</p>
  <p><strong>The ways in which people learn and how they consume information are also evolving. How is SAP adapting its learning solutions to keep pace with meeting the needs of the learner and the organization?</strong></p>
  <p>As the world of work changes so must our approach to educating and reskilling the workforce. In 2019, SAP identified <a href="/2020/10/experience-wins-hxm-market">human experience management</a> – or HXM – as the next market category for human resources (HR) technology. We recognized the need to evolve our solutions from focusing on just HR processes to delivering engaging, individualized employee experiences. Work may look different today, but intuitive, personalized experiences and technology that prioritizes human connection remain vital to success.</p>
  <p>When it comes to learning, we continue to make several updates to our solutions with HXM in mind. We introduced a <a href="/2020/10/advancing-hxm-innovations-sap-successfactors">redesigned experience</a> for <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/corporate-lms.html">SAP SuccessFactors Learning</a> in late 2020 to help boost engagement, deliver a more intuitive experience on web and mobile, and surface recommended learning courses. We recently launched an in-product course authoring tool within <a href="https://www.litmos.com/blog/articles/november-release-2011">SAP Litmos</a> to help organizations easily develop engaging courses and deliver the best possible learning experience. And finally, we launched <a href="/2020/10/sap-work-zone-hr-new-digital-workplace">SAP Work Zone for HR</a> to help include guided learning experiences to support employees during critical work and life events.</p>
  <p>With digital and virtual learning on the rise, it’s become more important to foster an environment where people can collaborate and share knowledge to build up skills quickly. We are enabling learners to easily find and consume learning content on any device, at any time by advancing our own solutions and tapping into our robust partner ecosystem. Placing learning in the immediate context of employees’ day-to-day activities can help create stronger collaboration and increase workplace productivity.</p>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_154ff721e11d9ba93953465de19bd6838f265dd88.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_154ff721e11d9ba93953465de19bd6838f265dd88.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_154ff721e11d9ba93953465de19bd6838f265dd88.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Creating a New Digital Workplace Experience with SAP Work Zone for HR" src="./media_154ff721e11d9ba93953465de19bd6838f265dd88.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://youtu.be/ztJliCgYPS4">Creating a New Digital Workplace Experience with SAP Work Zone for HR</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><strong>Speaking of your partner ecosystem, SAP and Microsoft recently expanded their partnership with new learning integrations. Can you tell us more about these innovations and what SAP customers can expect?</strong></p>
  <p>Many of our customers rely on Microsoft solutions to support collaboration across the business, and we want to seamlessly offer SAP solutions where we know employees can most naturally and seamlessly access them. <a href="https://word-edit.officeapps.live.com/we/aka.ms/vivalearningblog">Two new integrations</a> bring together SAP SuccessFactors Learning and Microsoft technologies, furthering our vision to make learning accessible when, where, and how individuals prefer.</p>
  <p>The first integration will make the course catalog within SAP SuccessFactors Learning accessible in Microsoft Viva. Learners can search for a course without having to switch applications and choose to either open it, share it, pin it to a channel, or add it to their own personal learning page in Microsoft Teams where they can access it at a later time. The second integration will help our customers foster learning communities, collaboration, and social learning by connecting SAP SuccessFactors Learning with Microsoft Teams. Learners can interact with other course participants or the instructor before, during, and after the course within Microsoft Teams, as well as access the activity feed on SAP SuccessFactors Learning.</p>
  <p><strong>What are you hearing from your customers about their current challenges with learning? How is SAP addressing these challenges?</strong></p>
  <p>We continue to speak with our customers about the importance of learning to the success of their people and their organizations. As business continues to grow and change, the number of platforms and sheer volume of content can become quite complex. Employees can become overwhelmed with the number of tools for learning and how they link back to their development or broader business goals. At the same time, organizations struggle to understand how learning is being consumed and applied.</p>
  <p>At SAP, our vision is to deliver unified access to all kinds of learning experiences – content-focused, experiential, and even from different vendors. Employees need to be able to access learning quickly and easily, effectively collaborate and connect with others, and share knowledge – anytime, anywhere, and across all different systems of work. Achieving this requires a personalized learning path with context-based recommendations that make it easy for employees to find relevant content and understand how their learning and skills contribute to the broader organization. We are reimagining learning so organizations can be more agile in the face of change, more resilient to ever-changing market dynamics, and more effective in driving employee and organizational transformation.</p>
  <p>Learn more about SAP SuccessFactors Learning and Microsoft integrations in the <em><a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/01/ca0f4c25-c87d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff.html">Collaborating for Success</a></em> e-book and <a href="https://ms-sap-immersive-v3.netlify.app/#/innovations/workplace-collaboration">Come Explore the Future</a> immersive website.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Samantha Yerks is global public relations lead for SAP SuccessFactors.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/future-of-work</category>
            <category>product/sap-litmos</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-learning</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>