<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/pledge-to-flex/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Future of Work Beyond Flex Work]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/future-of-work-beyond-flex-work</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/future-of-work-beyond-flex-work</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The future of work will go beyond flex work; we are just scratching the surface when it comes to the many opportunities. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1fe50fe3db75fc6d5437a22dc37e75d23a81dacf4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1fe50fe3db75fc6d5437a22dc37e75d23a81dacf4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1fe50fe3db75fc6d5437a22dc37e75d23a81dacf4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="The Future of Work Beyond Flex Work" src="./media_1fe50fe3db75fc6d5437a22dc37e75d23a81dacf4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="the-future-of-work-beyond-flex-work">The Future of Work Beyond Flex Work</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>For many, the introduction into a new world of work was driven by a focus on employee safety and business continuity in response to the pandemic. As we move forward into a post-pandemic era, organizations can finally shift their focus from crisis management to strategically thinking about the future of work. Now is the time to switch gears.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>It’s the heyday of flex-work models, but the future of work is so much more, with opportunities ready to be tackled along the spectrum of workforce transformation, new people practices, and next-generation HR models.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="the-mission-and-vision-of-saps-chief-future-of-work-officer">The Mission and Vision of SAP's Chief Future of Work Officer</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2022/07/christian-schmeichel-sap-chief-future-of-work-officer">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="saps-holistic-future-of-work-agenda-shaping-the-next-world-of-work">SAP’s Holistic Future of Work Agenda: Shaping the Next World of Work</h2>
  <p>Managing the future of work holistically is a strategic imperative to build a resilient, agile, and innovative organization that is future-fit for the digital age. As global provider of leading-edge human experience management (<a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/what-is-hxm-suite.html">HXM</a>) software, SAP has been putting its focus on designing a holistic future of work agenda that empowers its more than 100,000 people across the globe to thrive while creating value for its customers.</p>
  <p>The agenda is SAP’s north star to reimagine work at its core. It considers business elements and strategic HR components along three dimensions to create a sustainable work experience for its global and diverse workforce:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Future of Workforce</strong>, aiming to define a target picture for a future-proof workforce at SAP</li>
    <li><strong>Future of People Practices</strong>, making new, flexible, and healthy work “work” for everyone</li>
    <li><strong>Future of HR</strong>, reimagining the way how HR functions need to operate in future along a strategic HR master plan</li>
  </ul>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e04b008630c7dc9c8f6a1874d5435820627aa597.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e04b008630c7dc9c8f6a1874d5435820627aa597.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1e04b008630c7dc9c8f6a1874d5435820627aa597.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Infographic: SAP&#x27;s Future of Work agenda" src="./media_1e04b008630c7dc9c8f6a1874d5435820627aa597.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1986" height="1129">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p><em>Click to enlarge</em></p>
  <h2 id="future-proof-the-workforce">Future-Proof the Workforce</h2>
  <p>Accelerated digitalization and technology advances fuel the need for skill transformations across large portions of today’s workforce. The shift of skills as well as demographic changes result in a shortage of available talent, emphasizing the necessity of a clear understanding of future workforce demands. At the same time, this increases the competition for available talent in the market.</p>
  <p>SAP’s workforce transformation is based on scenario modeling to provide a clear understanding of what our workforce will need to look like five to 10 years down the road and how it will be composed. From these projections, we can derive a strategy to define the target picture with the right mix of permanent employees, gig workers, as well as the use of technology and <a href="/topics/artificial-intelligence">artificial intelligence</a> (AI). HR leaders play a crucial role by engaging in systematic resource planning in line with business strategy requirements.</p>
  <p>To future-proof their workforce, organizations need to prioritize continuous employee development through up- and reskilling. One example of this commitment is SAP’s internal talent marketplace, which offers project work, fellowships, or mentoring opportunities. Employees can take on respective assignments and apply their expertise where it is most needed while also acquiring new skills on the job: a win-win for everybody.</p>
  <h2 id="leading-edge-people-practices">Leading-Edge People Practices</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="what-is-human-experience-management">What is human experience management?</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/what-is-hxm-suite.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>People are the heartbeat of every organization. To meet ever-changing employee needs, organizations need to create innovative and effective strategies to attract, develop, engage, and retain top talent, as well as constantly challenge and evolve their people and workplace practices.</p>
  <p><strong>Empowerment Through Flexibility</strong> Flexibility is in more demand than ever, making it a strong lever for outstanding employee experience. With <a href="/topics/pledge-to-flex">Pledge to Flex</a>, SAP offers a hybrid work model that empowers employees to decide with their managers when, where, and how they work best in alignment with customer and business requirements.</p>
  <p>There is measurable success to the advantages of flexibility: SAP’s recent global future of work pulse survey revealed that over 80% of the workforce feel at least as or even more productive, satisfied, and engaged through hybrid work. The grand majority also believes that flexibility increases SAP’s attractiveness as employer.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c1940cbbe88ce3898664f0813f29bbe2f1039fc3.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c1940cbbe88ce3898664f0813f29bbe2f1039fc3.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1c1940cbbe88ce3898664f0813f29bbe2f1039fc3.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Infographic: Pledge to Flex continuum" src="./media_1c1940cbbe88ce3898664f0813f29bbe2f1039fc3.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1994" height="1127">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p><em>Click to enlarge</em></p>
  <p>Providing the best setup for every team with the right balance between office and remote work is one of the key elements in making hybrid work “work” for everyone. At the same time, the office remains the number one place to meet and support cultural affiliation, networking, and onboarding of new joiners.</p>
  <p>To promote SAP’s hybrid work approach with Pledge to Flex, we launched the internal “I’m In” campaign, encouraging employees to find the right ratio of in-office and remote work. At SAP, we see that a combination of splitting time between remote work and two to three days of in-person office work per week seems to be a good practice, given that it fosters team spirit, engagement, and excitement about the organization.</p>
  <p><strong>Enablement for a Successful Transition</strong> To navigate the added level of complexity in a hybrid landscape and build a routine, enablement and trainings are key. SAP supports employees, managers, and teams with hands-on tools and resources to balance team and individual needs while keeping customer requirements front and center.</p>
  <p>One example is the Flex Team Workshop, allowing leaders and team members to jointly determine the hybrid work setup that best fits their needs in terms of productivity, collaboration, work-life balance, and, of course, business and customer requirements. Additionally, the Meeting Workout toolkit is a gamified approach to review and declutter meetings, making each interaction more valuable to everyone. And with “Lighten the Load” and “Are you OK?,” SAP runs powerful personalized programs to enhance employee health and people sustainability, while providing stress relief.</p>
  <p>Leadership becomes more demanding in the new world of work. Leaders need to become even stronger facilitators when communicating direction and strategy in a hybrid environment. Critical skills to adjust to the evolving role of management include communicating and listening with empathy and being agile when connecting with people. Modern leadership today also includes to keep teams engaged and tackle Zoom fatigue in times of unprecedented change.</p>
  <h2 id="next-generation-hr">Next-Generation HR</h2>
  <p>A data-driven and agile HR approach is the foundation to bringing the future of workforce and people practices to life. With the help of leading-edge technology, the HR function can evolve while addressing the demand for scalable and flexible services to meet changing needs of employee and the business quickly and efficiently.</p>
  <p>Besides technological advancements, the required skills for the future HR function will evolve as well. SAP focuses on a set of key themes:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Experience management in HR, emphasizing the needs of employees, managers, or applicants from a HR consumer point of view</li>
    <li>Data-driven HR, leveraging advanced analytics to solve talent and organization related business problems and support decision-making</li>
    <li>Digital HR to reap the fruits of technological advances across the entire employee life cycle</li>
    <li>Agile HR, applying an agile mindset, values, principles, practices, and tools when serving the business</li>
  </ul>
  <p>Capabilities like digital savviness, analytical skills, data interpretation, and an agile mindset will become must-have skills for successful HR work in the new era.</p>
  <h2 id="stay-curious-and-keep-learning">Stay Curious and Keep Learning</h2>
  <p>Looking ahead, it is fair to say that we are just scratching the surface when it comes to the many opportunities to shape the future of work. With an industry-leading hybrid work model in place, SAP built a strong foundation to tackle the workplace evolution as part of a holistic future of work agenda.</p>
  <p>Getting the triad of future workforce planning, people practices, and next generation HR teams right sets the path to make organizations more future-ready while the world around us is changing at breakneck speed. In the end it all comes down to continuously learning and discovering what works best for the creation of outstanding employee experiences while driving sustainable business success — truly exciting times for HR!</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Dr. Christian Schmeichel is chief future of work officer at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/future-of-work</category>
            <category>news-tag/mental-health-well-being</category>
            <category>news-tag/pledge-to-flex</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pledge to Flex: Empowerment in the Future of Work]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/pledge-to-flex-empowerment-new-world-of-work</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/pledge-to-flex-empowerment-new-world-of-work</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Success in the new world of work requires a flexible and trust-based working environment. Learn what SAP is doing.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/future-of-work</category>
            <category>news-tag/mental-health-well-being</category>
            <category>news-tag/pledge-to-flex</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-apphaus</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Holistic Future of Work Agenda for SAP: Mission and Vision of Chief Future of Work Officer Christian Schmeichel]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/christian-schmeichel-sap-chief-future-of-work-officer</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/christian-schmeichel-sap-chief-future-of-work-officer</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[What kind of work environment can SAP employees expect in the future? SAP's Chief Future of Work Officer Christian Schmeichel explains.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/future-of-work</category>
            <category>news-tag/mental-health-well-being</category>
            <category>news-tag/pledge-to-flex</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Eye-Tracking: Control Your Computer with Your Gaze]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/eye-tracking-control-computer-with-gaze</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/eye-tracking-control-computer-with-gaze</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Aug 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Eye-tracking solutions support ergonomic work and accessibility. A solution from partner 4tiitoo offers SAP employees just that. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ab1214d045a6406f722cc1b99b0f533e397f7cf1.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ab1214d045a6406f722cc1b99b0f533e397f7cf1.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1ab1214d045a6406f722cc1b99b0f533e397f7cf1.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Eye-Tracking: Control Your Computer with Your Gaze" src="./media_1ab1214d045a6406f722cc1b99b0f533e397f7cf1.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="eye-tracking-control-your-computer-with-your-gaze">Eye-Tracking: Control Your Computer with Your Gaze</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Historically, exceptional situations always give innovations a nudge. When the <a href="/covid-19">pandemic</a> hit, companies of all sizes and areas of business had to rethink the ways their workforce would work best in the ‘new normal.’</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Many companies have always been investing heavily in how their workforce can work best, whether they are developers, sales and services employees, or in administration. Each has individual needs, but what they all have in common is that they need access to a computer in order to fulfill their tasks. They use a keyboard, a mouse, and touch as the de-facto, standard interaction with the machine. This technology hasn’t evolved much over recent years.</p>
  <p>At offices, we are used to working according to ergonomic standards whereas in our home offices we may not have these standards available.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="how-ai-and-gaze-control-will-help-businesses-reopen-safely">How AI and Gaze Control Will Help Businesses Reopen Safely</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2020/05/ai-gaze-control-help-businesses-reopen">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="next-generation-of-user-experience--from-touch-less-to-touchless">Next Generation of User Experience – From ‘Touch Less’ to ‘Touchless’</h2>
  <p>Did you know that, on average, 25% of a work day is spent using a mouse, accounting for thousands of clicks and scrolls? We switch between the keyboard and mouse up to 2,000 times per day. In an internal pilot at SAP with 35 users from different departments, almost 500 kilometers of mouse-movement distance was measured within six weeks.</p>
  <p>This not only costs a lot of time but also causes stress-related diseases, such as repetitive strain injuries (RSI), also known as ‘mouse arm.’</p>
  <p>With the eye-tracking solution NUIA from SAP partner <a href="/2020/05/ai-gaze-control-help-businesses-reopen">4tiitoo GmbH Munich</a>, it is possible to provide an innovative tool to employees, working to address their ergonomic situation, reduce mouse movements and mouse-keyboard swaps, and improve efficiency and appearance during customer calls.</p>
  <p>All SAP colleagues can order this solution to use in the office and even their home offices.</p>
  <p>Following its <a href="/wp-content/blogs.dir/1/files/2021/06/01/pledge-to-flex.pdf">pledge to flex</a>, SAP’s future of work plans include monitors equipped with eye-trackers by default and the ability to download necessary software just by scanning a QR code.</p>
  <h2 id="eye-tracking-supports-accessibility">Eye-Tracking Supports Accessibility</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="eye-tracking-startup-co-innovates-with-sap">Eye-Tracking Startup Co-Innovates with SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2019/02/video-eyetracking-startup-co-innovates-sap">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP supports individual accessibility needs above the standard functionalities with this interaction opportunity, which perfectly matches <a href="https://www.thevaluable500.com/company/sap/">SAP’s Valuable 500 commitment</a> for an inclusive workplace.</p>
  <p>“People are the most important resource we have in technology,” says Sabine Bendiek, chief people and operating officer and member of the Executive Board of SAP SE. “Therefore, people have to be put at the center. It should always be about doing the right thing for people, empowering them to thrive.”</p>
  <p>The User Experience EMEA Services Team has the eye-tracking expertise and works together with 4tiitoo. The team covers even more advanced use cases, such as completely touchless, gaze-controlled scenarios, and is ready to provide SAP customers with tailored services around this innovation topic. One of those is now live within SAP Labs Munich at Munich Urban Colab, working with the Technical University of Munich.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em><a href="/germany/2021/08/computerbedienung-eyetracking-blicksteuerung">This story also appeared on the German SAP News Center.</a></em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>news-tag/pledge-to-flex</category>
            <category>news-tag/ux</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pledge to Flex: The Future of Work at SAP Is 100% Flexible and Trust Based]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2021/06/pledge-to-flex-future-of-work-at-sap</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2021/06/pledge-to-flex-future-of-work-at-sap</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP's pledge to flex is designed to ensure employees have what they need to be productive, creative, and inspired in a post-COVID world.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18a61b5b4abe3e166ea57a57df98ae8928bee19c8.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18a61b5b4abe3e166ea57a57df98ae8928bee19c8.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_18a61b5b4abe3e166ea57a57df98ae8928bee19c8.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Pledge to Flex: The Future of Work at SAP Is 100% Flexible and Trust Based" src="./media_18a61b5b4abe3e166ea57a57df98ae8928bee19c8.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="pledge-to-flex-the-future-of-work-at-sap-is-100-flexible-and-trust-based">Pledge to Flex: The Future of Work at SAP Is 100% Flexible and Trust Based</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-at-newssapcompledge-to-flex">Learn more at news.sap.com/pledge-to-flex</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/wp-content/blogs.dir/1/files/2021/06/01/pledge-to-flex.pdf">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>As vaccinations increase and <a href="/covid-19">COVID-19</a> restrictions ease, companies across the globe are revisiting their work policies to address employee feedback for greater flexibility. The global shift to working from home has led to new employee preferences and better understanding of how productivity and collaboration can successfully continue despite working remotely.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP has embraced a location-agnostic work style for decades. By doing this, we have built a truly global workforce and supported employees with mobile technology to enable work to happen from anywhere, anytime.</p>
  <p>Our recent employee surveys on work style post-COVID show that this continued work flexibility is desired. Over 80% of SAP employees say they want a mix of working from home or remote with some time in the office.</p>
  <p>Today, SAP is building on our proven ways of remote work that our​ ​employees have enjoyed across the world for decades into a new global framework that is entirely flexible and trust based. We continue to believe in​ ​a workplace based on​ ​trust and empowerment​ ​because employees are​ ​at the heart of what we do.</p>
  <p>Today, SAP pledges to provide a setup that fits every​ ​role, style, and location with:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>A 100% flexible and trust-based workplace as the norm, not the​ ​exception</li>
    <li>An inclusive environment in which people can work from home, at the office, or remotely, so everyone is​ ​empowered to run at their personal best, driving success for SAP’s customers</li>
    <li>Flexible work schedules, so employees can decide​ ​when they work aligned with business needs</li>
    <li>Inspiring office designs tailored for creativity, collaboration, community, ​and focused work, enabling​ ​employees to find the right space for every task</li>
    <li>Office buildings that prioritize ​sustainability and health</li>
    <li>An approach that meets local regulations across the many regions where our employees work</li>
  </ul>
  <p>Our pledge to flex is designed to ensure employees have what they need to be productive, creative, and inspired while running the business responsibly and meeting business requirements. And, as we have seen in industry surveys, women and recent graduates particularly desire and benefit from a flexible work environment. With our pledge, we hope and believe SAP will be a preferred company for these groups of valuable employees.</p>
  <p>A centerpiece of SAP’s flexible work approach is our technology. <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm.html">SAP SuccessFactors software</a> provides an end-to-end human experience management (HXM) solution from employees’ onboarding throughout their career development – improving engagement, growth, and retention wherever they work. Qualtrics enables us to stay connected with employee sentiment by providing instant visibility into the employee’s lived experience across the globe. To enable easy and smooth collaboration regardless of where people are located, we are working on <a href="/2021/01/sap-and-microsoft-expand-partnership-integrate-teams">integration of Microsoft Teams</a> across our portfolio, allowing a broader choice of access tools.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_13cb51f3b37d9b0ae998caea937438ba3c74cb364.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_13cb51f3b37d9b0ae998caea937438ba3c74cb364.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_13cb51f3b37d9b0ae998caea937438ba3c74cb364.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP&#x27;s pledge to flex: the future of work" src="./media_13cb51f3b37d9b0ae998caea937438ba3c74cb364.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="625" height="328">
    </picture><br><a href="/wp-content/blogs.dir/1/files/2021/06/01/pledge-to-flex.pdf">/wp-content/blogs.dir/1/files/2021/06/01/pledge-to-flex.pdf</a>
  </p>
  <p><em>Click to enlarge</em></p>
  <p>At SAP, we are honored and humbled to be chosen multiple times as employer of choice in the countries where we are located. Our pledge to flex is another expression of our profound respect for our employees.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Christian Klein is CEO of SAP SE.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/blog/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/blog/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/blog/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/blog/article-read-more</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/executive-blog</category>
            <category>news-tag/covid-19</category>
            <category>news-tag/future-of-work</category>
            <category>news-tag/pledge-to-flex</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>