<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/gartner/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Named a Leader in the Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Warehouse Management Systems for the 11th Consecutive Year]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/sap-a-leader-2024-gartner-magic-quadrant-wms</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/sap-a-leader-2024-gartner-magic-quadrant-wms</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[For the 11th time, SAP is a Leader in the Magic Quadrant for WMS, based on ability to execute and for the completeness of vision. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ac123a0a67e3b19450c432a63245f50c1e68b889.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ac123a0a67e3b19450c432a63245f50c1e68b889.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1ac123a0a67e3b19450c432a63245f50c1e68b889.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Named a Leader in the Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Warehouse Management Systems for the 11th Consecutive Year" src="./media_1ac123a0a67e3b19450c432a63245f50c1e68b889.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-named-a-leader-in-the-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-warehouse-management-systems-for-the-11th-consecutive-year">SAP Named a Leader in the Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Warehouse Management Systems for the 11th Consecutive Year</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>SAP has been named as a Leader in the 2024 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Warehouse Management Systems. For the 11th consecutive year, SAP is positioned in the Leaders quadrant based on Ability to Execute and Completeness of Vision.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>We believe that this recognition confirms our strategy in logistics, which is based on three pillars:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Connecting every process to facilitate synchronized logistics execution, supporting highly efficient and fast-paced fulfillment cycles through seamless integration with logistics applications like SAP Transportation Management, SAP Business Network for Logistics, etc.</li>
    <li>Collaborating within a diverse ecosystem of system integrators, software partners, hyperscalers, hardware partners, and robotics OEMs, with warehouse management being an integral part of cloud ERP.</li>
    <li>Contextualizing every decision leveraging artificial intelligence (AI) and machine learning to optimize operations and to provide business insights</li>
  </ul>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="keep-pace-with-demand-minimize-costs-and-maintain-sustainable-risk-resilient-warehouse-operations">Keep pace with demand, minimize costs, and maintain sustainable, risk-resilient warehouse operations</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/extended-warehouse-management.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/extended-warehouse-management.html">SAP Extended Warehouse Management</a> (SAP EWM) is an integral part of the overall SAP strategy and gives companies the ability to operate modern warehouses that must respond quickly to changing business conditions. The flexibility of SAP EWM helps manage a high volume of goods and run sustainable, risk-resilient operations with digitized warehouse processes in the cloud including direct control of warehouse automation equipment.</p>
  <p>SAP continues to innovate in SAP EWM based on market analysis and even more importantly based on feedback from our global install base and ecosystem. Recent innovations include cross-process integration in the areas of transportation, production, and quality management, addressing industry-specific requirements, extensibility, and usability.</p>
  <p>SAP EWM combined with SAP Transportation Management and SAP Business Network for Logistics provides a platform for companies to collaborate with their logistics partners to gain end-to-end visibility and insights across their logistics operations.</p>
  <p>Our global partner network — made up of systems integrators, business consultants, and technology providers — helps our customers manage their warehouse management transformations, whether they be system replacements, upgrades, greenfield deployments, or part of larger enterprise transformations.</p>
  <p>“Warehouse Management with SAP EWM is an integral part of our cloud ERP offering,” said Till Dengel, global head of Logistics and Manufacturing Product Marketing at SAP. “Customers use SAP EWM to manage their warehouse operations in 66 countries and 24 industries.”</p>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div>SAP Extended Warehouse Management helped Bridgestone reduce errors, with a new level of productivity and safety.</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>Eric Dyason, National Distribution Manager, Bridgestone New Zealand Ltd.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/extended-warehouse-management.html?campaigncode=CRM-YD24-DSC-2695614&#x26;url_id=magic-quadrant-for-warehouse-management-systems&#x26;rc=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.gartner.com%2Freprints%2F%3Fid%3D1-2HGS0BJ4%26ct%3D240502%26st%3Dsb">Get more details on the latest</a><br><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/extended-warehouse-management.html?campaigncode=CRM-YD24-DSC-2695614&#x26;url_id=magic-quadrant-for-warehouse-management-systems&#x26;rc=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.gartner.com%2Freprints%2F%3Fid%3D1-2HGS0BJ4%26ct%3D240502%26st%3Dsb">Gartner Magic Quadrant for WMS here</a>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Ganesh Wadawadigi is chief product marketing owner for Logistics at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>*Gartner, Magic Quadrant for Warehouse Management Systems, Simon Tunstall, Dwight Klappich, Rishabh Narang, Federica Stufano, 2 May 2024</p>
  <p>GARTNER is a registered trademark and service mark of Gartner, Inc. and/or its affiliates in the U.S. and internationally, MAGIC QUADRANT is a registered trademark of Gartner, Inc. and/or its affiliates and are used herein with permission. All rights reserved.<br>Gartner does not endorse any vendor, product or service depicted in its research publications, and does not advise technology users to select only those vendors with the highest ratings or other designation. Gartner research publications consist of the opinions of Gartner’s research organization and should not be construed as statements of fact. Gartner disclaims all warranties, expressed or implied, with respect to this research, including any warranties of merchantability or fitness for a particular purpose.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/magic-quadrant</category>
            <category>product/sap-extended-warehouse-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Signavio Is a Leader in the 2024 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Process Mining Platforms]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/sap-signavio-a-leader-2024-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-process-mining-platforms</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/sap-signavio-a-leader-2024-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-process-mining-platforms</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In the 2024 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Process Mining, SAP Signavio has again been recognized as a Leader. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_138b3ef0b5b24b564b18da25ef3b2cde982bba0f8.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_138b3ef0b5b24b564b18da25ef3b2cde982bba0f8.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_138b3ef0b5b24b564b18da25ef3b2cde982bba0f8.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Signavio Is a Leader in the 2024 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Process Mining Platforms" src="./media_138b3ef0b5b24b564b18da25ef3b2cde982bba0f8.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-signavio-is-a-leader-in-the-2024-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-process-mining-platforms">SAP Signavio Is a Leader in the 2024 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Process Mining Platforms</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>In the 2024 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Process Mining, SAP Signavio has once again been recognized as a Leader in the market based on Completeness of Vision and Ability to Execute.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="complimentary-copy-2024-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-process-mining-platforms">Complimentary copy: 2024 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Process Mining Platforms</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.signavio.com/downloads/analyst-reports/2024-gartner-magic-quadrant-process-mining/">Download yours here</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>This is the second year in a row that SAP Signavio has been positioned as a Leader in the report. We believe that this positioning implies that SAP Signavio is a key driver for SAP’s growth and long-term strategy.</p>
  <p>According to the Gartner Magic Quadrant research methodology, “Leaders execute well against their current vision and are well positioned for tomorrow.”</p>
  <p>Our solutions solve today’s real and diverse customer use cases — operational excellence, compliance, automation, transformation, etc.– and recognizes that we have a compelling vision for a future in which process automation and process AI open up new opportunities for our customers and partners.</p>
  <p>SAP Signavio continues to focus on ensuring the long-term success of all of our customers and partners.</p>
  <h2 id="revenue-nsw">Revenue NSW</h2>
  <p>In the Australian state of New South Wales, the tax collected by Revenue NSW accounts for more than 35% of finances, helping fund essential services, from healthcare to education and policing.</p>
  <p>With a vision to be the world’s most innovative and customer-centric revenue agency, Revenue NSW set out with a very specific objective: it wanted to analyze cases in which clients had overpaid land tax to identify why these overpayments occur and what experience clients received when obtaining refunds. This analysis would not only help reduce overpayment volumes and improve the client experience, but also enable the agency to work more efficiently for its diverse stakeholders.</p>
  <p>“As part of our Aspire 2032 strategy, our vision is to be the world’s most innovative and customer-centric revenue collection agency,” shared Jocelyn Yem, director of Strategy and Innovation at Revenue NSW.”‘Embrace Innovation’ is one of our strategic focus areas, where we can respond to our customers’ needs by embedding a culture of continuous improvement. SAP Signavio Process Intelligence has helped us achieve our first stage in this journey.”</p>
  <p>“SAP Signavio Process Intelligence has painted a clear picture of why clients pay too much land tax and how we can process refunds smoothly, along with a detailed road map to help us put these insights into action,” confirmed Sabrina Bazouni, director of Land Tax at Revenue NSW.</p>
  <h2 id="fujitsu-limited">Fujitsu Limited</h2>
  <p>Recognizing the wide-ranging effect of business process transformation solutions, Fujitsu Limited has embraced SAP Signavio solutions across its operations and portfolio.</p>
  <p>At one of its manufacturing plants in Japan, Fujitsu used the SAP Signavio Process Intelligence solution to gather process execution data directly from the shop floor into the continuous improvement model the company had been using for many years. Integrating process data into the Kaizen discussions delivered never-before-seen insights, which helped the company further optimize its shop-floor processes and transform their Kaizen from traditional to digital, using process mining to generate data-driven insights.</p>
  <p>This firsthand experience of the solutions has also allowed Fujitsu to enrich its customer offerings with new frameworks, insights, and tools that can help customers realign their organizations and make changes at speed.</p>
  <p>Having seen the potential of SAP Signavio solutions, Fujitsu now plans to extend its use both internally and externally. One such planned initiative involves combining the concepts of the digital twin on an organization and the intelligent enterprise, using business process transformation solutions as the mechanism of change.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Download a <a href="https://www.signavio.com/downloads/analyst-reports/2024-gartner-magic-quadrant-process-mining/">complimentary copy of the report here</a>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Dee Houchen is global head of Market Impact for SAP Signavio.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="optimize-and-transform-business-processes-fast-and-at-scale">Optimize and transform business processes fast and at scale</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-process-transformation.html">Learn how</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Gartner, Magic Quadrant for Process Mining Platforms, Marc Kerremans, David Sugden, Nick Duffy, 29 April 2024</p>
  <p>GARTNER is a registered trademark and service mark of Gartner, Inc. and/or its affiliates in the U.S. and internationally, and MAGIC QUADRANT is a registered trademark of Gartner, Inc. and/or its affiliates and are used herein with permission. All rights reserved. Gartner does not endorse any vendor, product or service depicted in its research publications, and does not advise technology users to select only those vendors with the highest ratings or other designation. Gartner research publications consist of the opinions of Gartner’s research organization and should not be construed as statements of fact. Gartner disclaims all warranties, expressed or implied, with respect to this research, including any warranties of merchantability or fitness for a particular purpose.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/business-process-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/magic-quadrant</category>
            <category>news-tag/process-mining</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-signavio</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Named a Leader in the 2024 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Transportation Management Systems]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-named-a-leader-2024-gartner-magic-quadrant-transportation-management-systems</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-named-a-leader-2024-gartner-magic-quadrant-transportation-management-systems</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[For the 10th consecutive year, SAP has been named as a Leader in the 2024 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Transportation Management Systems.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_129328166e826d3a52e6b9854f483cc4a5f36fd9a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_129328166e826d3a52e6b9854f483cc4a5f36fd9a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_129328166e826d3a52e6b9854f483cc4a5f36fd9a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Named a Leader in the 2024 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Transportation Management Systems" src="./media_129328166e826d3a52e6b9854f483cc4a5f36fd9a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-named-a-leader-in-the-2024-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-transportation-management-systems">SAP Named a Leader in the 2024 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Transportation Management Systems</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>For the 10th consecutive year, SAP has been named as a Leader in the 2024 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Transportation Management Systems.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP is positioned in the Leaders Quadrant based on our Ability to Execute and for the Completeness of our Vision.</p>
  <p>We believe that this recognition confirms our strategy in Logistics, which is based on three pillars:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Connecting every process and providing synchronized logistics execution to support highly efficient and fast paced fulfillment cycles</li>
    <li>Collaborating with a single network of carriers, digital forwarders, and visibility providers to spot risks and avoid disruptions and thereby provide best-in-class delivery experience</li>
    <li>Contextualizing every decision, leveraging artificial intelligence (<a href="/topics/artificial-intelligence">AI</a>) and machine learning to optimize operations and to provide business insights</li>
  </ul>
  <p>SAP Transportation Management is an integral part of the overall SAP strategy and gives companies the ability to manage their end-to-end transportation processes from procurement through planning and execution to freight settlement with analytics to support each step.</p>
  <p>We continue to innovate in SAP Transportation Management based on our market analysis and even more importantly based on feedback from our global install base and ecosystem. Recent innovations include advancements in areas like sustainability, planning and optimization, supply chain execution, and generative AI.</p>
  <p>SAP Transportation Management and SAP Business Network for Logistics enable logistics partners to collaborate with each other and provide visibility to all stakeholders throughout the shipment lifecycle and help manage risks as they arise through intelligent insights. We continue to grow SAP Business Network, adding more carriers and additional networks to provide expanded coverage around the world and across all transportation modes.</p>
  <p>As more customers evaluate SAP Transportation Management, we continue to strategically expand our partner network to ensure our customers have access to an ecosystem that supports their operations no matter where they are in the world or how they move their freight. Our global partner network made up of systems integrators, business consultants, and technology providers help our customers manage their transportation transformations, whether they be system replacements, upgrades, greenfield deployments, or part of larger enterprise transformations.</p>
  <p>“Our customers use SAP Transportation Management and SAP Business Network for Logistics to manage transportation operations in more than 20 industries and in every corner of the world,” said Till Dengel, global head of Logistics and Manufacturing Product Marketing at SAP. “Because we look at logistics holistically, clients can confidently confirm their orders, knowing that fulfillment can be executed as promised, since ERP, warehousing, and transportation are always in sync.”</p>
  <p>“Adopting logistics solutions from SAP across our facilities in all our markets allowed us to optimize freight transportation,” said Carlo Noè, Global Process and Applications Manager for Trade, Transport, and Logistics Division at Hitachi Energy Ltd. “We can interact with our stakeholders and carriers in a digital way, helping us manage supply chain risk, enhance agility, and build supply chain resilience.”</p>
  <p>For more details on the latest Gartner Magic Quadrant for TMS <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/transportation-logistics.html?campaigncode=CRM-YD24-DSC-2678872&#x26;url_id=magic-quadrant-for-transportation-management-systems&#x26;rc=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.gartner.com%2Freprints%2F%3Fid%3D1-2H3J1JVF%26ct%3D240327%26st%3Dsb">read the Gartner Reprint here</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Bill King is senior product marketing manager for Logistics at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-transportation-management-reduce-complexity-increase-efficiency-and-improve-agility-for-a-more-sustainable-risk-resilient-supply-chain">SAP Transportation Management: Reduce complexity, increase efficiency, and improve agility for a more sustainable, risk-resilient supply chain</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/transportation-logistics.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>GARTNER is a registered trademark and service mark of Gartner, Inc. and/or its affiliates in the U.S. and internationally, MAGIC QUADRANT is a registered trademark of Gartner, Inc. and/or its affiliates and are used herein with permission. All rights reserved.<br><em>Gartner does not endorse any vendor, product or service depicted in its research publications, and does not advise technology users to select only those vendors with the highest ratings or other designation. Gartner research publications consist of the opinions of Gartner’s research organization and should not be construed as statements of fact. Gartner disclaims all warranties, expressed or implied, with respect to this research, including any warranties of merchantability or fitness for a particular purpose.</em></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/travel-transportation</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/magic-quadrant</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-network-for-logistics</category>
            <category>product/sap-transportation-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Named Leader in the 2024 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for iPaaS for Fourth Consecutive Time]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/sap-named-leader-2024-gartner-magic-quadrant-ipaas</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/sap-named-leader-2024-gartner-magic-quadrant-ipaas</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP was named a Leader in the 2024 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Integration Platform as a Service (iPaaS) for the fourth consecutive time.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11e0cc32a99eaafa84b0f392021aac0d9ea3ac792.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11e0cc32a99eaafa84b0f392021aac0d9ea3ac792.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_11e0cc32a99eaafa84b0f392021aac0d9ea3ac792.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Named Leader in the 2024 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for iPaaS for Fourth Consecutive Time" src="./media_11e0cc32a99eaafa84b0f392021aac0d9ea3ac792.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-named-leader-in-the-2024-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-ipaas-for-fourth-consecutive-time">SAP Named Leader in the 2024 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for iPaaS for Fourth Consecutive Time</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>We are proud to announce SAP has been recognized as a Leader in the 2024 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Integration Platform as a Service (iPaaS) with SAP Integration Suite for the fourth consecutive time.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>We believe this prestigious recognition is a testament to our current capabilities, ongoing innovation, and commitment to providing world-class integration solutions for customers.</p>
  <h2 id="unparalleled-recognition-in-ipaas">Unparalleled Recognition in iPaaS</h2>
  <p>The Gartner Magic Quadrant provides an overview of the technology vendors in the iPaaS market and positions them according to their Ability to Execute and Completeness of Vision. According to Gartner, “Leaders have a deep understanding of the iPaaS market. They have a record of strong execution and an ability to influence the market’s direction. Leaders have a clear product road map to solidify the product’s position and to help buyers protect their investments. In <a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/dg/integration-platform-as-a-service-leader/index.html">the latest report</a>, SAP is positioned as a Leader again.”</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="unleash-the-power-of-connectivity-and-innovation-with-sap-integration-suite">Unleash the power of connectivity and innovation with SAP Integration Suite</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/integration-suite.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The ability for an organization to connect and automate its business applications faster and in new ways is critical in today’s digital world. SAP customers are seeking a robust integration solution to support their innovation and modernization initiatives. We believe this recognition serves as validation of our commitment to delivering industry-leading solutions that can empower businesses to seamlessly connect their applications, data, and processes.</p>
  <h2 id="a-winning-combination-of-technology-and-expertise">A Winning Combination of Technology and Expertise</h2>
  <p>SAP’s vision for SAP Integration Suite is to connect and automate business processes. As the key integration technology of <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform.html">SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP)</a>, SAP Integration Suite can empower customers to achieve seamless, scalable business processes without disruption. Its user-friendly interface, extensive library of proven prebuilt content for SAP and non-SAP applications, and robust security features help make it easy for customers to jump-start their integrations.</p>
  <p>Organizations across the globe have embraced SAP Integration Suite to help support automation of business processes, streamline operations, and strengthen their collaboration with partners and customers. Take <a href="https://www.sap.com/asset/dynamic/2024/01/6a507734-a27e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Pitney Bowes</a> for example. It wanted a solution to support its transformation from selling stand-alone products to offering holistic solutions that orchestrate physical delivery, installation, and support while minimizing the need for customization and providing growth for the company.</p>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div>Using SAP Integration Suite, part of SAP BTP, to integrate SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition with SAP Sales Cloud and third-party providers, we’re simplifying and standardizing business processes, increasing agility, and supporting our growth ambitions in select countries.</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>Stuart Beadle, Senior Director, Global Order Management, Supply Chain Applications and SAP Service, Pitney Bowes Inc.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Customer experience is one of the criteria evaluated by Gartner in the report for the ability to execute. According to the report, “Relationships, products, and services/programs that enable clients to be successful with the products are evaluated. Specifically, this includes the ways customers receive technical support or account support. This can also include ancillary tools, customer support programs (and the quality thereof), availability of user groups, service-level agreements, and so on.”</p>
  <p>See <a href="https://www.gartner.com/reviews/market/integration-platform-as-a-service-worldwide/vendor/sap/product/sap-integration-suite">Gartner Peer Insights</a> to read the reviews.</p>
  <h2 id="learn-more">Learn More</h2>
  <p><a href="/topics/sap-integration-suite">SAP Integration Suite</a> can accelerate innovation, speed connectivity, and connect everyone to automated processes. We remain steadfast in providing powerful and reliable integration solutions. To learn more:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/dg/integration-platform-as-a-service-leader/index.html">Read the full report</a></li>
    <li>Explore exclusive iPaaS content on <a href="https://gateway.on24.com/wcc/eh/3869277/integration-space">SAP’s integration space</a></li>
    <li><a href="https://discovery-center.cloud.sap/serviceCatalog/integration-suite?region=all&#x26;category=all">Get started for free</a> with SAP Integration Suite</li>
    <li>Learn more about <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/integration-suite.html">SAP Integration Suite</a></li>
  </ul>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>JG Chirapurath is chief marketing and solutions officer for SAP BTP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-sap-news-delivered-to-your-inbox-once-a-week">Get the latest SAP news delivered to your inbox once a week</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/nl/sap-news-center-newsletter/index.html">Sign up today</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Gartner, Magic Quadrant for Integration Platform as a Service 19 February 2024, Keith Guttridge Et Al.<br>Gartner does not endorse any vendor, product or service depicted in its research publications and does not advise technology users to select only those vendors with the highest ratings or other designation. Gartner research publications consist of the opinions of Gartner’s research organization and should not be construed as statements of fact. Gartner disclaims all warranties, expressed or implied, with respect to this research, including any warranties of merchantability or fitness for a particular purpose.<br>GARTNER is a registered trademark and service mark of Gartner and Magic Quadrant is a registered trademark of Gartner, Inc. and/or its affiliates in the U.S. and internationally and are used herein with permission. All rights reserved.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-integration-suite</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[What Industry Analysts Say About SAP Sustainability]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/what-industry-analysts-say-about-sap-sustainability</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/what-industry-analysts-say-about-sap-sustainability</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Industry analysts assess the sustainability performance of companies across industries. Learn about what they had to say about SAP.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e36ed2496934d2a62eef72bc90f762db5c48d221.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e36ed2496934d2a62eef72bc90f762db5c48d221.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1e36ed2496934d2a62eef72bc90f762db5c48d221.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="What Industry Analysts Say About SAP Sustainability" src="./media_1e36ed2496934d2a62eef72bc90f762db5c48d221.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="what-industry-analysts-say-about-sap-sustainability">What Industry Analysts Say About SAP Sustainability</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>For nearly 15 years, SAP has committed to being a <a href="/topics/sustainability">sustainability</a> leader both in our operations and through our sustainability product offerings for customers. Industry analysts review and assess the sustainability performance of companies across industries. SAP has recently been assessed by some of the most important analyst firms for both our own sustainability performance and the sustainability solutions we offer customers.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Gartner, an independent analyst firm, recently published a report titled “<a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/dg/sap-rated-positively-in-sustainability/index.html">Sustainability Assessment: SAP</a>.” A report from analyst firm IDC earlier this year, “Sustainability Index for Software Providers: SAP”, noted SAP performed “exceptionally well.” The published <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2023/05/d2950cf3-737e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.rc.html?campaigncode=CRM-Y23-IMM-21123823">IDC report</a> highlights how SAP is leading by example as a sustainable vendor.</p>
  <p>It’s abundantly clear that businesses need to urgently address sustainability challenges. Companies are adopting new technology solutions to help them manage sustainability across many different dimensions, from environmental issues like energy, water, and waste, to social issues like diversity and human rights, to governance and reporting issues.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d31b118dcbe3ac649ef3a08129aad3c3e6a33702.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d31b118dcbe3ac649ef3a08129aad3c3e6a33702.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1d31b118dcbe3ac649ef3a08129aad3c3e6a33702.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_1d31b118dcbe3ac649ef3a08129aad3c3e6a33702.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="986">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>Source: Gartner. Click to enlarge.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Business leaders are looking for the best tools that allow them to quantify, analyze, and act on real-time, accurate, and shareable sustainability data throughout their end-to-end operations. With SAP’s ERP-centric solutions, financial and non-financial data can be brought together for holistic decision-making. Business leaders can not only manage their productivity and operating results but connect that information with sustainability-related data to help make climate protection measurable, diversity and inclusion visible, and ethical responsibility transparent.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="record-report-and-act-with-sap-sustainability-solutions">Record, report, and act with SAP Sustainability solutions</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/sustainability.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP has a unique role to play in supporting our customers’ sustainability efforts. SAP customers produce 87% of the world’s global commerce. That means our products and services can help the vast majority of companies driving the global economy organize their supply chains, transportation, and financial data in a way that can enable an equitable, circular economy and net-zero emissions.</p>
  <p>Sustainability data in ERP is the foundation for holistic, integrated sustainability management. As the leader in enterprise resource management, SAP has more than 50 years of experience helping businesses across 25 industries optimize resources.</p>
  <p>Our comprehensive portfolio is designed to help customers find the solutions they need to run their business processes and enterprise more efficiently, with offerings such as SAP Business Network, business process transformation solutions, SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP), and the SAP Customer Experience portfolio. Our solutions, increasingly powered with AI capabilities, can help customers not only in their own operations, but across their entire value chain – from calculating product-level carbon footprints, to ensuring diversity and inclusion, to protecting human rights. In addition, SAP’s broad ecosystem of partners can support customers with industry- and technology-specific consulting and implementation, advancing SAP’s “sustainable by design” approach.</p>
  <p>SAP leads by example as well, having committed to net-zero emissions across our entire value chain by 2030. We also <a href="/2021/12/sap-leads-sustainability-rankings">have been recognized</a> as the leading software firm in the Dow Jones Sustainability Indices for 15 years and as a leader in environmental transparency and action by CDP, an international organization considered the gold standard of environmental reporting.</p>
  <h2 id="whats-next">What’s Next</h2>
  <p>Sustainability is not an end state, it’s a state of being. In that respect, companies should adopt an approach that constantly evolves and adapts to remain sustainable. SAP is dedicated to advancing sustainable business through our own operations and our comprehensive portfolio of solutions that can help other companies with their end-to-end sustainability management. Across the business network and our wide solution portfolio, SAP supports our customers in tackling their biggest sustainability challenges.</p>
  <p>Try the free <a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/dg/sap-rated-positively-in-sustainability/index.html">SAP Sustainability Navigator</a> tool, and read the full <a href="https://www.gartner.com/reprints/?id=1-2FWN452Z&#x26;ct=231213&#x26;st=sb">complimentary Gartner Sustainability report</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Daniel Schmid is chief sustainability officer at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-sap-news-on-linkedin">Connect with SAP News on LinkedIn</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news">Follow us</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Gartner, Sustainability Assessment: SAP, 11 December 2023, Ed Anderson, Fabio Di Capua<br>GARTNER is a registered trademark and service mark of Gartner, Inc. and/or its affiliates in the U.S. and internationally and is used herein with permission. All rights reserved. This graphic was published by Gartner, Inc. as part of a larger research document and should be evaluated in the context of the entire document. The Gartner document is available upon request from SAP.<br>Gartner does not endorse any vendor, product or service depicted in its research publications and does not advise technology users to select only those vendors with the highest ratings or other designation. Gartner research publications consist of the opinions of Gartner’s research organization and should not be construed as statements of fact. Gartner disclaims all warranties, expressed or implied, with respect to this research, including any warranties of merchantability or fitness for a particular purpose.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Is a Leader in the 2023 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Financial Planning Software]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/sap-leader-2023-gartner-magic-quadrant-financial-planning-software</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/sap-leader-2023-gartner-magic-quadrant-financial-planning-software</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[We are proud to announce that Gartner has recognized SAP as a Leader in its 2023 Magic Quadrant for Financial Planning Software.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_12c0f62a0c1bea8cebafaf88b1a2478cf4d11b899.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_12c0f62a0c1bea8cebafaf88b1a2478cf4d11b899.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_12c0f62a0c1bea8cebafaf88b1a2478cf4d11b899.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Is a Leader in the 2023 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Financial Planning Software" src="./media_12c0f62a0c1bea8cebafaf88b1a2478cf4d11b899.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-is-a-leader-in-the-2023-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-financial-planning-software">SAP Is a Leader in the 2023 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Financial Planning Software</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>We are proud to announce that Gartner has recognized SAP as a Leader in its <a href="https://www.gartner.com/reprints/?id=1-2FU0XES5&#x26;ct=231206&#x26;st=sb">2023 Magic Quadrant for Financial Planning Software</a>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>At SAP, our commitment extends beyond traditional financial planning and analysis (FP&#x26;A), reaching across the entire enterprise of financial professionals. To achieve a comprehensive FP&#x26;A transformation, organizations need effortless access to crucial finance data, regardless of its location. In a landscape where financial information is dispersed across various applications, files, and systems – both on premise and in the cloud – organizations often expend significant resources on extracting, rebuilding, and integrating their financial data to deliver forecasts and simulations.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-analytics-cloud-make-decisions-without-doubt">SAP Analytics Cloud: Make decisions without doubt</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/cloud-analytics.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>By harnessing cutting-edge FP&#x26;A software tools and adopting strategic approaches, organizations can seamlessly explore, connect, integrate, govern, and orchestrate their planning and analysis. SAP’s solutions for financial planning and analysis can provide a reliable foundation for finance information, delivering trustworthy, pertinent, and timely financial insights. This can streamline finance data, helping to maximize business information potential. Simultaneously, it can foster an analytics-driven approach to planning and decision-making. Our primary solution for financial planning and analysis is <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/cloud-analytics/features/planning.html">SAP Analytics Cloud</a>. This solution is part of <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">SAP Business Technology Platform</a> (SAP BTP).</p>
  <p>Gartner evaluated 16 vendors and named SAP a Leader based on our “ability to execute” and “completeness of vision.” We believe this recognition serves as an acknowledgment of SAP’s continued commitment to providing our customers with world-class financial planning software.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1db92051bee73b9bb29a5433d2213c41cc9f52bab.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1db92051bee73b9bb29a5433d2213c41cc9f52bab.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1db92051bee73b9bb29a5433d2213c41cc9f52bab.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_1db92051bee73b9bb29a5433d2213c41cc9f52bab.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="570" height="592">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>This graphic was published by Gartner, Inc. as part of a larger research document and should be evaluated in the context of the entire document. The Gartner document is available upon request from SAP here. Click to enlarge.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="future-proof-your-organization-with-sap-solutions-for-xpa">Future-Proof Your Organization with SAP Solutions for xP&#x26;A</h2>
  <p>Our focus on accelerating planning and analysis (xP&#x26;A) is achieved by integrating with SAP S/4HANA Cloud and other SAP applications. This integration helps enable swift planning cycles, providing live access to actuals and plans. Customers can use our solutions to help extend their planning and analysis across the enterprise to facilitate seamlessly connected financial, workforce, sales, and supply chain plans. By adopting this approach, SAP customers can react quickly to changes and increase decision-making agility and performance no matter what events unfold.</p>
  <p>A pivotal aspect of our approach involves harnessing the power of artificial intelligence (AI) and machine learning for everyday planning. With a single click, our users can activate predictive analytics, allowing for insights with greater ease and speed. The AI capabilities within SAP Analytics Cloud are helping organizations unlock the full potential of their data and derive greater value from analytics and planning. With these capabilities, planners can model a wide range of scenarios and generate more accurate forecasts and plans.</p>
  <p>We are committed to instilling unwavering confidence in plans by meticulously ensuring the trustworthiness of data. Leveraging the powerful combination of <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/datasphere.html">SAP Datasphere</a> and SAP Analytics Cloud, we go beyond traditional boundaries to help harmonize planning data seamlessly across SAP and third-party sources, presenting natively integrated plans that can form a reliable foundation for strategic decision-making.</p>
  <p>This approach has yielded tangible benefits for organizations such as <a href="https://www.sap.com/asset/dynamic/2023/06/34b2b0e8-797e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Watco</a> and <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/customer-stories/roche.html">F. Hoffmann-La Roche AG</a>. These SAP Analytics Cloud customers have experienced firsthand the transformative impact of having their planning data seamlessly integrated, resulting in enhanced precision and efficacy in their planning and analysis endeavors. With our holistic approach, we help pave the way for you to navigate the complex landscape of financial planning with confidence, working to ensure your business decisions are backed by a foundation of accurate and planning-ready data.</p>
  <h2 id="next-steps">Next Steps</h2>
  <p>SAP is dedicated to advancing financial planning and analysis through our suite of financial planning software tools. Our commitment is reflected in the seamless transformation of financial data into actionable insights at scale for our customers. If you’re poised to unlock the full potential of your financial data and elevate your FP&#x26;A capabilities, explore the next steps with the resources provided:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Visit our <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/financial-management/financial-planning-analysis-fpa.html">financial planning and analysis page</a></li>
    <li>Try the free <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/financial-management/financial-planning-analysis-fpa/guided-experience.html">financial planning and analysis guided experience</a></li>
    <li>Read the full, complimentary <a href="https://www.gartner.com/reprints/?id=1-2FU0XES5&#x26;ct=231206&#x26;st=sb">Gartner Magic Quadrant for Financial Planning Software</a> report</li>
  </ul>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Dan Yu is senior vice president of SAP Business Technology Platform.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Gartner, Magic Quadrant for Financial Planning Software, Regina Crowder, Matthew Mowrey, Vaughan Archer, 5 December 2023<br>Gartner does not endorse any vendor, product or service depicted in its research publications and does not advise technology users to select only those vendors with the highest ratings or other designation. Gartner research publications consist of the opinions of Gartner’s Research &#x26; Advisory organization and should not be construed as statements of fact. Gartner disclaims all warranties, expressed or implied, with respect to this research, including any warranties of merchantability or fitness for a particular purpose.<br>GARTNER is a registered trademark and service mark of Gartner, Inc. and/or its affiliates in the U.S. and internationally, Magic Quadrant is a registered trademark of Gartner, Inc. and/or its affiliates and is used herein with permission. All rights reserved.</p>
  <p>Top image courtesy of SAP employee Laurentia-Iulia Pavel.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/financial-management</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/magic-quadrant</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Recognized as a Leader in 2023 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Data Integration Tools]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/sap-a-leader-gartner-magic-quadrant-data-integration-tools</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/sap-a-leader-gartner-magic-quadrant-data-integration-tools</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[For the 16th consecutive time, Gartner has recognized SAP as a Leader in its Magic Quadrant for Data Integration Tools.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18676e13249083c87480612ffdb6501c1181d00cd.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18676e13249083c87480612ffdb6501c1181d00cd.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_18676e13249083c87480612ffdb6501c1181d00cd.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Recognized as a Leader in 2023 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Data Integration Tools" src="./media_18676e13249083c87480612ffdb6501c1181d00cd.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-recognized-as-a-leader-in-2023-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-data-integration-tools">SAP Recognized as a Leader in 2023 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Data Integration Tools</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>We are proud to announce that Gartner has recognized SAP as a Leader in its 2023 <a href="https://www.gartner.com/reprints/?id=1-2FTDYPZU&#x26;ct=231204&#x26;st=sb">Magic Quadrant for Data Integration Tools</a> for the 16th consecutive time.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-an-engaging-hands-on-experience-with-sap-datasphere">Get an engaging, hands-on experience with SAP Datasphere</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/datasphere/guided-experience.html">Start now</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>To achieve true digital transformation, organizations must have seamless access to their mission-critical business data no matter where it resides. Yet with data landscapes distributed among different applications and systems both in the cloud and on premises, organizations spend countless resources extracting, rebuilding, and integrating their data.</p>
  <p>By leveraging the right data integration tools and strategies, organizations can easily discover, connect, integrate, govern, and orchestrate their data assets. Data integration offerings from SAP deliver trusted, relevant, and timely information to enable customers to simplify their data landscape and unleash the power of business data. Our primary solutions include <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/datasphere.html">SAP Datasphere</a>, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/cloud-platform/capabilities/integration.html">SAP Data Intelligence</a> Cloud, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/data-services.html">SAP Data Services</a>, and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/cloud-platform/capabilities/integration.html">SAP Integration Suite</a>. These offerings are part of <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">SAP Business Technology Platform</a> (SAP BTP).</p>
  <p>Gartner evaluated 21 vendors and named SAP a Leader based on our “ability to execute” and “completeness of vision.” We believe this recognition serves as acknowledgment of SAP’s continued commitment to providing our customers with world-class data integration tools.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b4a7dd1fbccb32babb1428357e9df797fb738917.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b4a7dd1fbccb32babb1428357e9df797fb738917.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1b4a7dd1fbccb32babb1428357e9df797fb738917.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_1b4a7dd1fbccb32babb1428357e9df797fb738917.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="926" height="1024">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>This graphic was published by Gartner, Inc. as part of a larger research document and should be evaluated in the context of the entire document. The Gartner document is available upon request from SAP here.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="unleash-the-power-of-business-data">Unleash the Power of Business Data</h2>
  <p>Data integration is necessary for customers to gain intelligent, relevant, and contextual insights for better decision-making. However, without the right data management approach and technology, companies can face an uphill battle in integrating, processing, curating, governing, and augmenting their data.</p>
  <p>SAP takes a business data fabric approach, which goes beyond a traditional data fabric. A business data fabric is a data management architecture that delivers an integrated, semantically rich data layer over underlying data landscapes to provide users with scalable access to their data without duplication.</p>
  <p>It eliminates the need to recreate the business context that was lost from extracting and replicating data. This gives users the ability to accelerate their decision-making with trust and confidence, knowing they always have the complete picture of their data regardless of where it is stored or how it was designed.</p>
  <p>SAP Datasphere — and its open data ecosystem — is the foundation for a business data fabric. It equips any organization to deliver meaningful data to every data consumer — with business context and logic intact. SAP Datasphere helps customers:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Access authoritative data:</strong> Accelerate time-to-value by automatically reusing the semantical definitions and associations from SAP applications</li>
    <li><strong>Enrich all data projects:</strong> Harmonize heterogeneous data into a business semantic model of diverse data landscape</li>
    <li><strong>Simplify the data landscape:</strong> Access all data across hybrid and cloud environments no matter where it resides</li>
  </ul>
  <p>With a unified experience for data integration, data cataloging, semantic modeling, data warehousing, data federation, and data virtualization, SAP Datasphere enables data professionals to easily distribute authoritative business data — with business context and logic preserved — across the data landscape.</p>
  <p>Since the launch of SAP Datasphere, we have seen tremendous growth of customers innovating with this technology. For example, Messer CIO David Johnston describes his experience with the solution this way:“The business data fabric architecture enables us to bring SAP and non-SAP data together in the seamless and self-service way we’ve been envisioning. SAP Datasphere provided us with a solution to build a harmonized layer, or business data fabric, across SAP and non-SAP, cloud or on-premise data sources, making the best use of our existing investments in SAP, Microsoft Azure, Salesforce, and Oracle.”</p>
  <h2 id="next-steps">Next Steps</h2>
  <p>For over 16 years, data integration tools from SAP have enabled our customers to turn disjoined data assets into actionable business insights at scale. Take the next step and begin your business data fabric journey today:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Visit the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/datasphere.html">SAP Datasphere page</a></li>
    <li>Try the free <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/datasphere/guided-experience.html">SAP Datasphere guided experience</a></li>
    <li>Read the <a href="https://www.gartner.com/reprints/?id=1-2FTDYPZU&#x26;ct=231204&#x26;st=sb">2023 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Data Integration Tools report</a></li>
  </ul>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Kaiser Larsen is vice president of Data and Analytics at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Gartner, Magic Quadrant for Data Integration Tools, Ehtisham Zaidi, Robert Thanaraj, Sharat Menon, Thornton Craig, Roxane Edjlali, Michele Launi, 4 December 2023<br>Gartner does not endorse any vendor, product or service depicted in its research publications and does not advise technology users to select only those vendors with the highest ratings or other designation. Gartner research publications consist of the opinions of Gartner’s Research &#x26; Advisory organization and should not be construed as statements of fact. Gartner disclaims all warranties, expressed or implied, with respect to this research, including any warranties of merchantability or fitness for a particular purpose.<br>GARTNER is a registered trademark and service mark of Gartner, Inc. and/or its affiliates in the U.S. and internationally, Magic Quadrant is a registered trademark of Gartner, Inc. and/or its affiliates and is used herein with permission. All rights reserved.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/data-fabric</category>
            <category>news-tag/data-integration</category>
            <category>news-tag/database-and-data-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/magic-quadrant</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-datasphere</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP S/4HANA Cloud Is a Leader in the 2023 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Cloud ERP for Product-Centric Enterprises]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/gartner-magic-quadrant-cloud-erp-product-centric-enterprises-sap-s-4-hana</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/gartner-magic-quadrant-cloud-erp-product-centric-enterprises-sap-s-4-hana</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[As enterprises transition mission-critical ERP processes to the cloud, they look to SAP to help them realize business value.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/magic-quadrant</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP S/4HANA Cloud Is a Leader in the 2023 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Cloud ERP for Service-Centric Enterprises]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/sap-leader-2023-gartner-magic-quadrant-cloud-erp-service-centric</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/sap-leader-2023-gartner-magic-quadrant-cloud-erp-service-centric</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP has been recognized as a leader in the 2023 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Cloud ERP for Service-Centric Enterprises. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/grow-with-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/magic-quadrant</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Named a Leader in 2023 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Digital Commerce]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/sap-named-a-leader-in-2023-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-digital-commerce</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/sap-named-a-leader-in-2023-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-digital-commerce</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[This is the ninth time in a row SAP has been rated a leader by Gartner in the Magic Quadrant for Digital Commerce. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/magic-quadrant</category>
            <category>product/sap-commerce-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-customer-experience</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Named a Leader in the 2023 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Warehouse Management Systems]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/sap-a-leader-2023-gartner-magic-quadrant-wms</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/sap-a-leader-2023-gartner-magic-quadrant-wms</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is again a Leader in the Gartner Magic Quadrant for WMS, based on ability to execute and for the completeness of vision. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/magic-quadrant</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-network-for-logistics</category>
            <category>product/sap-extended-warehouse-management</category>
            <category>product/sap-transportation-management</category>
            <category>product/sap-warehouse-insights</category>
            <category>product/sap-warehouse-robotics</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Named a Leader in the 2023 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Transportation Management Systems]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/2023-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-transportation-management-systems</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/2023-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-transportation-management-systems</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is a Leader in the Gartner Magic Quadrant for Transportation Management Systems based on ability to execute and completeness of vision.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/travel-transportation</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/magic-quadrant</category>
            <category>product/sap-transportation-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Three Key Highlights from the Gartner Data & Analytics Summit 2023]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/three-key-highlights-gartner-data-analytics-summit</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/three-key-highlights-gartner-data-analytics-summit</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[At the Gartner Data & Analytics Summit attendees explored recent data and analytics trends, technologies, and strategies, like SAP Datasphere.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/data-analytics</category>
            <category>news-tag/data-fabric</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-datasphere</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Signavio Is a Leader in the 2023 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Process Mining Tools]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/sap-signavio-leader-gartner-magic-quadrant-process-mining-tools</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/sap-signavio-leader-gartner-magic-quadrant-process-mining-tools</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In the first Gartner Magic Quadrant for Process Mining, SAP Signavio has been recognized as a Leader in the market. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/process-mining</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-signavio</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[In 2023, SAP Will Continue to Lead the Market in Procurement Innovation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/procurement-innovation-leading-market</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/procurement-innovation-leading-market</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In 2023, SAP intends to lead the market with procurement innovation. Learn how SAP plans to continue to deliver actionable insights.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>news-tag/procure-to-pay</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-spend-connect-live</category>
            <category>news-tag/supplier-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Named a Leader in 2023 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Integration Platform as a Service, Worldwide]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/01/2023-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-ipaas-sap-a-leader</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/01/2023-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-ipaas-sap-a-leader</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Gartner has recognized SAP as a Leader in the 2023 Magic Quadrant for iPaaS, Worldwide for the third time in a row. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/enterprise-integration</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/integration</category>
            <category>news-tag/magic-quadrant</category>
            <category>product/sap-integration-suite</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Named a Leader in 2022 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Procure-to-Pay Suites]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/sap-a-leader-procure-to-pay-suites-gartner-magic-quadrant</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/sap-a-leader-procure-to-pay-suites-gartner-magic-quadrant</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[For the seventh consecutive time, SAP has been recognized as a Leader in the Gartner Magic Quadrant for Procure-to-Pay suites. Learn why.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/magic-quadrant</category>
            <category>news-tag/procure-to-pay</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Again a Leader in Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Cloud Database Management Systems]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/sap-a-leader-in-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-cdbms</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/sap-a-leader-in-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-cdbms</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP's position in the CDBMS Magic Quadrant supports its mission to help organizations transform their data strategy and give data purpose.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/magic-quadrant</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Recognized as a Leader in 2022 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Data Quality Solutions]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/gartner-magic-quadrant-for-data-quality-solutions-sap-a-leader</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/gartner-magic-quadrant-for-data-quality-solutions-sap-a-leader</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is once again a Leader in the Gartner Magic Quadrant for Data Quality Solutions, for the 16th consecutive year. Learn why.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17da0610c34e8f257d6b846afd52d20285c5e3f79.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17da0610c34e8f257d6b846afd52d20285c5e3f79.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_17da0610c34e8f257d6b846afd52d20285c5e3f79.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Recognized as a Leader in 2022 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Data Quality Solutions" src="./media_17da0610c34e8f257d6b846afd52d20285c5e3f79.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-recognized-as-a-leader-in-2022-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-data-quality-solutions">SAP Recognized as a Leader in 2022 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Data Quality Solutions</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="data-management-transform-your-business-by-making-information-ready-for-action">Data Management: Transform your business by making information ready for action</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/data-management.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>We are proud to announce that Gartner has recognized SAP as a Leader in its <a href="https://www.gartner.com/reprints/?id=1-2BKS6A63&#x26;ct=221102&#x26;st=sb">2022 Magic Quadrant for Data Quality Solutions</a> for the 16th consecutive year.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Digital transformation has changed the conversation about data; it is a shift from “data is not my problem” to “data is everyone’s opportunity.” Organizations are looking for ways to embrace the opportunity — specifically, by exploiting their data as a strategic enterprise asset.</p>
  <p>By leveraging the right data quality solutions, organization can create the data excellence and discipline needed to drive better business outcomes, going beyond just fixing data to helping solve the data challenge. Data quality solutions from SAP provide data profiling and monitoring, metadata management, data cataloging, data cleansing and enrichment, and information policy management capabilities. They helps improve collaboration among data workers, business users, and IT while equipping them to understand, analyze, and quantify the impact of data — and data quality — on enterprise processes, analytics, and governance initiatives. Solutions include <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/data-intelligence.html">SAP Data Intelligence Cloud</a>, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/data-profiling-steward.html">SAP Information Steward</a>, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/data-services.html">SAP Data Services</a>, and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/data-quality-management.html">SAP Data Quality Management, microservices for location data</a>.</p>
  <p>Gartner evaluated 16 vendors and named SAP a Leader based on its “ability to execute” and “completeness of vision.” We believe this recognition serves as acknowledgment of our continued commitment to providing customers with world-class data quality solutions.</p>
  <p>Data is the lifeline of business today. It is critical to not only manage data quality proactively to eliminate the risk to operations and analytics, but also look for opportunities to create organization-wide data excellence and discipline. The SAP portfolio of data management solutions improves the quality of data across the enterprise, delivering trusted, relevant, and timely information to drive better business outcomes and help customers on their path to becoming intelligent enterprises.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-started-with-sap-btp">Get started with SAP BTP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/trial.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Leading integrated business conglomerate <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/customer-stories/adani.html">Adani</a> set out to build a foundation for centralized data management across its business. The company is using SAP Data Services and SAP Information Steward software for regular data validation and enrichment in order to support a single source of truth based on high-quality data. This outcome gives employees the visibility and insights they need to make in-the-moment decisions confidently and supports better quality data with regular data validation, consistent data definition, and internal quality checks.</p>
  <p>As part of <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">SAP Business Technology Platform</a>, the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/data-management.html">SAP portfolio of data management solutions</a> helps customers to optimize analytics, achieve new insights, and improve business outcomes. Users can proactively govern data across the organization to help ensure trustworthy information for smarter decision-making.</p>
  <p>Data quality solutions from SAP help businesses discover, understand, and manage multifaceted data. Companies can profile, cleanse, enrich, and match customer, product, supplier, material, and other data — driving more accurate, trustworthy, and timely information.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Mike Keilen is global vice president for SAP BTP Integration and Data Management Marketing and Solutions.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/database-and-data-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/magic-quadrant</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Industry 4.0 Attracts Workers Whose Entire Lives Are on Their Mobile Device]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/industry-4-0-attracts-workers-whose-entire-lives-are-on-their-mobile-device</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/industry-4-0-attracts-workers-whose-entire-lives-are-on-their-mobile-device</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Manufacturers are transforming factories, hoping next-generation workers come for the cool factor and stay for career-building innovations.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-4-0</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>news-tag/mobile</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Named a 2022 Magic Quadrant™ Transportation Management Systems and Magic Quadrant™ for Warehouse Management Systems Leader by Gartner®]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/gartner-magic-quadrant-tms-wms-sap-a-leader</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/gartner-magic-quadrant-tms-wms-sap-a-leader</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP has been recognized by Gartner as a leader in TMS and WMS, demonstrating its position as leading provider in supply chain and procurement.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/travel-transportation</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/magic-quadrant</category>
            <category>news-tag/warehouse-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Positioned as a Leader in 2022 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Cloud HCM Suites for 1,000+ Employee Enterprises for Seventh Consecutive Year]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/sap-a-leader-magic-quadrant-for-cloud-hcm-suites-employee-enterprises</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/sap-a-leader-magic-quadrant-for-cloud-hcm-suites-employee-enterprises</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is a a Leader in the Magic Quadrant for Cloud HCM Suites for 1,000+ Employee Enterprises for the seventh consecutive year.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_12e84929eba593a9c963c2135bbd9c29c6a2d4176.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_12e84929eba593a9c963c2135bbd9c29c6a2d4176.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_12e84929eba593a9c963c2135bbd9c29c6a2d4176.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Positioned as a Leader in 2022 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Cloud HCM Suites for 1,000+ Employee Enterprises for Seventh Consecutive Year" src="./media_12e84929eba593a9c963c2135bbd9c29c6a2d4176.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-positioned-as-a-leader-in-2022-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-cloud-hcm-suites-for-1000-employee-enterprises-for-seventh-consecutive-year">SAP Positioned as a Leader in 2022 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Cloud HCM Suites for 1,000+ Employee Enterprises for Seventh Consecutive Year</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>For the seventh consecutive year, <a href="http://sap.com/hr">SAP</a> has been named a Leader in the “Gartner Magic Quadrant for Cloud HCM Suites for 1,000+ Employee Enterprises.”</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The world of work has changed dramatically since the report’s inception, elevating the role of people and culture leaders. The need for rich data and actionable insights, employee expectations for greater self-service and mobile functionality, a growing skills gap, and the ability to manage an increasingly dispersed workforce are just a few of the major shifts we have experienced. With all of these changes, one constant has remained clear: the need for people to be at the center of business is more critical than ever.</p>
  <p>This is why more than 9,400 customers worldwide — from mid-market organizations to global enterprises with 100,000+ employees — count on SAP SuccessFactors Human Experience Management (HXM) Suite to elevate their people function and drive transformational change throughout their business. Together with <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/s4hana.html">SAP S/4HANA Cloud</a>, <a href="https://www.fieldglass.com/">SAP Fieldglass</a> solutions, and the broader SAP portfolio, they can connect their people processes across the business to truly put people at the center.</p>
  <p>“For MOD Pizza, providing exceptional employee experiences is key to driving workforce engagement and business success,” said Tara Gambill, senior director of Enterprise Systems for <a href="https://www.sap.com/asset/dynamic/2022/8/ed4692e7-32d5-49e9-9240-a0a2dc2f8909.html">MOD Pizza LLC</a>. “People data is the lifeblood of the system. With intelligent technologies from SAP, we can create integration end to end, and leverage that data to get people connected and productive faster.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="put-people-at-the-heart-of-your-hr-strategy">Put people at the heart of your HR strategy</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="building-a-future-ready-workforce">Building a Future-Ready Workforce</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-more-new-and-coverage-from-successconnect">Read more new and coverage from SuccessConnect</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/topics/successconnect">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As we look at the changing dynamics of what people and organizations need to succeed, it requires a change in thinking. People thrive when they are engaged in their careers and have a sense of belonging; organizations thrive when their people are properly skilled and aligned to the right opportunities.</p>
  <p>Global HR industry influencer Josh Bersin recently <a href="https://joshbersin.com/2022/09/sap-successfactors-launches-its-biggest-release-in-a-decade/">said</a>: “[<a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/opportunity-marketplace.html">SAP SuccessFactors Opportunity Marketplace]</a> is integrated into the [SAP] SuccessFactors stack, making talent marketplace an integrated part of HCM. SAP is going further. While the talent marketplace is often seen as a ‘product’ or set of features, it really is much more. It’s a new, modern way of thinking about pay, jobs, roles, and growth.”</p>
  <p>At <a href="https://events.sap.com/successconnect/en/global-home">SuccessConnect</a>, we introduced new innovations to transform talent development for the future of work, and bring the whole self model to life. Informed by our team of behavioral scientists, these innovations use data and machine learning to continuously understand the capabilities within the workforce as well as each person’s whole self — their skills, aspirations, interests, strengths. This intelligence enables organizations to match people with dynamic teams and ongoing growth opportunities. The result is people-centric organizations that provide individuals with opportunities to grow and learn in alignment with the needs of the business.</p>
  <p>Vicki Furnish, vice president of Global People Solutions Operations and Analytics at <a href="/2022/09/ntt-data-it-takes-entire-team-to-win">NTT DATA Services,</a> said it perfectly when discussing NTT DATA Services’ move to SAP SuccessFactors: “If we put the right foundation in for our team and people, our team members will be successful. If they are successful, we will then be successful in our business.”</p>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div>Read the full report here: <a href="https://www.gartner.com/reprints/?id=1-2BGRQGI7&#x26;ct=221021&#x26;st=sb">Gartner Magic Quadrant for Cloud HCM Suites for 1,000+ Employee Enterprises</a>.</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>Amy Wilson is senior vice president of Products and Design for SAP SuccessFactors.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Gartner does not endorse any vendor, product or service depicted in its research publications and does not advise technology users to select only those vendors with the highest ratings or other designation. Gartner research publications consist of the opinions of Gartner’s research organization and should not be construed as statements of fact. Gartner disclaims all warranties, expressed or implied, with respect to this research, including any warranties of merchantability or fitness for a particular purpose.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/future-of-work</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/magic-quadrant</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Digital Innovations Behind the Booming Life Sciences Industry]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/digital-innovations-life-sciences-industry</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/digital-innovations-life-sciences-industry</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The pandemic has irrevocably disrupted the life sciences industry, revealing a new vision for innovation from cloud-based collaboration.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/covid-19</category>
            <category>news-tag/forrester</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>industry/healthcare</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>industry/life-sciences</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Disrupted ERP Systems Rise to Reckoning in the Cloud]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/composable-business-for-disrupted-erp-systems</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/composable-business-for-disrupted-erp-systems</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Composable business is the future for cloud ERP software, promising faster innovation for stronger resilience against market disruptions.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
            <category>news-tag/new-ventures-and-technologies</category>
            <category>product/sap-erp</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Is a Leader in the 2022 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Cloud ERP for Product-Centric Enterprises]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/09/magic-quadrant-cloud-erp-for-product-centric-enterprises-sap-a-leader</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/09/magic-quadrant-cloud-erp-for-product-centric-enterprises-sap-a-leader</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Gartner has named SAP a Leader in the Magic Quadrant for Cloud ERP for Product-Centric Enterprises with S/4HANA Cloud being evaluated.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/magic-quadrant</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Is Your Factory Intelligent Enough to Withstand the Next Business Crisis?]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/09/is-your-factory-intelligent-enough-to-withstand-the-next-business-crisis</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/09/is-your-factory-intelligent-enough-to-withstand-the-next-business-crisis</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Manufacturers are embracing Industry 4.0 and intelligent factories to anticipate and respond faster to market demands. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-4-0</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
            <category>news-tag/machine-learning</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Recognized as a Leader in 2022 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Data Integration Tools]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/2022-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-data-integration-tools-sap-a-leader</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/2022-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-data-integration-tools-sap-a-leader</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is a Leader in the 2022 Magic Quadrant for Data Integration Tools for the 15th consecutive year. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/data-fabric</category>
            <category>news-tag/data-integration</category>
            <category>news-tag/database-and-data-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/magic-quadrant</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-data-intelligence</category>
            <category>product/sap-data-intelligence-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Named a Leader in 2022 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Digital Commerce]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/2022-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-digital-commerce-sap-a-leader</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/2022-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-digital-commerce-sap-a-leader</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP been named a leader in the 2022 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Digital Commerce for the eighth time. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/magic-quadrant</category>
            <category>product/sap-commerce-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-customer-experience</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Recognized as Visionary in 2022 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Robotic Process Automation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/sap-visionary-gartner-robotic-process-automation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/sap-visionary-gartner-robotic-process-automation</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Gartner has ranked SAP as a Visionary in the 2022 Magic Quadrant for Robotic Process Automation (RPA) for its SAP Process Automation solution.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/automation</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/low-code-no-code</category>
            <category>news-tag/rpa</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[For High-Tech Supply Chains, CO2 Emission Tracking Is Sustainable Business Currency]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/high-tech-supply-chains-co2-emission-tracking</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/high-tech-supply-chains-co2-emission-tracking</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[High-tech industry leaders are making sustainability a core commitment, and it is transforming business models to address climate change.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-footprint</category>
            <category>news-tag/circular-economy</category>
            <category>topic/data-analytics</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>industry/high-tech</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/net-zero</category>
            <category>product/sap-product-footprint-management</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>