<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/djsi/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Acknowledging SAP's Concrete Steps to Tackle Climate and Social Challenges]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/02/sap-tackles-climate-and-social-challenges</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/02/sap-tackles-climate-and-social-challenges</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP’s efforts to tackle climate and social challenges have been recognized by many of the most trusted business sustainability organizations.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_12b7510ab12f449bf1595e9b13360e8e5a8ae903c.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_12b7510ab12f449bf1595e9b13360e8e5a8ae903c.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_12b7510ab12f449bf1595e9b13360e8e5a8ae903c.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Acknowledging SAP’s Concrete Steps to Tackle Climate and Social Challenges" src="./media_12b7510ab12f449bf1595e9b13360e8e5a8ae903c.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="acknowledging-saps-concrete-steps-to-tackle-climate-and-social-challenges">Acknowledging SAP’s Concrete Steps to Tackle Climate and Social Challenges</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Today’s business leaders incorporate environmental and social governance metrics into their core strategy and use it to guide investment choices, product development, human capital agenda, and corporate reputation.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>To help customers reinvent themselves and become intelligent and sustainable enterprises, SAP has strengthened its commitments and pledges. We are helping our customers be sustainably profitable and profitability sustainable.</p>
  <p>From accelerating the goal to achieve net-zero emissions across SAP’s value chain by 2030 rather than 2050 to delivering solutions that enable customers to measure carbon emissions, reduce waste, and integrate financial and non-financial metrics, SAP is delivering its promise to help customers run better, all the while serving its higher purpose to improve people lives.</p>
  <p>SAP’s environmental, social, and governance (ESG) efforts — along with its measures, initiatives, and targets — have been recognized by the world’s most trusted business sustainability ratings and ranking organizations.</p>
  <p>As Julia White, chief marketing and solutions officer and member of the Executive Board of SAP SE, <a href="/2022/01/sap-cloud-for-sustainable-enterprises-take-action-together">recently pointed out</a>: “We have learned a great deal through years of focus, investment, and experience working with customers and managing our own sustainability efforts. Urgent action is needed in 2022 and the calls of a ‘<a href="https://news.un.org/en/story/2021/08/1097362">code red for humanity</a>‘ are not overstated. It’s time for every business to act.”</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <table>
          <thead>
            <tr>
              <th colspan="2">Promo</th>
            </tr>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td>
                <h3 id="choose-both-profitability-and-sustainability-with-sap">Choose both profitability and sustainability with SAP</h3>
              </td>
              <td><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/purpose-and-sustainability/economics.html">Learn more</a></strong></td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
        <h2 id="selected-ranking-and-ratings">Selected Ranking and Ratings</h2>
        <table>
          <thead>
            <tr>
              <th colspan="2">Promo</th>
            </tr>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td>
                <h3 id="embed-sustainable-practices-into-the-core-of-your-business-strategy-and-operations">Embed sustainable practices into the core of your business strategy and operations</h3>
              </td>
              <td><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/cloud-for-sustainable-enterprises.html">Learn more</a></strong></td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17dbcd8c8cca91e5dd4ee43148780855bf2bedf0b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17dbcd8c8cca91e5dd4ee43148780855bf2bedf0b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_17dbcd8c8cca91e5dd4ee43148780855bf2bedf0b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_17dbcd8c8cca91e5dd4ee43148780855bf2bedf0b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="273" height="500">
          </picture><strong>CDP</strong> | <a href="https://www.cdp.net/en/research/global-reports/engaging-the-chain">Learn more</a>
        </p>
        <p>In addition to receiving an <a href="/2021/12/sap-achieves-top-scores-dow-jones-sustainability-index-and-cdp-carbon-disclosure-project">A-rating in CDP’s last climate change assessment</a> once again, SAP was recognized by CDP (formerly Carbon Disclosure Project) as a 2021 CDP Supplier Engagement Leader, raising the level of climate action across its value chain and for taking action to measure and reduce climate risk within its supply chain.</p>
        <p>“Our data shows that companies currently have blinkers on when it comes to assessing their indirect impacts and engaging with suppliers to reduce them,” said Sonya Bhonsle, Global Head of Value Chains &#x26; Regional Director Corporations, CDP. “Companies must act urgently to cascade action and manage environmental impacts throughout their supply chains to scale the level of action to secure a 1.5°C future. Many congratulations to the more than 500 companies earning a place on CDP’s 2021 Supplier Engagement Leaderboard. As a supplier engagement leader, SAP SE is a trailblazer driving the transition toward a sustainable net-zero future.”</p>
        <p><strong>Corporate Knights</strong> | <a href="https://www.corporateknights.com/rankings/global-100-rankings/2022-global-100-rankings/global-100-companies-prove-sustainability-is-good-for-business/">Learn more</a></p>
        <p>In the 18th annual ranking of Corporate Knights’ 2022 100 most sustainable corporations in the world, <a href="https://www.corporateknights.com/rankings/global-100-rankings/2022-global-100-rankings/100-most-sustainable-corporations-of-2022/">SAP ranked 55</a>. This award has a special significance as Global 100 companies represent the top one percent in the world on sustainability performance. To determine the ranking, the Toronto-based media, research, and financial information products company analyzed 7,000 companies with more than US$1 billion in revenues against 23 key performance indicators.</p>
        <p>“Strong performance on these metrics is foundational to achieving a clean and carbon-neutral economy in the necessary time frame and the sustained momentum is encouraging,” said Toby Heaps, Corporate Knights CEO and Editor-in-Chief.</p>
        <p><strong>Corporate Sustainability Assessment by S&#x26;P (Dow Jones Sustainability Indices)</strong></p>
        <p>Learn more in “<a href="/2021/12/sap-achieves-top-scores-dow-jones-sustainability-index-and-cdp-carbon-disclosure-project">SAP Achieves Top Scores in Dow Jones Sustainability Index and Carbon Disclosure Project</a>.”</p>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c29a99547b3d9ff01123b7afce588d58c673785f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c29a99547b3d9ff01123b7afce588d58c673785f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1c29a99547b3d9ff01123b7afce588d58c673785f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_1c29a99547b3d9ff01123b7afce588d58c673785f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="500" height="156">
          </picture><strong>EcoVadis</strong> | <a href="https://ecovadis.com/">Learn more</a>
        </p>
        <p>In the last sustainability assessment of EcoVadis in August 2021, SAP was awarded a gold medal again and upheld its position in the top two percent, with a score of 72 of 100. With more than 85,000 rated companies, EcoVadis is one of the world’s most trusted business sustainability rating providers. Its assessment covers a broad range of non-financial management systems, including environments, labor and human rights, ethics, and sustainable procurement impacts.</p>
        <p><strong>FTSE4Good</strong> | <a href="https://www.ftserussell.com/products/indices/ftse4good">Learn more</a></p>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ff143d6314cf04014a2bdef0bc6c2f2101b0de2b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ff143d6314cf04014a2bdef0bc6c2f2101b0de2b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1ff143d6314cf04014a2bdef0bc6c2f2101b0de2b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_1ff143d6314cf04014a2bdef0bc6c2f2101b0de2b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="500" height="500">
          </picture>Administered by the Financial Times Stock Exchange-Russell Group (FTSE), the FTSE4Good Index Series is designed to measure the performance of companies demonstrating strong ESG practices. Transparent management and clearly defined ESG criteria make FTSE4Good indices suitable tools to be used by a wide variety of market participants when creating or assessing sustainable investment products.
        </p>
        <p>SAP received an ESG score of 4.1 out of 5 — the top nine percent of analyzed companies — based on assessment questions in areas such as environment, climate change, human rights, community and labor standards, tax transparency, and anti-corruption. Due to its good scoring, SAP remains a constituent of the FTSE4Good Index Series following the December 2021 review.</p>
        <p><strong>ISS ESG</strong> | <a href="https://www.issgovernance.com/esg/">Learn more</a></p>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1080762659d302477a03a59ddc949a3e9c0cc63e8.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1080762659d302477a03a59ddc949a3e9c0cc63e8.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1080762659d302477a03a59ddc949a3e9c0cc63e8.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_1080762659d302477a03a59ddc949a3e9c0cc63e8.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="500" height="316">
          </picture>The Institutional Shareholder Services (ISS) ESG Corporate Rating provides an assessment of companies’ sustainability performance based on high-quality and in-depth research and up to 100 sector-specific rating criteria that are regularly reviewed and developed. With its B rating, SAP has been acknowledged with prime status and is among the top percentile, also receiving the top score in both the social and environmental quality dimension . The last governance profile update was November 19, 2021; the last E and S profile update was May 6, 2021.
        </p>
        <p><strong>Moody’s ESG Solutions</strong> | <a href="https://esg.moodys.io/solutions">Learn more</a></p>
        <p>In the last assessment in January 2022*, SAP maintained the highest of four performance levels (“advanced”) and ranked two of 83 in its sector, acknowledging its strength of managing material <a href="https://vigeo-eiris.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/VE_ESG-Assessment-Summary_2021-2.pdf">ESG factors, mitigating risks, and creating sustainable value</a>. Due to its good performance, SAP remained a constituent in the Euronext Vigeo Eiris indices Europe120 and Eurozone120. These indices are composed of the highest ranking listed companies according to its evaluation of companies’ ESG performance based on 38 criteria, including industry weightings, and monitoring of company-related ESG controversies.</p>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1558b6b66d8aa1d36ccbb2b13fea5443cd752c8f8.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1558b6b66d8aa1d36ccbb2b13fea5443cd752c8f8.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1558b6b66d8aa1d36ccbb2b13fea5443cd752c8f8.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_1558b6b66d8aa1d36ccbb2b13fea5443cd752c8f8.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="650" height="73">
          </picture><strong>MSCI</strong> | <a href="https://www.msci.com/our-solutions/esg-investing/esg-ratings/esg-ratings-corporate-search-tool/issuer/sap-se/IID000000002705885">Learn more</a>
        </p>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18036f5fb16d621ae3bbeea951f3ded07f478183f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18036f5fb16d621ae3bbeea951f3ded07f478183f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_18036f5fb16d621ae3bbeea951f3ded07f478183f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_18036f5fb16d621ae3bbeea951f3ded07f478183f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="500" height="222">
          </picture>MSCI ESG Research provides in-depth research, ratings, and analysis of the ESG-related business practices of thousands of companies worldwide. Its research is designed to provide critical insights that can help institutional investors identify risks and opportunities that traditional investment research may overlook. The MSCI ESG Ratings are also used in the construction of the MSCI ESG Indexes produced by MSCI, Inc. SAP upholds the highest rating of AAA** and is an ESG leader in human capital development, corporate governance, privacy and data security, and clean tech as of the last assessment in April 2021.
        </p>
        <p><strong>Sustainalytics</strong> | <a href="https://www.sustainalytics.com/esg-rating/sap-se/1008004721">Learn More</a></p>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_19ee802f20246fab24be0693c450487bc07821701.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_19ee802f20246fab24be0693c450487bc07821701.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_19ee802f20246fab24be0693c450487bc07821701.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_19ee802f20246fab24be0693c450487bc07821701.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="500" height="305">
          </picture>As of August 2021, SAP received an ESG Risk Rating of 9.7 from Sustainalytics and was assessed to be at negligible risk of experiencing material financial impacts from ESG factors. Founded in 1992, Sustainalytics, a Morningstar company, provides analytical ESG research, ratings, and data to institutional investors and companies.
        </p>
        <p><em>*This ESG Assessment was originally conducted by V.E, which is now part of Moody’s ESG Solutions.**Scale: AAA (leader) to CCC (laggard). The use by SAP SE of any MSCI ESG Research LLC or its affiliates (‘MSCI”) data, and the use of MSCI logos, trademarks or index names herein, do not constitute a sponsorship, endorsement, recommendation or promotion of SAP SE by MSCI. MSCI Services and Data are the property of MSCI or its information providers and are provided “as-is” and without warranty. MSCI names and logos are trademarks or service marks of MSCI.</em></p>
        <p><em>Copyright ©2022 Sustainalytics. All rights reserved. This article contains information developed by Sustainalytics (<a href="https://eur03.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.sustainalytics.com%2F&#x26;data=04%7C01%7Clilli-jane.popp%40sap.com%7Cc549e8045d4246c5cd8708d9ea241655%7C42f7676cf455423c82f6dc2d99791af7%7C0%7C0%7C637798263015410153%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJWIjoiMC4wLjAwMDAiLCJQIjoiV2luMzIiLCJBTiI6Ik1haWwiLCJXVCI6Mn0%3D%7C3000&#x26;sdata=h8v1ATSF7al7lgNdumBuL1DjZTg3%2BZegFCGke1snOu0%3D&#x26;reserved=0">www.sustainalytics.com</a>). Such information and data are proprietary of Sustainalytics and/or its third party suppliers (Third Party Data) and are provided for informational purposes only. They do not constitute an endorsement of any product or project, nor an investment advice and are not warranted to be complete, timely, accurate or suitable for a particular purpose. Their use is subject to conditions available at <a href="https://eur03.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.sustainalytics.com%2Flegal-disclaimers&#x26;data=04%7C01%7Clilli-jane.popp%40sap.com%7Cc549e8045d4246c5cd8708d9ea241655%7C42f7676cf455423c82f6dc2d99791af7%7C0%7C0%7C637798263015410153%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJWIjoiMC4wLjAwMDAiLCJQIjoiV2luMzIiLCJBTiI6Ik1haWwiLCJXVCI6Mn0%3D%7C3000&#x26;sdata=ECsLuLGE5VEIpDiXlghaad5Pg%2FMJAPyqeKddxCEt00I%3D&#x26;reserved=0">https://www.sustainalytics.com/legal-disclaimers</a></em>.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/cdp</category>
            <category>news-tag/djsi</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Accelerating Our Commitment to Net-Zero]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/01/accelerating-net-zero-commitment</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/01/accelerating-net-zero-commitment</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is accelerating its goal of net-zero emissions across the value chain by 2030 – 20 years earlier than originally planned.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f31da15a2f74a12d58551608246c312a20b7d4ac.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f31da15a2f74a12d58551608246c312a20b7d4ac.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1f31da15a2f74a12d58551608246c312a20b7d4ac.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Accelerating Our Commitment to Net-Zero" src="./media_1f31da15a2f74a12d58551608246c312a20b7d4ac.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="accelerating-our-commitment-to-net-zero">Accelerating Our Commitment to Net-Zero</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>SAP has committed to achieve net-zero along our value chain in line with a 1.5°C future in 2030 – 20 years earlier than originally targeted.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Is this too bold? I don’t think so. The recent COP26 climate conference and the Glasgow Climate Pact gave a strong signal to countries and businesses to set more ambitious targets in order to prevent further irreversible damage from climate change. Given the climate and social crisis the world faces, we need to “go big” with our ambitions and have the courage to act, thereby living up to SAP’s purpose to help the world run better and improve people’s lives.</p>
  <p>More than a decade ago, SAP set out on its sustainability journey with the objective to create positive economic, environmental, and social impact within planetary boundaries. Along the way, we have <a href="/2021/07/cfo-sustainability-reporting-esg-metrics-enterprise-software">experienced the benefits as well as the challenges</a> of integrating economic, social, and environmental performance into how we measure and steer our business success holistically. Setting and monitoring ambitious and measurable targets while leveraging digital solutions have proven crucial to decarbonization.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="choose-both-profitability-and-sustainability-with-sap">Choose both profitability and sustainability with SAP</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/sustainability/our-approach.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Raising our ambition to get to net-zero is therefore one of the key cornerstones on our path forward to implementing our holistic approach to sustainability, which looks across climate action, the circular economy, social responsibility, holistic steering and reporting, and the many areas of interconnection.</p>
  <p>The <a href="https://www.ipcc.ch/report/sixth-assessment-report-working-group-i/">2021 Sixth Assessment</a> from the Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change (IPCC) as well as <a href="/2021/11/cop26-reflections-enabling-business-action-and-planetary-ambition">SAP’s intense engagement on the ground at COP26</a> have left us with a deepened understanding of the science, the role of business, and the impact of SAP. With an increased sense of urgency, we recognize the responsibility, as well as the opportunity, to step up and drive a faster transformation toward a sustainable future.</p>
  <p>Leveraging SAP’s global reach, today we <a href="/">announced the release of SAP Cloud for Sustainable Enterprises</a> to help companies quickly adopt holistic sustainability management capabilities. In addition, we commit to accelerate SAP’s <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/purpose-and-sustainability/economics/net-zero-commitment.html">timeline to net-zero</a> from 2050 to 2030 and to reach our climate goals, in line with the Paris Agreement, 20 years earlier.</p>
  <h2 id="what-does-net-zero-mean">What Does Net-Zero Mean?</h2>
  <p>Net-zero is a state in which the greenhouse gases going into the atmosphere are balanced by removal out of the atmosphere. It has gained significant traction, with net-zero pledges covering 16% of the global economy in 2019 and recently growing to nearly 80% committed to net-zero by 2050. Because the various definitions of net-zero and how to get there have been growing too, so have criticism and skepticism.</p>
  <p>Leading up to COP26, the Science Based Targets initiative (SBTi) <a href="https://sciencebasedtargets.org/news/sbti-launches-world-first-net-zero-corporate-standard">launched its Net-Zero Standard</a> to provide a credible and independent assessment of corporate net-zero target setting in line with climate science, which enables companies to align their near- and long-term climate action with limiting global warming to 1.5°C.</p>
  <p>­­­Building on its <a href="/2021/10/integrating-climate-action-end-to-end">carbon reduction journey since 2009</a>, SAP became a member of SBTi and, in 2017, was the first German company with a science-based carbon reduction target for 2050. In 2019, SAP raised its commitment and adopted a <a href="/2019/07/sap-emissions-reduction-targets">1.5°C science-based emissions reduction target</a>.</p>
  <p>On our pathway toward net-zero, the next intermediate milestone is 2023, when <a href="/2021/03/sap-carbon-neutrality-goal-2023">SAP aims to be carbon neutral in its own operations</a> – two years earlier than originally targeted. This includes all direct (Scope 1), indirect (Scope 2), and selected categories of value chain (Scope 3) carbon emissions, such as business flights, employee commuting, and external data centers (co-locations and hyperscalers).</p>
  <p>The potential for decarbonization can be amplified considerably if we enhance our efforts along the entire value chain. In 2020, carbon emissions amounted to 12,300 kt along SAP’s entire value chain (including upstream and downstream emissions) compared to 135 kt net emissions for SAP’s own operations.</p>
  <h2 id="targeting-our-entire-value-chain">Targeting Our Entire Value Chain</h2>
  <p>Reducing emissions from the use of SAP’s sold products will be the primary lever, followed by purchased goods and services. Our focus will be on the following key areas:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Accelerating the transformation of on-premise customers to cloud</li>
    <li>Strengthening engagement with key suppliers to commit to net-zero and deliver products and services on a carbon-neutral basis</li>
    <li>Using best-in-class data centers (our own, our co-locations, and hyperscalers) with sustainable programming and a cloud carbon footprint calculator for all SAP cloud solutions</li>
    <li>Enhancing direct investments in renewable electricity as well as nature-based and technical-based funds to neutralize residual carbon emissions</li>
  </ul>
  <p>The next step is to receive external validation by SBTi. We have started setting up a cross-company program involving experts from different lines of business to prepare for our net-zero transformation and will continue to make progress transparent, for example in our annual <a href="http://www.sapintegratedreport.com">Integrated Report</a>.</p>
  <p>We are not starting from scratch. We have many achievements to build on, but we are also charting new territory. 2030 is just nine years away. The challenge will increase the more we move upstream and downstream into our value chain. We will face both synergies as well as additional complexity as we interface with our further focus areas for sustainability, including holistic steering and reporting, circular economy, and social responsibility based on respect for human rights.<br>But as our external sustainability advisory panel confirmed for us, this is the right thing to do. Our net-zero commitment is one of many actions we are taking at SAP. It will take all of us to work together to deliver the outcomes we need for people and planet, and for a profitable, sustainable business.</p>
  <p>As Luka Mucic, CFO, member of the Executive Board of SAP SE, and Board sponsor for sustainability at SAP, <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=aRA6IbREmvw">noted at the end of the Sustainable Innovation Forum</a> at COP26: “We must reinvent the global economy. That is what it will take to limit global warming to 1.5℃. All of us must build sustainability into the fabric of how we do business. Only when a business strategy is sustainable itself, and is embedded in all aspects of the business, can we reduce negative impacts and create regenerative systems.”</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Daniel Schmid is chief sustainability officer of SAP SE.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/cdp</category>
            <category>non-sap-event/cop26</category>
            <category>news-tag/djsi</category>
            <category>news-tag/net-zero</category>
            <category>product/sap-cloud-for-sustainable-enterprises</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Takes Top Spots in Leading Sustainability Rankings]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/sap-leads-sustainability-rankings</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/sap-leads-sustainability-rankings</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP once again leads the sustainability rankings: CDP’s A List as well as the Dow Jones Sustainability Indices (DJSI). Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>news-tag/djsi</category>
            <category>product/sap-product-footprint-management</category>
            <category>product/sap-responsible-design-and-production</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Gets Top ESG Ratings from Corporate Knights and CDP]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/01/corporate-knights-cdp-sap-top-esg-ratings</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/01/corporate-knights-cdp-sap-top-esg-ratings</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Corporate Knights Inc. has included SAP in its 2021 Global 100 Index, and SAP is included on CDP’s A List 2020. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>news-tag/cdp</category>
            <category>news-tag/djsi</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>