<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/sap-fieldglass/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[New Supply Chain and External Workforce Innovations Reduce Organizational Inefficiencies]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/supply-chain-external-workforce-innovations</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/supply-chain-external-workforce-innovations</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[At SAP Sapphire, we introduced supply chain and external workforce innovations to help reduce inefficiency and improve decision-making.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/automation</category>
            <category>news-tag/external-workforce-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fieldglass</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ardent Partners Positions SAP Fieldglass as a Market Leader for Vendor Management Systems]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/ardent-partners-sap-fieldglass-vms-market-leader</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/ardent-partners-sap-fieldglass-vms-market-leader</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Ardent Partners positioned SAP Fieldglass as a Market Leader for vendor management systems (VMS). Read to learn more about the recognition.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/external-workforce-management</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fieldglass</category>
            <category>news-tag/total-workforce-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Is on the Cutting Edge of How to Best Manage Company Spend]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-cutting-edge-company-spend-management</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-cutting-edge-company-spend-management</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP has been on the cutting edge of how to best manage company spend. Read about some recent updates to SAP spend management solutions.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11441be6b25f7c09e02cd28d0b0aa9997b84c22a1.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11441be6b25f7c09e02cd28d0b0aa9997b84c22a1.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_11441be6b25f7c09e02cd28d0b0aa9997b84c22a1.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Is on the Cutting Edge of How to Best Manage Company Spend" src="./media_11441be6b25f7c09e02cd28d0b0aa9997b84c22a1.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-is-on-the-cutting-edge-of-how-to-best-manage-company-spend">SAP Is on the Cutting Edge of How to Best Manage Company Spend</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>As a pioneer of spend management software, SAP has been on the cutting edge of how to best comprehensively manage company spend and supplier relationships.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Like at home, identifying every dollar you spend and getting the most out of it is more critical than ever for your business. And as we continue to roll out SAP Business AI technology, the teams behind SAP solutions are working on ways to help you reduce the time spent on mundane tasks so you can focus on executing your strategy, unlocking spend potential, and unleashing efficiency.</p>
  <p>The first quarter of 2024 was among the most productive in my 18 years at SAP. We debuted new AI capabilities in various SAP spend management solutions. Check out some of these highlights:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>SAP Ariba Category Management</strong>: We’ve incorporated <a href="https://community.sap.com/t5/spend-management-blogs-by-sap/generative-ai-powered-content-recommendations-in-sap-ariba-category/ba-p/13640447?campaigncode=CRM-YD24-ISM-2422141&#x26;source=blog-glo-JCollierQ124">generative AI-enabled features</a> that can assist category managers by generating recommendations in the solution’s category segmentation, market dynamics, and cost structure tools.</li>
    <li><strong>Scoutbee Discovery</strong>: SAP partnered with Scoutbee, a leading AI-powered supplier intelligence and discovery platform, to launch <a href="https://store.sap.com/dcp/en/product/display-2001012892_live_v1/scoutbee-discovery?campaigncode=CRM-YD24-ISM-2422141&#x26;source=blog-glo-JCollierQ124">Scoutbee Discovery</a>. This SAP endorsed app can rapidly identify qualified suppliers that meet specific criteria and can help advance strategic business imperatives. <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/events/7176993552332140544/comments/">Watch the recording</a> of me participating in a recent LinkedIn Live with the Scoutbee team.</li>
    <li><strong>Concur Request:</strong> Now, this service uses generative AI to help provide <a href="https://www.concur.com/blog/article/sap-concur-delivers-enriched-travel-and-expense-experiences-at-fusion-2024?campaigncode=CRM-YD24-ISM-2422141&#x26;source=blog-glo-JCollierQ124">intelligent cost estimates</a> for trip planning.</li>
    <li><strong>ExpenseIt</strong>: Users can upload receipt images to the ExpenseIt solution, which taps AI to help <a href="https://www.concur.com/blog/article/sap-concur-delivers-enriched-travel-and-expense-experiences-at-fusion-2024?campaigncode=CRM-YD24-ISM-2422141&#x26;source=blog-glo-JCollierQ124">automatically create a new expense</a> with several key fields prepopulated. Plus, ExpenseIt can now itemize hotel folios using generative AI.</li>
    <li><strong>Generative AI search</strong>: A new capability within Concur Support allows SAP Concur customers to type questions in natural language and get quick answers using generative AI, <a href="https://www.concur.com/blog/article/sap-concur-delivers-enriched-travel-and-expense-experiences-at-fusion-2024?campaigncode=CRM-YD24-ISM-2422141&#x26;source=blog-glo-JCollierQ124">without submitting a support ticket</a>.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>SAP’s market-leading spend and business network solutions are getting even smarter, working to unlock greater value for our customers. We have many resources devoted to spend management and that’s why we continue to deliver innovation in spend management.</p>
  <p>And we are only getting started. By the end of 2024, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-network.html?campaigncode=CRM-YD24-ISM-2422141&#x26;source=blog-glo-JCollierQ124">SAP Business Network</a> is planning the following enhancements:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Generative AI RFI/RFP responses in SAP Business Network Discovery</strong>: With generative AI-enabled responses for postings in SAP Business Network Discovery, suppliers will be able to respond to RFIs promptly and more accurately, helping to save time and reduce costs associated with manual labor and resource allocation.</li>
    <li><strong>Catalog enrichment using ChatGPT recommendations</strong>: This feature can enable suppliers to generate and improve product descriptions and overall catalog quality based on prompts and keyword recommendations from ChatGPT.</li>
    <li><strong>Intelligent error simplification using generative AI</strong>: This feature uses machine learning and a large language model to interpret and categorize invoice rejection reasons, allowing suppliers to reduce the number of failing invoices, improve rapid invoice submission and payment, and optimize cash flow.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>For more on how AI is transforming business networks, read <a href="/2024/04/business-networks-accelerate-ai-value">this recent article</a> from my colleague Joern Keller.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="eliminate-the-mundane-and-elevate-the-strategic-in-spend-management-with-generative-ai">Eliminate the mundane and elevate the strategic in spend management with generative AI</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/spend-management/innovations.html#ai">Discover SAP solutions</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="but-what-are-our-customers-saying">But What Are Our Customers Saying?</h2>
  <p>Each quarter, G2 highlights the top rated solutions in the industry, chosen by the source that matters most: customers. Spring 2024 is no different, and once again our suite of spend and business network solutions scored extremely well.</p>
  <ul>
    <li><a href="https://www.g2.com/products/sap-sap-fieldglass/reviews">SAP Fieldglass</a> is a G2 Spring Leader in Vendor Management.</li>
    <li><a href="https://www.g2.com/products/sap-ariba/reviews">SAP Ariba</a> is a G2 Spring Leader in Procure to Pay, Purchasing, Strategic Sourcing, Supplier Relationship Management, and Contract Lifecycle Management.</li>
    <li><a href="https://www.g2.com/products/sap-concur/reviews">SAP Concur</a> is a G2 Spring Leader in Expense, Travel &#x26; Expense, and Invoicing.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>What’s more, G2 recently announced its <a href="https://www.g2.com/best-software-companies">2024 Best Software Award winners</a>, with SAP Fieldglass and SAP Concur receiving high honors:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>SAP Fieldglass came in at No. 26 in G2’s Best Software Awards across all products and No. 12 in G2’s Best Software Awards for best midmarket products.</li>
    <li>SAP Concur came in at No. 4 in G2’s Best Software Awards for the account and software product category.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>My colleagues are also getting their flowers. Etosha Thurman, chief marketing and solutions officer of Intelligent Spend and Business Network, and Steve Seide, global head of Adoption for Intelligent Spend and Business Network, were named Top Procurement Pros in the <a href="https://issuu.com/supplydemandchainfoodlogistics/docs/sdc0324_digital?fr=sNGVkZTcxMzY1NTY">Supply &#x26; Demand Chain Executive 2024 Pros to Know awards</a>. A big congratulations also goes out to Darcy MacClaren, CRO for SAP Digital Supply Chain, who received a Pros to Know Lifetime Achievement award.</p>
  <h2 id="driving-success-for-our-customers">Driving Success for Our Customers</h2>
  <p>Hearing me spotlight our direct and indirect procurement, external workforce, and travel and expense management solutions is one thing. Seeing them in action is something way more powerful. Here are a few recent customer success stories to take in:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>American Eagle Outfitters</strong> (AEO), a leading global specialty retailer offering high-quality on-trend clothing, accessories, and personal care products through its portfolio of brands, needed to evaluate indirect purchasing processes and vendor relationships to maximize efficiency. See how <a href="https://www.sap.com/asset/dynamic/2023/10/2ed3b1af-917e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.htm?campaigncode=CRM-YD24-ISM-2422141&#x26;source=blog-glo-JCollierQ124l">SAP Business Network for Procurement and SAP Ariba solutions</a> helped simplify processes and deliver compliant purchasing protocols across the company.</li>
    <li>Power provider to over 900,000 electric customers, <strong>Oklahoma Gas &#x26; Electric Company</strong> (OG&#x26;E) faced challenges with the complexity of third-party and cross-department management of contingent workers. After transitioning SAP Fieldglass solutions to internal management, OG&#x26;E <a href="/2024/02/oge-and-brightspeed-manage-employees-contingent-workers">gained the visibility</a> to make more informed financial decisions, like supplier negotiations.</li>
    <li><a href="https://www.sap.com/idea-place/sap-innovation-awards/entries/2024-award.html#winners?campaigncode=CRM-YD24-ISM-2422141&#x26;source=blog-glo-JCollierQ124">2024 SAP Innovation Award winner</a> <strong>Vestas Wind Systems</strong>, the world’s largest manufacturer of wind turbines, launched a large-scale quality initiative powered by SAP Business Network to help mitigate product defects in a highly complex supply chain. Now, using SAP Business Network, suppliers complete predefined quality tests and document them before confirming or sending an order. This enables Vestas employees to be warned in advance of any quality issues further up the supply chain, so they can <a href="/2024/02/vestas-powering-quality-in-supply-chain">take corrective action</a>.</li>
    <li>Most <strong>KUKA</strong> employees are based in Germany, where tax regulation is complex and submitting hotel and entertainment expenses is anything but simple. The KUKA team worked together to develop a simple process using SAP Concur solutions, connected to SAP ERP, that allows employees to create hotel and entertainment expenses <a href="https://www.concur.com/en-us/casestudy/kuka?campaigncode=CRM-YD24-ISM-2422141&#x26;source=blog-glo-JCollierQ124">seven times faster</a> with fewer errors and fewer rejected expense reports.</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="join-us-at-sap-sapphire">Join Us at SAP Sapphire!</h2>
  <p>SAP Sapphire &#x26; ASUG Annual Conference is June 3-5 in Orlando, Florida, this year and I can’t wait to meet with customers, partners, and my fellow colleagues. This is the best event in the industry in my opinion and you don’t want to miss out. Join us by registering on the <a href="https://www.sap.com/events/sapphire.html?campaigncode=CRM-YD24-ISM-2422141&#x26;source=blog-glo-JCollierQ124">SAP Sapphire event website</a>, where you can also save your spot at the SAP Sapphire Virtual and SAP Sapphire Barcelona events. See you there!</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Jeff Collier is chief revenue officer for SAP Intelligent Spend and Business Network.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>product/sap-ariba-category-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-spend</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-concur</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fieldglass</category>
            <category>topic/spend-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Procurement Teams Can Drive Innovation in Services Procurement]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/how-procurement-drives-innovation-in-services-procurement</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/how-procurement-drives-innovation-in-services-procurement</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A new study conducted by Art of Procurement and sponsored by SAP examines the current state of services procurement. Read about its findings.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fieldglass</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Total Workforce Management Evolution: How OG&E and Brightspeed Manage Employees and Contingent Workers]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/oge-and-brightspeed-manage-employees-contingent-workers</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/oge-and-brightspeed-manage-employees-contingent-workers</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[OG&E and Brightspeed highlight the importance of strategic planning and the effective use of technological tools in managing the workforce.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/contingent-workforce-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fieldglass</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>news-tag/total-workforce-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Cares About Your Company’s Spend]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/sap-cares-about-your-companys-spend</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/sap-cares-about-your-companys-spend</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP spend management and business network solutions continue evolving and improving with time – and 2024 will be no different.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>product/sap-ariba-category-management</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc-marketscape</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-spend</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-concur</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fieldglass</category>
            <category>news-tag/trustradius</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP’s Source-to-Pay Solution Strategy Focuses on Customer Success]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/sap-source-to-pay-strategy-focuses-customer-success</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/sap-source-to-pay-strategy-focuses-customer-success</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Within the source-to-pay landscape, SAP delivers integrated solutions to help manage all forms of spend. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>product/sap-ariba-category-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/icertis</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fieldglass</category>
            <category>product/sap-spend-control-tower</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[What Does 2024 Have in Store for Spend Management and Supply Chain Professionals?]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/spend-management-supply-chain-2024-predictions</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/spend-management-supply-chain-2024-predictions</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP professionals share their 2024 predictions for spend management and supply chain. Read to learn what they said about the coming year.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18efa0d05f945b26c1dda8d2694f972656f97e05a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18efa0d05f945b26c1dda8d2694f972656f97e05a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_18efa0d05f945b26c1dda8d2694f972656f97e05a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="What Does 2024 Have in Store for Spend Management and Supply Chain Professionals?" src="./media_18efa0d05f945b26c1dda8d2694f972656f97e05a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="what-does-2024-have-in-store-for-spend-management-and-supply-chain-professionals">What Does 2024 Have in Store for Spend Management and Supply Chain Professionals?</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>When we look back on 2023, we’ll remember it as a year when economic conditions put the spotlight back on cost containment. At the same time, spend management professionals continued to face unexpected supply chain risks and environmental, social, and governance (ESG) requirements created more pressure to comply with government regulations and consumer demands.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>It was also the year when business leaders worldwide decided enough is enough. They began taking steps to future proof their supply chains. And we can’t forget that 2023 was the year when generative <a href="/topics/ai">AI</a> came to dominate every conversation about technology.</p>
  <p>Now it’s time to look ahead. Where will world events, business developments, and technology innovations take spend management in 2024? What strategies and technology will business leaders employ to bring greater resilience and efficiency to their supply chains?</p>
  <p>Here are predictions for 2024, from SAP’s intelligent spend and business network leaders.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>“In 2023, generative AI was like a bolt of lightning that compelled every business and technology leader to sit up and take notice. We’re no longer asking <em>if</em> businesses will adopt AI technology, but rather <em>how quickly</em> they can deploy it and realize its benefits. In 2024, businesses leaders will look beyond the industry buzz for solutions that deliver real-life, AI-based use cases. They’ll also see firsthand that AI is only as effective as the quality and availability of data. With the huge number of data and transactions running through our <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/spend-management/solutions.html?campaigncode=CRM-Y123-ISM-1980086&#x26;source=blog-glo-2024ISBNPredictions">systems</a> and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-network.html?campaigncode=CRM-Y123-ISM-1980086&#x26;source=blog-glo-2024ISBNPredictions">business network</a>, SAP is uniquely positioned to help organizations access the data they need, visualize it, and take decisive action to drive their success.”</p>
        <p>– <em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/muhammad-s-alam/">Muhammad Alam</a>, President and Chief Product Officer,</em><br><em>SAP Intelligent Spend and Business Network,</em><br><em>and General Manager for SAP Business Network</em></p>
        <p>“As we enter 2024, procurement organizations will continue to focus on cost containment and supply continuity in order to bring value to their businesses. These have traditionally been the primary value drivers and, in today’s economic environment, I see this continuing. The opportunity will be maintaining the expanded voice earned with stakeholders during the volatile, crisis-riddled past few years, given the resurgence of hyper focus on cost containment. I believe that the scope of procurement will not contract back to a sole focus on supply stability and cost containment. In fact, I think procurement’s remit will continue to evolve to lead broader supply chain risk management, given the growing variety and number of risks faced such as geopolitical tensions, sustainability expectations, the need for more diverse sources of supply, and lingering labor availability concerns. The challenge facing procurement will be how to tackle all of this successfully. What we’ll see is the use of innovation like generative AI, spend analysis, and category management solutions to not only provide relevant, real-time business insights, but, importantly, to increase the efficiency and productivity of procurement teams, giving more capacity to focus on the strategic work stakeholders now expect.”</p>
        <p>– <em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/etoshathurman/">Etosha Thurman</a>, Chief Marketing and Solutions Officer,</em><br><em>Intelligent Spend and Business Network, SAP</em></p>
        <p>“The more things change, the more they stay the same. Or do they? Last year we were talking about how businesses needed to grapple with economic, political, and environmental uncertainty. That hasn’t changed. What’s different is how quickly new strategies and technologies have emerged to help businesses deal with these challenges. In 2024, I expect business leaders to continue pursuing supply chain resilience and to look for solutions such as AI that enable them to make big leaps. There will also be a continued focus on cost savings. With economic concerns looming as central banks raise funds rates to counter inflation, I foresee leaders being asked to deliver higher margins for their enterprises. To do this, traditional cost-focused sourcing and procurement cost compliance will be essential.”</p>
        <p>– <em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/jeffcollier/">Jeff Collier</a>, Chief Revenue Officer,</em><br><em>Intelligent Spend and Business Network, SAP</em></p>
        <p>“As enterprises continue on their journey to digitalize procurement processes, the need for an even more intuitive user experience will increase. Procurement professionals are looking for ways to spend more time on value-adding tasks and are looking to generative AI and analytics to support them at the point of decision. Moving into 2024 and beyond, we expect the demand for these technologies to increase, as well as for new use cases to arise. At SAP, we are already evaluating further ways to embed generative AI and analytics into solutions throughout our SAP Ariba portfolio to help make our customers’ business lives easier than ever.”</p>
        <p>– <em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/salvatore-lombardo-a579662/">Salvatore Lombardo</a>, SVP, Chief Product Officer,</em><br><em>SAP Ariba Procurement Solutions, SAP</em></p>
        <p>“As technology evolves, pragmatic business leaders are looking for ways to leverage these new developments to help streamline and simplify their processes. Managing a workforce that can be comprised of up to 40% external workers demands tools that can simplify the user experience and offer broad visibility to both external and full-time workers. I predict that in 2024 we will see more organizations lean into total workforce management strategies to address this need for greater visibility across full-time and external workers, allowing businesses to align the skills they have with the work they need to complete. Along with a more holistic approach to managing their workforce, these same companies can leverage innovative AI tools designed to offer efficiencies and improve the user experience. In 2024, SAP Fieldglass customers will be able to leverage powerful AI tools, including AI-enhanced statement of work creation, translation capabilities, and our new <a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2023/10/e8cd2e18-937e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">job description builder</a> powered by generative AI. These offerings are just the beginning, with many more use cases to come.”</p>
        <p>– <em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/vishbaliga/">Vish Baliga</a>, Chief Technology Officer,</em><br><em>SAP Fieldglass Solutions, SAP</em></p>
        <p>“In my conversations with customers and prospects about their plans for 2024, they consistently voice concerns about supply chain disruption and economic uncertainty. Meanwhile, most seem to appreciate that artificial intelligence is vital to maintaining their competitive edge, yet many are unsure how to distinguish the actual value from the ample hype. In 2024, we will see more of the value that AI can deliver to organizations with capabilities to support their value chains. These include generative and predictive AI capabilities to help forecast disruptions, recommend alternate sources of raw materials, detect errors in invoices, extract pertinent data from requests for information, predict shipment and delivery times, and complete catalogue details. Trading partners need the ability to enter into additional collaborative relationships, such as those between buyers and suppliers spanning SAP Business Network Supply Chain Collaboration and material traceability and freight collaboration solutions. Also in 2024, we see network convergence taking center stage to give organizations a shared onboarding experience across all network applications, as well as a set of common data federation services to support data residency requirements.”</p>
        <p>– <em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/joernkeller/">Joern Keller</a>, Executive Vice President and Chief Product Officer,</em><br><em>SAP Business Network</em></p>
        <p>“In 2024, generative AI will deliver trillions in economic benefits. It will help companies realize greater top-line growth, be more productive, and safeguard supply chains. At the same time, resiliency will continue to be a major focus. The combination of AI and business networks will drive game-changing resiliency and productivity by facilitating improved demand forecasting and more efficient inventory management. These technologies will empower businesses to respond proactively to market changes, allowing them to source new suppliers quickly. In times of supply chain disruptions or demand surges, the nimblest companies will benefit most. Business networks will help them anticipate challenges with real-time information sharing and enhanced supply chain visibility. And there’s more good news for midmarket and smaller companies: as enterprise adoption of these technologies may begin to lag behind due to complex and unique use cases, segments like the midmarket and smaller companies will start to gain the competitive edge, building more resilient, predictable, and sustainable supply chains at scale.”</p>
        <p>– <em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/valerie-blatt-3790091/">Val Blatt</a>, Global Head, SAP Business Network</em><br><em>Customer Success and Go-to-Market, SAP</em></p>
        <p>“We’ll see business digitalization efforts go a level deeper – and become substantially more integrated – in 2024. Continued adoption of AI, automation, and virtual forms of payment will drive streamlined processes in travel, expense, and invoice. Instead of using a company credit card, employees will be able to expand their use of virtual payments for all business expenses, including travel. In turn, we’ll start to see two types of transactions emerge: trusted and exceptions. Most transactions will use trusted payment methods, and AI will quickly validate them as compliant, enabling near-immediate reimbursement. Exceptions will trigger AI-driven, automated audits to ensure compliance. In both cases, payments will be issued faster with more ease, and employees will have more time to focus on what matters most to them and the organization.”</p>
        <p>– <em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/cajseattle/">Christopher Juneau</a>, Head of SAP Concur Market Strategy,</em><br><em>SAP Concur</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-more-predictions-from-sap-concur">Get more predictions from SAP Concur</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.concur.com/blog/article/sap-concur-predictions-for-2024">Read the 2024 predictions blog</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“After another year of significant disruption caused by economic and geopolitical uncertainty, supply chain optimization has risen up the agenda as companies seek to better manage their working capital. Embedded finance has emerged as a solution, promising to reshape the way we do business and interact. Embedded finance has the power to expedite transactions, facilitate financing between trading partners, and lower trade barriers. By harnessing embedded finance, companies have the potential to optimize processes and access financing solutions seamlessly through B2B platforms. Ultimately, this will result in more streamlined payments, faster credit decisions, and expanded access to working capital.”</p>
  <p>– <em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/dweinblatt/">Danielle Weinblatt</a>, Chief Product Officer, Taulia</em></p>
  <p>“As organizations, especially midmarket companies, continue to navigate today’s dynamic business environment, they are realizing the need to work with solution partners to create more value for their customers and themselves. A strong relationship between organizations and their partner ecosystems is critical to success, and I expect we will continue to see more businesses, both large and small, looking to establish these relationships. With the cost of managing sustainable supply chains continuing to increase, companies should turn to their partner ecosystems to leverage their expertise, skills, and services. This approach can help unify a company’s operations to provide a greater experience for its buyers and sellers, enabling stronger collaboration, greater visibility and transparency, risk mitigation, and more efficient operations.”</p>
  <p>– <em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/clausgruenewald/">Claus Gruenewald</a>, Head of Intelligent Spend and</em><br><em>Business Network Partner Ecosystem, SAP</em></p>
  <h2 id="one-more-prediction">One More Prediction</h2>
  <p>Recent times have shown that unexpected disruptions aren’t the only reason businesses struggle in times of crisis. It’s also about their readiness to deal with disruption, to adapt, and to come out stronger when the crisis subsides. Many business leaders have learned this lesson. They’re taking action to ensure – to the best of their ability – that their businesses are prepared for what comes next.</p>
  <p>Of course, that’s easier said than done. Sometimes it feels like we need a crystal ball to see into the future. Or, to use a more common term, we need “visibility.” Visibility into market trends. Visibility into world events. Visibility into every corner of the supply chain.</p>
  <p>Here’s a prediction you can take to the bank: in 2024, SAP will continue to design and deliver <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/spend-management/solutions.html?campaigncode=CRM-Y123-ISM-1980086&#x26;source=blog-glo-2024ISBNPredictions">spend management</a> and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-network.html?campaigncode=CRM-Y123-ISM-1980086&#x26;source=blog-glo-2024ISBNPredictions">business network</a> solutions that can drive efficiency, leverage AI in ways that are relevant, reliable, and responsible, and create greater visibility for every size business.</p>
  <p>Mike Conners is a communications specialist for the SAP Spend Management Communications team.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-sap-news-delivered-to-your-inbox-once-a-week">Get the latest SAP news delivered to your inbox once a week</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/nl/sap-news-center-newsletter/index.html">Sign up</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-concur</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fieldglass</category>
            <category>topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/taulia</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[What’s New in Intelligent Spend Management Solutions from SAP]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/whats-new-intelligent-spend-management-from-sap</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/whats-new-intelligent-spend-management-from-sap</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Intelligent spend management solutions from SAP are evolving with AI, being adopted by customers, and receiving recognition. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-spend</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-concur</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fieldglass</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-spend-connect-live</category>
            <category>topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/trustradius</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Customers Realize the Power of Connected Cloud HR and ERP]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/sap-customers-realize-power-of-connected-cloud-hr-erp</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/sap-customers-realize-power-of-connected-cloud-hr-erp</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP customers connect SAP SuccessFactors solutions for HR with SAP S/4HANA Cloud to improve end-to-end business processes and experiences.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_12c8a896617a0e516f610561e9bf9c127d0a779ff.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_12c8a896617a0e516f610561e9bf9c127d0a779ff.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_12c8a896617a0e516f610561e9bf9c127d0a779ff.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Customers Realize the Power of Connected Cloud HR and ERP" src="./media_12c8a896617a0e516f610561e9bf9c127d0a779ff.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-customers-realize-the-power-of-connected-cloud-hr-and-erp">SAP Customers Realize the Power of Connected Cloud HR and ERP</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>SAP customers are unlocking strategic value across the organization by using a single cloud platform to connect HR, run on <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm.html?campaigncode=CRM-YI23-HXM-2053446&#x26;source=text-glo-SAPNews">SAP SuccessFactors</a> solutions, with finance and other business operations that use <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/s4hana.html?campaigncode=crm-ya22-int-1517075&#x26;source=ppc-de-google_ads-search-71700000111912410-58700008464076060-s4hana_s4fin-x-&#x26;dfa=1&#x26;gclid=EAIaIQobChMImKnKw_7tgQMV94ZoCR1j7QLcEAAYASAAEgJPEfD_BwE&#x26;gclsrc=aw.ds?campaigncode=CRM-YI23-HXM-2053446&#x26;source=text-glo-SAPNews">SAP S/4HANA Cloud</a>. In various industries, large and midsized organizations alike are discovering the power of having a common people and skills data model that is used across the entire organization. The combined effectiveness of SAP SuccessFactors solutions and SAP S/4HANA Cloud is moving leading brands to new levels of strategic insight and organizational agility.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>With this integrated approach, real-time people data from the SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central solution is automatically consumed by SAP S/4HANA Cloud and other SAP cloud applications. This “single source of truth” helps to improve end-to-end business processes, experiences, and insights for the organization. Learn more in this SAP Community <a href="https://blogs.sap.com/2023/08/07/sap-successfactors-and-sap-s-4hana-cloud-public-edition-supercharge-your-hr-and-erp-investments-now-on-demand/?campaigncode=CRM-YI23-HXM-2053446&#x26;source=text-glo-SAPNews">blog</a>.</p>
  <p>Maryann Abbajay, chief revenue officer at SAP SuccessFactors, spoke with some of these customers at <a href="https://www.sap.com/events/successconnect/virtual.html?campaigncode=CRM-YI23-HXM-2055448&#x26;source=text-glo-SAPNews?campaigncode=CRM-YI23-HXM-2053446&#x26;source=text-glo-SAPNews">SuccessConnect</a> to find out how they are leveraging the combined power of SAP SuccessFactors solutions and SAP S/4HANA Cloud to overcome business challenges and grow their organizations with people at the center of business. “These organizations show how HR and finance come together to enable business transformation while keeping employee experience at the center,” she underscored.</p>
  <h2 id="pandora-becomes-a-future-ready-organization">Pandora Becomes a Future-Ready Organization</h2>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="catch-up-on-this-years-event-with-successconnect-virtual-on-demand">Catch up on this year’s event with SuccessConnect Virtual on-demand</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/events/successconnect/virtual.html?campaigncode=CRM-YI23-HXM-2055448&#x26;source=text-glo-SAPNews?campaigncode=CRM-YI23-HXM-2053446&#x26;source=ctabutton-glo-SAPNews">Watch now</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Connecting people in the moments that matter is at the heart of <a href="https://us.pandora.net/">Pandora</a>, the world’s largest jewelry brand. Based in Copenhagen, Denmark, Pandora employs 32,000 people worldwide. With 6,500 points of sale, including 2,500 concept stores, Pandora depends on the experience of its brick-and-mortar stores, which account for the majority of its sales.</p>
  <p>Three years ago, Pandora began its transformation from an analog retailer to a future-ready organization. It set out to strengthen and harmonize the global HR system landscape with an implementation of SAP SuccessFactors solutions to gain efficiency in how the company hires, manages, and develops employees worldwide, thus replacing a multitude of local applications.</p>
  <p>“We used the SAP SuccessFactors portfolio as a driver of transformation,” said Mihael Šutalo, vice president of People Technology, Pandora. “This is transforming the experience. The future integration of SAP S/4HANA Cloud with SAP SuccessFactors solutions will give us a tremendous opportunity to manage our workforce and manage our revenue model in a completely different way.”</p>
  <h2 id="bt-group-connects-people-for-good">BT Group Connects People for Good</h2>
  <p><a href="https://www.bt.com/about">BT Group</a>, the world’s oldest telecommunications company, recently modernized its HR information systems to provide a digital colleague experience for its 100,000 employees working in 44 countries. “In 2021, we started what we call our I-Connect program,” said Elaine Bergin, director of Colleague Experience and Delivery, BT Group. The program name highlights BT Group’s purpose: “We connect for good.”</p>
  <p>The new colleague experience, launched in 2022, now uses the SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central solution, reporting and analytics, and the full suite of talent and learning management solutions to support the organization’s big focus on skills. BT Group also uses SAP SuccessFactors and SAP Fieldglass solutions to manage a contingent workforce of 60,000 additional employees.</p>
  <p>Bergin said, “Through our SAP SuccessFactors journey, we’re in a great place with a single master source of truth on our colleague and contingent workforce data – and our organizational hierarchy.”</p>
  <h2 id="brightspeed-manages-rapid-growth-and-contingent-workforce">Brightspeed Manages Rapid Growth and Contingent Workforce</h2>
  <p><a href="https://www.brightspeedplans.com/about">Brightspeed</a> is a telecommunications company that provides affordable, quality internet in rural areas of the U.S. Since it started in 2022 with 30 permanent employees, Brightspeed has grown exponentially through acquisition. Today, it has 4,200 employees using SAP solutions and a sizable contingent workforce. To manage growth, Brightspeed implemented SAP SuccessFactors solutions, SAP Fieldglass solutions, and SAP S/4HANA Cloud.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="predict-manage-and-create-a-future-ready-workforce-with-sap-successfactors">Predict, manage, and create a future-ready workforce with SAP SuccessFactors</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm.html?campaigncode=CRM-YI23-HXM-2053446&#x26;source=text-glo-SAPNews">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Greg Williams, director of Human Resources Information Systems, Brightspeed, summarized the value of an integrated approach for the organization: “Finance is up and running on SAP S/4HANA and with SAP Fieldglass solutions. We import that data into SAP SuccessFactors Learning, so our contractors can train on compliance and technical training. The SAP S/4HANA data is integrated into <a href="https://api.sap.com/package/SuccessFactorsEmployeeCentralwithThirdPartyTimeVendorWorkForceSoftwareWFS/overview">WFS</a>, which is our time system. We capture millions of dollars of project costs. Those are sent back to SAP S/4HANA on a pay-for-period basis.”</p>
  <h2 id="versuni-gains-agility-with-hxm-and-connected-cloud-erp">Versuni Gains Agility with HXM and Connected Cloud ERP</h2>
  <p><a href="https://www.versuni.com/">Versuni</a>, formerly known as Philipps Domestic Appliances, is a consumer products company with the purpose to help people turn their houses into homes. It took the unique opportunity of reinventing itself as an independent company to transform its entire technology landscape. To succeed in a dynamic, consumer marketplace, it had to adopt best-of-suite applications that power advanced, digital-first consumer goods organizations.</p>
  <p>By connecting SAP S/4HANA Cloud to SAP SuccessFactors solutions, Versuni has achieved three key benefits: a seamless user journey based on a single source of truth across the entire landscape; increased visibility achieved from the integration with other systems, especially finance; and improved reporting, which is leading to better decision-making. Lokesh Rastogi, IT platform leader for Finance and HR at Versuni, summarized: “It’s one source of truth, one system, and one number.”</p>
  <h2 id="nestlé-creates-engaging-people-experiences-at-scale">Nestlé Creates Engaging People Experiences at Scale</h2>
  <p><a href="https://www.nestle.com/">Nestlé</a>, one of the world’s largest food and beverage companies, is using RISE with SAP to help advance its digital transformation. With 275,000 employees in 188 countries, Nestlé focused on the modernization of its HR systems. SAP SuccessFactors solutions now enable it to standardize and automate HR processes and provide a personalized employee experience from recruitment to retirement. Nestlé plans to continue its journey to migrate its entire business operations to <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/s4hana-private-edition.html">SAP S/4HANA Cloud</a> with finance and procurement already live. To learn more, watch this <a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2023/09/5c433416-8d7e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html?campaigncode=CRM-YI23-HXM-2053446&#x26;source=text-glo-SAPNews">video</a>.</p>
  <p>Giancarlo Pala, head of IT/HR, Nestlé S.A., said, “SAP SuccessFactors is our people backbone. It provides the common processes, systems, and data that let us create engaging people experiences at scale.”</p>
  <h2 id="accelerating-business-performance">Accelerating Business Performance</h2>
  <p>SAP customers are experiencing firsthand the value of having HR and finance connected on a single cloud platform to help improve speed, accuracy, and insights. This integration can extend beyond the data to connect business processes and employee experiences across all business areas. To find out more about the benefits of connected cloud HR and ERP, watch <a href="https://www.sap.com/events/successconnect/virtual.html?campaigncode=CRM-YI23-HXM-2055448&#x26;source=text-glo-SAPNews?campaigncode=CRM-YI23-HXM-2053446&#x26;source=ctabutton-glo-SAPNews">SuccessConnect Virtual</a> on demand.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="follow-sap-news-on-linkedin">Follow SAP News on LinkedIn</h3>
        <p><em><a href="">Connect with us</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fieldglass</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-employee-central</category>
            <category>sap-event/successconnect</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pushing the Boundaries of Procurement Customer Support with Innovations]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/procurement-customer-support-innovations</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/procurement-customer-support-innovations</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In this interview, SAP's Rohan Patel gives insight into how SAP support can benefit procurement customers. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1560e17ebf571c1cad896fad5b3fe9c897622bb2c.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1560e17ebf571c1cad896fad5b3fe9c897622bb2c.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1560e17ebf571c1cad896fad5b3fe9c897622bb2c.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Pushing the Boundaries of Procurement Customer Support with Innovations" src="./media_1560e17ebf571c1cad896fad5b3fe9c897622bb2c.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="pushing-the-boundaries-of-procurement-customer-support-with-innovations">Pushing the Boundaries of Procurement Customer Support with Innovations</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>In today’s environment, customers are reevaluating how they use and source software solutions to run their business. The move from on-premise only solutions to the cloud is SAP’s reality as a cloud vendor.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“Customers undergo a cloud transformation because they want to accelerate their time to realize business value and they want to take advantage of innovations faster,” says Rohan Patel, global vice president, Customer Support and Innovation, Product Support – Procurement, SAP. “That’s what helps them maintain a competitive edge. And they want to do this while decreasing overall cost and minimizing risk.”</p>
  <p>This is where <a href="https://support.sap.com/en/offerings-programs/strategy.html">Real-Time Support</a> from SAP can add real value. In this conversation, Patel gives insight into how SAP support can benefit procurement customers.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Q: How are you supporting procurement customers on their journey to the cloud?</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><strong>A:</strong> Support in the old, on-premise world is what I like to call ‘break-fix’ support. When something failed, the IT department submitted a ticket for support, the problem was fixed, and communication ended until another issue arose. Being a break-fix support provider doesn’t work in the cloud environment. Support requires speed and foresight. Support today identifies problems and optimizes products before customers even notice something’s not working as it should.</p>
  <p>SAP’s strategy is predictive and proactive. We want continuous dialogue with customers to provide insights and guidance that are a value-add so we’re there long before something breaks. Success in the cloud requires adoption outside of the traditional IT environment. Business end users and lines of business, like procurement, supply chain, and HR, expect easy-to-use support portals that are intuitive and quickly anticipate user needs.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-creates-support-programs-to-drive-an-innovative-and-consistent-experience">SAP creates support programs to drive an innovative and consistent experience</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://support.sap.com/en/offerings-programs/strategy.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Can you share some examples of how SAP is using data to enhance predictive support?</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The tools we use not only help us deliver a great experience to our customers, they also continue to improve the SAP solution itself. Consider the cloud health monitoring tools within <a href="https://support.sap.com/en/alm/sap-cloud-alm.html">SAP Cloud ALM</a>, our application lifecycle management solution that helps streamline the way our customers implement and operate their cloud and hybrid environments across the entire business.</p>
  <p>These tools can analyze what’s happening at the customer experience layer – for example, how long it takes a specific page to load, how long a user needs to complete a task, and any delays that could frustrate users, hinder adoption, and slow business outcomes. We act proactively at the engineering and cloud operations layer to help continuously improve that user experience.</p>
  <p>We also use knowledge and data to improve the support experience, such as with <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-network.html">SAP Business Network</a>, which has millions of active trading partners. This business-to-business network of companies connecting, transacting, and partnering with numerous shared processes and information expands the SAP footprint well beyond the four walls of traditional operations.</p>
  <p>Equally important is that our consumers today aren’t just IT support users, but rather work in departments throughout the clients’ operations. We’ve taken steps to help meet the needs of all those different user types. We can provide quick, easy-to-understand guidance and answers to their questions using intuitive, personalized, and real-time channels driven by both humans and artificial intelligence (AI). This recommendation engine can provide guided answers based on who the users are, what they’re doing in the application, or what questions they ask. Users can quickly get useful and relevant content for answering their questions. The data from those guided-answer experiences is then fed into the product road map to help make the entire user experience more optimal and eliminate problems before they happen.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>What have procurement customers seen in 2023 from SAP support?</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Our procurement coverage in 2023 hits two themes: harmonization and Real-Time Support. Let me begin with the harmonization perspective. We’re taking significant steps to create a customer support experience that’s consistent across all SAP solutions – most notably a single entry point to SAP support with <a href="https://me.sap.com/">SAP for Me</a>. SAP Fieldglass solutions went live on SAP for Me case management in March 2023, and SAP Ariba solutions and SAP Business Network will soon follow. The SAP for Me portal can give users the information and answers they need, specific to the solution they’re using. Earlier this year, procurement support went live on <a href="https://community.sap.com/">SAP Community</a>, where our business and IT users can access blog posts, tips, and connect with experts. Even customers and partners can provide an additional layer of insights and guidance, especially to a specific industry.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-real-time-support">Learn more about Real-Time Support</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://support.sap.com/en/offerings-programs/strategy.html">Explore now</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>This year we have been working to bring our Real-Time Support concept to reality for procurement. When I talk about Real-Time Support, I mean support that is always on, continuously evolves, and adapts to customer needs. This can be direct access to support experts for business-critical processes when and where customers need it. It’s the live support channels such as <a href="https://support.sap.com/en/my-support/product-support.html?anchorId=section_519294480">Expert Chat</a>, Ask an Expert Peer, context-sensitive help, <a href="https://support.sap.com/en/my-support/product-support.html?anchorId=section_1255553798">support built into our software</a>, and <a href="/2022/05/artificial-intelligence-future-of-customer-support-experiences">AI-driven self-service access</a> to a vast knowledge base and user community.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>What do you see in the future of support for procurement?</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>I envision a day when customers don’t need to see or hear from us because we’re already working behind the scenes to give our customers a seamless, reliable, and delightful experience. The ultimate vision is preventative support with the help of AI and machine learning – in other words, self-healing IT systems.</p>
  <p>Of course, there will always be times when customers need us. In those times, SAP is prepared to offer as simple of a support experience as possible, such as with <a href="https://support.sap.com/en/my-support/product-support.html?anchorId=section_1255553798">Built-In Support</a> and direct access to experts or a quick call to solve an issue the moment it occurs. We also continuously look to disrupt ourselves by using new technologies such as ChatGPT to enable self-help or self-guidance and provide the best possible customer experience.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>What sets the SAP support experience apart in the industry?</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP mindfully takes steps that help give customers the best support experience possible. We can provide a cohesive array of support channels, self-service tools, and cloud health and integration monitoring. Even with these successes in hand, SAP will continuously push the boundaries of customer support with new innovations, help ensure support interactions are delightful, and offer Real-Time Support that can bring ambition to life.</p>
  <p>Follow Rohan Patel on <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/rohan-patel-1897941/">LinkedIn</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Regina Postman is part of Customer Support and Innovation Communications at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="follow-sap-news-on-linkedin">Follow SAP News on LinkedIn</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news">Connect with us</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/product-support</category>
            <category>news-tag/real-time-support</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fieldglass</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-for-me</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Future of Procurement Is Already a Reality at SAP Spend Connect Live]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/procurement-news-sap-spend-connect-live</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/procurement-news-sap-spend-connect-live</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[At SAP Spend Connect Live, we announced a series of procurement innovations focused on streamlining procurement processes. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>product/sap-ariba-buying</category>
            <category>product/sap-ariba-contracts</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-concur</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fieldglass</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-spend-connect-live</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Announces Winners of the SAP Global Intelligent Spend and Business Network Partner Excellence Awards for 2023]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/2023-sap-global-intelligent-spend-business-network-partner-excellence-awards</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/2023-sap-global-intelligent-spend-business-network-partner-excellence-awards</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Six SAP Global Intelligent Spend and Business Network Partner Excellence Awards were presented at SAP Spend Connect Live in Vienna.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-concur</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fieldglass</category>
            <category>sap-award/sap-global-lob-partner-excellence-awards</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-spend-connect-live</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Latest Innovations in Spend Management Revealed at SAP Spend Connect Live]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/innovations-ai-spend-management-sap-spend-connect-live</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/innovations-ai-spend-management-sap-spend-connect-live</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[As shown at SAP Spend Connect Live, SAP has made it a mission to enable the use of generative AI in spend management. Read to find out how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-spend</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-concur</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fieldglass</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-spend-connect-live</category>
            <category>topic/spend-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Standard Chartered Gains Agility with Total Workforce Management]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/standard-chartered-total-workforce-solution</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/standard-chartered-total-workforce-solution</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Standard Chartered uses total workforce management with SAP SuccessFactors and SAP Fieldglass for one view of permanent and external workers.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/banking</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/external-workforce-management</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fieldglass</category>
            <category>sap-award/sap-innovation-awards</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-employee-central</category>
            <category>news-tag/total-workforce-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No Breaks for SAP Spend Management Solutions]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/no-breaks-sap-spend-management</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/no-breaks-sap-spend-management</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP spend management solutions continue to help our customers and gain recognition from trusted review sites. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-spend</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-concur</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fieldglass</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-spend-connect-live</category>
            <category>topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/trustradius</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Winning Combination: SAP Customers and Our Spend Management Solutions]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/winning-combination-sap-customers-spend-management</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/winning-combination-sap-customers-spend-management</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Our commitment to delivering a complete set of SAP spend management solutions has only grown, as shown by the recognitions we've received.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc-marketscape</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-spend</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-concur</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fieldglass</category>
            <category>topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/trustradius</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Vodafone Builds Its Future-Ready Workforce on Cloud HR Foundations]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/vodafone-builds-cloud-hr-foundations</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/vodafone-builds-cloud-hr-foundations</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Vodafone Group Plc implements SAP SuccessFactors solutions as its cloud HR foundation for improved efficiency and employee engagement.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fieldglass</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-learning</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-work-zone</category>
            <category>sap-event/successconnect</category>
            <category>news-tag/total-workforce-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP and Icertis Deliver Enterprise-Wide Value with Contract Intelligence]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/sap-and-icertis-contract-intelligence-enterprise-wide-value</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/sap-and-icertis-contract-intelligence-enterprise-wide-value</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP and Icertis are turning static contracts into structured data that connects to SAP solutions. Learn more about their partnership.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>product/sap-cpq</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-endorsed-apps</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fieldglass</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Customers Continue to Solve Their Toughest Business Challenges with Spend Management Solutions]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/sap-customers-solve-business-challenges-with-spend-management-solutions</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/sap-customers-solve-business-challenges-with-spend-management-solutions</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Customers leverage our procurement, external workforce, travel, and supply chain solutions to help understand and solve business challenges.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-spend</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-concur</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fieldglass</category>
            <category>topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/trustradius</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Supply Chain Due Diligence Acts: What You Should Know]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/01/lksg-supply-chain-due-diligence-acts-what-to-know</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/01/lksg-supply-chain-due-diligence-acts-what-to-know</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn what you need to know about LkSG and other supply chain due diligence acts that aim to create more transparent supply chains.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-concur</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fieldglass</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Thriving Amid Uncertainty and Disruption: 2023 Predictions for Intelligent Spend Management and Business Network]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/2023-predictions-for-spend-management-business-network</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/2023-predictions-for-spend-management-business-network</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[How we deal with uncertainty and disruption can set us apart. Get the 2023 predictions for spend management and business networks.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-concur</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fieldglass</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-spend-connect-live</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reflections on SAP Spend Connect Live: How We Are Earning Customer Trust]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/sap-spend-connect-live-recap-earning-customer-trust</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/sap-spend-connect-live-recap-earning-customer-trust</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In this SAP Spend Connect Live recap, get the details on how SAP continues to earn customer trust as well as recent accomplishments.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a24b7a5adff5dc172e8a5a7c1d904d545aab9cee.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a24b7a5adff5dc172e8a5a7c1d904d545aab9cee.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1a24b7a5adff5dc172e8a5a7c1d904d545aab9cee.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Reflections on SAP Spend Connect Live: How We Are Earning Customer Trust" src="./media_1a24b7a5adff5dc172e8a5a7c1d904d545aab9cee.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="reflections-on-sap-spend-connect-live-how-we-are-earning-customer-trust">Reflections on SAP Spend Connect Live: How We Are Earning Customer Trust</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>The events of recent weeks — SAP Spend Connect Live, a slew of industry accolades, and most importantly the trust our customers have shown us — have put a permanent smile on my face.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/events/spend-connect-live.html">SAP Spend Connect Live</a> in Dallas was incredible. Attendees were engaged in the conference and passionate about the important work they do. But most gratifying were my conversations with customers, who spoke about how they trust SAP to help them solve large, complex problems. Things like economic challenges, supply chain disruptions, and sustainability, along with environmental, social, and governance (ESG) goals: these are challenges SAP is uniquely qualified to address, and we’ve made it our purpose to help our customers tackle them.</p>
  <p>It was an honor to <a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2022/11/823c1eda-4c7e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">share the SAP Spend Connect Live stage</a> with Christine Hipp of Los Alamos National Labs (pictured below), who spoke about a successful transformation with SAP Ariba and SAP Fieldglass solutions. Likewise, we were all fascinated by Patricia Miller’s account of Accenture’s internal services spend journey with SAP Fieldglass.</p>
  <p>We came to Dallas to hear from SAP customers like these — and we were not disappointed.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ab0014b1b6bc9d525c8ed7d2becdf7cff9e12028.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ab0014b1b6bc9d525c8ed7d2becdf7cff9e12028.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1ab0014b1b6bc9d525c8ed7d2becdf7cff9e12028.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_1ab0014b1b6bc9d525c8ed7d2becdf7cff9e12028.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2250" height="1500">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p><em>© LILA PHOTO</em></p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="explore-the-sap-spend-connect-virtual-experience">Explore the SAP Spend Connect Virtual Experience</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/events/spend-connect-live.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="recognitions-accolades-and-awards">Recognitions, Accolades, and Awards</h2>
  <p>SAP Spend Connect Live was a great moment for SAP and the organizations that use our solutions to run their business. In fact, more than a few customers told me we should “brag a little more” about what we’re doing.</p>
  <p>I won’t do that, but I would like to share some of the accolades that our solutions and our customers have received in the past few months.</p>
  <p><strong>SAP Ariba</strong></p>
  <ul>
    <li>SAP Named a Leader for the seventh consecutive time in the <a href="https://www.ariba.com/resources/library/library-pages/2022-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-procure-to-pay-suites">2022 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Procure-to-Pay Suites</a> for SAP Ariba</li>
    <li>SAP was recognized in the <a href="https://www.ariba.com/resources/library/library-pages/2022-gartner-critical-capabilities-for-procure-to-pay-suites">2022 Gartner Critical Capabilities for Procure-to-Pay Suites</a> among the three highest vendors across all the five Gartner Use Cases and ranked highest for the Use Case Service Focused</li>
    <li>No. 1 in Procure-to-Pay, <a href="https://www.g2.com/reports/63afc547-2264-438d-91af-1b7b929e30b9/preview">G2 Fall 2022 Grid® Reports</a></li>
    <li>Top Rated Procurement Software award, TrustRadius</li>
    <li>No. 1 leading procurement software provider, <em><a href="https://supplychaindigital.com/procurement/top-10-sap-oracle-lead-way-on-procurement-solutions">Supply Chain Digital</a></em></li>
    <li>Procurement Platform, <em><a href="https://procurementmag.com/magazine/procurement-magazine-november-2022">Procurement Magazine</a></em></li>
  </ul>
  <p><strong>SAP Concur</strong></p>
  <ul>
    <li>No. 1 for Worldwide Travel and Expense Management Software, <a href="https://eur03.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.concur.com%2Fen-us%2Fresource-center%2Freports%2Fidc-worldwide-travel-and-expense-management-software-market-shares-2021&#x26;data=05%7C01%7Cmike.conners%40sap.com%7Cf0072dc7a5b6487c8e3b08dabce6abc3%7C42f7676cf455423c82f6dc2d99791af7%7C0%7C0%7C638029996180986109%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJWIjoiMC4wLjAwMDAiLCJQIjoiV2luMzIiLCJBTiI6Ik1haWwiLCJXVCI6Mn0%3D%7C3000%7C%7C%7C&#x26;sdata=aFgPT7hdI8WoAO%2B%2BsYONCoMMaGZIclfHWNhjKz4SfRY%3D&#x26;reserved=0">IDC</a></li>
    <li>No. 1 leader in Expense Management, Travel and Expense Management, and Invoice Management, <a href="https://www.g2.com/reports">G2 Fall 2022 Grid® Reports</a></li>
    <li>2022 Top-Rated Software (Concur Travel &#x26; Expense), <a href="https://www.trustradius.com/expense-management#bestof">TrustRadius</a></li>
    <li>No. 1 in ZDNet’s list of the five best travel planner apps (TripIt), <a href="https://www.zdnet.com/article/best-trip-planner-app/">ZDNet</a></li>
  </ul>
  <p><strong>SAP Fieldglass</strong></p>
  <ul>
    <li>No. 1 in Strategic Sourcing, <a href="https://www.g2.com/reports/c2ce88b3-670a-4d70-8077-78fe942e0b20/preview">G2 Fall 2022 Grid® Reports</a></li>
    <li>Market Leader, <a href="http://ardentpartners.com/">Ardent Partners</a>’ 2022 Vendor Management System (VMS) Technology Advisor</li>
  </ul>
  <p>SAP Fieldglass and SAP Ariba were also selected for Spend Matters’ <a href="https://spendmatters.com/almanac/50-to-know-2022/">50 Procurement Providers to Know for 2022</a>. And Capgemini, an SAP Fieldglass customer, is the winner in the “Innovations in Talent” category of the <a href="https://futureofsourcing.com/innovations-in-talent-management-sap-capgemini">Sourcing Industry Group (SIG)</a> Future of Sourcing Awards.</p>
  <h2 id="beyond-the-accolades">Beyond the Accolades</h2>
  <p>While it is great to receive industry accolades, at the end of the day, our truest measure of success lies with our customers. This quarter, hundreds of SAP customers worldwide — including Chow Tai Fook Jewellery Group, the City of Vienna, Austria, The Pennsylvania State University, Dole Asia Holdings Pte., Ltd, and Hapag-Lloyd Aktiengesellschaft — are engaging with SAP, either for the first time or by expanding their footprint, to leverage our market-leading procurement, travel management, and supply chain finance solutions.</p>
  <p>Here are a few of their stories:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><a href="https://www.chowtaifook.com/en/">Chow Tai Fook Jewellery Group Limited</a> is a top jewelry brand with a huge retail network in China and the rest of the world. To support the group’s strategy to drive sustainable growth empowered by technology, the company chose SAP Ariba software to build its unified digital procurement system, deploy procurement in the cloud, improve end-to-end visibility and efficiency, reduce procurement cost, and greatly improve business efficiency.</li>
    <li><a href="https://www.psu.edu/">The Pennsylvania State University</a> has been using SAP Concur solutions for more than 15 years. This quarter, it chose to expand that partnership as it has seen an increase in student, faculty, and administrator travel and expense management requirements.</li>
    <li><a href="https://www.dolenz.co.nz/about/about-dole">Dole Asia Holdings Pte., Ltd</a>. is a Singapore-based, global consumer food and beverage company that produces and distributes fresh and packaged fruit products. It has chosen <a href="/2022/03/sap-completes-acquisition-of-taulia">Taulia</a>, part of SAP, for Taulia Dynamic Discounting and Taulia Supply Chain Finance on the Taulia multi-funder network. This will enable the company to strengthen its supply chain by improving the financial resilience of suppliers, therefore improving sustainability.</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="another-reason-to-smile">Another Reason to Smile</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-more-news-and-coverage-from-sap-spend-connect-live">Read more news and coverage from SAP Spend Connect Live</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="news.sap.com/tags/sap-spend-connect-live">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>I am also proud that our team considers it our purpose to lend a hand to the people who have served our nation. We are thrilled to announce that Nettie, short for “Network,” the beautiful service dog our North America sales team helped to sponsor, is now a graduate of the <a href="https://k9sforwarriors.org">K9s For Warriors</a> program. She has joined her Warrior, Kevin, and we wish them a wonderful life together.</p>
  <h2 id="our-customers-moment">Our Customers’ Moment</h2>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18e2063e48f8dcabc916ceaa42618a59591b8258b.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18e2063e48f8dcabc916ceaa42618a59591b8258b.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_18e2063e48f8dcabc916ceaa42618a59591b8258b.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Kevin and Nettie" src="./media_18e2063e48f8dcabc916ceaa42618a59591b8258b.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2250" height="1496">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p>As we near the end of 2022, we are working harder than ever to help our current customers, as well as customers we haven’t met yet, to address their biggest challenges and achieve their business goals — always with purpose; now, with a smile.</p>
  <h2 id="experience-sap-spend-connect-live-virtually">Experience SAP Spend Connect Live virtually</h2>
  <p>If you were not able to join us in Dallas, check out the <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/events/spend-connect-live.html">SAP Spend Connect Virtual Experience</a>. This on-demand forum will share recordings of the keynotes and select breakout sessions from the conference. It will also feature additional, recorded sessions not seen at SAP Spend Connect Live.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><em>Jeff Collier is chief revenue officer for SAP Intelligent Spend and Business Network.</em></p>
        <p>GARTNER is a registered trademark and service mark of Gartner and Magic Quadrant is a registered trademark of Gartner, Inc. and/or its affiliates in the U.S. and internationally and are used herein with permission. All rights reserved.<br>Gartner does not endorse any vendor, product or service depicted in its research publications, and does not advise technology users to select only those vendors with the highest ratings or other designation. Gartner research publications consist of the opinions of Gartner’s research organization and should not be construed as statements of fact. Gartner disclaims all warranties, expressed or implied, with respect to this research, including any warranties of merchantability or fitness for a particular purpose.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-concur</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fieldglass</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-spend-connect-live</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Carrying on SAP’s Heritage of Innovation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/spend-management-at-sap-spend-connect-live-heritage-innovation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/spend-management-at-sap-spend-connect-live-heritage-innovation</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[News around spend management at SAP Spend Connect Live showcased how SAP enables organizations to manage their complete, end-to-end spend.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fieldglass</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-spend-connect-live</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Fieldglass: Cloud Innovation for Commercial Regulated Industries]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/sap-fieldglass-sap-ns2-cloud-innovation-commercial-regulated-industries</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/sap-fieldglass-sap-ns2-cloud-innovation-commercial-regulated-industries</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With SAP Fieldglass at SAP NS2, government agencies and highly regulated industries in the U.S. can adopt market-leading cloud applications.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/external-workforce-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fieldglass</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ns2</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-spend-connect-live</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Announces Winners of the SAP Global Intelligent Spend and Business Network Partner Excellence Awards 2022]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/sap-global-intelligent-spend-and-business-network-partner-excellence-awards-2022</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/sap-global-intelligent-spend-and-business-network-partner-excellence-awards-2022</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Global Intelligent Spend and Business Network Partner Excellence Awards were presented at SAP Spend Connect Live in Dallas.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-concur</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fieldglass</category>
            <category>sap-award/sap-global-lob-partner-excellence-awards</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-spend-connect-live</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Rounds Up Big Innovations in Spend Management at SAP Spend Connect Live]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/sap-spend-connect-live-spend-management-innovations</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/sap-spend-connect-live-spend-management-innovations</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[From SAP Spend Connect Live, SAP announced spend management innovations and milestones. Get the news from the event.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-concur</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fieldglass</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-spend-connect-live</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>