<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/sap-btp-in-the-sap-ecosystem/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Partner TheValueChain Trusts in SAP BTP]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/02/sap-partner-thevaluechain-trusts-sap-btp</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/02/sap-partner-thevaluechain-trusts-sap-btp</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Read to learn how SAP BTP delivers value for TheValueChain's customers and helps to drive innovation within its own teams.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16bf2da8fac6f5d95a7c2802ea45f607d9f718153.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16bf2da8fac6f5d95a7c2802ea45f607d9f718153.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_16bf2da8fac6f5d95a7c2802ea45f607d9f718153.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Partner TheValueChain Trusts in SAP BTP" src="./media_16bf2da8fac6f5d95a7c2802ea45f607d9f718153.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-partner-thevaluechain-trusts-in-sap-btp">SAP Partner TheValueChain Trusts in SAP BTP</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-btp-is-future-proof-innovation-says-zoosh">SAP BTP Is “Future-Proof Innovation” Says Zoosh</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2022/01/sap-btp-is-future-proof-innovation-says-zoosh">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>As the name would suggest, value is key to the work TheValueChain delivers for its partners. As a service provider, the Belgium-based partner’s aim is to improve its customers’ investments in SAP tech and add value to their businesses.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>With a focus on the wholesale distribution, utilities, manufacturing, and professional services industries, TheValueChain first used SAP Cloud Platform when it was managing a global tech rollout for one of its customers.</p>
  <p>When <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">SAP Business Technology Platform</a> launched, TheValueChain could see how it would provide complete end-to-end enablement and support for its customers.</p>
  <p>“We were early adopters of SAP BTP, using it in its original incarnation to manage an <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/s4hana-erp.html">SAP S/4HANA Cloud</a> rollout,” explains <a href="https://people.sap.com/kennymattheyssen">Kenny Mattheyssen</a>, the supply chain team lead at TheValueChain. “We could create apps and extend our customer’s system. It was such a success that we’ve used it time and again since, for both cloud and on-premise customers.”</p>
  <p>“We have always been a front-runner with intelligent robotic process automation (RPA), but when SAP BTP was unveiled, we were able to take a step back and see it as a complete solution, not just for RPA, but as a big automation platform that serves as a great toolbox, where you take and use the tools you need depending on what you’re delivering. It is fast for integration. It’s a great solution for RPA and for workflow management. We can pick the services that work for our customers.”</p>
  <p>The platform has enabled TheValueChain to extend its remit and become an innovation partner, collaborating with its customers on process innovation.</p>
  <p>Adds Mattheyssen: “We are mainly a service provider, but we want to be a product development company too, and we can do that now with SAP BTP. We have the innovation, we have the methodology, and we’re using the platform to develop packages that we can take to market, either as TheValueChain or via <a href="https://store.sap.com/">SAP Store</a>.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-btp-the-platform-for-the-intelligent-enterprise">SAP BTP: The platform for the Intelligent Enterprise</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>According to Mattheyssen, <a href="/topics/business-technology-platform">SAP BTP</a> makes life better for partners and customers. It’s an enabler for “things that were not possible before;” an automation platform that does all the previously manual business tasks.</p>
  <p>The value it brings, he says, is very tangible: SAP BTP can be agile and quick and so the return on investment can be almost immediate.</p>
  <p>The customer experience is also reflective of the way consumers choose and use apps. “You shop in SAP BTP as you would do in an app store – the whole experience is being received extremely well by customers.”</p>
  <p>He says they chose to work on SAP BTP for three main reasons: for its seamless integration, for the prepackaged content, and for the competitive licensing model.</p>
  <p>“We trust in the tech. We don’t see any reason to look elsewhere for our development needs. SAP is on a really good track with SAP BTP. The innovation flows automatically into the platform and we’re able to use it,” says Mattheyssen.</p>
  <p>“If I were to sum up the benefits of SAP BTP in three words, I’d say instant business value, agile, and innovative.”</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-btp-in-the-sap-ecosystem</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP BTP Is "Future-Proof Innovation" Says Zoosh]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/01/sap-btp-is-future-proof-innovation-says-zoosh</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/01/sap-btp-is-future-proof-innovation-says-zoosh</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Venture builders and SAP partner Zoosh uses SAP BTP to create cloud-based solutions for its customers. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1165c6b35143196e4459dad93240252f074bafc50.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1165c6b35143196e4459dad93240252f074bafc50.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1165c6b35143196e4459dad93240252f074bafc50.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP BTP Is “Future-Proof Innovation” Says Zoosh" src="./media_1165c6b35143196e4459dad93240252f074bafc50.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-btp-is-future-proof-innovation-says-zoosh">SAP BTP Is “Future-Proof Innovation” Says Zoosh</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="bluestonex-a-massive-advocate-for-sap-btp">Bluestonex: A “Massive Advocate” for SAP BTP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/11/bluestonex-massive-advocate-for-sap-btp">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><a href="https://www.zooshgroup.com/">Zoosh</a> is a venture building company that helps its customers to validate new ideas and then build, deploy, and operate them using cloud technology.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Businesses go to them to innovate and transform, and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">SAP Business Technology Platform</a> is the platform Zoosh uses to enable that process.</p>
  <p>One of its most recent SAP BTP success stories is OptaHaul, a solution for the dairy industry that streamlines the often-complex process of collecting and delivering milk to the processing plant.</p>
  <p>Mervyn Graham, co-founder and CEO of Zoosh, explains how it works: “Optahaul automatically understands all of the factors and parameters that come into play when collecting milk from suppliers – from the turning circles on farms, to the availability of on-site pumps, to the amount and type of milk being collected and the distances between farms and processing plants. It allows for greater efficiency in planning and kilometers traveled, as well as can tangibly reduce milk product waste and carbon emissions.”</p>
  <p>Zoosh was initially approached to solve the problem by a milk producer in Hungary, Eastern Europe’s largest milk producer. But, based on research, it became clear to the team that the issues were commonplace across the dairy industry.</p>
  <p>“Dairy processors were using generic, traditional logistics planning software that didn’t understand the industry and the variables within it,” adds Graham. “Dairy processors need one system that offers complete synchronicity, bringing together every element of the milk collection workflow.”</p>
  <p>Zoosh is a ‘design-led’ organization, with every project starting with a research and consultation phase so the team can interview, observe, and put into context how the customer will use and benefit from the solution. Then it builds the tech response around its acquired understanding of the user and business priorities.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-btp-the-platform-for-the-intelligent-enterprise">SAP BTP: The platform for the Intelligent Enterprise</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>What <a href="/topics/business-technology-platform">SAP BTP</a> enables the company to do is to build that response in a simple way.</p>
  <p>“Previously the SAP portfolio was more fragmented and compartmentalized. SAP BTP is a cocktail of enablers that together can be quite powerful,” says Graham. “SAP BTP encompasses all the tech we are familiar with and have typically leveraged for solution creation, but it simplifies the conversation that we have with our customers.”</p>
  <p>Summing up the platform, Graham describes it as ‘future-proof innovation’ that can work for both greenfield customers and existing SAP customers.</p>
  <p>“With SAP BTP, you’re investing in a much more solid experience, one with much less risk, that has scalability when you need it,” adds Graham. “You’re keeping the business core systems clean by having this isolated and agile innovation platform that you can expand and contract with your varying business needs.”</p>
  <p>While there is always going to be a need to service customers’ IT needs and solutions, what SAP BTP does is allow partners to become product developers. As consumers become ever more app-savvy, customers expect easy-to-access, plug-and-play apps that solve their business needs.</p>
  <p>“This is the future of our partner ecosystem: we’re seeing more and more partners building parallel business streams so they can invest in product development,” says Graham.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-btp-in-the-sap-ecosystem</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bluestonex: A "Massive Advocate" for SAP BTP]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/bluestonex-massive-advocate-for-sap-btp</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/bluestonex-massive-advocate-for-sap-btp</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Bluestonex began using the application development and integration capabilities of SAP BTP in 2018 because of its speed and agility.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1734fd603b43bbe281df9fe532bf472bc6839924a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1734fd603b43bbe281df9fe532bf472bc6839924a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1734fd603b43bbe281df9fe532bf472bc6839924a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Bluestonex: A “Massive Advocate” for SAP BTP" src="./media_1734fd603b43bbe281df9fe532bf472bc6839924a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="bluestonex-a-massive-advocate-for-sap-btp">Bluestonex: A “Massive Advocate” for SAP BTP</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-btp-accelerate-business-outcomes-with-integration-data-to-value-and-extensibility">SAP BTP: Accelerate business outcomes with integration, data to value, and extensibility</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Innovation is built into the DNA at <a href="https://bluestonex.com/">Bluestonex</a> – it’s what makes it tick. As part of SAP AppHaus Network, it shifted its entire business processes to run on SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP), making this boutique team the perfect advocate for converting its own customers to the tech platform.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Recognized for design, innovation, and user experience, Bluestonex began using the application development and integration capabilities of <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">SAP BTP</a> in 2018, then known as SAP Cloud Platform, because of its speed and agility.</p>
  <p>“Being an innovation partner, we wanted to be able to move and deliver quickly for our customers,” explains Dan Barton, COO and co-founder. “SAP BTP allows us to do that. Plus, the low-cost, high-impact nature of the platform is always going to be an attractive proposition to customers. So, it was a clear route for us as a business and for our customers.”</p>
  <p>Bluestonex sees itself as a true integration of a client’s team, holding their hands as they shift to SAP BTP. They work with customers of all shapes and sizes and from cross-industry sectors, everything from food and drinks to aerospace. However, Barton is clear that SAP BTP breaks down any misconceptions that SAP is purely for larger-sized businesses.</p>
  <p>“It’s very, very well-suited to micro-businesses. It’s agile, it’s low-cost from an entry point of view, and it has a huge number of capabilities that can grow over time. SAP BTP has opened up new opportunities for us within the micro-business market because, typically, there isn’t another product out there to match it.”</p>
  <p>Barton says customers can often become “over-awed” when faced with all the different tech products available to run and manage businesses. He and the team use SAP BTP to “transform that user experience.”</p>
  <p>“It’s a really easy entry point: instead of people having to use multiple clicks and screen jumps, SAP BTP gets rid of that. It streamlines and strips away complexity to give a consistent user experience,” Barton explains. “And that transformation is key. When they realize what a nice platform it is, it opens the door to other experiences, such as chatbots and automation. It’s all there and plugs in really nicely. Lots of customers love the fact that they can start small and grow with the platform.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-sap-apphaus-network">Learn more about SAP AppHaus Network</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://apphaus.sap.com/network">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>It also helps Bluestonex to grow as a business, driving its specialism in innovation and, in turn, encouraging customers to think in new ways. “This is a massive shift, not only are they going from running different processes into one, smooth, easy-to-use platform, we’re seeing a big cultural shift in the way our customers think,” he adds.</p>
  <p>Being part of SAP AppHaus Network means Bluestonex can access the latest, state-of-the-art design thinking methodologies, helping to move customers to new digital experiences.</p>
  <p>From its converted chapel office space, Bluestonex regularly invites customers in to co-innovate.</p>
  <p>“We invite our customers here and bring them out of their comfort zone,” says Barton. “And we have a usability lab where we get customer input on an idea as early in the development process as possible, so that key stakeholders know what they’re going to get and can be part of the iteration process. This helps to set expectations and build a better business case.”</p>
  <p>To sum up SAP BTP in three words? “Strategic, innovative, and responsive,” he says. “It’s opened a different angle for us. We would always go and speak to our existing SAP customers, but this is different. Now we go to a competitor’s customer, we go to micro-businesses, because it’s flexible and cost effective. SAP BTP is a very strategic platform: there’s a sense that whatever a business does in the future, that platform is going to be there and continue to add value. It’s future-proof and I’m a massive advocate for it.”</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-apphaus</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-apphaus-network</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-btp-in-the-sap-ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-tag/ux</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Award-Winning SAP Partner Clarivos Creates Dedicated Role for Customer Success Manager]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/clarivos-creates-dedicated-role-customer-success-manager</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/clarivos-creates-dedicated-role-customer-success-manager</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Clarivos, an award-winning SAP partner, is investing in customer success by creating a dedicated customer success manager role. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1316a4793c0be932c172b8ef5c5c96203bce86784.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1316a4793c0be932c172b8ef5c5c96203bce86784.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1316a4793c0be932c172b8ef5c5c96203bce86784.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Award-Winning SAP Partner Clarivos Creates Dedicated Role for Customer Success Manager" src="./media_1316a4793c0be932c172b8ef5c5c96203bce86784.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="award-winning-sap-partner-clarivos-creates-dedicated-role-for-customer-success-manager">Award-Winning SAP Partner Clarivos Creates Dedicated Role for Customer Success Manager</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>At <a href="https://www.clarivos.com/">Clarivos</a>, customer success has always been a key part of everyone’s role – from sales through to service and support.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>But the role of customer success manager – fulfilled by Melissa Lewington – is a completely new one for the UK-based tech consultancy, which specializes in delivering cloud-based apps such as <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-bydesign.html">SAP Business ByDesign</a> and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/cloud-analytics.html">SAP Analytics Cloud</a> to its customers.</p>
  <p>The key differentiators? The customer success manager is a true extension of a client’s team and remains accessible long after the solution has gone live. And, because Lewington is a part of Clarivos’ service team, her goals are based on delivering customer satisfaction rather than sales.</p>
  <p>“Consultants have constant calendar constraints due to live projects,” explains Pablo Castagnini, head of Digital Transformation at Clarvios. “Melissa’s calendar is driven by our customers. They can initiate sessions as and when they feel the need because they have access to it.”</p>
  <p>This increased level of communication is a tangible benefit for both customers and Clarivos. And, in Lewington, the customer has a genuine advocate within Clarivos when it comes to getting the right level of support at the right time.</p>
  <p>“I know that when Melissa asks me to move priorities it’s because we have a customer in real need. We can then focus in on the solution, relieving the customer from any immediate operational pain and allowing them to focus on their business,” adds Castagnini.</p>
  <p>As businesses continue to transform to a largely cloud-based way of operating, applying a customer success focus is increasingly important to retain and deepen client-partner relationships.</p>
  <p>“The key benefit to customers is the opportunity to maximize the value they are getting from their investment in their cloud application, through awareness and education. As far as Clarivos is concerned, we get unprecedented access to the daily operations of our customers, so we know when and where to jump in and provide advice and support. In addition, we have seen a rapid return on investment since Melissa took up her post – in less than a month of her joining us, in fact. As I see it, it’s a win-win!” adds Castagnini.</p>
  <p>Expanding the function over time is a “no-brainer,” he adds, as Clarivos moves from a reactive, “firefighting” position into the role of fully trusted advisor. “I’m delighted to say we’re already there with some of our customers.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>“Melissa has been very proactive in helping us to enhance our system…She provided us with detailed guidance when we reassessed our licensing requirements and gives us regular updates on future systems developments that we need to plan for. Additionally, she has built strong relationships with Clarivos’ technical experts which has allowed us to resolve any maintenance issues quickly and efficiently.”</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-all-the-cloud-analytics-features-you-need-with-sap-analytics-cloud">Get all the cloud analytics features you need with SAP Analytics Cloud</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/cloud-analytics.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="the-csm-view">The CSM View</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="discover-the-power-of-partnership-with-sap">Discover the power of partnership with SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/partner.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Lewington joined Clarivos earlier in 2021, bringing with her experience in providing customer support across the sales cycle from an outsourcing consultancy.</p>
  <p>While no two days are the same, at Clarivos the customer is front and center when it comes to prioritizing workload.</p>
  <p>“All my days start and end with a diary review, so I know what meetings I need what for, and when!” she says.</p>
  <p>“I spend a lot of time with new customers, getting to know them and their businesses and ensuring they have support as and when they need it. Then there are the existing customers, understanding their growth plans, keeping track of business challenges, sharing relevant updates.”</p>
  <p>Lewington also acts as the intermediary between Clarivos, the customer, and SAP, ensuring licenses are up to date and escalating any issues as needed.</p>
  <p>She’s in touch with the Clarivos marketing team regularly so she can keep customers in the loop on any news, and she’s also a religious note-checker.</p>
  <p>“I am always checking for common themes in my notes. With one customer, I found that solving one problem fixed two more. By being ruthless in reviewing my notes, I can see recurring problems and act quickly to resolve them.”</p>
  <p>Lewington sees customer success managers as a prevention to churn as well as a dedicated resource invested in the customer which negates the need for ad hoc, reactive work.</p>
  <p>“Ad hoc work is bad because it brings additional cost and time to a project,” she says. “Separating the ad hoc work into distinct projects gives a clear view not only of the resources available at any one time, but also of timelines and project planning. When a project manager is involved too, this only becomes more powerful.”</p>
  <p>“Customer success managers can also advocate and coordinate around the partner and SAP, delivering a much more holistic service to the customer,” she adds. “A customer success manager does a lot of the leg work and can provide a lot of assistance, which only helps to increase our reach within our customers’ organizations and deepen the relationship with SAP.”</p>
  <p>As Lewington settles into her role, she’s keen to develop new areas, including closer coordination with SAP account teams. “It will lead to better planning for customers and a better understanding of upcoming renewal incentives and licensing fees. That’s a powerful offering for SAP, the customer, and Clarivos.”</p>
  <p>When asked about the future of customer success, Lewington is clear: “The priority has to be getting organizations to realize that investing in customer success is an investment in growth.”</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-btp-in-the-sap-ecosystem</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>