<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/learning-management-system/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Accelerate Your Skills Transformation with the New Integrated Learning Experience for SAP SuccessFactors]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/new-integrated-learning-experience-sap-successfactors</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/new-integrated-learning-experience-sap-successfactors</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The integrated learning experience for SAP SuccessFactors helps to address skills gaps and considers employees' whole self in skills growth.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills-gap</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning-management-system</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-learning</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Wellstar Health Improves the Employee Experience through Innovative LMS Governance]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/wellstar-health-employee-experience-lms-governance</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/wellstar-health-employee-experience-lms-governance</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Improved governance helped Wellstar Health make the most out of its SAP SuccessFactors Learning solution. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_133c1cc6858830182923838b672bf97c1f0d1448f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_133c1cc6858830182923838b672bf97c1f0d1448f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_133c1cc6858830182923838b672bf97c1f0d1448f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Wellstar Health Improves the Employee Experience through Innovative LMS Governance" src="./media_133c1cc6858830182923838b672bf97c1f0d1448f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="wellstar-health-improves-the-employee-experience-through-innovative-lms-governance">Wellstar Health Improves the Employee Experience through Innovative LMS Governance</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="building-a-lifelong-learning-culture-is-more-important-than-ever">Building a Lifelong Learning Culture Is More Important Than Ever</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2022/10/building-a-lifelong-learning-culture">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Imagine that you’ve just been hired into a new job, but due to training you can’t really start your actual duties for a week and a half. Now add to this the fact that you’re a healthcare worker whose expertise is very much in need. This was the scenario at Wellstar Health System prior to the start of its learning management system (LMS) governance initiative.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As a customer of multiple <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/hxm-suite.html">SAP SuccessFactors solutions</a>, Wellstar is familiar with the power of SAP and knew it could be getting more out of its SAP SuccessFactors Learning solution. Danielle Mecum, manager of Learning Technology at Wellstar, believed that improved governance of the system was part of the road to getting there. “When governance is lacking, the employee experience suffers,” Mecum explained.</p>
  <p>With a nursing background, she knew firsthand the need to get new hires trained properly and quickly, and that reducing the time from hire to actual work was key. She added, “In addition to our non-clinical employees, our medical employees were taking longer to get to the patient floors to start providing care because of how the required onboarding training was organized and set up. There were inaccurate training assignments, courses not marked as required, and, in some cases, no required-by dates.”</p>
  <p>In addition, users said that their learning assignments were too cluttered and disorganized, Mecum explained. And there were instances where new employees would get to a patient floor and realize that they were not able to enter a patient’s chart, for example, because a course hadn’t been assigned to them in the correct sequence.</p>
  <p>The need to get employees onboarded faster could have been enough to justify the governance project, but to add to the complex nature of the project – and completely out of Wellstar’s control – the organization faced the impending deprecation of Flash content and the impacts of the <a href="/topics/covid-19">COVID-19</a> pandemic. To help tackle this challenge, Wellstar decided to work with its customer engagement executive to start a solution adoption engagement. This type of engagement is intended to provide recommendations to a customer to help them create an action plan to optimize their use of their system – in this case <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/corporate-lms.html">SAP SuccessFactors Learning</a>. A recommendation came out of this engagement that confirmed the needed for the governance initiative.</p>
  <p>Mecum’s nursing background helped her understand the urgency of the situation. She and her team looked at the issues already discussed and began to build a governance model. For example, they instituted a content life cycle management process that incorporated a formal method for requesting the creation of new items, curricula, and assignment profiles. In addition, they implemented an ongoing review procedure that included automated notifications to course owners to review material that had reached expiration. Additionally, Wellstar leveraged and configured custom fields within SAP SuccessFactors Learning to track key data and report on it from within the system to ensure compliance with the new governance process.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="foster-continuous-learning-and-reduce-compliance-risk-with-sap-successfactors-learning">Foster continuous learning and reduce compliance risk with SAP SuccessFactors Learning</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/corporate-lms.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Other governance steps included reviewing and consolidating LMS admin roles to ensure the right administrators had the right permissions to perform administrative tasks as appropriate in the system – without giving them freedom to add to the problem at large. A formal process for vetting new LMS administrators was created to ensure they weren’t simply giving just anyone these permissions. “We knew we needed to define what goes into the system, so we could control what comes out. This helps when we need to get rid of old, outdated courses,” Mecum explained.</p>
  <p>These changes, among others, were implemented as part of the governance initiative. The result is that Wellstar is now reaping greater benefits from <a href="/topics/sap-successfactors-learning">SAP SuccessFactors Learning</a> and, most importantly, employees now have an improved experience with the system. Frustration levels are down and new hires are able to start their actual jobs much sooner than before – in three days rather than a week and a half!</p>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/corporate-lms.html">Learn how an LMS can help your organization.</a></div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>Mark Tarallo is a solution marketing fellow for SAP SuccessFactors.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/covid-19</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>industry/healthcare</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning-management-system</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-learning</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Building a Lifelong Learning Culture Is More Important Than Ever]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/building-a-lifelong-learning-culture</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/building-a-lifelong-learning-culture</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Continuous learning options and a culture of lifelong learning will be critical to develop the workforce of the future. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning-for-life</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning-management-system</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-learning</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Entel Charted a Path to Digital Self-Learning Despite Disruption]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/entel-digital-self-learning-sap-successfactors</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/entel-digital-self-learning-sap-successfactors</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Employees at leading Chilean telecommunications company Entel enjoy an enhanced learning experience with SAP SuccessFactors. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16b818302542f7c5bfe597377655d0c473ae578e5.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16b818302542f7c5bfe597377655d0c473ae578e5.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_16b818302542f7c5bfe597377655d0c473ae578e5.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="How Entel Charted a Path to Digital Self-Learning Despite Disruption" src="./media_16b818302542f7c5bfe597377655d0c473ae578e5.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="how-entel-charted-a-path-to-digital-self-learning-despite-disruption">How Entel Charted a Path to Digital Self-Learning Despite Disruption</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="support-continuous-learning-with-a-unified-learning-management-system">Support continuous learning with a unified learning management system</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/corporate-lms.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>The best employees have always had a vested interest in building their skills but precious little time to train. Then the <a href="/covid-19">COVID-19</a> pandemic hit, and a new way of working gave many employees pause – and the chance to think long and hard about their careers. So, Empresa Nacional de Telecomunicaciones S.A., commonly known as Entel, responded to a disrupted workforce and provided these employees with the digital tools to reskill and <a href="https://insights.sap.com/importance-upskilling/">upskill</a>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Today, employees at this leading Chilean telecommunications company enjoy an enhanced learning experience with SAP SuccessFactors solutions. Entel used SAP SuccessFactors solutions to help fully digitalize Entel University, the company’s training program, as the pandemic rocked the lives of workers worldwide. Rather than caving to this disruption, HR leaders at Entel transformed crisis into opportunity and adapted the company’s training formula to the new normal.</p>
  <p>“The COVID-19 pandemic accelerated the process that we had been developing, causing us to completely digitalize our corporate learning plan,” said Angélica Sánchez, organizational development and learning management analyst at Entel. “Today, the focus is to maintain this trend and concentrate our digital offerings, further democratizing knowledge.”</p>
  <p>By providing fully digital learning experiences to a <a href="https://insights.sap.com/connect-remote-workforces-strengthen-corporate-culture/">newly remote workforce</a>, Entel empowered employees to take control of their careers during an increasingly uncertain time. Not only that, but remote e-learning courses helped provide structure to employees’ workdays as they adjusted to working from home.</p>
  <p>Entel adapted learning content to face the pandemic head-on, developing leadership workshops and trainings focused on supporting employees. These included sessions on increasing productivity at home and best practices for remote collaboration, as well as tips for self-care and overcoming anxiety in times of uncertainty.</p>
  <p>“We know that in the current reality, one of the main interests of companies and organizations is to maintain productivity,” said Cristóbal Vergara, a general manager at SAP Chile. “To achieve this, it is relevant to reimagine the processes and invest in distance collaboration tools, technologies to facilitate work, and worker training programs because building a culture of continuous learning reflects that the company is investing in potential and growth.”</p>
  <p>Entel’s digital learning journey began in 2016 when the company implemented a <a href="https://insights.sap.com/what-is-lms/">learning management system (LMS)</a> from SAP SuccessFactors solutions to help enhance Entel University, a largely in-person education center. The company founded Entel University in 2010 with a face-to-face classroom format that proved to be a constant challenge for learners spread across locations. Not only that, but in-person learning also required a large investment in time and money. The digital LMS helped reduce these costs by initiating self-learning processes and bringing content online, and it offered specialized training tailored to the needs of each employee’s role and specialization.</p>
  <p>Then, in the midst of the pandemic, Entel decided to take the plunge and completely digitalize Entel University. It consolidated its entire learning infrastructure on a single platform on SAP SuccessFactors solutions. The solutions helped create a foundation for permanent corporate learning through diverse and dynamic courses that align with the company’s strategy. Employees can easily access topics of interest intuitively organized on one digital experience through their desktop or mobile devices. They can take advantage of a new professional skills program that includes performance management workshops and more. In addition, specialized courses help employees gain new skills in sales, e-commerce, cybersecurity, and customer experience.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="create-a-more-flexible-engaged-workforce-and-a-more-resilient-business">Create a more flexible, engaged workforce and a more resilient business</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>At its core, Entel University promotes a new digital culture that emphasizes self-management and continuous learning. In 2020, 3,098 employees took one or more e-learning courses at Entel University for a total of 6,003 completed remote courses – three times more than all of the courses completed in 2019. Entel University will make it easy for employees to continue learning, even after the pandemic subsides.</p>
  <p>“For Entel, learning management is in constant evolution, mobilizing the capacities that our company requires in its permanent transformation,” said Sanchez. “That is why, within the next 12 years, the main challenge will be to train talent with an emphasis on the development of digital capabilities and a mentality willing to change.”</p>
  <p>To achieve this, the company continues the successful journey it started with SAP SuccessFactors solutions. Entel hopes that its digital training, in addition to future developments in human experience management (HXM), will help reduce employee turnover by improving the overall Entel employee experience.</p>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div>To learn more about how SAP SuccessFactors solutions can help your business provide effective digital enablement for employees, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/corporate-lms.html">visit sap.com/lms</a>.</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div><a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2021/04/21/this-telecommunications-company-charted-a-path-to-digital-self-learning-despite-disruption/?sh=724ec7e6eda5">This story originally appeared on SAP BrandVoice on Forbes</a>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/covid-19</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning-management-system</category>
            <category>industry/telecommunications</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>