<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/product/sap-successfactors-opportunity-marketplace/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Growing Your Business Begins with Growing Your People]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/growing-your-business-begins-with-growing-your-people</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/growing-your-business-begins-with-growing-your-people</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[An Oxford Economics study, sponsored by SAP, reveals how to optimizing talent management with best practices for HR and IT. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/sme</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors-hcm-suite</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-learning</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-opportunity-marketplace</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-performance-goals</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-recruiting</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP SuccessFactors First Half 2024 Release: Make Every Employee a Success Story]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-successfactors-first-half-2024-release</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-successfactors-first-half-2024-release</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[To help take HR to the next level, the SAP SuccessFactors first half 2024 release delivers more than 250 features and enhancements.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_115cc4b7786cb688433caf45dec5bf248f041afdb.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_115cc4b7786cb688433caf45dec5bf248f041afdb.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_115cc4b7786cb688433caf45dec5bf248f041afdb.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP SuccessFactors First Half 2024 Release: Make Every Employee a Success Story" src="./media_115cc4b7786cb688433caf45dec5bf248f041afdb.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-successfactors-first-half-2024-release-make-every-employee-a-success-story">SAP SuccessFactors First Half 2024 Release: Make Every Employee a Success Story</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Success can take many forms. It’s achieving AI-driven results faster and smarter. It’s unlocking more meaningful and aspirational career development experiences. It’s empowering employees and managers through simple HR-related tasks in the flow of work, freeing up more productive time across the organization.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>And for you and your business, you can tell all those success stories – and more – with the SAP SuccessFactors HCM suite and our first half 2024 release.</p>
  <p>As your organization and employees begin to embrace AI, <a href="/topics/human-resources">HR</a> has the opportunity to drive new levels of employee productivity, engagement, and growth. SAP SuccessFactors HCM can give you everything you need – the global foundation, skills framework, people-first experiences, and purpose-built AI capabilities – to help take HR to the next level. With the SAP SuccessFactors first half 2024 release, we are delivering more than 250 innovative features and enhancements.</p>
  <h2 id="sap-business-ai">SAP Business AI</h2>
  <p>In 1H 2024, we are thrilled to introduce more than 25 new AI capabilities to enable better employee experiences and new levels of productivity.</p>
  <p>Among these capabilities include the ability for applicants to provide skills during the application process. This can enable recruiters to see a skills compatibility for each applicant based on matching the applicant’s skills and the job requisition, helping improve applicant screening and time to hire. Furthermore, personalization in SAP SuccessFactors Opportunity Marketplace is enhanced with new AI-driven recommendation categories, “Ignite Your Role” and “Reach Your Aspirations.” These guided experiences can enable employees to proactively take steps to reach their development goals.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e755ea739e2394a3bec10a53f644e2d9cd718123.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e755ea739e2394a3bec10a53f644e2d9cd718123.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1e755ea739e2394a3bec10a53f644e2d9cd718123.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Screenshot of the assisted screening and skills match capabilities" src="./media_1e755ea739e2394a3bec10a53f644e2d9cd718123.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="803" height="521">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>Assisted screening and skills match available in 1H 2024 release. Click to enlarge.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Generative AI continues to be embedded across the SAP SuccessFactors HCM suite, including new capabilities to help employees create ready-made performance and development goals and AI-assisted writing to help improve the quality, clarity, and conciseness of writing across a variety of areas within SAP SuccessFactors solutions.</p>
  <p>Further, with this release, insights based on an employee’s compensation and job history are available to help support managers in having effective and well-informed compensation discussions.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="the-ai-copilot-that-truly-understands-your-business">The AI copilot that truly understands your business</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/ai-assistant.html">Meet Joule</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>We have also added more than 15 new <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/ai-assistant.html">Joule</a> capabilities in this release to help both managers and employees get work done in a conversational way, such as creating or changing a position, creating spot awards, clocking in and out, and viewing pay statements as well as time capabilities like requesting time off, checking leave balances, and syncing holidays to Outlook calendars while managers can review and approve time off. Further, employees can now clock in and out using Joule, Microsoft Teams, or the SAP SuccessFactors Mobile app.</p>
  <h2 id="sap-successfactors-employee-central">SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central</h2>
  <p>We are excited to unveil two new people profile experiences – the profile preview and the spotlight view. The profile preview can provide a snapshot of key areas of the employee profile, including job, manager, location, and contact details, to quickly view and connect with others. Additionally, the spotlight view can showcase employee skills and competencies, mentoring and target roles, and other relevant personal and organizational information.</p>
  <p>We are also introducing a new org chart experience with a refreshed look and feel. Available on desktop and mobile, users can explore their organizational structure with improved expand and collapse capabilities, which helps provide full accessibility to an employee’s profile preview, with an option to open the new spotlight view.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b181ba5a94a8b936ff644a1c243245079ecbbab4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b181ba5a94a8b936ff644a1c243245079ecbbab4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1b181ba5a94a8b936ff644a1c243245079ecbbab4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Screenshot of the new org chart experience" src="./media_1b181ba5a94a8b936ff644a1c243245079ecbbab4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="576">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>The new org chart experience. Click to enlarge.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Customers can now automatically process new hires from SAP SuccessFactors Recruiting and SAP SuccessFactors Onboarding into SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central. This capability helps further reduce the time to hire, which is especially important with mass, seasonal, and high-volume hiring.</p>
  <h2 id="sap-successfactors-employee-central-global-benefits">SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central Global Benefits</h2>
  <p>With this release, we are pleased to introduce a new benefits enrollment experience for insurance, savings, and pension benefit types. Available on both desktop and mobile, the guided experience for benefits elections can give employees increased convenience with improved navigation and increased confidence with side-by-side plan comparisons and embedded instructional text. Additionally, employees can update dependent information and manage beneficiaries directly from the benefits enrollment process, which helps further streamline the enrollment experience.</p>
  <h2 id="sap-successfactors-time-tracking">SAP SuccessFactors Time Tracking</h2>
  <p>We are thrilled to share the launch of a new time sheet experience that integrates the latest version of My Timesheet in SAP S/4HANA with SAP SuccessFactors. Employees can now record time for payroll, as well as against activities and cost objects, from a single time sheet across applications. This helps organizations leverage real-time connectivity between HR and finance operations to keep track of employee activity and labor costs and to pay employees accurately and on time.</p>
  <p>Additionally, a new monthly calendar view for time sheets can give employees and managers a complete picture of recorded time over a month. Users can drill down into specific days and submit or approve time for pay periods beyond a week, such as biweekly or monthly.</p>
  <p>For managers, a new time approval center helps simplify approvals with a centralized dashboard highlighting anomalies for swift resolution. Managers can monitor team working hours effectively, helping to ensure accurate and timely payroll processing.</p>
  <h2 id="sap-successfactors-onboarding">SAP SuccessFactors Onboarding</h2>
  <p>With enhancements to the onboarding journey experience, new hires can now use the new Your Onboarding Checklist page to reference and complete all tasks – onboarding data collection, compliance tasks, additional onboarding tasks, and exploring the onboarding guide – from one place with a single view. Available for new hires, rehires, internal hires, and employees with global assignments, this improved experience can save time for onboarding participants while helping to ensure productivity from the start.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e12cd49909a64b18778552665ee0147fcacdc707.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e12cd49909a64b18778552665ee0147fcacdc707.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1e12cd49909a64b18778552665ee0147fcacdc707.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Screenshot of the new onboarding journey experience" src="./media_1e12cd49909a64b18778552665ee0147fcacdc707.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="576">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>The new onboarding journey experience. Click to enlarge.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>And that’s only a fraction of all the innovations we’re bringing to customers in 1H 2024. There’s much more in the release, including new and exciting updates in:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Generative AI and Joule capabilities</li>
    <li>SAP SuccessFactors Opportunity Marketplace</li>
    <li>SAP SuccessFactors Compensation</li>
    <li>SAP SuccessFactors Succession &#x26; Development</li>
    <li>SAP SuccessFactors Incentive Management</li>
    <li>SAP SuccessFactors Work Zone</li>
  </ul>
  <p>Read the <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2024/04/300e8c6d-b77e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">SAP SuccessFactors first half 2024 release highlights brochure</a> and watch the <a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2024/04/8c907f14-b77e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">1H 2024 release highlights video</a> to find out more.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Bianka Woelke is group vice president of Application Product Management at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-employee-central</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors-hcm-suite</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-onboarding</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-opportunity-marketplace</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-recruiting</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Building a Dynamic Organization with a Skills-Based Approach to Talent]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/building-dynamic-organization-skills-based-approach-to-talent</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/building-dynamic-organization-skills-based-approach-to-talent</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A skills-based approach to talent management can help organizations build a dynamic and resilient workforce. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/recruiting</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-learning</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-opportunity-marketplace</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-recruiting</category>
            <category>news-tag/talent-acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Realizing Employee Potential with HR Technology]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/realizing-employee-potential-with-hr-technology</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/realizing-employee-potential-with-hr-technology</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[HR leaders can improve employee potential practices and enable unbiased decision-making processes with HR technology. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-opportunity-marketplace</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-performance-goals</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Six Ways to Prepare Future-Ready People Managers with SAP SuccessFactors Solutions]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/six-ways-prepare-people-managers-sap-successfactors</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/six-ways-prepare-people-managers-sap-successfactors</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Create engaging experiences, boost productivity, and enhance results by empowering people managers with SAP SuccessFactors solutions.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_102238c9ba8fcf28bb39535e2bf9b2193b8900cdc.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_102238c9ba8fcf28bb39535e2bf9b2193b8900cdc.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_102238c9ba8fcf28bb39535e2bf9b2193b8900cdc.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Six Ways to Prepare Future-Ready People Managers with SAP SuccessFactors Solutions" src="./media_102238c9ba8fcf28bb39535e2bf9b2193b8900cdc.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="six-ways-to-prepare-future-ready-people-managers-with-sap-successfactors-solutions">Six Ways to Prepare Future-Ready People Managers with SAP SuccessFactors Solutions</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>People managers have the potential to make or break the employee experience at an organization. They are responsible for understanding the demands of the business and motivating their team members to meet those requirements. However, the people manager role is evolving due to three crucial factors – hybrid and remote work, automation, and elevated employee expectations.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>To help understand this evolution of the people manager role, the <a href="https://community.sap.com/topics/successfactors/growth-insights-research/growth-insights-team">Growth &#x26; Insights team</a> for SAP SuccessFactors hosted interviews with 31 HR leaders from SAP customer organizations and conducted a survey of 731 people managers and 716 individual contributors from around the globe. Based on the research findings, below are six ways organizations can improve current people managers’ performance and experience with SAP SuccessFactors solutions.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-the-full-research-report">Read the full research report</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/dg/people-management/index.html">Check it out</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="utilize-co-leadership-models">Utilize Co-Leadership Models</h2>
  <p>Organizations look to people managers to execute important initiatives and people practices, leading to an overload of responsibilities. Implementing co-leadership structures, even for a short period of time, can reduce a people manager’s role overload and provide individual contributors with a valuable experiential learning opportunity.</p>
  <p>One way to provide an experiential opportunity is through <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2023/05/bc7c3ca3-727e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">dynamic teams</a>, advanced capabilities available as part of SAP SuccessFactors solutions that can help create and manage cross-functional teams that exist beyond traditional hierarchies. <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2023/05/bc7c3ca3-727e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Statistics</a> reported that 66% of employees who had participated in a dynamic team felt a positive impact on their career, leading to higher engagement. Using dynamic teams can help organizations utilize co-leadership models for projects while also accessing individual contributor potential and incorporating those insights into future succession plans.</p>
  <h2 id="update-people-manager-job-descriptions">Update People Manager Job Descriptions</h2>
  <p>Many organizations have not updated their formal job descriptions for people managers to accurately reflect changes to their roles, leading to unclear performance expectations and ineffective systems for developing and selecting people managers. One way organizations can streamline this process is through <a href="/2023/10/new-sap-successfactors-ai-innovations-successconnect">generative artificial intelligence (AI) in the SAP SuccessFactors Recruiting solution</a>. Hiring managers and recruiters can fine-tune job descriptions with generative AI, which allows them to incorporate supplementary content, identify biased language, and help ensure alignment with business requirements. Instead of starting from scratch every time a new position is created or requirements are updated, recruiters and hiring managers can use AI to help draft job descriptions faster and stay in their normal flow of work. And more importantly, the final content is more meaningful, inclusive, and competitive – presenting a clear and accurate view of the role to attract a larger pool of qualified and interested candidates.</p>
  <h2 id="rethink-career-architecture-and-pathways-to-advancement">Rethink Career Architecture and Pathways to Advancement</h2>
  <p>Without other options for growing, gaining status, or increasing compensation, employees will seek people management roles even if they are not suitable for or interested in this type of role. Developing alternative pathways for advancement, such as specialist career paths, for high-performing individual contributors ensures that employees are entering people manager roles for the right reason – to manage people.</p>
  <p>Sharing career architectures more broadly can also improve managers’ awareness of internal mobility opportunities, which they cited as a top challenge. Talent marketplaces, like the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/opportunity-marketplace.html">SAP SuccessFactors Opportunity Marketplace</a> solution, can improve visibility into development and growth opportunities within the organization. It can provide AI-driven personalized recommendations for learning, mentors, internal roles, and dynamic teams. This allows employees to have experiential learning opportunities and can provide them alternate career paths.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="powerful-cloud-hr-software-empowers-individuals-to-reach-their-full-potential">Powerful cloud HR software empowers individuals to reach their full potential</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="implement-succession-planning-for-all">Implement Succession Planning for All</h2>
  <p>Everyone agrees that people manager roles should become more exclusive, but that also means talent pools will become shallower. Implementing succession planning at all levels of the organization allows organizations to identify “hidden” people manager talent. When developing succession plans, consider that a people manager does not always need to be replaced with an existing people manager – and that a people manager’s next role does not always need to be in management. The <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/succession-development.html">SAP SuccessFactors Succession &#x26; Development</a> solution can make this process easier by helping employees expand their skills and advance their careers with visibility into continuous development dialogue, mentoring opportunities, and AI-powered career planning. It can also optimize succession planning, making it scalable to place the right people in the right roles and helping to secure the “hidden” people manager talent.</p>
  <h2 id="create-a-community-for-people-managers">Create a Community for People Managers</h2>
  <p>People managers consider staying engaged, feeling included, and managing their well-being to be top challenges. Creating a people manager community provides this crucial workforce segment with social support, which research has shown to be a positive driver of the people manger experience. This also offers the organization a clear channel to host two-way communication with people managers. One way to foster a community for people managers is to leverage the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/workzone-hr.html">SAP SuccessFactors Work Zone</a> solution, which is a personalized digital workspace that helps support and encourage collaboration. People managers can create their own community and connect with each other, allowing for more engagement, sharing of best practices, and improvement in the overall employee experience.</p>
  <h2 id="leverage-technology">Leverage Technology</h2>
  <p><a href="/topics/human-resources">Cloud HR technology</a> can help support the strategies recommended here and solve many of managers’ most pressing challenges. With SAP SuccessFactors solutions, organizations can put their people at the center of everything and create AI-powered experiences that can support current people managers while using talent intelligence to help uncover and develop the managers of tomorrow.</p>
  <p>As the expectations of people managers from both employees and organizations undergo constant evolution, the role of people manager will increasingly become more “people-centric” – focusing on support, fostering development, and nurturing a positive culture. It’s important that organizations use the right HR technology to deliver engaging employee experiences, increase productivity, and drive better business outcomes.</p>
  <p>For additional insights on the evolution of the people manager role, read the full report, “<a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/dg/people-management/index.html">Six Best Practices to Prepare People Managers for Today and Tomorrow</a>.”</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Christina Russo is global director of Solution Marketing at SAP SuccessFactors.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-opportunity-marketplace</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-recruiting</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-work-zone</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Igniting Workforce Potential with the New SAP SuccessFactors AI Innovations]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/new-sap-successfactors-ai-innovations-successconnect</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/new-sap-successfactors-ai-innovations-successconnect</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[At SuccessConnect, SAP announced new innovations around AI and talent intelligence to help organizations address their skills gaps.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-opportunity-marketplace</category>
            <category>sap-event/successconnect</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Delivering a People-Centered User Experience with SAP SuccessFactors Solutions]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/delivering-people-centered-ux-with-sap-successfactors</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/delivering-people-centered-ux-with-sap-successfactors</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn about the focus of recent UX innovation and investment at SAP SuccessFactors and why a superior user experience enables efficient work.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-opportunity-marketplace</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-work-zone</category>
            <category>news-tag/ux</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dynamic Teams: How to Optimize the Outcomes of Increasingly Fluid Work Experiences]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/06/dynamic-teams-optimize-fluid-work-experiences</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/06/dynamic-teams-optimize-fluid-work-experiences</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Cohesive and cross-functional team strategies that support organizational agility unlock the door to dynamic teams. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/dynamic-teams</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-opportunity-marketplace</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-people-analytics</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-performance-goals</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Six Ways Growth-Focused Organizations Power Reskilling and Upskilling Initiatives with SAP SuccessFactors]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/six-ways-power-reskilling-upskilling-initiatives-sap-successfactors</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/six-ways-power-reskilling-upskilling-initiatives-sap-successfactors</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[An IDC survey sponsored by SAP reveals six ways midsize organizations use SAP SuccessFactors solutions to power reskilling and upskilling.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-learning</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-opportunity-marketplace</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-performance-goals</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP SuccessFactors First Half 2023 Release: Skill-Centric Innovation to Build Your Future-Ready Workforce]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/sap-successfactors-first-half-2023-release</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/sap-successfactors-first-half-2023-release</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With the SAP SuccessFactors first half 2023 release, we continue to deliver on our promise to help build future-ready workforces. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/future-of-work</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-employee-central</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-opportunity-marketplace</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-work-zone</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Take: Quiet Hiring, the Workplace Culture Cure for a Chilly Labor Market]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/01/the-take-quiet-hiring-workplace-culture-chilly-labor-market</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/01/the-take-quiet-hiring-workplace-culture-chilly-labor-market</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Caution is the watchword in 2023, so quiet hiring is gaining attention as a strategy for organizations. Get SAP's take.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/perspective</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-opportunity-marketplace</category>
            <category>news-tag/the-take</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP SuccessFactors Second Half 2022 Release: Building a Future-Ready Workforce Today]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/sap-successfactors-second-half-2022-release</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/sap-successfactors-second-half-2022-release</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The SAP SuccessFactors second half 2022 release introduces new innovations around creating an agile and future-ready workforce. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1074c8b37f11498501b456579a1cc6d70dabc96f4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1074c8b37f11498501b456579a1cc6d70dabc96f4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1074c8b37f11498501b456579a1cc6d70dabc96f4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP SuccessFactors Second Half 2022 Release: Building a Future-Ready Workforce Today" src="./media_1074c8b37f11498501b456579a1cc6d70dabc96f4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-successfactors-second-half-2022-release-building-a-future-ready-workforce-today">SAP SuccessFactors Second Half 2022 Release: Building a Future-Ready Workforce Today</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>In today’s business landscape, organizations must equip themselves to respond to workforce opportunities or challenges <em>before</em> they arise. If recent trends have taught us anything, it’s that by the time a business reacts to a market shift, a new one is already occurring. Staying a step ahead of workforce demands is no longer a step ahead – it’s step one.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The SAP SuccessFactors second half 2022 release, which is available for preview today, introduces new innovations focused on empowering organizations to create an agile and future-ready workforce in a rapidly changing workplace as well as further investments for individualized experiences and agile and compliant HR.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="realizing-a-people-centered-future-of-work-through-the-intelligent-enterprise">Realizing a People-Centered Future of Work Through the Intelligent Enterprise</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/06/people-centered-future-of-work-intelligent-enterprise-hxm">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="creating-a-future-ready-workforce">Creating a Future-Ready Workforce</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="change-the-world-of-work-for-good-with-the-next-generation-of-hcm-software-from-sap">Change the world of work for good with the next generation of HCM software from SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In the face of increasingly complex and more urgent transformations, organizations must accelerate their talent development at scale. At the core of such adaptability is an understanding of the skills organizations need to build and grow. As part of our early adopter care program, select customers will have access to skills ontology, growth portfolio, and dynamic teams, which work together to deliver greater intelligence on the skills and capabilities that currently exist and are needed within an organization.</p>
  <p><strong>The skills ontology</strong> is a major advancement for SAP SuccessFactors that’s connected to global skills databases to help ensure that organizations have a comprehensive and up-to-date view of the most important skills for their workforce. It delivers machine learning and artificial intelligence (AI) powered recommendations to employees about relevant and trending skills to prioritize for development.</p>
  <p><strong>The growth portfolio</strong>, also part of the early adopter care program, is how employees can reveal their skills, capabilities, education, language proficiencies, and certifications. In the second half release, this data will connect employees to the most relevant assignments in <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/opportunity-marketplace.html">SAP SuccessFactors Opportunity Marketplace</a>. While the skills ontology gives organizations the ability to align talent development to the ambitions of the organization, the growth portfolio enables employees to align their own talent development to their ambitions.</p>
  <p><strong>Dynamic teams</strong> is also part of the SAP SuccessFactors foundation and available to all customers. Within organizations today, there are countless teams that exist outside of traditional organizational structures – groups of people that work cross-functionally on a project for a certain amount of time. The dynamic teams functionality can provide organizations with visibility into these teams as well as tools to help manage and assemble teams. Team progress can be measured using objectives and key results (OKRs) and employees can find a dynamic team within SAP SuccessFactors Opportunity Marketplace to help learn new skills and continue to grow their career. This transparency within the organization levels the playing field and creates equal opportunity for employees.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11660a4ded960363037d3e57f808136c91669c786.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11660a4ded960363037d3e57f808136c91669c786.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_11660a4ded960363037d3e57f808136c91669c786.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_11660a4ded960363037d3e57f808136c91669c786.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="534">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p><em>Click to enlarge</em></p>
  <p>With richer data and greater talent intelligence, organizations can help ensure that employees are connected to the most relevant talent development opportunities that are aligned to the ambitions of employees and the needs of the organization. Skills ontology, growth portfolio, and dynamic teams provide significant updates to the foundation of <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/hxm-suite.html">SAP SuccessFactors Human Experience Management (HXM) Suite</a> – built into what customers already have instead of requiring an entirely new solution.</p>
  <p>Some more exciting features for our second half 2022 release are around individualized experiences and agile and compliant HR, including:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Chosen name and personal pronouns:</strong> As part of our commitment to diversity, equity, and inclusion, we are taking important steps to help every individual be seen and valued. People can now indicate their chosen name, personal pronouns, and gender directly within the people profile. This information is displayed consistently across SAP SuccessFactors solutions – from recruiting to learning, helping to foster a greater sense of belonging.</li>
    <li><strong>End-to-end visual redesign:</strong> We are enhancing the overall look and feel of SAP SuccessFactors by implementing the Horizon visual theme for SAP Fiori. This new theme enhances consistency while delivering a more informed and streamlined product experience. Employees will find nearly every element of the solution updated with new colors, typography, iconography, layouts, and visual hierarchy focused on intent and success. We remain on track to have every employee-facing SAP SuccessFactors experience unified with the theme by the end of 2023.</li>
    <li><strong>SAP SuccessFactors Work Zone guided onboarding experience:</strong> By bringing together SAP SuccessFactors solutions and third-party integrations, organizations can more efficiently handle an array of complex onboarding processes. This new feature helps ensure that employees receive individualized experiences, even before their first day. Covering key phases of the new hire journey, the guided onboarding experience for <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/workzone-hr.html">SAP SuccessFactors Work Zone</a> helps provide the tools and information employees need, both before and after hiring.</li>
    <li><strong>Cross-system workflow capability:</strong> We are unveiling a new cross-system workflow capability for processes that involve multiple users from multiple systems, such as SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central and the payroll component of SAP ERP Human Capital Management. A guided activity framework for key processes enables our on-premise customers to more rapidly unlock the value of the cloud with SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central and the latest HXM innovations while maintaining and progressively moving on-premise processes to the cloud over time.</li>
    <li><strong>Time management enhancements:</strong> We are continuing to <a href="/2022/09/sap-industry-leading-time-management-suite">enhance our capabilities in time management</a> with the much-anticipated ability to export leave events into calendar applications along with better support for public holidays and handling of grace rules. Time administrators can now copy time-related configuration objects, reducing the need for manual duplication during configuration. In addition, temporary work schedules and absence information on a per day basis will now be available for reporting in SAP SuccessFactors People Analytics.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>All these and many more exciting features will be available in our 2H 2022 release, in preview today and production on Friday, December 9. Please watch our <a href="https://dam.sap.com/mac/app/p/video/asset/preview/KvodB4Q?ltr=a&#x26;rc=10">second half 2022 release highlights video</a> for more information.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Amy Wilson is senior vice president of Products and Design for SAP SuccessFactors.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>news-tag/dynamic-teams</category>
            <category>news-tag/future-of-work</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-erp-hcm</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-opportunity-marketplace</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-work-zone</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Some Organizations Have Successfully Changed Their Learning and Talent Experience]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/organizations-successfully-changed-learning-culture</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/organizations-successfully-changed-learning-culture</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP customers have transformed their learning culture by leveraging SAP SuccessFactors Learning and SAP SuccessFactors Work Zone.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning-for-life</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-learning</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-opportunity-marketplace</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-work-zone</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Why Building a Lifelong Learning Culture Is Challenging and How to Be Successful]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/building-lifelong-learning-culture-challenges</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/building-lifelong-learning-culture-challenges</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Building a culture of lifelong learning is key to an organization’s long-term viability and can ensure that your workforce is future ready.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning-for-life</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-learning</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-opportunity-marketplace</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-work-zone</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP SuccessFactors Innovation: Supporting New Ways of Working in Dynamic Teams]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/supporting-working-in-dynamic-teams</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/supporting-working-in-dynamic-teams</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With future SAP SuccessFactors solutions, organizations will be able to bring people together in dynamic teams to drive better outcomes.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/dynamic-teams</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-opportunity-marketplace</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How SAP SuccessFactors Innovation Can Help You Tackle Your Toughest Challenges]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/sap-successfactors-innovation-tackle-2022-hr-trends</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/sap-successfactors-innovation-tackle-2022-hr-trends</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Take on 2022 HR trends like hybrid work, diversity and inclusion, well-being, and the race for talent with SAP Successfactors solutions.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-technologies</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/mental-health-well-being</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-employee-central</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-opportunity-marketplace</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-performance-goals</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-recruiting</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-work-zone</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP SuccessFactors Earns Top Rated Awards from TrustRadius in Eight Categories]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/sap-successfactors-top-rated-awards-trustradius</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/sap-successfactors-top-rated-awards-trustradius</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[TrustRadius has recognized SAP SuccessFactors with eight Top Rated Awards this year. Read to learn more about this recognition.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/future-of-work</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-compensation</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-opportunity-marketplace</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-people-analytics</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Will the Great Reshuffle Incentivize Employers to Reckon with AI?]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/will-great-reshuffle-incentivize-employers-to-reckon-with-ai</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/will-great-reshuffle-incentivize-employers-to-reckon-with-ai</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[AI innovations enable HR teams to deliver a new level of experience to transform internal mobility and talent attraction. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/recruiting</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-store</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-opportunity-marketplace</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Incorporating Expressive States into the Human Experience at Work]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/expressive-states-human-experience-at-work</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/expressive-states-human-experience-at-work</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Expressive states are critical to realizing the whole self model, a framework to understand how employees experience change and opportunity.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/future-of-work</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-opportunity-marketplace</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Ideal Work Environment: What Is It and How to Deliver It]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/02/ideal-work-environment-what-is-it-how-to-deliver-it</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/02/ideal-work-environment-what-is-it-how-to-deliver-it</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Workers today expect more flexibility in their work environment. How can businesses provide the right tools, experiences, and capabilities?]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e5a7f7b4548009f6307ffbd3d0fa8ada45c8d093.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e5a7f7b4548009f6307ffbd3d0fa8ada45c8d093.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1e5a7f7b4548009f6307ffbd3d0fa8ada45c8d093.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="The Ideal Work Environment: What Is It and How to Deliver It" src="./media_1e5a7f7b4548009f6307ffbd3d0fa8ada45c8d093.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="the-ideal-work-environment-what-is-it-and-how-to-deliver-it">The Ideal Work Environment: What Is It and How to Deliver It</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>The hiring market continues to heat up, anxious employees are making retention more challenging, and workers expect more flexibility in their work environments. How can businesses provide the right tools, experiences, and capabilities necessary to create a workplace in which employees can thrive?</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In today’s changing world of work, employees expect better experiences – especially when it comes to their learning, development, and growth. However, employees struggle with multiple outdated or inadequate systems and tools that create a fragmented digital experience at work.</p>
  <p>The pressure is undoubtedly on executives, organizational leaders, and their HR teams to fill those gaps to create a workplace culture that is motivating, empowering, and fulfilling. They are expected to provide personalized work experiences that include access to individualized learning and growth, guided and simplified technology interfaces, continuous process improvements, embedded listening, and increased productivity and efficiency.</p>
  <p>Organizations that deliver on these promises exceptionally well are usually more effective in attracting, retaining, and developing the best talent. However, this is easier said than done because no single definition of an ideal workplace meets everyone’s expectations. To create a truly empowering, engaging, and enriching environment, decision-makers must consider the unique locations, job roles, personal responsibilities, and situations that each employee faces daily.</p>
  <p>At SAP SuccessFactors, we understand the importance of fostering an environment where people are thriving, collaborating, and ready to succeed today and tomorrow – no matter where they work. And in virtually every case, that experience begins with technologies that cater to each employee’s whole self even as they evolve, making everyone consistently feel valued, heard, and recognized.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="provide-an-employee-centric-hr-user-experience-with-sap-successfactors-work-zone">Provide an employee-centric HR user experience with SAP SuccessFactors Work Zone</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/workzone-hr.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="personalized-integrated-experience">Personalized, Integrated Experience</h2>
  <p>A good starting point is giving employees the freedom to reimagine their work experience with hyper-personalized, team-centric, and project-focused workspaces created through the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/workzone-hr.html">SAP SuccessFactors Work Zone solution</a>. This integrated digital experience connects the entire SAP software landscape and third-party applications to help streamline work and intelligently surface relevant content, recommendations, insights, and actions.</p>
  <p>By providing employees with a more simplified and unified digital experience tailored to their unique needs, SAP SuccessFactors Work Zone can enable companies to increase employee productivity and efficiency.</p>
  <p>For example, <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/11/90572075-047e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">AKT Solutions Limited</a> (AKT Global) resolved the presence of inefficient communication and collaboration across borders and time zones to improve productivity and lower employee stress. As a result, its employees work smarter and faster now that they have 24/7 access to everything they need to keep up with changes – no matter where they work, what device they use, or where they are based.</p>
  <h2 id="culture-of-continuous-and-agile-learning">Culture of Continuous and Agile Learning</h2>
  <p>Employees need on-demand access to individualized and engaging learning programs as part of their everyday experience. With learning established as a priority in the workspace, they are empowered to develop skills at their convenience and participate in opportunities to further develop their expertise and leadership abilities.</p>
  <p><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/corporate-lms.html">SAP SuccessFactors Learning</a> helps to foster a continuous and agile culture with learning that is personalized and relevant for each employee while being embedded into daily activities. Through learning workspaces employees can get access to relevant learning applications, information, collaboration tools, and content from any source – all through a single entry point and embedded into the flow of work – to be able to benefit from a more simplified and contextual way of learning. Organizations can then help ensure their people feel empowered to own their career path and growth while helping them become more engaged and develop the skills that align with current and future business needs.</p>
  <p><a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/10/90d46430-007e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Rich Products Corporation</a> (Rich’s) is taking advantage of the solution to support a culture of continuous learning. The family-owned food company sought to elevate its training and development program with a modern, consumer-grade learning experience for its associates. By mapping and enabling access to learning content with individualized recommendations, Rich’s offers its associates a customized view of their development plans and objectives and connects them to integrated external content libraries and resources on demand.</p>
  <h2 id="employees-retained-with-opportunities-they-want">Employees Retained with Opportunities They Want</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="turn-employees-into-ambassadors-with-employee-experience-management">Turn employees into ambassadors with employee experience management</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm/employee-experience-management.html?sort=title_asc&#x26;tab=all">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>According to joint research from <a href="https://www2.deloitte.com/us/en/insights/focus/technology-and-the-future-of-work/importance-of-investing-in-employees.html">Deloitte Consulting and the MIT Sloan Management Review</a>, making job opportunities visible and accessible in the workforce helps improve retention by aligning employee interests with strategic priorities. But first, most companies require a conscious shift that embraces each employee’s whole self – who they are today, who they are becoming, and the value they bring as individuals.</p>
  <p>By adding the <a href="/2021/10/sap-successfactors-opportunity-marketplace-drives-internal-mobility-and-upskilling-to-help-organizations-future-proof-their-business">SAP SuccessFactors Opportunity Marketplace</a> solution to their workspace, employees can find short-term assignments, fellowships, learning recommendations, and mentors. The solution can empower everyone across the organization to pursue multiple opportunities for professional development, networking, and project participation.</p>
  <h2 id="meaningful-work-shaped-by-real-time-feedback">Meaningful Work Shaped by Real-Time Feedback</h2>
  <p>Measuring work experiences helps businesses remain agile and strive to give employees what they need to feel supported, productive, and engaged. With <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm/employee-experience-management.html?sort=title_asc&#x26;tab=all">Experience Management solutions from SAP and Qualtrics</a>, organizations can evaluate how employees are doing, listen to their feedback, and respond to their concerns quickly and effectively.</p>
  <p>To enable a people-centric business transformation, luxury retailer <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2019/12/de86ec87-767d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff.html">Chalhoub Group</a> combines employee experience data with operational HR data. This approach allows the business to gain new insights, identify areas for improvement, and foster a culture where all employees are engaged and fully equipped to provide exceptional customer service. Chalhoub uses Experience Management solutions from SAP and Qualtrics to actively listen to its workforce and provide the right training, processes, and tools. The company is capturing feedback at every interaction touchpoint and discovering new ways to meet unique employee needs and continuously improve everyday work experiences.</p>
  <p>As a result, the company is redesigning and optimizing key aspects of the employee journey. For example, its HR transformation priorities are supported by hard data on the issues that employees really care about, driving greater emphasis on employee well-being and recognition as top strategic goals.</p>
  <h2 id="all-wrapped-with-a-human-experience">All Wrapped with a Human Experience</h2>
  <p>HR organizations are constantly challenging their business executives and organizational managers. They know that seemingly adequate access to technology is no guarantee that an employee’s specific needs are met. Meanwhile, it is understood that remote and <a href="/2021/08/essential-but-under-supported-improving-deskless-worker-experience">deskless workers</a> face even more complexity in their experiences, such as limited bandwidth and privacy controls, as they juggle work with their personal circumstances.</p>
  <p>With SAP SuccessFactors Work Zone, SAP SuccessFactors Learning, SAP SuccessFactors Opportunity Marketplace, and Experience Management solutions from SAP and Qualtrics, organizations can deliver engaging, individualized experiences that enable everyone to thrive.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Stephanie Craig is global director of Solution Marketing for SAP SuccessFactors.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/future-of-work</category>
            <category>news-tag/qualtrics</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-learning</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-opportunity-marketplace</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-work-zone</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unleashing Your Unique Superpowers at Work]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/unleashing-your-unique-superpowers-at-work</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/unleashing-your-unique-superpowers-at-work</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP SuccessFactors helps organizations improve employee experience by gaining a better understanding of their employees’ strengths and styles.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1df429da97e966ecc5c6bebbe80b490eb10f84fe3.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1df429da97e966ecc5c6bebbe80b490eb10f84fe3.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1df429da97e966ecc5c6bebbe80b490eb10f84fe3.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Unleashing Your Unique Superpowers at Work" src="./media_1df429da97e966ecc5c6bebbe80b490eb10f84fe3.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="unleashing-your-unique-superpowers-at-work">Unleashing Your Unique Superpowers at Work</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>You hear it all the time: “It’s in her DNA” or “He’s just wired that way.” Our innate core styles and traits are a critical and often overlooked component of our personal narrative and the formula that makes up who we are. Although they don’t tell our whole story, our traits have a significant influence on our behaviors and tendencies at work. These unique superpowers should be identified, fostered, and leveraged to create more positive and individualized work experiences.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Knowing and understanding our traits is highly valuable both to organizations and to individuals yet remains largely elusive in the workplace. Despite the <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/alisonescalante/2020/06/03/this-new-book-takes-on-the-2-billion-personality-testing-industry-a-review/?sh=715175b37b10">US$2 billion spent annually</a> on assessments for recruitment and selection, employees typically receive little or no feedback, and their data is left to gather dust for the remainder of their time at the organization.</p>
  <p>With human experience management (HXM), the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm.html">SAP SuccessFactors portfolio</a> is pursuing a shift towards individualization and building on the opportunity of a deeper level of diversity: the diversity of personality. In an earlier <a href="/2021/07/opportunity-in-x-redefine-employee-experience">article</a>, we described the formula for understanding <a href="/2020/10/whole-self-model-organizational-agility">the whole self</a>, which includes various elements – both traits, like work styles and team strengths, as well as states, like passions and motivations – of the individual. How the whole-self model describes an individual’s traits is referred to as ‘strengths and styles.’ Although traits are somewhat malleable over time – they might change somewhat over the course of five years – they largely define who we are.</p>
  <p>Organizations have a great opportunity to better leverage employee’s strengths and styles to create a more positive employee experience. Here’s how.</p>
  <h2 id="step-1-understanding-me">Step 1: Understanding Me</h2>
  <p>Most of us have an insatiable curiosity to learn about ourselves. Consider the social media quiz craze. What color is your aura? What city should you live in? Which Hogwarts professor are you? Consider channeling this curiosity at work to make a meaningful impact on your career and day to day experience.</p>
  <p>However, today there is a self-awareness gap at work. Ask someone about their communication style and you’ll likely receive a blank stare. This is further supported by <a href="https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/abs/10.1002/hrm.3930320204">psychological research</a> that indicates we are not always the best judges of our own behaviors. This lack of self-awareness can be addressed via well-designed and well-implemented assessments that use data to help us better understand ourselves. Organizations that embrace this strength and style data can help employees build confidence, drive development, and inspire careers.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d54e43c9283e9d885a07a6609d4fe967ef9b3b1a.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d54e43c9283e9d885a07a6609d4fe967ef9b3b1a.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1d54e43c9283e9d885a07a6609d4fe967ef9b3b1a.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_1d54e43c9283e9d885a07a6609d4fe967ef9b3b1a.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="290" height="300">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p>To better understand ourselves, consider these questions: How do I behave in a team? What strengths do I bring to an organization? What environment am I most likely to thrive in? How do I interact with others at work?</p>
  <p>There is no such thing as a “bad” personality. Regardless of what you uncover, it’s all good news. The potential of knowing who we are, releasing preconceived notions of good or bad, and truly understanding our value can help unlock our uniqueness and potential.</p>
  <p>Understanding our strengths and styles also plays a critical role in giving us confidence. <a href="https://psycnet.apa.org/record/2011-21800-020">Self-determination theory</a> tells us that if employees have a strong sense of competency, they are more likely to feel a sense of intrinsic motivation, which leads to increased productivity and efficiency and ultimately better outcomes.</p>
  <h2 id="step-2-put-this-data-to-work">Step 2: Put This Data to Work</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="put-employees-at-the-heart-of-everything-you-do-with-sap-successfactors">Put employees at the heart of everything you do with SAP SuccessFactors</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm/hxm-suite.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Every individual has unbound potential to be tapped, but many struggle to find their ideal place in the world of work. We dream of a future where our uniqueness allows us to be our best, which can include work we love to do that brings fulfillment, meaning, and purpose; work we are good at and an environment fit that helps us perform at our very best; or work that builds our confidence to tackle any challenge.</p>
  <p>When organizations create optimal conditions characterized by inclusion, support, and understanding of uniqueness, employees are empowered to be their authentic selves. Doing this opens the gate to a dynamic, thriving workforce.</p>
  <p>How can organizations leverage data to find the right person–environment fit? Imagine having individually curated options, selected for each individual, to match their strengths and styles. Our research demonstrates two primary pain points in the workplace today: finding available opportunities to learn what’s possible and assessing the right fit to an individual’s strengths. The degree of fit, match for an opportunity, and even potential gaps can be a black hole for employees today. At SAP, we have developed a new solution, SAP SuccessFactors Opportunity Marketplace, which uses data to help individuals find these individualized opportunities and realize their potential.</p>
  <p>The workplace experience is no longer just a hire-to-retire, linear story. Our individuality allows us to create our own paths, learn and grow, and leverage our strengths in the avenues of our choice. A deep understanding of individuals’ strengths and styles helps us curate our own path and select opportunities where we are most likely to succeed and thrive. Putting data to work is brought to life through short-term assignments, formal or experiential learning, peer connections, potential roles, and practicing new skills.</p>
  <h2 id="step-3-living-my-best-self-at-work">Step 3: Living My Best Self at Work</h2>
  <p>With a solid understanding of strengths and styles, organizations can create space for us to be our best selves at work. Consider an example of how one might apply strengths and styles to daily work. Let’s use the example of an operations supervisor whose role and team provide a high degree of structure. The operations supervisor learns through her strengths and styles data that she is extremely high in the creativity trait. She feels the urgency to make a creative impact and enrolls in a design thinking skill path, which has been curated for her as a possible interest. After completing the course, she has increased confidence in her strengths and skills and exceeds even her own expectations by taking on the responsibility of leading the operations innovation workstream.</p>
  <h2 id="close-the-gaps">Close the Gaps</h2>
  <p>New opportunities exist for organizations that can close the gap between organizational need and the strengths and styles of their employees. They can craft their next wave of employee experience around individualization and power their people strategy with unique personal formulas that define who they are.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-successfactors-opportunity-marketplace-drives-internal-mobility-and-upskilling-to-help-organizations-future-proof-their-business">SAP SuccessFactors Opportunity Marketplace Drives Internal Mobility and Upskilling to Help Organizations Future-Proof Their Business</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/10/sap-successfactors-opportunity-marketplace-drives-internal-mobility-and-upskilling-to-help-organizations-future-proof-their-business">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="learn-more-about-delivering-individualized-recommendations-for-employees-with-sap-successfactors-opportunity-marketplace"><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/dg/g-experience-opportunity-campaign/index.html">Learn more about delivering individualized recommendations for employees with SAP SuccessFactors Opportunity Marketplace.</a></h3>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Scott Lietzke is vice president of Product Design at SAP SuccessFactors.</em><br><em>Julie Bartholic is vice president of Product Innovation Design at SAP SuccessFactors.</em><br><em>Caitlynn Sendra is EX product scientist at SAP SuccessFactors.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/future-of-work</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-opportunity-marketplace</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dynamic Teams Will Power the Future of Work]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/dynamic-teams-power-future-of-work</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/dynamic-teams-power-future-of-work</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Identify, track, measure and optimize the outcomes of dynamic teams within your workforce with SAP SuccessFactors software. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_12559a4c109c05d7d3f688b310b0124d46ae0bc39.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_12559a4c109c05d7d3f688b310b0124d46ae0bc39.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_12559a4c109c05d7d3f688b310b0124d46ae0bc39.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Dynamic Teams Will Power the Future of Work" src="./media_12559a4c109c05d7d3f688b310b0124d46ae0bc39.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="dynamic-teams-will-power-the-future-of-work">Dynamic Teams Will Power the Future of Work</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Each year when we host <a href="https://events.sap.com/successconnect/en/global-home">SuccessConnect</a>, it takes a village. For several months, a cross-functional group of people from sales, marketing, communications, product, and engineering come together to collaborate and put on an incredible program for our customers. At the end, the group celebrates their success, debriefs, then returns to their “day jobs.”</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>This is the perfect example of a <strong>dynamic team</strong>: a group of people with different skills, strengths, and work styles, that work together on a mission-critical initiative, and once the team’s goals are achieved, they disband. Increasingly, this is the way work gets done. Our research found that 82% of employees have participated in a dynamic team more than once in their current organizations.*</p>
  <p>Dynamic teams are sometimes the most innovative and productive groups within an organization, creating important networks and lasting impact. However, with today’s human capital management (HCM) systems, these teams – and their value – are hidden.</p>
  <p>Consider what happens today when a leader needs to assemble a team for an important, high-visibility project. They’re likely to pull in people they already know. But is this the best way to optimize both initial results and long-lasting effects? Does this serve diverse populations that may be hidden themselves?</p>
  <p>With dynamic teams hidden from view, organizations lack insight into how work is allocated, how to optimize and replicate results, and how well capabilities are building. Meanwhile, employees are not getting recognition for the skills they are gaining and the results they are delivering. And within the dynamic teams themselves, leaders and team members lack the visibility into what each person brings to the table and how they can most effectively work together.</p>
  <p>This lack of transparency is holding us back in our pursuit of personal and organizational sustainability and adaptability.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-successfactors-opportunity-marketplace-drives-internal-mobility-and-upskilling-to-help-organizations-future-proof-their-business">SAP SuccessFactors Opportunity Marketplace Drives Internal Mobility and Upskilling to Help Organizations Future-Proof Their Business</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="the-next-chapter-for-hxm-dynamic-teams">The Next Chapter for HXM: Dynamic Teams</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-more-news-and-coverage-from-successconnect">Read more news and coverage from SuccessConnect</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/topics/successconnect">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Today at SuccessConnect, we announced the <a href="/">delivery of SAP SuccessFactors Opportunity Marketplace</a>, backed by our center of capabilities, as the foundation for bottom-up learning, skilling, and self-development. It is an ever-evolving platform that extends beyond the traditional matching capabilities of HCM software to support a range of opportunities, from learning content and mentor relationships to temporary assignments and career roles, curated around an <a href="/2021/07/opportunity-in-x-redefine-employee-experience">individual’s whole self</a> — who they are today and who they are becoming.</p>
  <p>But we are not stopping there. We believe that dynamic teams are the pinnacle of opportunities. Just think about when you experienced your most significant growth – was it when you were holed up in your office studying or when you were surrounded by a team working together on an audacious goal? It was most likely the latter. Our research found that when an employee participates on a dynamic team, more than 70% of their line managers report a positive impact on their career development and engagement.</p>
  <p>Today, we shared our vision to bring dynamic teams to the forefront of <a href="https://www.sap.com/programs/experience-wins.html">human experience management</a> (HXM). With HXM technology to support dynamic teams, organizations can identify, track, measure and optimize the outcomes of these hidden groups, and individuals can access broader development and networking opportunities.</p>
  <p>The benefits of elevating the power of teams include:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Diversity and inclusion:</strong> By making dynamic teams and the roles within them transparent, organizations can open opportunities to a broader set of colleagues. With data and insight into diversity of thought, strengths and backgrounds, they can assemble teams with balance and belonging.</li>
    <li><strong>Trackable investments:</strong> Understanding where and how work is being done, organizations can gain greater insights into what and who is driving innovation and agility throughout their business.</li>
    <li><strong>Sustainable development and transformation:</strong> Participating in a cross-functional team helps people acquire new skills and strengthen their network. This growth benefits their “day jobs” by fostering ongoing adaptability and development. In turn, organizations can accelerate broad transformation initiatives that rely on the network effects of cross-functional skill development and behavioral change.</li>
    <li><strong>Health and prosperity:</strong> With a better understanding of who we are as individuals and what we can bring to a team, along with greater empathy and understanding of our teammates and how best to work together, we can optimize team dynamics. Not only does this help deliver tremendous results, but it also helps people have more fun in doing so.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>Human experience management is about putting people at the center of business. With our introduction of <a href="http://sap.com/opportunitymarketplace">SAP SuccessFactors Opportunity Marketplace</a> and the center of capabilities this year, and dynamic teams next year, we are reshaping the way we work and grow – as organizations and as humans. So together, we can change work for good.</p>
  <p>Our journey to bring our HXM vision to life would not be possible without the hundreds of customers who have partnered and co-innovated with us. To get involved, visit the <a href="https://training.sap.com/successfactors-community?redirectreason=notregistered&#x26;referer=https%3A%2F%2Fcommunity.successfactors.com%2F">SAP SuccessFactors Community page</a>.</p>
  <p>Learn more about dynamics teams by tuning into <a href="https://events.sap.com/successconnect/en/global-home">SuccessConnect</a> and reading our current research on <a href="https://community.successfactors.com/t5/SAP-SuccessFactors-HR-Research/ct-p/HRResearch">SAP SuccessFactors Community</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><em>Amy Wilson is senior vice president of Products and Design for SAP SuccessFactors.</em></p>
        <p><em>*Based on a survey of 1,492 dynamic team-members and line managers globally, conducted by the SAP SuccessFactors HR Research Team (March, 2021).</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/dynamic-teams</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/future-of-work</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-opportunity-marketplace</category>
            <category>sap-event/successconnect</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP SuccessFactors Opportunity Marketplace Drives Internal Mobility and Upskilling to Help Organizations Future-Proof Their Business]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/sap-successfactors-opportunity-marketplace-drives-internal-mobility-and-upskilling-to-help-organizations-future-proof-their-business</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/sap-successfactors-opportunity-marketplace-drives-internal-mobility-and-upskilling-to-help-organizations-future-proof-their-business</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP SuccessFactors Opportunity Marketplace offers workers individualized recommendations to fuel growth and increase organizational agility.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_184abae706dea2e2c38f49dcb13cd8426b669d7fc.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_184abae706dea2e2c38f49dcb13cd8426b669d7fc.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_184abae706dea2e2c38f49dcb13cd8426b669d7fc.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP SuccessFactors Opportunity Marketplace Drives Internal Mobility and Upskilling to Help Organizations Future-Proof Their Business" src="./media_184abae706dea2e2c38f49dcb13cd8426b669d7fc.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-successfactors-opportunity-marketplace-drives-internal-mobility-and-upskilling-to-help-organizations-future-proof-their-business">SAP SuccessFactors Opportunity Marketplace Drives Internal Mobility and Upskilling to Help Organizations Future-Proof Their Business</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced <a href="http://sap.com/opportunitymarketplace">SAP SuccessFactors Opportunity Marketplace</a>, a new solution that connects workers with individualized recommendations to fuel personal growth and development and increase organizational agility.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Backed by a capabilities framework, the SAP SuccessFactors Opportunity Marketplace solution goes beyond traditional skills-based matching to consider an individual’s interests, workstyles and experience to recommend mentorships, learning and networking opportunities as well as short-term assignments, gigs and fellowships.</p>
  <p>Forty-five percent of leaders believe building an organizational culture that celebrates growth, adaptability and resilience is the most important action they can take to transform work, <a href="https://www2.deloitte.com/us/en/insights/focus/human-capital-trends/2021.html">according to Deloitte</a>. At the same time, a <a href="https://www.qualtrics.com/blog/labor-shortage-study/?utm_medium=social&#x26;utm_campaign=gl+socialSharer&#x26;utm_content=onpage+share&#x26;utm_source=email">recent Qualtrics study</a> found that purposeful work is among the top three priorities for job candidates.</p>
  <p>SAP SuccessFactors Opportunity Marketplace provides individuals the agency to find and pursue internal opportunities that align with their personal values, passions and interests as well as the strategic needs of the business. At the same time, leaders can gain increased visibility and a better understanding of the strengths and capabilities of their people and teams. The potential gains for individuals and organizations are immense: increased retention and engagement, and ongoing adaptability that will keep people and companies growing and ready for change.</p>
  <p>“Preparing for the jobs of the future requires organizations to rethink how they approach learning, internal mobility and upskilling in a way that is informed by data and puts the needs of individuals at the center,” said Meg Bear, Chief Product Officer, SAP SuccessFactors. “The center of capabilities and SAP SuccessFactors Opportunity Marketplace, which we previewed at the SuccessConnect event last year, are the latest examples of how we continue to deliver on our vision of human experience management. By empowering people to celebrate their individuality, from their skills to aspirations, we can elevate their strengths, build dynamic teams and transform the human experience at work.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-how-sap-successfactors-opportunity-marketplace-puts-employees-in-control-of-their-development-and-growth">Learn how SAP SuccessFactors Opportunity Marketplace puts employees in control of their development and growth</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/dg/g-experience-opportunity-campaign/index.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="using-machine-learning-to-help-people-bring-their-whole-selves-to-work">Using Machine Learning to Help People Bring Their Whole Selves to Work</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-more-news-and-coverage-from-successconnect">Read more news and coverage from SuccessConnect</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/topics/successconnect">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The foundation of SAP SuccessFactors Opportunity Marketplace is the center of capabilities, a centralized framework embedded throughout SAP SuccessFactors Human Experience Management (HXM) Suite. The center of capabilities uses machine learning to power an <a href="/2021/08/swooptalent-future-ready-workforce">adaptable talent profile</a> that continuously shapes and refines a digital picture of an individual’s <a href="/2020/10/whole-self-model-organizational-agility">whole self</a> over time, including their skills, competencies, strengths, styles and expertise as well as their motivations, work styles, aspirations and interests. It continuously updates an individual’s preferences for development and growth to ensure the recommendations presented within SAP SuccessFactors Opportunity Marketplace reflect their current interests and goals.</p>
  <p>SAP SuccessFactors Opportunity Marketplace and the center of capabilities will be generally available as part of the <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2019/11/26c9b241-717d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff.html">2H 2021 release</a> of SAP SuccessFactors HXM Suite. Learn more about these innovations at <a href="https://events.sap.com/successconnect/en/global-home">SuccessConnect</a> and read about our vision for 2022 in “<a href="/">Dynamic Teams Will Power the Future of Work</a>.”</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_13ad81641e749b4d078fbb3710b7f04687658ab39.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_13ad81641e749b4d078fbb3710b7f04687658ab39.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_13ad81641e749b4d078fbb3710b7f04687658ab39.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Infographic: SAP SuccessFactors Opportunity Marketplace" src="./media_13ad81641e749b4d078fbb3710b7f04687658ab39.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1462" height="657">
    </picture>Visit the <a href="/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP on Twitter at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.
  </p>
  <p><strong>About SAP</strong></p>
  <p>SAP’s strategy is to help every business run as an intelligent enterprise. As a market leader in enterprise application software, we help companies of all sizes and in all industries run at their best: 77% of the world’s transaction revenue touches an SAP system. Our machine learning, Internet of Things (IoT), and advanced analytics technologies help turn customers’ businesses into intelligent enterprises. SAP helps give people and organizations deep business insight and fosters collaboration that helps them stay ahead of their competition. We simplify technology for companies so they can consume our software the way they want – without disruption. Our end-to-end suite of applications and services enables business and public customers across 25 industries globally to operate profitably, adapt continuously, and make a difference. With a global network of customers, partners, employees, and thought leaders, SAP helps the world run better and improve people’s lives. For more information, visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/">www.sap.com</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Note to editors:</strong><br>To preview and download broadcast-standard stock footage and press photos digitally, please visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/photos">www.sap.com/photos</a>. On this platform, you can find high resolution material for your media channels. To view video stories on diverse topics, visit <a href="http://www.sap-tv.com">www.sap-tv.com</a>. From this site, you can embed videos into your own Web pages, share video via email links, and subscribe to RSS feeds from SAP TV.</p>
  <p><strong>For customers interested in learning more about SAP products:</strong><br>Global Customer Center: +49 180 534-34-24<br>United States Only: 1 (800) 872-1SAP (1-800-872-1727)</p>
  <p><strong>For more information, press only:</strong><br>Samantha Yerks, +1 (914) 918-6087, <a href="mailto:samantha.yerks@sap.com">samantha.yerks@sap.com</a>, ET<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>Any statements contained in this document that are not historical facts are forward-looking statements as defined in the U.S. Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995. Words such as “anticipate,” “believe,” “estimate,” “expect,” “forecast,” “intend,” “may,” “plan,” “project,” “predict,” “should” and “will” and similar expressions as they relate to SAP are intended to identify such forward-looking statements. SAP undertakes no obligation to publicly update or revise any forward-looking statements. All forward-looking statements are subject to various risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results to differ materially from expectations. The factors that could affect SAP’s future financial results are discussed more fully in SAP’s filings with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (“SEC”), including SAP’s most recent Annual Report on Form 20-F filed with the SEC. Readers are cautioned not to place undue reliance on these forward-looking statements, which speak only as of their dates.<br>© 2021 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.<br>Please consider our <a href="https://www.sap.com/corporate/en/legal/privacy.html">privacy policy</a>. If you received this press release in your e-mail and you wish to unsubscribe to our mailing list please contact <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a> and write Unsubscribe in the subject line.</p>
  <p><em>Please see <a href="http://www.deloitte.com/us/about">www.deloitte.com/us/about</a> for a detailed description of our legal structure.</em></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-opportunity-marketplace</category>
            <category>sap-event/successconnect</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>