<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/service-industries/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2021 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[IBM and SAP Partnering to Help Industrial Manufacturers Thrive in the New Service-Based Economy]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/industrial-manufacturers-service-based-economy-ibm-sap</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/industrial-manufacturers-service-based-economy-ibm-sap</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In a service-based economy, IBM and SAP provide the intelligent workflows to help industrial manufacturers thrive. Read about the partnership.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1dee27b3b14075492b8e43739a32a35fc2bd351cf.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1dee27b3b14075492b8e43739a32a35fc2bd351cf.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1dee27b3b14075492b8e43739a32a35fc2bd351cf.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="IBM and SAP Partnering to Help Industrial Manufacturers Thrive in the New Service-Based Economy" src="./media_1dee27b3b14075492b8e43739a32a35fc2bd351cf.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="ibm-and-sap-partnering-to-help-industrial-manufacturers-thrive-in-the-new-service-based-economy">IBM and SAP Partnering to Help Industrial Manufacturers Thrive in the New Service-Based Economy</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Industrial manufacturing companies are dealing with significant economic challenges, changing customer demands, increased digitalization, new competitors, and complex global supply chains. These challenges have been amplified during the <a href="/covid-19">pandemic</a>, forcing industrial manufacturing companies to focus on building resilient operations and optimize and automate their existing business processes.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>However, to sustain and grow their business, industrial manufacturing companies must develop new business models that address an economy that is moving to outcome-based and sustainable solutions.</p>
  <p>The IBM Institute for Business Value and Oxford Economics recently published the results of a survey, based on interviews with 500 executives. According to this <a href="https://www.ibm.com/downloads/cas/0VQ6LXK1">survey</a>:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Sixty-six percent of industrial manufacturing companies are already focusing on new service business models and increasing revenue share from services</li>
    <li>Five to 10% yearly growth is forecasted in services revenue against two percent in selling new equipment</li>
    <li>EBIT margin generated by service-based models is three to seven times higher compared to new equipment sales</li>
    <li>Twenty-two percent growth is expected in outcome-based services</li>
  </ul>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-the-solution-sheet-harness-the-power-of-intelligent-manufacturing-workflows-with-sap-and-ibm">Read the solution sheet: Harness the Power of Intelligent Manufacturing Workflows with SAP and IBM</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/05/9eb062fe-e07d-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="ibm-cognitive-enterprise-solutions-enable-intelligent-workflows-for-industrial-manufacturers">IBM Cognitive Enterprise Solutions Enable Intelligent Workflows for Industrial Manufacturers</h2>
  <p>In this time of constant and accelerated change, industrial manufacturing companies must adapt quickly to optimize their existing business and develop new service models for growth. They have to manage complex processes across their entire enterprise and systems. So they are looking for out-of-the-box integrated business applications, which support modular processes that solve specific industry problems, be flexibly consumed, and have intelligence embedded in the processes.</p>
  <p>The IBM Cognitive Enterprise solution, jointly developed by IBM and SAP, provides the intelligent workflows that support these data-driven processes: Intelligent as they are embedded with artificial intelligence to predict outcomes; workflow as they follow the natural flow of work, from one employee to the next, tapping into application data along the way and making appropriate decisions — whether it means capturing customer feedback to further personalize the next client interaction or leveraging machine data to increase the productivity of the production line.</p>
  <p>We are grateful for the feedback that the SAP Global Industry Advisory Council for Industrial Machinery &#x26; Components shared with our joint teams. This input was leveraged as the blueprint of the now available end-to-end intelligent workflows.</p>
  <p>The teams, under the umbrella of the SAP/IBM Evolution Partnership, have delivered four differentiating intelligent workflows — lead-to-order, plan-to-manufacture, order-to-cash, and maintain-to-resolve (aftermarket) — that include new capabilities focused on improving specific business metrics. Key capabilities include intelligent Ssles, cognitive pricing, outcome-based business model, connected manufacturing, and connected asset, which help clients improve win-rates, reduce lead-to-order cycle time, improve customer experience, improve worker safety, and improve overall equipment effectiveness, as well as other key performance indicators (KPIs).</p>
  <h2 id="scale-your-transformation">Scale Your Transformation</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="video-harness-the-power-of-intelligent-manufacturing-workflows-with-sap-and-ibm">Video: Harness the Power of Intelligent Manufacturing Workflows with SAP and IBM</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2021/04/00e0d5b0-de7d-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>These intelligent workflows are built on IBM’s Essentials® platform. This platform helps with technology adoption and modernization by individualizing the orchestration of these industry-specific intelligent workflows into our client environments. It enables seamless deployment into heterogeneous landscapes that globally distributed organizations are characterized with, along with a modern architecture that allows for integration with existing applications. It provides possibilities to modernize applications, without disturbing the end-to-end process orchestration, while providing process visibility and control through embedded intelligence and automation.</p>
  <p>This helps our clients to deploy and scale innovations, and supports them on their journey to become intelligent enterprises by:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Accelerating implementations and reducing time to value</li>
    <li>Lowering the cost of implementation through reduced need for customization</li>
    <li>Providing the ability to rapidly adapt the preconfigured workflows to each clients’ specific needs</li>
    <li>Allowing different solutions to be incorporated flexibly via a consumption model</li>
  </ul>
  <p>We are pleased to report early successes in various life-cycle stages of clients in this industry. These include</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Lead-to-order at an European engineered appliances manufacturer</li>
    <li>Outcome-based business model at a leading European packaging machinery manufacturer</li>
    <li>Connected manufacturing at a leading defense equipment manufacturer in the Middle East</li>
    <li>End-to-end industry capability model at a leading Japanese machine tools, automation, and textile machinery manufacturer</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="ready-for-the-next-transition">Ready for the Next Transition</h2>
  <p>We continue to listen to our customers, and our current focus areas include incorporating sustainable and carbon metrics through the design-to-operate process as well as a control tower, which will provide additional data-driven insights to co-ordinate agile and responsive supply chains.</p>
  <p>To read more about the solutions see the Industrial <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/05/9eb062fe-e07d-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Manufacturing</a> Solution Sheet: <a href="https://www.ibm.com/downloads/cas/ZRBEEBZ1">https://www.ibm.com/downloads/cas/ZRBEEBZ1</a></p>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div>To get more information on IBM’s partnership with SAP and additional solutions visit <a href="http://www.ibm-sap.com/digitaltransformation">www.ibm-sap.com/digitaltransformation</a></div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>Georg Kube is global vice president of Industrial Machinery and Components at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><em>Manish Chawla is general manager of Global Chemicals, Petroleum &#x26; Industrial Products Industries at IBM.</em></p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="industrial-machinery-and-components-deliver-personalized-smart-products-and-solutions-at-scale-and-as-a-service">Industrial Machinery and Components: Deliver personalized, smart products and solutions at scale and as a service</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/industrial-manufacturing.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/ibm</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/service-industries</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Servitization: The Shift from Products to Services that’s Redefining Competitive Differentiation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/06/servitization-redefining-competitive-differentiation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/06/servitization-redefining-competitive-differentiation</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Servitization, or integrating services into the overall business model, can reveal new business potential and new sources of revenue.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15b44b0dd65c5841b6afea455abca0008bcc10677.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15b44b0dd65c5841b6afea455abca0008bcc10677.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_15b44b0dd65c5841b6afea455abca0008bcc10677.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Servitization: The Shift from Products to Services that’s Redefining Competitive Differentiation" src="./media_15b44b0dd65c5841b6afea455abca0008bcc10677.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="servitization-the-shift-from-products-to-services-thats-redefining-competitive-differentiation">Servitization: The Shift from Products to Services that’s Redefining Competitive Differentiation</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>The quest for improvement and innovation to build productivity, drive greater value, and seek opportunities in new markets is perpetual for every successful business. As a result, executives and organizational leaders alike continuously evaluate their business models, offerings, and operational processes to gain any advantage they can find, especially when their products become increasingly commoditized.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Based on current research, servitization appears to be an effective antidote against the ease of product switching. McKinsey &#x26; Company <a href="https://www.mckinsey.com/business-functions/operations/our-insights/aftermarket-services-the-near-term-growth-opportunity-in-targeting-the-right-customers">reports</a> that while margins on new product sales are typically 10%, aftermarket service margins average 25%.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="keep-your-systems-running-at-peak-performance-with-sap-services-and-support">Keep your systems running at peak performance with SAP Services and Support</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/support.html#services-support-offerings">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="what-is-servitization">What Is Servitization?</h2>
  <p>Servitization is a strategy that product-oriented companies use to enhance and differentiate their competitiveness by integrating services into their overall business model. This shift can be seen on a continuum in which producing and selling products is coupled with a focus on adding services to the offering and ultimately integrating them. Very quickly, customer value moves from owning and using the product to capturing value with the product while services are perceived as a cost factor.</p>
  <p>While this concept is not new, widespread <a href="https://www.mdpi.com/2076-3417/10/8/2957/htm">adoption of intelligent technology</a> – such as <a href="https://insights.sap.com/what-is-iot-internet-of-things/">the Internet of Things (IoT)</a>, <a href="https://insights.sap.com/what-is-machine-learning/">machine learning</a>, and <a href="https://insights.sap.com/what-is-predictive-analytics/">predictive analytics</a> – is fueling this approach to break into new markets and fulfill underserved customer needs. More recent product-service <a href="https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/abs/10.1002/bse.414">servitization models</a> may include bundled support services, consumption or pay-for-use, and outcome-based services.</p>
  <p>An earlier form of servitization emerged in 1962 when <a href="https://www.rolls-royce.com/media/press-releases-archive/yr-2012/121030-the-hour.aspx">Rolls-Royce</a> pioneered its famous “Power by the Hour” engine maintenance service concept. This model allowed airlines to pay for the time spent maintaining and replacing their aircraft engine. As technology advanced, sensors were incorporated for engine-condition monitoring and predictive maintenance services.</p>
  <p>A few decades later, tire manufacturer Michelin redefined the service-oriented model to help trucking companies reduce fuel consumption. Payment for the service is based on achieving predefined fuel consumption targets, tracked through telematics and IoT, and assessed in real time with data analytics.</p>
  <p>Many more companies have followed Rolls-Royce’s and Michelin’s example, including <a href="https://www.sap.com/dmc/exp/2019-11-sap-leonardo-customer-success/book/index.html?chapter=20">Kaeser Kompressoren</a>, <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2020/01/10/learn-how-to-obtain-a-superior-b2b-customer-experience-with-these-valuable-insights/?sh=3f981bdd7777">Grundfos</a>, and <a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2020/09/50b8398d-b27d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff.html">Tetra Pak</a>. It is noted that in all cases, IT – specifically IoT and <a href="https://insights.sap.com/what-is-industry-4-0/">Industry 4.0</a> – <a href="https://www.researchgate.net/publication/311206173_The_servitization_of_industry_EU_law_implications_and_challenges">plays a significant role</a> in enabling product-service servitization.</p>
  <p>Over time, this approach has become a critical component of manufacturers’ growth strategies. In fact, a <a href="https://www.paconsulting.com/globalassets/downloads/servitization-report.pdf">survey</a> of 60 European industrial manufacturing firms reported that servitization increases average growth margin from services delivered ranging between 15% and 35%. Another <a href="https://www.porsche-consulting.com/fileadmin/docs/04_Medien/Publikationen/745199_Beyond_the_product/Beyond_the_Product_C_2021_Porsche_Consulting-v3.pdf">survey</a> found that the 10% total returns to shareholders (TRS) achieved by servitization champions significantly exceeded the -1% median TRS of their peers. And in the spirit of these findings, Professor Klaus Schwab, founder and executive chairman of the World Economic Forum, <a href="https://www.researchgate.net/publication/327583386_THE_SERVITIZATION_IN_INDUSTRY_40_FACING_CHALLENGES_AND_TENDENCIES">identified</a> servitization as one of the megatrends that will shape the future of business and society.</p>
  <h2 id="how-to-turn-servitization-into-a-revenue-generator">How to Turn Servitization Into a Revenue Generator</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="gain-greater-insight-into-the-internet-of-things">Gain greater insight into the Internet of Things</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://insights.sap.com/what-is-iot-internet-of-things/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Regardless of the advantages servitization offers, many businesses still question how to best recognize and adopt appropriate service options that deliver the best value to the customer. Some of the challenges encountered include culture change, competency adoption, process, system creation, and commercialization.</p>
  <p>In many ways, a transformation journey toward servitization includes four fundamental maturity stages:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Splintered:</strong> The organization struggles under a myriad of silos that lead to disjointed, manual processes. Legacy, fragmented enterprise resource planning (ERP) environments provide little or no visibility on operational performance. The business model is on pure product, with challenges to profitability.</li>
    <li><strong>Side car:</strong> The organization has standardized the two chunks of the value chain – back and front desk – but keeps them separated. Since efficiency is critical at this stage, few add-on services are delivered, field services are based on basic mobile capabilities, and IoT stacks are only proofs of concept.</li>
    <li><strong>Joined up:</strong> Front- and back-office flows are integrated bidirectionally and leverage advanced technologies, such as IoT, to feed core systems with real-time data. In some cases, edge capabilities bring coordinated autonomy to local sites, a suite of digital services are made fully available, and business model enhancements including pay-as-you-use and outcome-based contracts are actively explored.</li>
    <li><strong>Borderless:</strong> Processes start and end outside the organization and operations, while technology enables different elements of the value chain to connect. Co-creation, data-sharing, and collaboration with customers, suppliers, partners from other sectors, and even competitors are part of the business model.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>After demonstrating the importance of servitization during existing economic conditions and business performance, appropriate servitization concepts steadily replace the status quo, closing the gap between strategic intent and realized goals.</p>
  <p>A critical part of progressing servitization maturity is transforming the business culture to encourage leaders and employees to <a href="https://www.emerald.com/insight/content/doi/10.1108/09564230310474138/full/html">shift their perception</a> of services from add-ons or giveaways to a valued part of the business model.</p>
  <p>According to Guido Schlief, senior vice president and head of Services in Middle and Eastern Europe at SAP, “Our observation is that customers increasingly expect business outcomes from their suppliers – outcome-based services are a clear industry trend.”</p>
  <p>Successfully embracing this shift can have a significant effect on the <a href="https://www.researchgate.net/publication/225473204_Exploring_the_financial_consequences_of_the_servitization_of_manufacturing">profitability</a> of a servitized business. Deep insights into customer needs are required to design value-added services that are valuable from the market perspective, not from the supplier side. For example, although monitoring of equipment condition has limited value to the customer, equipment availability directly impacts the customer experience.</p>
  <p>Product companies must also consider a servitization model that shifts upfront transactional sales and payments to long-term contracts with perpetual payments, enabling customer-centric relationship building. <a href="https://www.emerald.com/insight/content/doi/10.1108/09564230310474138/full/html">Successful delivery of this approach</a> demands an effective services organization, resembling a professional services firm containing the right processes, tools, and personnel who possess specialized skills. Although service personnel typically <a href="https://www.researchgate.net/publication/225473204_Exploring_the_financial_consequences_of_the_servitization_of_manufacturing">cost</a> more than manufacturing personnel, the investment can help <a href="https://www.mdpi.com/2076-3417/10/8/2957/htm">overcome critical hurdles</a>, such as lack of knowledge in systematic transformation and the ability to make required changes, in gaining the full benefit of servitization.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1adca1e54ae4bfb993a639078ad89fa90438c6d33.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1adca1e54ae4bfb993a639078ad89fa90438c6d33.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1adca1e54ae4bfb993a639078ad89fa90438c6d33.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_1adca1e54ae4bfb993a639078ad89fa90438c6d33.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="300" height="168">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p><em>Figure 1: Servitization performance balanced scorecard. Click to enlarge.</em></p>
  <p>Over time, the transformation into a servitization model can be assessed to help ensure it satisfies the core needs of the business: financial, internal, customers, innovation, and learning. For example, pure financial measures – such as service revenue growth or services market share – can be <a href="https://www.researchgate.net/publication/322834491_Measuring_servitization_progress_and_outcome_the_case_of_&#x27;advanced_services&#x27;">evaluated</a> alongside a proposed a balanced scorecard to provide a comprehensive view on servitization performance (See Figure 1).</p>
  <h2 id="get-ready-servitization-is-here-to-stay">Get Ready: Servitization Is Here to Stay</h2>
  <p>As customers gain less interest in the shiny new functionalities of new products and pay more attention to the outcomes they achieve, all signs point to the growing importance of services as a competitive differentiator.</p>
  <p>But remember, servitization is more than a pure vertical integration of the business model and goes far beyond add-on or giveaway services. In essence, it is a strategic transformation that spans across most business silos, requiring alignment between the business and IT and between the front and back office of the supplier.</p>
  <p>And if approached appropriately, the new business model can open new sources of revenue and bring a fundamental shift from a reactive break-fix mentality to proactive outcome-based services.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Frits Verhoef is head of Business Transformation Services CXO Advisory, Middle and Eastern Europe, at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-4-0</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-technologies</category>
            <category>news-tag/internet-of-things</category>
            <category>news-tag/service-industries</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Vodafone Is Changing the World of Telecommunications from the Inside Out]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/05/vodafone-group-telecommunications-sap-solutions</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/05/vodafone-group-telecommunications-sap-solutions</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 May 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Vodafone Group created a single digital core for the entire business based on SAP S4/HANA to gain greater consistency everywhere it operates.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16822df66158e2206f5da710120b1243898efd0bf.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16822df66158e2206f5da710120b1243898efd0bf.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_16822df66158e2206f5da710120b1243898efd0bf.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="How Vodafone Is Changing the World of Telecommunications from the Inside Out" src="./media_16822df66158e2206f5da710120b1243898efd0bf.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="how-vodafone-is-changing-the-world-of-telecommunications-from-the-inside-out">How Vodafone Is Changing the World of Telecommunications from the Inside Out</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>It is hard to imagine a technology that has changed the modern world more than the smartphone. Every day, millions of us use a single device to talk with friends, take videos, share photos, check e-mail, get driving directions, or go shopping. It’s been a global revolution.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As one of the world’s largest telecommunications companies, Vodafone Group connects more than 300 million people across the globe. And company leaders fully believe that tomorrow’s communications services will continue to transform our lives in powerful ways.</p>
  <p>Vodafone is already preparing for this future by making significant changes – and it is starting from within.</p>
  <h2 id="looking-for-global-consistency">Looking for Global Consistency</h2>
  <p>“Vodafone has been growing in recent years to strengthen its portfolio of services and expand into new geographies,” says Ignacio Garcia, CIO of Corporate Information Systems at Vodafone Group. But, as Garcia explains, much of this growth has been through acquisitions, resulting in various system landscapes and often inconsistent business practices throughout the group of companies.</p>
  <p>“We needed to operate as a single global organization and drive further innovation across the entire business,” Garcia adds. “To do that, we needed to run our company with a consistent, digital-first focus.” This realization led to big changes at Vodafone.</p>
  <p>The company migrated its complex and disparate enterprise resource planning (ERP) environment to a single digital core based on <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/s4hana-erp.html?btp=e479f1e4-7ee5-4e94-abfc-84a0233a3fb8">SAP S/4HANA</a>. “And we built on this solid foundation with SAP SuccessFactors, SAP Ariba, and SAP Concur solutions,” adds Holger Grewe, head of Corporate Transformation at Vodafone Group.</p>
  <p>Grewe – who has played a key leadership role in this project – points out that Vodafone benefited from some strong relationships along the way. This included implementation support from Accenture, SAP Services and Support, and customer success experts from SAP.</p>
  <p>“This was a massive transformation, covering more than twenty countries,” reports Grewe. “And SAP was by our side throughout the journey, supporting us with a <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/customer-involvement/customer-first.html">Customer First approach</a>.”</p>
  <h2 id="driving-needed-change">Driving Needed Change</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="discover-how-sap-empowers-telecommunications-providers">Discover how SAP empowers telecommunications providers</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/telecommunications.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The impact of the project on Vodafone’s operations has been huge.</p>
  <p>“We now have one data model that is standard across the footprint,” Grewe says. And Vodafone is simplifying the workplace for its more than 100,000 employees by digitizing business areas such as HR, travel and expense, and supply chain.</p>
  <p>Garcia estimates that Vodafone has standardized more than 80% of its core business processes and boosted automation levels to over 60%. “And it’s not the endgame,” remarks a smiling Garcia. “This is just the beginning.”</p>
  <p>In addition, Garcia notes that new capabilities like <a href="https://insights.sap.com/what-is-machine-learning/">machine learning</a> and advanced analytics will help Vodafone develop the next generation of products and services.</p>
  <h2 id="building-a-digital-future-at-vodafone-group">Building a Digital Future at Vodafone Group</h2>
  <p>Innovation will be crucial as <a href="https://www.vodafone.com/our-purpose">Vodafone looks ahead</a> to achieve specific goals for improving lives.</p>
  <p>By 2025, for example, the company wants to:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Connect over 50 million people and their families to mobile money services</li>
    <li>Bring mobile to an additional 20 million women in Africa and Turkey</li>
    <li>Support 10 million young people in learning the digital skills needed to thrive in the digital economy</li>
    <li>Connect 150 million vehicles to <a href="https://insights.sap.com/what-is-iot-internet-of-things/">the Internet of Things (IoT)</a></li>
  </ul>
  <p>Vodafone is confident that today’s transformation will enable the company to build a digital future that works for everyone. “These changes are helping Vodafone work as one company,” Grewe says, “so people around the world will stay better connected.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="test-drive-sap-s4hana-today">Test drive SAP S/4HANA today</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/s4hana-erp.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="to-hear-more-from-ignacio-garcia-and-holger-grewe-about-the-changes-at-vodafone-group-watch-this-video-also-check-out-these-videos-on-vodafones-experience-with-sap-successfactors-sap-concur-and-sap-ariba-solutions-as-well-as-sap-maxattention-services">To hear more from Ignacio Garcia and Holger Grewe about the changes at Vodafone Group, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/intelligent-enterprise.html?campaigncode=CRM-YD21-SOC-CUSTREF&#x26;video=d07a8f9f-df7d-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b">watch this video</a>. Also check out these videos on Vodafone’s experience with <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm.html?campaigncode=CRM-YD21-SOC-CUSTREF%E2%80%A2&#x26;video=ba32689d-df7d-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b">SAP SuccessFactors</a>, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/e-procurement/travel-expense-management.html?campaigncode=CRM-YD21-SOC-CUSTREF&#x26;video=eae78f9f-df7d-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b">SAP Concur</a> and <a href="https://www.ariba.com/?campaigncode=CRM-YD21-SOC-CUSTREF&#x26;video=2c7d909f-df7d-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b">SAP Ariba</a> solutions, as well as <a href="https://www.sap.com/uk/services/premium-engagement/maxattention.html?sort=latest_desc?campaigncode=CRM-YD21-SOC-CUSTREF&#x26;video=84788d9f-df7d-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b">SAP MaxAttention</a> services.</h3>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-concur</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-hana</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/service-industries</category>
            <category>industry/telecommunications</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP.iO Foundries San Francisco and New York Launch New Accelerator Programs]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/sap-io-foundries-san-francisco-and-new-york-programs</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/sap-io-foundries-san-francisco-and-new-york-programs</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New programs at SAP.iO Foundries San Francisco and New York focus on the future of work and professional services respectively.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-io</category>
            <category>news-tag/service-industries</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Electrification of Mobility: Challenges and Opportunities for Travel and Transportation Operators]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/e-mobility-travel-transportation-operators</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/e-mobility-travel-transportation-operators</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP recently hosted an industry forum about the e-mobility with leading operators and industry value chain actors. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-footprint</category>
            <category>news-tag/electric-vehicles</category>
            <category>news-tag/mobile</category>
            <category>industry/travel-transportation</category>
            <category>news-tag/service-industries</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Graham Construction Selects the ETM.next Solution to Digitally Transform Equipment and Tools Management]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/03/graham-construction-etmnext-equipment-tools-management</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/03/graham-construction-etmnext-equipment-tools-management</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Graham Construction has selected ETM.next to transform its equipment fleet and improve construction project profitability. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/service-industries</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Will Technology Keep Us Together? Ask Vodafone]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/03/technology-together-vodafone-cio-ignacio-garcia</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/03/technology-together-vodafone-cio-ignacio-garcia</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Mar 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Vodafone CIO Ignacio Garcia recently appeared on Getting Real with SAP to discuss leveraging technology to serve customers amid COVID-19.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e5eb9658e7797cedc7b5a1fe87983fdcf92873d7.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e5eb9658e7797cedc7b5a1fe87983fdcf92873d7.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1e5eb9658e7797cedc7b5a1fe87983fdcf92873d7.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Will Technology Keep Us Together? Ask Vodafone" src="./media_1e5eb9658e7797cedc7b5a1fe87983fdcf92873d7.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="will-technology-keep-us-together-ask-vodafone">Will Technology Keep Us Together? Ask Vodafone</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>It is easy to feel isolated these days, so it’s no wonder that we seem to rely on our smartphones more than ever to stay in touch through calls, texts, and social media.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>But the global health crisis has been challenging for everyone – including the companies that have been working hard to keep us connected, like Vodafone Group. Vodafone is a multinational technology communications company that serves more than 300 million mobile customers around the world.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="watch-the-episode-with-vodafone-conquering-the-challenge-head-on-by-doubling-service">Watch the episode with Vodafone: Conquering the Challenge “Head-On” By Doubling Service</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/covid-19/back-to-best.html?video=10d8458c-d17d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="quick-response-to-customers-and-employees">Quick Response to Customers and Employees</h2>
  <p>Ignacio Garcia, CIO of Corporate Information Systems at Vodafone, recently appeared on <em>Getting Real with SAP</em>. There, he discussed how companies are leveraging technology to manage their business and continue to serve customers in the age of <a href="/covid-19">COVID-19</a>.</p>
  <p>“You can imagine what we were thinking: How much extra demand are we going to have?” says Garcia. “We needed to keep our employees safe and make sure we supported our customers in the best possible way.”</p>
  <p>Vodafone was able to do both.</p>
  <p>In short order, the company developed a <a href="https://www.vodafone.com/covid19">five-point plan</a> to help the communities it serves. Keystones of the plan were a commitment to maintaining the quality of service and providing network capacity and network services for critical government functions.</p>
  <p>Vodafone also made sure to quickly address the needs of a global workforce that encompasses more than 100,000 employees. Vodafone offered support for working at home, created richer virtual training opportunities for its people, and adjusted performance goals and objectives to align with new business needs.</p>
  <h2 id="the-right-technology-pays-dividends">The Right Technology Pays Dividends</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="make-your-organization-more-resilient-and-agile-in-todays-challenging-environment-get-back-to-best-with-sap">Make your organization more resilient and agile in today’s challenging environment: Get back to best with SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/covid-19/back-to-best.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Vodafone’s business agility was not merely the result of good luck.</p>
  <p>Less than a year ago, Vodafone completed a massive global rollout of SAP S/4HANA to help improve operational efficiency in business functions such as finance, supply chain, and IT.</p>
  <p>It was an impressive project covering more than 20 countries. And in addition to establishing a single digital core for the company, it included retooling Vodafone’s worldwide HR systems. “Using the power of the technology was fundamental, having a single data model, a single way to optimize and understand the different markets,” says Garcia.</p>
  <h2 id="stay-creative">Stay Creative</h2>
  <p>Vodafone may have been ahead of the curve in its ability to meet the challenges of COVID-19. But many other companies are responding with technology-driven innovation. There has been an incredible degree of creativity in how businesses have reacted.</p>
  <p>Staying connected will only be one of the challenges we face in the days ahead. This is a critical time for all of us – as individuals and as businesses.</p>
  <p>Check out <a href="https://www.sap.com/covid-19/back-to-best.html?video=10d8458c-d17d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff">this episode of <em>Getting Real with SAP</em></a> to learn more.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em><a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2021/03/03/will-technology-keep-us-together-ask-vodafone/?sh=655f126042da">This story originally appeared on SAP BrandVoice on Forbes.</a></em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/back-to-best</category>
            <category>news-tag/covid-19</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/service-industries</category>
            <category>industry/telecommunications</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>