<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/opensap/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Navigating Tax Requirements in the Digital Era: Manage Compliance with Cloud ERP]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/tax-transformation-in-the-digital-era-course</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/tax-transformation-in-the-digital-era-course</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[To help tax professionals prepare for and become valuable members of tax transformation projects, SAP is introducing a new course.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_12d216e0addd5a9233a73cb4294d58a8906d2b314.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_12d216e0addd5a9233a73cb4294d58a8906d2b314.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_12d216e0addd5a9233a73cb4294d58a8906d2b314.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Navigating Tax Requirements in the Digital Era: Manage Compliance with Cloud ERP" src="./media_12d216e0addd5a9233a73cb4294d58a8906d2b314.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="navigating-tax-requirements-in-the-digital-era-manage-compliance-with-cloud-erp">Navigating Tax Requirements in the Digital Era: Manage Compliance with Cloud ERP</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>As businesses adapt to digitalization, they encounter various trends reshaping tax compliance. From emerging business models to governments’ digital initiatives, the tax landscape is undergoing significant transformation.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Authorities are starting to involve themselves in business transactions, disrupting well-established business processes and taking control of the invoicing flow between suppliers and buyers. As a result, they have the data needed to prevent tax evasion and start auditing taxpayers automatically or even auto-populating tax returns moving toward tax bills. Additionally, sustainability efforts and climate change regulations further impact tax regulations.</p>
  <p>Amid these shifts, SAP can provide peace of mind to navigate complexities efficiently. By understanding the evolving tax landscape, businesses can leverage SAP solutions to help streamline compliance processes and drive automation to capitalize on emerging opportunities.</p>
  <p>SAP solutions for global tax management are tailored to help address modern tax challenges. <a href="/topics/erp">SAP S/4HANA Cloud</a> can provide transparency and compliance on a global scale, enabling businesses to embed tax requirements in processes.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="pave-the-way-to-strategic-tax-management-and-automated-compliance-with-sap">Pave the way to strategic tax management and automated compliance with SAP</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/tax-management">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Through localized solutions that offer standardized but flexible business processes, a complete suite of solutions facilitates efficient tax management, from e-invoicing to statutory reporting and overall tax compliance. With SAP technology and expertise, businesses can achieve greater accuracy and agility in tax compliance, paving the way for sustainable growth and competitive advantage.</p>
  <p>To help tax professionals prepare for and become valuable members of tax transformation projects, SAP is introducing a new course: <strong><a href="https://open.sap.com/courses/s4htax-pc">Unlocking Tax Transformation with SAP</a></strong>.</p>
  <p>The course is designed to equip professionals with the knowledge needed to navigate today’s tax landscape and learn new capabilities that can be leveraged as part of SAP S/4HANA-enabled transformations to simplify tax compliance.</p>
  <p>The course offers practical strategies to learn about the different tax types, global developments and their business relevance, and the importance of technology with a focus on SAP S/4HANA and SAP solutions for global tax management. It begins on April 30 and <a href="https://open.sap.com/courses/s4htax-pc">enrollment is now open</a>. By enrolling in this course, tax professionals can gain valuable insights into industry best practices and leverage the latest SAP innovations to help optimize their tax processes.</p>
  <p>In a time of rapid change, SAP supports businesses on their journey to tax compliance and growth. Through collaboration with SAP and a commitment to continuous learning, businesses can navigate the complexities of taxation with confidence and achieve their long-term objectives.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Erika Buson is part of Product Marketing for Global Tax Management and Entity Close at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="follow-and-connect-with-sap-news-on-linkedin">Follow and connect with SAP News on LinkedIn</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news">Stay in touch</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/financial-management</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/financial-services</category>
            <category>news-tag/opensap</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Career Pathfinding on the AI Frontier: Become the Talent Behind the Tech]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/ai-careers-talent-behind-tech</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/ai-careers-talent-behind-tech</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The landscape of AI careers has exploded, with almost every industry needing people with AI skills at different levels.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/opensap</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Design a Circular Future with New openSAP Course]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/design-circular-future-opensap-course</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/design-circular-future-opensap-course</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A new openSAP course, Designing a Circular Economy, addresses how we can create the products we need in a circular way.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/circular-economy</category>
            <category>news-tag/opensap</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP's Vision for Supporting Business Transformation and the Workforce of the Future]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/vision-business-transformation-workforce-of-the-future</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/vision-business-transformation-workforce-of-the-future</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP has a vision for supporting the workforce of the future as humanity enters one of its most transformative phases. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/opensap</category>
            <category>non-sap-event/wef-davos</category>
            <category>product/sap-learning-hub</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-training-and-adoption</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-university-alliances</category>
            <category>news-tag/un-sdgs</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP CTO Juergen Mueller at SAP TechEd in 2021: We Can Reinvent the Global Economy]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/sap-cto-juergen-mueller-at-sap-teched-in-2021-we-can-reinvent-the-global-economy</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/sap-cto-juergen-mueller-at-sap-teched-in-2021-we-can-reinvent-the-global-economy</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Get a recap of the SAP CTO Juergen Mueller at SAP TechEd on the keynote stage, including how SAP is helping reinvent the global economy.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_191f9de1ccd2063bf3ea2a6f2f28afd66142e5e26.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_191f9de1ccd2063bf3ea2a6f2f28afd66142e5e26.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_191f9de1ccd2063bf3ea2a6f2f28afd66142e5e26.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP CTO Juergen Mueller at SAP TechEd in 2021: We Can Reinvent the Global Economy" src="./media_191f9de1ccd2063bf3ea2a6f2f28afd66142e5e26.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-cto-juergen-mueller-at-sap-teched-in-2021-we-can-reinvent-the-global-economy">SAP CTO Juergen Mueller at SAP TechEd in 2021: We Can Reinvent the Global Economy</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Juergen Mueller, chief technology officer and member of the Executive Board of SAP SE, kicked off <a href="https://reg.sapevents.sap.com/flow/sap/sapteched2021/portal/page/overview?source=social-glo-sap-newsblog1">SAP TechEd in 2021</a> with a hard-hitting strategic view of the major challenges business face and how leaders and developers are partnering with SAP to reinvent the global economy.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As companies and consumers struggle with the pandemic’s ongoing health and economic crises, supply chain disruptions remain the norm, and accelerated digital transformation demands cloud-based innovation. These challenges are taking place against the backdrop of increasing climate change and calls for equality.</p>
  <p>Mueller discussed how we can reinvent the global economy to meet climate change targets, rethinking how we deliver and consume products and services, how we manage waste, and how we use technology. Pointing out that inequality was causing social unrest worldwide, Mueller said that organizations needed to help everyone develop the right skills, which would open opportunities for people to work where they fit best.</p>
  <p>After going big with his global change vision, Mueller and his special guests went deep into SAP’s commitment to supporting its ecosystem of cloud-based innovators, spotlighting the latest <a href="/2021/11/sap-teched-news-citizen-professional-developer-tools-embedded-ai-free-learning-experience">solution announcements</a>, real-world customer examples, demonstrations of new developer tools, and free access to learning resources.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="watch-replays-from-sap-teched">Watch replays from SAP TechEd</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/events/teched.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="sap-helps-developers-innovate-at-scale-in-the-cloud">SAP Helps Developers Innovate at Scale in the Cloud</h2>
  <p>Mueller explained how RISE with SAP provides customers with a transition path to the cloud, while SAP continues to offer developers low-code/no-code and other tools to extend innovation on <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/s4hana-erp.html">SAP S/4HANA Cloud</a> built on <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP)</a>. In a preview of his developer keynote, SAP developer advocate Rich Heilman shared how the just-announced SAP S/4HANA Cloud, ABAP environment, equipped developers to build custom ABAP extensions for the public cloud offering SAP S/4HANA Cloud.</p>
  <p>Mueller said the objective was to make the ABAP environment for SAP S/4HANA Cloud <strong>the</strong> environment to build tightly coupled extensions for all cloud editions of SAP S/4HANA based on the public cloud APIs. This will help developers build upgrade-safe extensions and move toward a clean core. Equally important, it closes the last extension gap in SAP S/4HANA Cloud to ease the transition from on premise to the cloud.</p>
  <h2 id="making-it-easy-to-innovate-on-sap-btp">Making It Easy to Innovate on SAP BTP</h2>
  <p>As an example of how SAP continues responding to ecosystem innovation imperatives, Mueller announced the roll-out of the free tier model for SAP BTP to individual developers, including <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/integration-suite.html">SAP Integration Suite</a> and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hana/cloud.html">SAP HANA Cloud</a>. He was joined by Steffen Pietsch, head of Product Management for SAP BTP, who shared how developers can find available SAP BTP services, as well as use case examples to help build proofs of concept, on <a href="https://discovery-center.cloud.sap/">SAP Discovery Center</a>.</p>
  <p>Pietsch explained how a free tier makes it much easier to gain experience and start to innovate with SAP BTP. Developers can now build their proofs of concept on SAP BTP without any commitment; if they decide to move their applications toward productive usage, they can do so by changing from the free to the productive service plan without rebuilding the entire application in a different account.</p>
  <h2 id="low-codeno-code-speeds-up-development-on-sap-btp">Low-Code/No-Code Speeds Up Development on SAP BTP</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-the-sap-teched-news-guide">Read the SAP TechEd News Guide</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="http://sap.com/teched-news-guide">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Acknowledging the tech talent gap and the growing importance of citizen developers, Mueller said that SAP has doubled down on investments in low-code/no-code tools, announcing the launch of a unified <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/events/teched-news-guide/low-code-no-code-pro-code.html#top">low-code/no-code development experience</a> on SAP BTP. He said that SAP was introducing SAP AppGyver for no-code development, and making the <a href="https://www.sapstore.com/solutions/45318/SAP-Business-Application-Studio---the-evolution-of-SAP-Web-IDE">SAP Business Application Studio</a> available for low-code development. He also previewed <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/events/teched-news-guide/low-code-no-code-pro-code.html#article2">SAP Process Automation</a>, a no-code automation solution, showing the audience how non-technical business people, along with designers and experienced developers, can extend SAP Service Cloud with machine learning to quickly resolve customer service issues and speed up order approvals.</p>
  <p>Mueller said that low-code/no-code means both citizen and professional developers can increase productivity and innovate at scale, reflecting how business and IT work together. He saw this unlocking a new order of magnitude of value creation for individuals and society at-large.</p>
  <h2 id="gain-sap-specific-knowledge-free-of-charge">Gain SAP-Specific Knowledge Free of Charge</h2>
  <p>Reinforcing SAP’s commitment to developer learning, Mueller outlined the company’s newly-launched learning experience, <a href="https://learning.sap.com/">SAP Learning now available for free</a>. The centerpiece consisted of seven SAP BTP-specific learning journeys, with more to come.</p>
  <p>He said that the new learner experience was designed for all developer skill levels, including pro-code developers, IT professionals, academic students, and technology thought leaders. Noting that becoming a trusted SAP expert with certified skills has never been easier, Mueller saw all “makers” learning comprehensive skills by taking <a href="https://learning.sap.com/learning-journey">free-of-charge learning journeys</a> to qualify for <a href="https://learning.sap.com/certification">SAP certifications</a>.</p>
  <h2 id="sap-btp-foundation-of-the-intelligent-enterprise">SAP BTP: Foundation of the Intelligent Enterprise</h2>
  <p>Mueller capped his keynote off with an example from Porsche, which uses SAP Business Warehouse on SAP HANA and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/cloud-analytics.html">SAP Analytics Cloud</a> for accurate finance and investment planning across approximately 70 subsidiaries worldwide. Mueller held up Porsche as an example of the many companies worldwide using SAP solutions to simplify business processes and reporting with connected data. He announced the new SAP Data Warehouse Cloud, SAP BW bridge, allowing organizations to innovate faster by moving data from their existing SAP BW application to the SAP Data Warehouse Cloud solution.</p>
  <p>Mueller concluded with a heartfelt message to developers that as demand for SAP grows, the company’s ecosystem is an exciting place to be, nothing less than a true movement. Emphasizing that SAP BTP is the foundation of the intelligent enterprise, he encouraged developers to join in, using SAP’s tools for their success in supporting their companies and customers throughout their digital transformation journey.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Follow me: @smgaler</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-teched</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/opensap</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[New openSAP Course on the Circular Economy]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/new-circular-economy-course-opensap</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/new-circular-economy-course-opensap</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A new circular economy course on openSAP is free and open to anyone who wants to make a difference to the future of the planet. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_113f2308f10670c1d9eb45f0e2ab7e83fb6637d2f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_113f2308f10670c1d9eb45f0e2ab7e83fb6637d2f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_113f2308f10670c1d9eb45f0e2ab7e83fb6637d2f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="New openSAP Course on the Circular Economy" src="./media_113f2308f10670c1d9eb45f0e2ab7e83fb6637d2f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="new-opensap-course-on-the-circular-economy">New openSAP Course on the Circular Economy</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="register-for-the-new-opensap-course-now">Register for the new openSAP course now</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://open.sap.com/courses/ce1">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>The world is on track to increase waste generation by <a href="https://openknowledge.worldbank.org/bitstream/handle/10986/30317/211329ov.pdf?sequence=11&#x26;isAllowed=y">70%</a> over the next 30 years. Much of this garbage is plastic, and it’s no surprise why: plastic production increased from <a href="https://www.nationalgeographic.com/environment/article/plastic-pollution">2.3 million tons in 1950 to 448 million tons in 2015</a> and is expected to double to 896 million by 2050. Now, about 8 million tons of plastic waste winds up in the ocean each year.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>George Leonard, <a href="https://www.nationalgeographic.com/science/article/plastic-pollution-huge-problem-not-too-late-to-fix-it">chief scientist at the Ocean Conservancy</a>, says, “If we don’t get the plastic pollution problem in the ocean under control, we threaten contaminating the entire marine food web, from phytoplankton to whales. And by the time the science catches up to this, perhaps definitively concluding that this is problematic, it will be too late. We will not be able to go back. That massive amount of plastic will be embedded in the ocean’s wildlife essentially forever.”</p>
  <p>Clearly, the time for action is now. “We must rethink, innovate, and implement at an unprecedented pace and scale to enable a thriving future for environment, economy, and society,” says Thomas Saueressig, member of Executive Board of SAP SE, Product Engineering.</p>
  <p>It can be easy to feel overwhelmed by the enormity of the waste crisis facing the planet. Through education, the leaders of today can be empowered to change how we consume, how we operate, and how we do business.</p>
  <p>That thriving future will not be built on the current disposable culture but instead by embracing the <a href="https://ellenmacarthurfoundation.org/topics/circular-economy-introduction/overview">circular economy</a> model, one in which waste is eliminated, resources are recirculated, and nature is regenerated.</p>
  <p>As a leader in business software — including product design and manufacturing, supply chain and logistics, and product lifecycle management — SAP has both the technology and the responsibility to help global enterprises to develop circular systems. Indeed, the company has already started this vital work by providing the tools to companies that are interested in the circular economy through <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/purpose-and-sustainability/economy.html">sustainability solutions</a>.</p>
  <p>With these business models already in place, a new openSAP course, <a href="https://open.sap.com/courses/ce1">Helping Business Thrive in a Circular Economy</a>, offers anyone — SAP customer or not — a better understanding of how to apply these principles to their own business.</p>
  <p>Specifically, three key principles are defined by the Ellen MacArthur Foundation, an NGO dedicated to accelerating the adoption of this sustainable model:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Keep products and materials in use as long as possible</li>
    <li>Design out waste and pollution</li>
    <li>Regenerate natural systems</li>
  </ul>
  <p>With these three directives as a guide, the free on-demand course features pioneering experts in the circular economy, such as <a href="https://ellenmacarthurfoundation.org/our-story/the-team/ceo-trustees/andrew-morlet">Andrew Morlet</a>, CEO of the Ellen MacArthur Foundation, and <a href="http://business-school.exeter.ac.uk/about/people/profile/index.php?web_id=Peter_Hopkinson">Peter Hopkinson</a>, professor of Circular Economy and co-director of the Exeter Center for the Circular Economy. It also features environmental activists and sustainable product luminaries, including <a href="https://www.emilypenn.com/">Emily Penn</a>, an ocean advocate and co-founder of eXXpedition, a trip that took 300 remarkable women on a circumnavigation of the globe to study the problem of plastics in the ocean. <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/stephaniebenedetto/">Stephanie Benedetto</a>, CEO and co-founder of Queen of Raw, a marketplace for sustainable textiles, is a featured lecturer.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="chasing-zero-the-future-can-be-greener-cleaner-and-more-equal">Chasing Zero: The future can be greener, cleaner, and more equal</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/purpose-and-sustainability.html#chasing-zero">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="https://open.sap.com/courses/ce1">Helping Business Thrive in a Circular Economy</a> is more than just a course. It tackles some of the most important issues of the day and is intended to change the global trajectory on waste by bringing businesses into the process. According to Saueressig, “Now more than ever, to achieve circularity, we must connect linear fragmented supply chains into unified, collaborative, and intelligent business networks that enable the reuse of materials.”</p>
  <p>At SAP, we believe that technology is an important enabler to driving a circular and regenerative economy. It’s not the whole answer, but a key part of the solution. We need organizations to come together to tackle this, so SAP has launched the course to help spread the word and evangelize on why we must move to a world of zero waste — and move now.</p>
  <p>The course begins October 4, 2021, and is free and open to anyone who wants to make a difference to the future of the planet.Content is available on demand. <a href="https://open.sap.com/courses/ce1">Sign up here</a>, and share it with your networks.</p>
  <p>Participating in just a few hours of coursework each week provides a cutting-edge education in how to bring the principles of a circular economy to businesses operating today. In five weeks, participants can gain a new understanding of this pivotal concept for their edification and to share with friends and colleagues, and see how to apply this to their own organizations.</p>
  <p>In addition, it’s a valuable opportunity for team building. There are many options for collaboration within the course, including a discussion forum as well as optional peer-graded teamwork activities to gain extra credits. Those who complete all coursework will be eligible for a Record of Achievement certificate.</p>
  <p>Importantly, participants will also be engaging with a vital concept that is already helping to build a sustainable future through partnerships between SAP and their clients. This course could be the first step on the journey to a better future for all.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Darren West is business development director for Circular Economy at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/chasing-zero</category>
            <category>news-tag/circular-economy</category>
            <category>news-tag/economics</category>
            <category>news-tag/opensap</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Getting Ahead of the Skills Curve]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/getting-ahead-skills-curve</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/getting-ahead-skills-curve</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Businesses can get ahead of the skills curve by aligning strategic workforce planning and business strategy. Read to learn more!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1be3fe31204da0bc2c881ee5a27f5a8d1f0bd6231.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1be3fe31204da0bc2c881ee5a27f5a8d1f0bd6231.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1be3fe31204da0bc2c881ee5a27f5a8d1f0bd6231.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Getting Ahead of the Skills Curve" src="./media_1be3fe31204da0bc2c881ee5a27f5a8d1f0bd6231.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="getting-ahead-of-the-skills-curve">Getting Ahead of the Skills Curve</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>What’s the uber skill? The ability to constantly learn, evolve, update, or even un-learn relevant skills. Today, training workforces to acquire that mindset of continuous learning is everything. We spoke with Stefan Haenisch, senior vice president of SAP Learning Strategic Initiatives at SAP, to dive deeper into his perspective, especially as he comes out of the World Economic Forum’s summer event, <a href="https://www.weforum.org/events/the-jobs-reset-summit-2021">The Jobs Reset Summit</a>, and recently published an <a href="https://www.weforum.org/agenda/2021/05/back-to-school-4-lessons-in-workforce-skilling/">article</a> for WEF about the critical lessons in workforce skilling and lifelong learning.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-the-skills-you-need-anytime-anywhere-with-sap-learning-hub">Learn the skills you need anytime, anywhere with SAP Learning Hub</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://learninghub.sap.com/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="q-in-your-article-for-the-world-economic-forum-you-discuss-the-importance-of-connecting-business-strategy-to-workforce-skills-can-you-share-what-this-looks-like-and-why-its-so-essential">Q: In your article for the World Economic Forum, you discuss the importance of connecting business strategy to workforce skills. Can you share what this looks like and why it’s so essential?</h3>
  <p><strong>A:</strong> Every company plots out its business strategy. But how often does it think about how this relates and aligns with its people strategy and strategic workforce planning and skill building?</p>
  <p>For example, if our strategy is to use <a href="https://insights.sap.com/what-is-artificial-intelligence/">artificial intelligence (AI)</a> to make our products smarter, we must simultaneously be asking ourselves how we can <a href="https://insights.sap.com/importance-upskilling/">upskill the workforce</a> on the required skills to drive this vision.</p>
  <p>Skill training shouldn’t be an afterthought. Instead, by connecting skills and strategy from the very beginning, companies can proactively adapt and more effectively position themselves for long-term success.</p>
  <h3 id="how-does-an-organization-develop-skills-for-the-future-when-things-are-changing-so-frequently-and-we-cant-possibly-know-what-the-world-will-look-like-in-the-next-couple-of-years">How does an organization develop skills for the future when things are changing so frequently and we can’t possibly know what the world will look like in the next couple of years?</h3>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="how-to-upskill-staff-from-strategy-to-practical-steps">How to Upskill Staff: From Strategy to Practical Steps</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://insights.sap.com/how-to-upskill-guide/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As we saw with <a href="http://news.sap.com/covid-19">the global pandemic</a>, things may go differently than predicted. Companies must embrace ambiguity and disruption when it comes to skills for the future. A recent article in the <a href="https://hbr.org/2020/01/the-transformer-clo">Harvard Business Review</a> noted, “If you focus on building individual micro skills, you may be missing the bigger picture.” Indeed, there are ‘expiration dates’ on technical skills as innovation emerges, so companies must establish a culture that encourages agility and experimentation in the workforce – and, not least, motivates continuous learning – in order to yield sustainable success. Soft skills like dealing with uncertainty, staying curious, as well as embracing and tolerating ambiguity are the foundation of employees being ready for the future. They can then quickly and continuously keep up the relevant hard skills.</p>
  <p><a href="https://www2.deloitte.com/content/dam/Deloitte/global/Documents/HumanCapital/gx-the-future-of-work-post-covid-19-poc.pdf">A recent report from Deloitte</a> asserts that the <a href="https://insights.sap.com/what-is-future-of-work/">future of work</a> in our technology-driven world is about “creating an environment where organizations can optimize human potential” and “empowering workers with agency and choice over what they do, unleashing their interests and passions.” What this means is that the ultimate skill is being able to continuously learn in a constantly changing business environment. Fostering agile, innovative mindsets and curiosity throughout the workforce – promoting not only the <em>need</em> to learn, but the <em>want</em> to learn – helps companies to think big and earn a competitive edge.</p>
  <h3 id="how-do-offerings-at-sap-help-support-strategic-workforce-planning-and-continuous-learning">How do offerings at SAP help support strategic workforce planning and continuous learning?</h3>
  <p>At SAP, we value ongoing learning as part of the foundation for success. In the fast-moving tech sector where skill demand changes faster than in other industries, we’re constantly evolving our learning offerings to support the hard and soft skills needed to help people stay competitive.</p>
  <p>Inside SAP, for example, we look at a long and successful track record in deploying skills management to effective resource management in our consulting business and are now evolving this to support dynamic and forward-looking workforce planning and development.</p>
  <p>Our customers can benefit from our experience as we are incorporating the best practices we learned in people and skills management into our SAP SuccessFactors solutions. When it comes to helping our customers and partners build and sustain SAP product skills, our digital learning offerings, <a href="https://open.sap.com/">openSAP</a> and <a href="https://learninghub.sap.com/">SAP Learning Hub</a>, work to provide easy-to-use, engaging content for learners to explore, build, and maintain relevant skills. Additionally, we help support career planning around the skills that learners are honing, working to provide the right learning journey targeted to each learner’s goals.</p>
  <p>Our mission is to create learning and development opportunity for all across the SAP ecosystem. We aim to empower everyone to successfully build SAP software skills using future-oriented content delivered in different formats to fit individual ways of learning. By better aligning strategic workforce planning and business strategy at the onset, as well as becoming laser-focused on a workplace culture that values agility and curiosity, businesses can get ahead of the skills curve.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning-for-life</category>
            <category>news-tag/opensap</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-certification</category>
            <category>product/sap-learning-hub</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-training-and-adoption</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Process Improvement Means More Than Developing Apps at Sun Chemical]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/sun-chemical-process-improvement-apps</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/sun-chemical-process-improvement-apps</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Sun Chemical has brought 200+ SAP Fiori apps to life to support employees in their daily work. Learn about the UX transformation journey.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14c405e6c2cc1b477aab89285c9b5f33d1f24ad6b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14c405e6c2cc1b477aab89285c9b5f33d1f24ad6b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_14c405e6c2cc1b477aab89285c9b5f33d1f24ad6b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Process Improvement Means More Than Developing Apps at Sun Chemical" src="./media_14c405e6c2cc1b477aab89285c9b5f33d1f24ad6b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="process-improvement-means-more-than-developing-apps-at-sun-chemical">Process Improvement Means More Than Developing Apps at Sun Chemical</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>In 2016, the IT team behind Sun Chemical embarked on a journey to learn more about design thinking via <a href="https://open.sap.com/courses/dt1">a free openSAP course</a>. Since then, the team has been systematically improving the operational effectiveness and efficiency of business processes through design-led workshops, bringing over 200 SAP Fiori apps to life to support their daily work.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Sasi Reddy, senior SAP solution architect at Sun Chemical, shares the team’s user experience (UX) transformation journey, the biggest takeaways, and what it takes to be a UX champion.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="enroll-in-an-opensap-course-today">Enroll in an openSAP course today</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://open.sap.com/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="from-theory-to-action-with-an-opensap-course-on-design-thinking">From Theory to Action with an openSAP Course on Design Thinking</h2>
  <p>Sun Chemical is a recognized leader in printing inks, coatings, pigments, and supplies for the packaging, publication, commercial, industrial, and digital markets. With over 20,000 employees spread across 63 locations around the world, Sun Chemical relies on lean business processes to ensure its field service workers and customers can quickly and easily maintain field data and enter new requests on the go, both on- and offline.</p>
  <p>To further enhance their knowledge of design thinking and to learn how this methodology could be applied to both process improvements and application development, Reddy and his team took part in the openSAP course <a href="https://open.sap.com/courses/dt1">Developing Software Using Design Thinking</a> in 2017. The core of the methodology is developing empathy for users by putting oneself in their shoes. Design thinking also relies on prototyping and a strong iterative process rather than on intuition, something which Sun Chemical has embraced fully. Since completing the course, the team has worked with a few SAP partners, and later independently, to offer design thinking services to the entire company, with 15 major design-led projects to date.</p>
  <h2 id="sap-fiori-apps-support-lean-business-processes">SAP Fiori Apps Support Lean Business Processes</h2>
  <p>Over the past five years, Sun Chemical has groomed an elite team of UX champions that leverage design thinking to accelerate and digitize its processes. A key factor in the team’s success has been to build tailored SAP Fiori apps that support an agile development approach. This method scales and requires a minimal investment. It allows the team to build apps for a system that runs on SAP ERP, which plans to migrate to SAP S/4HANA later.</p>
  <p>If you ask Reddy which of the more than 200 existing apps he’s most proud of, there are many that come to mind, such as the Regulatory Inquiry App and the Raw Material Request App, both of which emerged from a prototype developed during the 2016 openSAP course and have since been rolled out globally.</p>
  <p>One example that captures the business impact of the UX transformation is the Field Service App.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17a816f25551901298d51f51c04309feac6f1e7a9.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17a816f25551901298d51f51c04309feac6f1e7a9.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_17a816f25551901298d51f51c04309feac6f1e7a9.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Sun Chemical product screenshot" src="./media_17a816f25551901298d51f51c04309feac6f1e7a9.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="360" height="200">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p>Remote field service application on desktop device.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_101663f3bed90c2d6897740ae72640aec44732cf7.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_101663f3bed90c2d6897740ae72640aec44732cf7.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_101663f3bed90c2d6897740ae72640aec44732cf7.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Sun Chemical product sceenshot" src="./media_101663f3bed90c2d6897740ae72640aec44732cf7.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="360" height="200">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p>Remote field service application: Signature pad on iOS device.</p>
  <h2 id="from-workshop-to-real-life-the-field-service-app">From Workshop to Real Life: The Field Service App</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-fiori-the-enterprise-user-experience-reimagined">SAP Fiori: The enterprise user experience, reimagined</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/fiori.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>A remote design thinking workshop was kicked off in 2018 to determine how to better manage the day-to-day activities for European field service engineers who relied on using a mix of e-mails and spreadsheets to maintain their work order history and incoming requests. The workshop included the field engineers, their supervisors, the administrator who orchestrated the work orders, and developers from India. From the workshop emerged the idea to develop an application that contains all the information in one place.</p>
  <p>The app, which was developed in a few short weeks, makes it easy to track what service has previously been done for a specific customer and supports detailed reports on previous work orders. Naturally, it allows field service workers to easily enter new orders and incorporates a digital signature on native iOS mobile devices, something which the workshop participants were “really surprised that we could deliver on so quickly,” says Reddy. Since the rollout in Europe, the app has been immediately accepted by its users and has made its way to North and South American field service workers as well.</p>
  <h2 id="its-about-the-mindset-not-just-the-apps">It’s About the Mindset, Not Just the Apps</h2>
  <p>There is no doubt that the design thinking method requires a significant time investment from those involved. From the initial workshop, where research, user empathy, and ideation take place, to the design process that relies on numerous iteration cycles with end users, you have to put in the work to ensure the end result solves the problem at hand and meets users’ expectations.</p>
  <p>Reddy agrees that the effort is time consuming. He and his UX champion colleagues spend a lot of time taking part in collaboration calls with teams who are currently <a href="https://blogs.sap.com/2021/03/31/sap-fiori-for-sap-s-4hana-recommendations-for-transitioning-users-from-sap-gui-to-sap-fiori/">switching from SAP GUI to SAP Fiori</a>. They receive feedback on the applications on a daily basis to ensure the transition to the new user experience goes smoothly.</p>
  <p>But Reddy has also seen the fruits of his team’s labor: “People are seeing the value of it. Our departments have seen our work. It’s been almost four years. Previously, we drove design thinking; now people request it from us. And not necessarily to build apps, though everyone’s now on board with SAP Fiori, but to improve processes in general. The mindset has really changed in our company.”</p>
  <p>To learn more about the SAP Fiori user experience, visit the <a href="https://url.sap/cdpj3b">SAP Fiori topic page on the SAP Community</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Andrea Waisgluss is a content strategist for SAP Design.</em><br><em><a href="https://blogs.sap.com/2021/04/20/process-improvement-means-more-than-developing-apps-sun-chemical-shares-why/">This article originally appeared in the SAP Community</a></em>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/opensap</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fiori</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Transforming Learning for a Digitally Native Future]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/03/digitally-native-future-transform-learning</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/03/digitally-native-future-transform-learning</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[To support readiness for a digitally native future, SAP is simplifying access to learning for all. Learn how the company is staying dynamic.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning-for-life</category>
            <category>news-tag/moocs</category>
            <category>news-tag/opensap</category>
            <category>product/sap-learning-hub</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-training-and-adoption</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[openSAP Celebrates 5 Million Course Enrollments, Continues to Provide Learners with Innovative Learning Resources]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/03/5-million-opensap-enrollments-innovative-learning</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/03/5-million-opensap-enrollments-innovative-learning</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Mar 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is celebrating 5 million openSAP enrollments, helping ensure that the entire ecosystem has the right skills to thrive in a digital world.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e3f34c5bd39a32b2cff91dc65c9bfe018ae5b588.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e3f34c5bd39a32b2cff91dc65c9bfe018ae5b588.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1e3f34c5bd39a32b2cff91dc65c9bfe018ae5b588.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="openSAP Celebrates 5 Million Course Enrollments, Continues to Provide Learners with Innovative Learning Resources" src="./media_1e3f34c5bd39a32b2cff91dc65c9bfe018ae5b588.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="opensap-celebrates-5-million-course-enrollments-continues-to-provide-learners-with-innovative-learning-resources">openSAP Celebrates 5 Million Course Enrollments, Continues to Provide Learners with Innovative Learning Resources</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="explore-the-opensap-course-catalog">Explore the openSAP course catalog</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://open.sap.com/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced a milestone of five million course enrollments on its openSAP platform – a free online platform that offers innovative, expert-led massive open online courses (MOOCs) with accompanying microlearning and podcasts across a range of topics for learners of all abilities.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>openSAP was established in 2013 to provide individuals with essential knowledge and the opportunity to acquire the skills necessary to navigate the SAP software landscape, all with the flexibility to learn from anywhere at any time. Leveraging tried and trusted learning concepts, the online platform integrates features such as gamification and discussion forums to allow learners to interact with experts and peers in a way that is impactful and enjoyable. Hosted and run by the Hasso Plattner Institute (HPI), SAP can look back on many years of close collaboration and successful codevelopment with the institute led by Director and CEO Prof. Dr. Christoph Meinel.</p>
  <p>“In today’s digitally-driven age, it’s important to create a learning environment that is accessible for all,” said Professor Hasso Plattner, Chairman of the Supervisory Board of SAP SE. “With the <a href="/covid-19">COVID-19</a> pandemic upending all facets of life and forcing many to move to a remote working and learning environment, it has become more important than ever to lower the barriers to essential knowledge to provide learners with the right tools and resources to continue to achieve and further their skills. It is tremendous to see what we have achieved so far with openSAP, and we are excited to continue to be part of our customers’ learning journeys as we work to meet their evolving needs.”</p>
  <p>The online learning platform has recently seen accelerated growth, with the number of course enrollments doubling over the last three years. Enrollments in approximately 250 different courses average out to 20,000 enrollments per course, totaling 1.2 million learners across the board. While the platform continues to provide new courses on the latest topics and innovations, such as SAP S/4HANA, SAP Business Technology Platform, intelligent integration, digital transformation and machine learning, older courses are still relevant and consistently attract new enrollments.</p>
  <p>“With the tremendous need for reskilling through our current period of digital transformation, SAP continues to invest in lowering learning barriers through free offerings like openSAP,” said Maxwell Wessel, EVP and Chief Learning Officer, SAP. “Our goal is to ensure that everyone in our ecosystem – customers, partners, developers and employees – all have the right skills to thrive in a digital world and are equipped with the knowledge they need to prepare for the future.”</p>
  <p>The award-winning platform has garnered great recognition and learner satisfaction over the years:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Ninety-eight percent are very satisfied with the learning experience openSAP provides.</li>
    <li>Ninety-five percent say that the skills taught will help them in their future work.</li>
    <li>Ninety-nine percent plan to take additional courses on the openSAP platform in the future.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>To celebrate this achievement, SAP is offering its course <a href="https://open.sap.com/">SAP’s Integrated Intelligent Suite</a> on the openSAP platform for an additional five months (until the end of July) to provide more learners with the opportunity to acquire essential knowledge and earn a record of achievement.</p>
  <p>Today, SAP’s learning portfolio consists of various offerings to support continuous learning, performance and validation for everyone within the SAP ecosystem. As the learning environment continues to evolve, the portfolio will be enhanced and expanded by additional freely accessible offerings to meet learners’ changing needs.</p>
  <p>To start learning with openSAP, visit <a href="https://open.sap.com/">open.sap.com</a>.</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP on Twitter at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>About SAP</strong></p>
  <p>SAP’s strategy is to help every business run as an intelligent enterprise. As a market leader in enterprise application software, we help companies of all sizes and in all industries run at their best: 77% of the world’s transaction revenue touches an SAP system. Our machine learning, Internet of Things (IoT), and advanced analytics technologies help turn customers’ businesses into intelligent enterprises. SAP helps give people and organizations deep business insight and fosters collaboration that helps them stay ahead of their competition. We simplify technology for companies so they can consume our software the way they want – without disruption. Our end-to-end suite of applications and services enables business and public customers across 25 industries globally to operate profitably, adapt continuously, and make a difference. With a global network of customers, partners, employees, and thought leaders, SAP helps the world run better and improve people’s lives. For more information, visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/">www.sap.com</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Note to editors:</strong><br>To preview and download broadcast-standard stock footage and press photos digitally, please visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/photos">www.sap.com/photos</a>. On this platform, you can find high resolution material for your media channels. To view video stories on diverse topics, visit <a href="http://www.sap-tv.com">www.sap-tv.com</a>. From this site, you can embed videos into your own Web pages, share video via email links, and subscribe to RSS feeds from SAP TV.</p>
  <p><strong>For customers interested in learning more about SAP products:</strong><br>Global Customer Center: +49 180 534-34-24<br>United States only: 1 (800) 872-1SAP (1-800-872-1727)</p>
  <p><strong>For more information, press only:</strong><br>Martin Gwisdalla, SAP, +49 (6227) 7-67275, <a href="mailto:martin.gwisdalla@sap.com">martin.gwisdalla@sap.com</a>, CET<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>Any statements contained in this document that are not historical facts are forward-looking statements as defined in the U.S. Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995. Words such as “anticipate,” “believe,” “estimate,” “expect,” “forecast,” “intend,” “may,” “plan,” “project,” “predict,” “should” and “will” and similar expressions as they relate to SAP are intended to identify such forward-looking statements. SAP undertakes no obligation to publicly update or revise any forward-looking statements. All forward-looking statements are subject to various risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results to differ materially from expectations. The factors that could affect SAP’s future financial results are discussed more fully in SAP’s filings with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (“SEC”), including SAP’s most recent Annual Report on Form 20-F filed with the SEC. Readers are cautioned not to place undue reliance on these forward-looking statements, which speak only as of their dates.<br>© 2021 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.<br>Please consider our <a href="https://www.sap.com/corporate/en/legal/privacy.html">privacy policy</a>. If you received this press release in your e-mail and you wish to unsubscribe to our mailing list please contact <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a> and write Unsubscribe in the subject line.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/moocs</category>
            <category>news-tag/opensap</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-training-and-adoption</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>