<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/sap-successfactors/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Roca Group Looks to the Future Through RISE with SAP]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/roca-group-looks-to-future-rise-with-sap</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/roca-group-looks-to-future-rise-with-sap</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn how Roca is leveraging the last SAP technology and innovations, including RISE with SAP, to boost its digital transformation.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16c0e3912183718e90a860d4272af02f88676684b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16c0e3912183718e90a860d4272af02f88676684b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_16c0e3912183718e90a860d4272af02f88676684b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Roca Group Looks to the Future Through RISE with SAP" src="./media_16c0e3912183718e90a860d4272af02f88676684b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="roca-group-looks-to-the-future-through-rise-with-sap">Roca Group Looks to the Future Through RISE with SAP</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>BARCELONA</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced that Roca Group, one of the world’s leading bathroom fixtures and design companies has selected SAP S/4HANA and the RISE with SAP solution as it embarks on its next phase of digital transformation, focused on integrating and standardizing its IT systems.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-sapphire-taking-business-to-the-next-level-in-the-era-of-ai">SAP Sapphire: Taking Business to the Next Level in the Era of AI</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/events/sapphire/news-guide.html">Read the news guide</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>A family-owned business with over 100 years of heritage, a presence in 170 markets, and more than 21,500 employees and nearly 80 factories globally, Roca Group had embraced digitalization to remain competitive and relevant in the dynamic sanitary industry. Having made several acquisitions over the years, Roca Group saw RISE with SAP as the ideal solution to consolidate various IT systems into one IT landscape. Roca’s decision in choosing SAP S/4HANA Cloud was driven by the desire to increase efficiency and the ability to make informed, real-time, data-driven business decisions.</p>
  <p>“Roca Group’s strategy is based on a long-term future vision supported by innovation, technology and sustainability,” said Albert Magrans, CEO of Roca Group. “Moving to SAP S/4HANA enables Roca to leverage the last technology and innovations of SAP software to boost our digital transformation. We are looking forward to faster execution speed, the enhancement of functionality with the Joule copilot, real-time analytics and further innovations from SAP and its ecosystem.”</p>
  <p>“Roca Group and SAP have collaborated closely for a number of years, with Roca trusting SAP with multiple SAP implementations,” said Manos Raptopoulos, VP of SAP Europe, Middle East and Africa. “Roca’s IT strategy is fully aligned with its business transformation with SAP solutions as an integral part of this strategy. Our close partnership allows our teams to have real-time insight into their business transformation, allowing for seamless integration of SAP solutions as they embark on their SAP S/4HANA Cloud journey.”</p>
  <p>In choosing SAP S/4HANA Cloud and various cloud solutions from SAP, such as SAP Customer Experience, SAP Ariba and SAP SuccessFactors solutions, Roca Group continues to be well-positioned to leverage SAP’s integrated suite of solutions that will enhance customer experience and potentially open up new business opportunities. In adopting a clean core approach, the group will have a single platform for its production centers and logistics platforms, tapping onto the SAP Integrated Business Planning for Supply Chain solution for demand and production planning, and the SAP Transportation Management application for transport management. With these solutions implemented, the operations already using them have seen a cubic capacity of their transports rise by 10%.</p>
  <p>Additionally, Roca plans to use SAP SuccessFactors to improve learning programs, manage global payroll and enhance the employee self-service portal through SAP’s suite of solutions in addition to travel expense management with SAP Concur solutions.</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="http://news.sap.com/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-news-and-coverage-from-sap-sapphire-in-2024">Get the latest news and coverage from SAP Sapphire in 2024</h3>
        <p><em><a href="/topics/sap-sapphire">Read more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><strong>Media Contacts:</strong><br>Belén Martinez, +34 914 567 220, <a href="mailto:belen.martinez@sap.com">belen.martinez@sap.com</a>, CET<br>Lesa Plingen, +49 6227 76 9000, <a href="mailto:lesa.plingen@sap.com">lesa.plingen@sap.com</a>, CET<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>This document contains forward-looking statements, which are predictions, projections, or other statements about future events. These statements are based on current expectations, forecasts, and assumptions that are subject to risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results and outcomes to materially differ. Additional information regarding these risks and uncertainties may be found in our filings with the Securities and Exchange Commission, including but not limited to the risk factors section of SAP’s 2023 Annual Report on Form 20-F.<br>© 2024 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP SuccessFactors Accelerates AI Capabilities in HR to Make Every Employee a Success Story]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-successfactors-accelerates-ai-capabilities</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-successfactors-accelerates-ai-capabilities</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Announced at SAP Sapphire Orlando, SAP SuccessFactors streamlines HR operations with AI-enabled capabilities for a new way of working.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors-hcm-suite</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Expands Business AI Portfolio with Meta Open-Source Models]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-business-ai-meta-open-source-models</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-business-ai-meta-open-source-models</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is integrating Meta Llama 2 and Meta Llama 3 models into generative AI hub to enable customers to create dashboards based on rich content.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Infuses Business AI Throughout Its Enterprise Cloud Portfolio and Partners with Cutting-Edge AI Leaders to Bring Out Customers’ Best]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-sapphire-news-business-ai-enterprise-cloud-portfolio-cutting-edge-partnerships</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-sapphire-news-business-ai-enterprise-cloud-portfolio-cutting-edge-partnerships</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New SAP Business AI innovations and collaborations with partners are igniting ingenuity. Read the news from SAP Sapphire Orlando in 2024.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18ff27978e1178b1dce994986e74f4cc1f6087f26.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18ff27978e1178b1dce994986e74f4cc1f6087f26.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_18ff27978e1178b1dce994986e74f4cc1f6087f26.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Infuses Business AI Throughout Its Enterprise Cloud Portfolio and Partners with Cutting-Edge AI Leaders to Bring Out Customers’ Best" src="./media_18ff27978e1178b1dce994986e74f4cc1f6087f26.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-infuses-business-ai-throughout-its-enterprise-cloud-portfolio-and-partners-with-cutting-edge-ai-leaders-to-bring-out-customers-best">SAP Infuses Business AI Throughout Its Enterprise Cloud Portfolio and Partners with Cutting-Edge AI Leaders to Bring Out Customers’ Best</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>SAP Business AI Innovations and Collaborations with Partners including Google Cloud, Meta, Microsoft, Mistral AI and NVIDIA Ignite Ingenuity</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <table>
          <thead>
            <tr>
              <th>Text Large</th>
            </tr>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td><strong><em>ORLANDO</em></strong> — At its annual SAP Sapphire conference, SAP unveiled generative AI innovations and partnerships that showcase how the company is taking business to the next level in the era of AI.</td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="taking-business-to-the-next-level-in-the-era-of-ai">Taking Business to the Next Level in the Era of AI</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/events/sapphire/news-guide.html">Read the news guide</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>By infusing Business AI across an enterprise cloud portfolio that powers the world’s most mission-critical processes and partnering with companies pushing the edge of what’s possible with AI, SAP is igniting a new wave of insight and ingenuity in global business.</p>
  <p>“The Business AI innovations we’re announcing at SAP Sapphire in 2024 will redefine the way businesses run,” says Christian Klein, CEO and member of the Executive Board of SAP SE. “Today’s AI announcements and partnerships build on our commitment to deliver revolutionary technology that drives real-world results, helping customers unleash the agility and ingenuity they need to succeed in today’s fast-moving business landscape.”</p>
  <h2 id="ai-that-means-business">AI That Means Business</h2>
  <p>As SAP embeds Business AI across its enterprise solutions, it puts rich insights at users’ fingertips, empowering them to deliver better outcomes and elevate the creative problem-solving humans do best. Examples include AI-generated reports in SAP SuccessFactors solutions that give people managers responsibly sourced insights for compensation-related discussions as well as forecasting capabilities in SAP Sales Cloud solutions that predict combinations of salespeople and products most likely to drive sales. Meanwhile, the SAP Business Technology Platform is adding large language models from Amazon Web Services, Meta and Mistral AI to its generative AI hub. This capability in the SAP AI Core infrastructure makes it easier to build generative AI use cases for SAP applications.</p>
  <p>SAP’s generative AI copilot Joule, which quickly sorts and contextualizes data from multiple systems to advance automation and improve decision-making, is expanding throughout the company’s solution portfolio. Joule launched in <a href="/2023/09/joule-new-generative-ai-assistant">SAP SuccessFactors solutions last fall</a> and is now embedded into SAP S/4HANA Cloud solutions and others including SAP Build and SAP Integration Suite. Further expansion by year-end will include SAP Ariba and SAP Analytics Cloud solutions. At Sapphire, SAP also announced <a href="/">plans to further broaden Joule’s scope</a> by integrating it with Microsoft Copilot to surface even richer insights. This deep, bi-directional integration gives users a unified experience built right into the flow of work, enabling seamless access to information from interactions with business applications in SAP and Microsoft 365.</p>
  <p>Reflecting Business AI’s increasing importance, SAP is redoubling its commitment to the principles of relevant, reliable, and responsible AI it pioneered. At Sapphire, SAP is adopting the 10 guiding principles of the UNESCO Recommendation on the Ethics of Artificial Intelligence, which aim to ensure that AI technologies are developed and used in ways that respect human rights, promote fairness and contribute to sustainable development.</p>
  <h2 id="partnerships-that-scale-innovation">Partnerships That Scale Innovation</h2>
  <p>SAP is partnering with best-in-class technology leaders to push the limits of what generative AI can do at an enterprise level. In addition to our expanded collaborations with <a href="/2024/05/aws-sap-generative-ai-new-innovation">AWS</a> and Microsoft, partnerships with Google Cloud, Meta, Mistral AI and NVIDIA ensure SAP can harness the power of AI-ready technology to innovate at speed and deliver richer real-world results.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Google Cloud</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP and Google Cloud are expanding their partnership, using Business AI to help enterprises better predict and mitigate supply-chain risks to minimize disruptions and maintain optimal inventory levels. The companies will integrate Joule and the SAP Integrated Business Planning for Supply Chain solution with Google Cloud’s Gemini models AI assistant and Google Cloud Cortex Framework’s data foundation.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Meta</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP will leverage Meta Llama 3 to generate scripts that render highly customized analytics applications in SAP Analytics Cloud. Meta’s next-generation AI model excels at language nuances and contextual understanding, making it an ideal candidate for translating enterprise business requirements into tangible outcomes.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Mistral AI</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP will also add <a href="/">new large language models from Mistral AI</a>, a global company headquartered in Paris specializing in generative AI, to the generative AI hub capability in SAP AI Core.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>NVIDIA</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP and NVIDIA Corporation advance a <a href="https://blogs.nvidia.com/blog/sap-sapphire-ai-omniverse/">cross-product partnership</a> to embed cutting-edge technologies into enterprise-ready business applications:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>As SAP trains Joule to serve as an AI assistant for the RISE with SAP solution implementations, NVIDIA’s state-of-the-art AI models sift through SAP consulting assets to provide relevant and precise answers to implementation-related questions;</li>
    <li>As SAP embeds Joule in the ABAP Cloud model to generate ABAP code for SAP developers, NVIDIA’s accelerated infrastructure will run, scale, and manage SAP’s generative AI model for ABAP code generation;</li>
    <li>As SAP infuses generative AI into the SAP Intelligent Product Recommendation solution, NVIDIA Omniverse Cloud APIs enable the simulation of complex manufacturing products and configurations as industrial digital twins.</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="cloud-technology-that-drives-agility-and-sustainability">Cloud Technology That Drives Agility and Sustainability</h2>
  <p>Business success in the era of AI means being in the cloud. SAP is making the move easier than ever with initiatives that help customers find partners with the expertise needed for complex SAP S/4HANA Cloud transformations. Further cloud innovations at SAP Sapphire include features that help the world’s organizations measure, manage and execute their sustainability strategies. SAP Sustainability Control Tower and SAP Sustainability Footprint Management solutions now track carbon footprints at scale and help businesses meet regulatory standards.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><a href="https://www.sap.com/events/sapphire/news-guide.html">Learn more in the 2024 SAP Sapphire News Guide</a>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Visit the <a href="/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-news-and-coverage-from-sap-sapphire-in-2024">Get the latest news and coverage from SAP Sapphire in 2024</h3>
        <p><em><a href="/topics/sap-sapphire">Read more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>About SAP</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As a global leader in enterprise applications and business AI, SAP (NYSE:SAP) stands at the nexus of business and technology. For over 50 years, organizations have trusted SAP to bring out their best by uniting business-critical operations spanning finance, procurement, HR, supply chain, and customer experience. For more information, visit <a href="http://www.sap.com">www.sap.com</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Note to editors:</strong><br>To preview and download broadcast-standard stock footage and press photos digitally, please visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/photos">www.sap.com/photos</a>. On this platform, you can find high resolution material for your media channels.</p>
  <p><strong>For customers interested in learning more about SAP products:</strong><br>Global Customer Center: +49 180 534-34-24<br>United States Only: 1 (800) 872-1SAP (1-800-872-1727)</p>
  <p><strong>For more information, press only:</strong><br>Joellen Perry, +1 (650) 445-6780, <a href="mailto:joellen.perry@sap.com">joellen.perry@sap.com</a> PT<br>Marcus Winkler, +49 6227-767497, <a href="mailto:marcus.winkler@sap.com">marcus.winkler@sap.com</a> CET<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>This document contains forward-looking statements, which are predictions, projections, or other statements about future events. These statements are based on current expectations, forecasts, and assumptions that are subject to risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results and outcomes to materially differ. Additional information regarding these risks and uncertainties may be found in our filings with the Securities and Exchange Commission, including but not limited to the risk factors section of SAP’s 2023 Annual Report on Form 20-F.<br>© 2024 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.<br>Please consider our <a href="https://www.sap.com/corporate/en/legal/privacy.html">privacy policy</a>. If you receive this press release in your e-mail and you wish to unsubscribe to our mailing list please contact <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a> and write Unsubscribe in the subject line.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/abap-cloud</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-sales-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-footprint-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP SuccessFactors Partners Recognized for Outstanding Achievements]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/sap-successfactors-partners-recognized-for-achievements</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/sap-successfactors-partners-recognized-for-achievements</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP SuccessFactors partners received SAP Global Line of Business Partner Excellence Awards for 2024. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>sap-award/sap-global-lob-partner-excellence-awards</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Kyndryl Adopts Next-Generation Tools for Sales Performance Management]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/kyndryl-adopts-tools-for-sales-performance-management</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/kyndryl-adopts-tools-for-sales-performance-management</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Kyndryl adopted SAP SuccessFactors sales performance management solutions to streamline compensation and territory and quota management.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/sales-performance-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[AI-Enabled Recruitment Is the Name of the Game for FC Bayern with SAP SuccessFactors]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/fc-bayern-sap-successfactors-ai-enabled-recruitment</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/fc-bayern-sap-successfactors-ai-enabled-recruitment</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[FC Bayern is leveraging the SAP SuccessFactors HCM suite and SAP Business AI capabilities to drive excellence on and off the pitch.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>industry/media: industry/sports-entertainment</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>industry/sports-entertainment</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Growing Your Business Begins with Growing Your People]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/growing-your-business-begins-with-growing-your-people</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/growing-your-business-begins-with-growing-your-people</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[An Oxford Economics study, sponsored by SAP, reveals how to optimizing talent management with best practices for HR and IT. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/sme</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors-hcm-suite</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-learning</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-opportunity-marketplace</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-performance-goals</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-recruiting</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP SuccessFactors Takes Home 12 Top Rated Awards from TrustRadius]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/sap-successfactors-12-top-rated-awards-from-trustradius</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/sap-successfactors-12-top-rated-awards-from-trustradius</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[TrustRadius has recognized SAP SuccessFactors with 12 Top Rated awards in 2024. Read to learn more about the recognition.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a157e78734853652179498700d8b366ba88f70cd.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a157e78734853652179498700d8b366ba88f70cd.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1a157e78734853652179498700d8b366ba88f70cd.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP SuccessFactors Takes Home 12 Top Rated Awards from TrustRadius" src="./media_1a157e78734853652179498700d8b366ba88f70cd.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-successfactors-takes-home-12-top-rated-awards-from-trustradius">SAP SuccessFactors Takes Home 12 Top Rated Awards from TrustRadius</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>SAP SuccessFactors has once again been recognized as a leader in human resources software by <a href="https://auth.trustradius.com/login?state=hKFo2SAxeFdmN3FRNFYweERQdWtYOUNrZlBpbXFSZE9QbXZRWqFupWxvZ2luo3RpZNkgVk5pZ3luZ0ZsZ1hGZVFvQjFzRVUwakNMZzlvOXRHTGmjY2lk2SAxQm41NHNobVlWMmpFbE5qZ1NZb2dKNHZWeHZBT3hhSw&#x26;client=1Bn54shmYV2jElNjgSYogJ4vVxvAOxaK&#x26;protocol=oauth2&#x26;prompt=login&#x26;scope=openid%20profile%20email&#x26;response_type=code&#x26;redirect_uri=https%3A%2F%2Ftrustradius.com%2Fapi%2Fauth%2Fcallback&#x26;login_hint=&#x26;customParams=%7B%22visitorId%22%3A%22662c047f7334ebca8f8661aa%22%2C%22visitId%22%3A%2266311414bf33ad1060cf30ff%22%2C%22returnTo%22%3A%22%2Freviews%2Fnew%22%7D&#x26;allow_signup=true&#x26;nonce=hYwbKE36k0mTMvPhuGwjobXr7VnrKjlPTnVy0Kbn5sQ&#x26;code_challenge_method=S256&#x26;code_challenge=0aAJd5l2mbjUn1d0SW7Qvrv5DkDvBp6W-0szabD3FVQ">TrustRadius</a>, earning 12 Top Rated awards in 2024. TrustRadius is a peer research and review platform designed to help business leaders find and select the right software to meet their needs.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“At TrustRadius, we pride ourselves on providing unbiased and transparent insights into the software industry,” said Allyson Havener, senior vice president of Marketing and Community at TrustRadius. “Receiving a TrustRadius Top Rated award is a testament to SAP SuccessFactors HCM’s exceptional performance as validated by unbiased user feedback. This recognition highlights SAP SuccessFactors’ commitment to delivering innovative human capital management solutions that truly meet the needs of businesses.”</p>
  <p>This year, <a href="/topics/human-resources">SAP SuccessFactors</a> earned awards across the following categories: Applicant Tracking, Compensation Management, Talent Management, Workforce Analytics, Sales Incentive Compensation Management, HR Management, Workforce Management, Employee Performance Management, Sales Performance Management, Corporate Learning Management, Succession Planning, and Internal Payroll.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="adopt-the-latest-in-hr-innovation-with-sap-successfactors-hcm">Adopt the latest in HR innovation with SAP SuccessFactors HCM</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>We are grateful to our more than 10,000 global customers whose partnership allows us to help make every employee a success story by harnessing the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/human-resources.html">power of AI</a> to elevate every experience, guide every people decision, and connect HR across every aspect of the business.</p>
  <p>In the past year, SAP has introduced new AI capabilities that span the entire SAP SuccessFactors HCM suite and help transform how organizations unlock individual and collective potential. <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/ai-joule-product-tour.html">Joule</a>, SAP’s natural language generative AI copilot, helps employees and managers work faster and smarter by making it easier to find information and complete common HR tasks. With an embedded AI-driven skills framework, SAP SuccessFactors solutions help power an organization’s learning and talent strategy and address critical skills gaps. The combined force of these innovations helps customers better meet the business challenges of today and tomorrow.</p>
  <p>Below are a few reviews from our customers:</p>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div>We chose SAP SuccessFactors over competitors for its comprehensive HR suite, superior integration capabilities with SAP systems, and global scalability. Its user-friendly interface and extensive analytics stood out, <strong>offering more in-depth insights and a seamless experience compared to other solutions in the market</strong>.</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div><a href="https://www.trustradius.com/reviews/sap-successfactors-2023-12-15-07-43-30">Solution Architect, Barclays</a></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div>“<strong>The benefit of [SAP] SuccessFactors is its flexibility</strong>. I have implemented [SAP] SuccessFactors at companies with as little as 1,500 employees and also with as many as 120,000 users. It can handle the complexities of global requirements while still being able to scale to a small, midsized business in a cost-effective manner.”​</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div><a href="https://www.trustradius.com/reviews/sap-successfactors-2023-10-16-10-44-42">HRIS Manager, Great Lakes Cheese</a></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div>“SAP SuccessFactors has a clean employee view of data and offers a wide range of functionality to <strong>support midsize to large companies</strong>.”​</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div><a href="https://www.trustradius.com/reviews/sap-successfactors-2023-10-21-10-48-58">Software Engineer, John Deere</a></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Learn more about <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm.html?url_id=ctabutton-us-hcm-trustradius-freetrial">SAP SuccessFactors HCM</a> and read our customer reviews on <a href="https://www.trustradius.com/products/sap-successfactors/reviews">TrustRadius</a>. For more information about these recognitions, visit the <a href="https://www.trustradius.com/static/about-trustradius-scoring">TrustRadius scoring FAQ page</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Aaron Green is chief marketing &#x26; solutions officer for SAP SuccessFactors.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors-hcm-suite</category>
            <category>news-tag/trustradius</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Modernizing Benefits Enrollment to Boost Employee Satisfaction and Retention]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/modernizing-benefits-enrollment-boost-employee-satisfaction-retention</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/modernizing-benefits-enrollment-boost-employee-satisfaction-retention</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central Global Benefits empowers employees to take control of their benefits with an intuitive, guided experience.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1330c66286be6108050da7ab27c52e68fc719102b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1330c66286be6108050da7ab27c52e68fc719102b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1330c66286be6108050da7ab27c52e68fc719102b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Modernizing Benefits Enrollment to Boost Employee Satisfaction and Retention" src="./media_1330c66286be6108050da7ab27c52e68fc719102b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="modernizing-benefits-enrollment-to-boost-employee-satisfaction-and-retention">Modernizing Benefits Enrollment to Boost Employee Satisfaction and Retention</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Employee satisfaction is driven by more than paychecks and perks – it’s also about everyday work experiences. One often-overlooked aspect that can significantly impact how employees feel about their workplace is the benefits enrollment experience.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>A confusing benefits enrollment experience is a significant source of frustration for many employees and can leave them feeling uncertain about their benefits elections. The majority of employees struggle to understand their benefits options and navigate through the enrollment process.</p>
  <p>As a result, many employees choose to simply roll over their previous year’s elections rather than review and update their choices to ensure they are getting the most out of their benefits. This often leads to missed opportunities to take advantage of lower-cost options or benefits that are a better fit for them and their family and can even lead to increased attrition of top talent.</p>
  <p>With <a href="/2024/04/sap-successfactors-first-half-2024-release">the first half 2024 release</a>, updates to the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/employee-central-hris/features.html#benefits?url_id=ctabutton-us-hcm-EC-freetrial">SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central Global Benefits</a> solution can enable you to empower your employees to take control of their benefits with an intuitive guided enrollment experience.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="extend-your-benefits-capabilities-with-sap-successfactors">Extend your benefits capabilities with SAP SuccessFactors</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/employee-central-hris/features.html#benefits">Learn how</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="making-benefits-enrollment-more-seamless-simple-and-intuitive">Making Benefits Enrollment More Seamless, Simple, and Intuitive</h2>
  <p>The new benefits enrollment experience in <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/employee-central-hris/features.html#benefits?url_id=ctabutton-us-hcm-EC-freetrial">SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central Global Benefits</a> introduces a process-driven approach to benefits enrollment that helps simplify and streamline the activity. Available for insurance, savings plans, and pension benefit types, this new enrollment experience can enable employees to make better, more informed benefits choices without the unnecessary hurdles.</p>
  <p>Here are some key highlights:</p>
  <h3 id="guided-enrollment">Guided Enrollment</h3>
  <p>A step-by-step progression flow guides employees through the process, working to simplify navigation and helping them complete benefits enrollment. Real-time benefits eligibility updates help employees continually understand the choices and options available by presenting them with all the benefits for which they are eligible to enroll.</p>
  <h3 id="personalized-user-experience">Personalized User Experience</h3>
  <p>Customizable text and instructions enable a tailored enrollment experience aligned with organizational policies.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c17ad14f21e83c7450704c1afdf399c3a412c660.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c17ad14f21e83c7450704c1afdf399c3a412c660.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1c17ad14f21e83c7450704c1afdf399c3a412c660.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Screenshot of benefits enrollment welcome page in SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central Global Benefits" src="./media_1c17ad14f21e83c7450704c1afdf399c3a412c660.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="580">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>Benefits enrollment welcome page. Click to enlarge.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="flexible-framework">Flexible Framework</h3>
  <p>Benefits admins can now have more flexibility in designing the enrollment experience to meet their organization’s needs with a new framework that helps support the capture of life insurance guaranteed issue amounts, customizable terms and conditions, and enhanced localization capabilities.</p>
  <h3 id="anytime-anywhere-access">Anytime, Anywhere Access</h3>
  <p>Available on both desktop and the SAP SuccessFactors Mobile app, employees can complete benefits enrollment from any location using a mobile-friendly platform that helps ensure a seamless experience across devices.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c77980d26be6e40ac83dd9b643d8a7c3585a72b5.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c77980d26be6e40ac83dd9b643d8a7c3585a72b5.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1c77980d26be6e40ac83dd9b643d8a7c3585a72b5.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Screenshots of benefits enrollment on mobile device and desktop" src="./media_1c77980d26be6e40ac83dd9b643d8a7c3585a72b5.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="452">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>Benefits enrollment on a mobile device or desktop. Click to enlarge.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="employee-educational-resources">Employee Educational Resources</h3>
  <p>Simplified on-screen access to additional resources and information helps employees better understand their benefits and can promote more informed decision-making throughout the enrollment process.</p>
  <p>Side-by-side benefit plan comparisons of costs and plan details help employees assess their plan options and select the best-fit plan. Localizable instructional text on each page helps ensure that the benefits and enrollment processes are well understood. Additionally, flexible options for defining contribution amounts within the IRS limits can make it easier for employees to make decisions regarding savings plans and pension elections.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a34b6a531c49ffa414de06cd26af9eae0983046c.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a34b6a531c49ffa414de06cd26af9eae0983046c.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1a34b6a531c49ffa414de06cd26af9eae0983046c.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Screenshot showing flexible options for defining HSA contribution amount" src="./media_1a34b6a531c49ffa414de06cd26af9eae0983046c.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="601">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>Flexible options for defining HSA contribution amount. Click to enlarge.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="consolidated-benefits-enrollment-process">Consolidated Benefits Enrollment Process</h3>
  <p>Employees can complete all benefits-related tasks including reviewing and updating dependents, completing health declarations, enrolling in benefits, managing beneficiaries, and more through a single consolidated process, helping to improve employee engagement and satisfaction.</p>
  <p><a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2024/03/72d228c0-b77e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html?url_id=ctabutton-us-hcm-benefits-demo">Watch the demo</a> to learn more about the new enrollment experience in SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central Global Benefits.</p>
  <p>To learn about all the other innovations in the SAP SuccessFactors first half 2024 release, read the <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2024/04/300e8c6d-b77e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">release highlights brochure</a> and watch the <a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2024/04/8c907f14-b77e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">1H 2024 release highlights video</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Nicole Ramirez is senior director of Product Marketing at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-employee-central</category>
            <category>news-tag/ux</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP SuccessFactors First Half 2024 Release: Make Every Employee a Success Story]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-successfactors-first-half-2024-release</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-successfactors-first-half-2024-release</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[To help take HR to the next level, the SAP SuccessFactors first half 2024 release delivers more than 250 features and enhancements.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_115cc4b7786cb688433caf45dec5bf248f041afdb.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_115cc4b7786cb688433caf45dec5bf248f041afdb.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_115cc4b7786cb688433caf45dec5bf248f041afdb.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP SuccessFactors First Half 2024 Release: Make Every Employee a Success Story" src="./media_115cc4b7786cb688433caf45dec5bf248f041afdb.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-successfactors-first-half-2024-release-make-every-employee-a-success-story">SAP SuccessFactors First Half 2024 Release: Make Every Employee a Success Story</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Success can take many forms. It’s achieving AI-driven results faster and smarter. It’s unlocking more meaningful and aspirational career development experiences. It’s empowering employees and managers through simple HR-related tasks in the flow of work, freeing up more productive time across the organization.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>And for you and your business, you can tell all those success stories – and more – with the SAP SuccessFactors HCM suite and our first half 2024 release.</p>
  <p>As your organization and employees begin to embrace AI, <a href="/topics/human-resources">HR</a> has the opportunity to drive new levels of employee productivity, engagement, and growth. SAP SuccessFactors HCM can give you everything you need – the global foundation, skills framework, people-first experiences, and purpose-built AI capabilities – to help take HR to the next level. With the SAP SuccessFactors first half 2024 release, we are delivering more than 250 innovative features and enhancements.</p>
  <h2 id="sap-business-ai">SAP Business AI</h2>
  <p>In 1H 2024, we are thrilled to introduce more than 25 new AI capabilities to enable better employee experiences and new levels of productivity.</p>
  <p>Among these capabilities include the ability for applicants to provide skills during the application process. This can enable recruiters to see a skills compatibility for each applicant based on matching the applicant’s skills and the job requisition, helping improve applicant screening and time to hire. Furthermore, personalization in SAP SuccessFactors Opportunity Marketplace is enhanced with new AI-driven recommendation categories, “Ignite Your Role” and “Reach Your Aspirations.” These guided experiences can enable employees to proactively take steps to reach their development goals.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e755ea739e2394a3bec10a53f644e2d9cd718123.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e755ea739e2394a3bec10a53f644e2d9cd718123.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1e755ea739e2394a3bec10a53f644e2d9cd718123.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Screenshot of the assisted screening and skills match capabilities" src="./media_1e755ea739e2394a3bec10a53f644e2d9cd718123.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="803" height="521">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>Assisted screening and skills match available in 1H 2024 release. Click to enlarge.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Generative AI continues to be embedded across the SAP SuccessFactors HCM suite, including new capabilities to help employees create ready-made performance and development goals and AI-assisted writing to help improve the quality, clarity, and conciseness of writing across a variety of areas within SAP SuccessFactors solutions.</p>
  <p>Further, with this release, insights based on an employee’s compensation and job history are available to help support managers in having effective and well-informed compensation discussions.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="the-ai-copilot-that-truly-understands-your-business">The AI copilot that truly understands your business</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/ai-assistant.html">Meet Joule</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>We have also added more than 15 new <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/ai-assistant.html">Joule</a> capabilities in this release to help both managers and employees get work done in a conversational way, such as creating or changing a position, creating spot awards, clocking in and out, and viewing pay statements as well as time capabilities like requesting time off, checking leave balances, and syncing holidays to Outlook calendars while managers can review and approve time off. Further, employees can now clock in and out using Joule, Microsoft Teams, or the SAP SuccessFactors Mobile app.</p>
  <h2 id="sap-successfactors-employee-central">SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central</h2>
  <p>We are excited to unveil two new people profile experiences – the profile preview and the spotlight view. The profile preview can provide a snapshot of key areas of the employee profile, including job, manager, location, and contact details, to quickly view and connect with others. Additionally, the spotlight view can showcase employee skills and competencies, mentoring and target roles, and other relevant personal and organizational information.</p>
  <p>We are also introducing a new org chart experience with a refreshed look and feel. Available on desktop and mobile, users can explore their organizational structure with improved expand and collapse capabilities, which helps provide full accessibility to an employee’s profile preview, with an option to open the new spotlight view.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b181ba5a94a8b936ff644a1c243245079ecbbab4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b181ba5a94a8b936ff644a1c243245079ecbbab4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1b181ba5a94a8b936ff644a1c243245079ecbbab4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Screenshot of the new org chart experience" src="./media_1b181ba5a94a8b936ff644a1c243245079ecbbab4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="576">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>The new org chart experience. Click to enlarge.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Customers can now automatically process new hires from SAP SuccessFactors Recruiting and SAP SuccessFactors Onboarding into SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central. This capability helps further reduce the time to hire, which is especially important with mass, seasonal, and high-volume hiring.</p>
  <h2 id="sap-successfactors-employee-central-global-benefits">SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central Global Benefits</h2>
  <p>With this release, we are pleased to introduce a new benefits enrollment experience for insurance, savings, and pension benefit types. Available on both desktop and mobile, the guided experience for benefits elections can give employees increased convenience with improved navigation and increased confidence with side-by-side plan comparisons and embedded instructional text. Additionally, employees can update dependent information and manage beneficiaries directly from the benefits enrollment process, which helps further streamline the enrollment experience.</p>
  <h2 id="sap-successfactors-time-tracking">SAP SuccessFactors Time Tracking</h2>
  <p>We are thrilled to share the launch of a new time sheet experience that integrates the latest version of My Timesheet in SAP S/4HANA with SAP SuccessFactors. Employees can now record time for payroll, as well as against activities and cost objects, from a single time sheet across applications. This helps organizations leverage real-time connectivity between HR and finance operations to keep track of employee activity and labor costs and to pay employees accurately and on time.</p>
  <p>Additionally, a new monthly calendar view for time sheets can give employees and managers a complete picture of recorded time over a month. Users can drill down into specific days and submit or approve time for pay periods beyond a week, such as biweekly or monthly.</p>
  <p>For managers, a new time approval center helps simplify approvals with a centralized dashboard highlighting anomalies for swift resolution. Managers can monitor team working hours effectively, helping to ensure accurate and timely payroll processing.</p>
  <h2 id="sap-successfactors-onboarding">SAP SuccessFactors Onboarding</h2>
  <p>With enhancements to the onboarding journey experience, new hires can now use the new Your Onboarding Checklist page to reference and complete all tasks – onboarding data collection, compliance tasks, additional onboarding tasks, and exploring the onboarding guide – from one place with a single view. Available for new hires, rehires, internal hires, and employees with global assignments, this improved experience can save time for onboarding participants while helping to ensure productivity from the start.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e12cd49909a64b18778552665ee0147fcacdc707.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e12cd49909a64b18778552665ee0147fcacdc707.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1e12cd49909a64b18778552665ee0147fcacdc707.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Screenshot of the new onboarding journey experience" src="./media_1e12cd49909a64b18778552665ee0147fcacdc707.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="576">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>The new onboarding journey experience. Click to enlarge.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>And that’s only a fraction of all the innovations we’re bringing to customers in 1H 2024. There’s much more in the release, including new and exciting updates in:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Generative AI and Joule capabilities</li>
    <li>SAP SuccessFactors Opportunity Marketplace</li>
    <li>SAP SuccessFactors Compensation</li>
    <li>SAP SuccessFactors Succession &#x26; Development</li>
    <li>SAP SuccessFactors Incentive Management</li>
    <li>SAP SuccessFactors Work Zone</li>
  </ul>
  <p>Read the <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2024/04/300e8c6d-b77e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">SAP SuccessFactors first half 2024 release highlights brochure</a> and watch the <a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2024/04/8c907f14-b77e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">1H 2024 release highlights video</a> to find out more.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Bianka Woelke is group vice president of Application Product Management at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-employee-central</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors-hcm-suite</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-onboarding</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-opportunity-marketplace</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-recruiting</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Building a Dynamic Organization with a Skills-Based Approach to Talent]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/building-dynamic-organization-skills-based-approach-to-talent</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/building-dynamic-organization-skills-based-approach-to-talent</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A skills-based approach to talent management can help organizations build a dynamic and resilient workforce. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/recruiting</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-learning</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-opportunity-marketplace</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-recruiting</category>
            <category>news-tag/talent-acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[2024 HR Trends: The Year of AI]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/2024-hr-trends-the-year-of-ai</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/2024-hr-trends-the-year-of-ai</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP research reveals the latest HR trends and how organizations can stay ahead of the curve with innovative strategies and technology.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ff8cf0ed03433df1c0da682bcb037e6567eeae0d.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ff8cf0ed03433df1c0da682bcb037e6567eeae0d.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1ff8cf0ed03433df1c0da682bcb037e6567eeae0d.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="2024 HR Trends: The Year of AI" src="./media_1ff8cf0ed03433df1c0da682bcb037e6567eeae0d.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="hr-trends-the-year-of-ai">2024 HR Trends: The Year of AI</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Over the past few years, HR has steadily evolved into one of the most critical functions for any organization. HR not only has a seat at the table, but the ability to become a driving force behind organizational change and growth. Most customers I speak with recognize this opportunity, but many have the same question: how can HR make the most impact?</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Each year, the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/resources.html">SAP SuccessFactors Growth &#x26; Insights team</a> conducts in-depth research on the latest trends and predictions impacting the HR function. Our PhD-level organizational psychologists and market intelligence experts aggregate and analyze a mountain of HR trends and predictions data to deliver a list of actionable “meta-trends.” For 2024, a list of 611 individual trends were broken down into nine key themes.</p>
  <p>Above all, there is no question that 2024 is the year of <a href="/topics/ai">artificial intelligence (AI)</a>. No longer just hype or speculation, AI is officially here. Exciting possibilities have become realities and organizations must embrace AI or risk being left behind. And while our number one HR trend is AI, you can also see its effects across every trend.</p>
  <p>Below is a snapshot of the top three 2024 HR meta-trends, with examples of how SAP SuccessFactors solutions can help organizations stay ahead of the curve.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <picture>
          <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d0e8557e1e73aae25728990f5b73d21af5fff939.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
          <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d0e8557e1e73aae25728990f5b73d21af5fff939.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
          <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1d0e8557e1e73aae25728990f5b73d21af5fff939.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
          <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_1d0e8557e1e73aae25728990f5b73d21af5fff939.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="208">
        </picture>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="ai-upends-the-world-of-work-as-we-know-it">1. AI Upends the World of Work as We Know It</h2>
  <p>I don’t go a day – or maybe 10 minutes – without a customer asking for all the latest and greatest on AI innovation. That makes sense, as AI has dominated the 2024 trends discourse and it’s increasingly become seen as a way to augment human work.</p>
  <p>Trends indicate that using all forms of AI to improve day-to-day productivity will be top of mind for organizations in 2024. In particular, self-serve AI tools like copilots are poised to increase employee productivity on various day-to-day tasks. As employee sentiment about using AI tools at work has improved, so has the ability of these tools to make employees more efficient and effective.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="be-ready-for-ai-built-for-business">Be ready for AI built for business</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/ai-assistant.html">Meet SAP’s AI copilot, Joule</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>HR use cases abound, particularly within talent acquisition, but concerns continue about data privacy, ethics, and regulatory compliance. There’s a lot of noise and movement in the space, and regulators and enforcement agencies are acting quickly to keep up.</p>
  <p>With the tech landscape and market realities in mind, the HR leaders who head AI implementation programs, maintain a strong policy posture, and avoid overhyped or underbaked propositions to take advantage of the most valuable capabilities will steer their organizations down the right AI path.</p>
  <p>Embedding an AI copilot in HR solutions, like <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/ai-joule-product-tour.html">Joule in SAP SuccessFactors solutions</a>, can help employees and managers work faster and smarter by making it easier to find information and complete common HR tasks, such as updating personal data, giving feedback, and initiating a promotion.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_102dca27542b692c9688525999ebc7b6cc402f1b5.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_102dca27542b692c9688525999ebc7b6cc402f1b5.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_102dca27542b692c9688525999ebc7b6cc402f1b5.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_102dca27542b692c9688525999ebc7b6cc402f1b5.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="614">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>Joule, SAP’s AI copilot. Click to enlarge.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="skills-become-the-center-of-hr-practices">2. Skills Become the Center of HR Practices</h2>
  <p>As AI needs rise within organizations, many organizations will need to immediately respond to determine what AI skills are needed, who possesses those skills, and how to fill skill gaps – whether build, borrow, buy, or bot. On the other hand, AI capabilities will also drive the ability for organizations to more effectively engage in strategic workforce planning.</p>
  <p>Furthermore, in today’s increasingly complex business environment, traditional top-down human resources approaches fail to address employees’ increasing expectations for flexible and personalized career development. In 2024, HR will need to meet employees’ growing expectations for bespoke career paths while also solving the broader organization’s growing skills gaps and talent shortages, which present a major concern for leaders.</p>
  <p>Looking forward, it will be interesting to see whether the average organization fully engages in long-term, strategic, skills-based workforce planning, which has long been a strategic objective for many but often remains out of reach as they react to immediate priorities. AI skills could work as a forcing function here – and contribute to other trend areas like learning and employee potential.</p>
  <p><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/talent-management.html">SAP SuccessFactors solutions for talent management</a> can drive better employee experiences and business outcomes by using a common skills framework across recruiting, learning, performance management, internal mobility, and development.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d381f1111939f272d8dd076b837ed2de4dd9aa20.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d381f1111939f272d8dd076b837ed2de4dd9aa20.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1d381f1111939f272d8dd076b837ed2de4dd9aa20.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_1d381f1111939f272d8dd076b837ed2de4dd9aa20.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="576">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>Overview of skills and aspirations in a growth portfolio for SAP SuccessFactors. Click to enlarge.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="hybrid-work-returns-to-the-office">3. Hybrid Work Returns to the Office</h2>
  <p>Looking back at our yearly analyses of HR meta-trends, we saw the hybrid work topic shift from a focus on remote work as a reactive tactic to protect employees’ health and safety in 2020, to a focus on flexibility in 2021, to maintaining productivity and collaboration while working flexibly in 2022, and finally to an emphasis on underlying flexibility and the need for and benefit of malleable guidelines and principles in 2023. With the recent increase in partial and full return-to-office (RTO) policies, 2024 trends data suggests that the pendulum has swung back to hybrid, referring specifically to work location versus a broader perspective centered on flexibility.</p>
  <p>Companies in 2024 will continue to experiment with motivating employees to return to the office in ways that promote productivity, collaboration, and cost savings but don’t alienate their top talent. But some organizations are focusing more on redesigning the nature of work rather than just mandating where or when work gets done.</p>
  <p><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/core-hr-payroll.html">SAP SuccessFactors solutions for core HR, time, and payroll</a> help employees adopt a hybrid working model by providing options for common HR tasks regardless of when and where they are working, such as clocking in and out via desktop, mobile, or Microsoft Teams.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16e1bb2544e733655fa31281e9dcd8f5220ded6f8.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16e1bb2544e733655fa31281e9dcd8f5220ded6f8.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_16e1bb2544e733655fa31281e9dcd8f5220ded6f8.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_16e1bb2544e733655fa31281e9dcd8f5220ded6f8.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="576">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>Clock in and out via Microsoft Teams with SAP SuccessFactors solutions. Click to enlarge.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>There are plenty more strategic takeaways in the full report – the entire paper is a must-read for HR leaders to learn more from our research team on the latest trends in:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Diversity, equity, inclusion, and belonging (DEI&#x26;B)</li>
    <li>Employee mental health</li>
    <li>Leadership trust</li>
    <li>HR skills and agility</li>
    <li>Compensation</li>
    <li>Sustainability</li>
  </ul>
  <p>For additional insights, <a href="https://www.sap.com/registration/protected/default-overlay.html?gated_asset_path=%2F%2Fwww.sap.com%2Fdocuments%2F2024%2F02%2F883d4dde-ad7e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.rc.html&#x26;pdf-asset=883d4dde-ad7e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b&#x26;page=1?url_id=ctabutton-us-hcm">read the full report</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Dan Beck is president and chief product officer for SAP SuccessFactors.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-sap-news-on-linkedin">Connect with SAP News on LinkedIn</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news">Follow us to stay up-to-date</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors-hcm-suite</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Convista Harmonizes Workplace Culture with SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central and SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/convista-harmonizes-workplace-culture-with-sap-successfactors</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/convista-harmonizes-workplace-culture-with-sap-successfactors</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Convista's people culture and respected brand built on trust and transparency is supported by SAP S/4HANA Cloud and SAP SuccessFactors.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11a18052b07fa380b0a184821d2508dc2d57d515a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11a18052b07fa380b0a184821d2508dc2d57d515a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_11a18052b07fa380b0a184821d2508dc2d57d515a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Convista Harmonizes Workplace Culture with SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central and SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition" src="./media_11a18052b07fa380b0a184821d2508dc2d57d515a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="convista-harmonizes-workplace-culture-with-sap-successfactors-employee-central-and-sap-s4hana-cloud-public-edition">Convista Harmonizes Workplace Culture with SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central and SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>In a merger between two well-matched organizations, cultural integration can be the key to successfully transforming into a single high-performing entity ready to take on new opportunities. Notably, more than a few high-profile mergers have failed due to cultural incompatibility. Add a third organization into the merger and the cultural complexities increase exponentially. But some multi-organization mergers do successfully navigate these challenges and reap the transformational benefits.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="https://www.convista.com/en/">Convista</a>, a consultancy and SAP partner based in Cologne, Germany, emerged stronger and better positioned to serve its clients following a <a href="https://www.convista.com/en/news/axxiome-health-and-enowa-become-part-of-the-new-convista/">recent merger</a> that brought together three former consultancies: Axxiome Health, ConVista Consulting, and enowa. With 25 years of experience delivering transformation projects to its clients, Convista used that expertise in its own rebranding to present its capabilities to clients and employees: a vibrant people culture as well as a respected and trusted brand supported by <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/s4hana.html">SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition</a> for ERP and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/employee-central-hris/features.html">SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central</a> for core HR.</p>
  <p>“Trust and transparency are common values that we share at Convista,” declares Convista CEO Martin Hinz. “Combined with a dynamic team spirit and passion, it’s what we bring to our clients every day.”</p>
  <p>With a workforce of around 1,200 employees, Convista has made a name for itself through its dedication and expertise providing end-to-end solutions to clients throughout the world with a presence in Germany, Austria, Switzerland, Poland, Spain, Brazil, Israel, and further locations across the globe. It supports client projects primarily in four sectors: insurance, industry, healthcare, and energy/utilities. In recent years, Convista has twice been awarded SAP <a href="https://www.convista.com/en/news/for-the-second-time-in-a-row-sap-partner-of-the-year-award-in-the-financial-services-sector/">Partner of the Year</a> in the Financial Services sector.</p>
  <p>“At Convista you meet everyone on the same level, independent of your skill level or where you are in your career,” says Stefanie Weber, project lead of People and Culture – HR Systems, Convista. “Also, when we’re working with customers, we try to approach them at eye level, which makes quite a good working environment. The implementation of SAP SuccessFactors came as a natural extension to our brand and our culture.”</p>
  <h2 id="the-challenges-of-data-siloed-in-three-systems">The Challenges of Data Siloed in Three Systems</h2>
  <p>Weber says one of the reasons she joined Convista in 2012 while studying business at university was the high priority its leaders place on trust and transparency, values that permeate the entire organization and empower employees in their work and career development. “Trust is one of our main values,” she underscores. “Also, the trust that people are willing to do their best to get motivated and move the company ahead.”</p>
  <p>Convista grew quickly both organically and as a result of mergers with other consultancies. In 2019, IT service provider Axxiome Health joined the ConVista Group to deepen the organization’s expertise in the health insurance sector. In 2021, enowa joined the group, infusing its knowledge of industries and insurance. With the mergers complete, the incipient organization became <a href="https://www.convista.com/en/news/axxiome-health-and-enowa-become-part-of-the-new-convista/">the new Convista</a> on January 1, 2023.</p>
  <p>Though team members were highly motivated to collaborate from the start, Convista’s vision for itself as a modern organization was held back in both its daily work for projects and internal services. Using disparate tools based on older technology and a patchwork of third-party solutions that lacked integration proved to be inefficient and unsuitable as a basis for decision-making.</p>
  <p>“Whenever we wanted to have a report, even something as simple as a headcount, we always had to go into three different systems, collect the data, and report on that,” Weber recalls. “It’s just one of the many examples of why we really urgently needed one IT platform.”</p>
  <h2 id="project-one-achieves-milestone-integration">Project ONE Achieves Milestone Integration</h2>
  <p>To build a strong foundation for future growth, Convista embarked on “Project ONE” with the goal to have one digital platform flexible and powerful enough for the entire organization. For this, it chose SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition and SAP SuccessFactors solutions with self-service capabilities for employees to log time-off.</p>
  <p>Overall, implementing SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central with SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition can result in streamlined HR processes; end-to-end integration with seamless connectivity between HR and finance functions for accurate and up-to-date employee data across the organization; greater transparency of data for analytics and reporting on workforce trends, costs, and profitability to enable better strategic planning and resource allocation; and compliance with regulatory requirements and data security.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-successfactors-solutions-can-fuel-the-success-of-every-individual-and-drive-org-agility-at-scale">SAP SuccessFactors solutions can fuel the success of every individual and drive org agility at scale</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm.html">Learn how</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Among the key advantages is the ability for employees to access their own HR-related information, such as personal details and time-off balances. This self-service capability helps empower employees, improve transparency, and enhance the overall employee experience.</p>
  <p>Convista’s project team decided for a phased approach to the implementation by first introducing the SAP solutions in Poland and later in Germany, Austria, and Switzerland – with SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition planned to launch in the German-speaking countries during the course of 2024. To optimize success, the project team used the combined best practices of Convista and SAP and hosted regular meetings that provided clear communication to steer the project. “We were always aligned on the requirements of the other teams,” says Weber, who managed the HR workstream. “We all knew the main goal of the implementation. This was helpful for everyone on the project.”</p>
  <p>In-house experts from Convista certified on SAP SuccessFactors solutions contributed valuable knowledge for the implementation. Consultants from SAP Services and Support successfully integrated the cost center replication from SAP S/4HANA Cloud to SAP SuccessFactors and the workforce replication from SAP SuccessFactors to SAP S/4HANA Cloud, and delivered a detailed administration guide on the integration setup for Convista. Additionally, they provided an overview, the architecture guidance, and the navigation through major hurdles in performing the configuration to set up identity access governence (IAG), identity provisioning service (IPS), and identity authentication services (IAS). The SAP Early Adopter Care program supported Convista for the master data integration (MDI) during the implementation and helped to solve all roadblocks efficiently.</p>
  <p>On January 1, 2023, Convista’s 80-person team in Poland was the first to go live with the new SAP solutions. “It was really a great experience for them and quite an advancement,” says Weber, citing the benefits of the new solutions that provide optimizations and intuitive workflows. The project took a pivotal turn on January 1, 2024, with the launch of SAP SuccessFactors solutions for Convista’s 800 employees in the German-speaking countries.</p>
  <p>“The biggest milestone was to have [SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition and SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central] speaking with each other,” says Weber, who emphasizes how valuable it is for the team “to have an end-to-end process within one platform.” With an integrated IT platform in place, she says that it is no longer necessary to do workflows, authorizations, or any other processes in other systems.</p>
  <p>The seamless synchronization of data by using a common data model for SAP business applications helps reduce the need for manual data entry and redundant processes. This means, for example, employee data that is maintained in SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central is available in real-time in SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition; while master data, like cost center data, flows seamlessly from SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition to SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central. Eliminating data silos enables the HR and finance teams to work with consistent, accurate data for all-important employment decisions and legal reporting obligations.</p>
  <p>Now Convista’s team is unified in its brand, values, spirit – and employee data.</p>
  <h2 id="more-transparency-and-intuitive-workflows-are-just-the-beginning">More Transparency and Intuitive Workflows Are Just the Beginning</h2>
  <p>Feedback has been overwhelmingly positive, according to Weber, with employees speaking favorably about the improved transparency and workflows. “The first thing I heard from everyone was, well, this is simple and intuitive. They were so happy about it,” she says. “They are big fans of the mobile application. They find it very transparent and easy to use.”</p>
  <p>For some colleagues, the new solution lets them view their own data for the first time. “When we went live, everyone was viewing their profile,” says Weber. “This was also quite new that you are able to see what data is maintained for your person, your address, but also job information – to view it and have this transparency. People like this very much and also the ability to have the self-services in SAP SuccessFactors.”</p>
  <p>To strengthen communication between HR and employees, Convista will bring more people processes onto the new digital platform. In fact, the team very recently implemented the SAP SuccessFactors Performance &#x26; Goals solution for annual employee appraisals, goal setting, and project feedback. “It’s just the beginning,” Weber says. “There’s still a lot of work ahead of us.”</p>
  <p>Hinz says, “We have been careful to preserve our workplace culture during the transformation. Now that we are rebranded as one organization, we are seeing the benefits of that early effort. With SAP, we now have the digital platform to build people-centered processes that advance our vision as a unified, high-performing organization serving our clients.”</p>
  <p>Find out more about <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/solutions.html?url_id=ctabutton-us-hcm-convista">SAP SuccessFactors solutions</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Jacqueline Prause is a journalist at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-sap-news-delivered-to-your-inbox-once-a-week">Get the latest SAP news delivered to your inbox once a week</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/nl/sap-news-center-newsletter/index.html">Sign up today</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-employee-central</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP SuccessFactors Strategy for Building Future-Ready Workforces]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/sap-successfactors-strategy-building-future-ready-workforces</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/sap-successfactors-strategy-building-future-ready-workforces</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The SAP SuccessFactors HCM suite provides HR cloud software to help organizations meet the challenges of today and innovate for tomorrow.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1aa60aead41f035043e44cbfe1f53c8c65e859485.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1aa60aead41f035043e44cbfe1f53c8c65e859485.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1aa60aead41f035043e44cbfe1f53c8c65e859485.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP SuccessFactors Strategy for Building Future-Ready Workforces" src="./media_1aa60aead41f035043e44cbfe1f53c8c65e859485.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-successfactors-strategy-for-building-future-ready-workforces">SAP SuccessFactors Strategy for Building Future-Ready Workforces</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Without a doubt, the world of work has dramatically transformed over the past several years, with generative AI initiating the latest wave of change for organizations around the world. In a more complex and less homogenous business landscape, top-down HR processes of the past no longer meet the rising demands of employees for flexible career paths, intuitive work processes, and two-way communication – not to mention the growing skills gaps and talent shortages that keep leaders up at night.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Leaders need to embrace generative AI as a way to address these challenges with talent intelligence and advanced analytics. According to <a href="https://emt.gartnerweb.com/ngw/globalassets/en/human-resources/documents/trends/hr-top-priorities-ebook-2024.pdf?_gl=1*1bmqwvn*_ga*NjU0NzU1ODk5LjE3MDY4MDI5MDY.*_ga_R1W5CE5FEV*MTcwNjgwMjkwNS4xLjEuMTcwNjgwMzA4Mi4yNi4wLjA.">Gartner</a>, 26% of CEOs rank the talent shortage as the top damaging factor to business outlook, and 76% of HR leaders agree they will be lagging in organizational success if they don’t adopt and implement generative AI in the next 12 to 24 months.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="adopt-the-latest-in-hr-innovation-with-sap-successfactors-solutions">Adopt the latest in HR innovation with SAP SuccessFactors solutions</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>At SAP, we have a proven track record of providing <a href="/topics/human-resources">HCM</a> solutions in the cloud for leading organizations around the globe. Our customers trust us to not only manage their sensitive employee data and payroll, but to help them understand their workforces as they prepare for the skills they need in the future.</p>
  <p>The <a href="http://sap.com/hr">SAP SuccessFactors HCM suite</a> provides truly global HR cloud software with powerful AI capabilities to help organizations meet the challenges of today and innovate for tomorrow. Our more than 10,000 customers – from startups and midmarket companies to large enterprises – use our solutions to help bring out the best in their people by harnessing the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/human-resources.html">power of AI</a> to elevate every experience, guide every people decision, and connect HR across every aspect of the business. We do this with:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/solutions.html#active_tab_item_1602592257238">Core HR and payroll</a></strong>: A single source of truth is key for any organization to enable insight into the entirety of its workforce: employees, contingent workers, and dynamic teams. The SAP SuccessFactors HCM suite can provide localized support for over 100 countries and territories and cloud payroll for 50 countries and territories, plus additional modular solutions for time, benefits, and HR service delivery.</li>
    <li><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/solutions.html#active_tab_item_1602592296240">Talent and learning</a></strong>: Skills gaps and talent shortages have been persistent challenges that continue to exist across all industries. Addressing them starts with an understanding of skills that currently exist, followed by pathways for employees to find new opportunities, learn new skills, and access mentors and feedback. The talent intelligence hub across SAP SuccessFactors solutions uses AI to continuously help organizations and employees understand their skills and match people with personalized career pathways.</li>
    <li><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/solutions.html#active_tab_item_1602592051931">A modern user experience</a></strong>: Every person has unique needs and preferences – in how they work, how they communicate, and what’s required for their role. Along with a refreshed, modern user experience, we’ve built in generative AI capabilities throughout our solutions to help people work smarter. And with Joule, SAP’s copilot, they can quickly complete HR tasks and get conversational responses to their questions.</li>
    <li><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/hr-and-finance.html">HR connected to ERP, finance, and more</a></strong>: Having access to people data connected across the business is critical to building agility, speed, and resilience within an organization. With the power of the broader SAP portfolio, organizations can improve end-to-end business processes across the entire business. This is also complemented with our partner ecosystem, which includes over 350 apps for HR.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>We firmly believe that when organizations invest in their people – in their passions and potential – they return the investment over and over. And with the rapid acceleration of AI, it’s more important than ever to build pathways to employee growth, including new ways to upskill, reskill, and discover opportunities that align with a person’s skills, interests, and aspirations.</p>
  <p>Learn more about the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm.html?url_id=text-us-hcm-hr-freetrial">SAP SuccessFactors HCM suite</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Dan Beck is president and chief product officer for SAP SuccessFactors.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors-hcm-suite</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Recognized as a Strategic Challenger in 2024 Fosway 9-Grid™ for Learning Systems]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/sap-strategic-challenger-2024-fosway-9-grid-for-learning-systems</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/sap-strategic-challenger-2024-fosway-9-grid-for-learning-systems</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP was recently named a Strategic Challenger in the 2024 Fosway 9-Grid for Learning Systems. Read to learn more about the recognition.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1909b111011bdb2e7f1b173d6614d6bdebec89073.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1909b111011bdb2e7f1b173d6614d6bdebec89073.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1909b111011bdb2e7f1b173d6614d6bdebec89073.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Recognized as a Strategic Challenger in 2024 Fosway 9-Grid™ for Learning Systems" src="./media_1909b111011bdb2e7f1b173d6614d6bdebec89073.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-recognized-as-a-strategic-challenger-in-2024-fosway-9-grid-for-learning-systems">SAP Recognized as a Strategic Challenger in 2024 Fosway 9-Grid™ for Learning Systems</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>SAP was recently named a Strategic Challenger in the <a href="https://www.fosway.com/9-grid-2/learning-systems/">2024 Fosway 9-Grid<sup>TM</sup> for Learning Systems</a>, a multidimensional learning market analysis model. As a Strategic Challenger, SAP is recognized as demonstrating solid performance with solutions that have a rich and broad suite of capability compared to the market.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>With the widened availability of AI, the race for skills is impacting both people and organizations. While people are learning how to use AI to drive more efficiency within their individual roles, organizations are also under pressure to adopt AI technology that can deliver more personalized development opportunities and greater talent intelligence.</p>
  <p>Over the last year, SAP has made significant investments across <a href="http://sap.com/hr">SAP SuccessFactors solutions</a>, specifically in <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/corporate-lms.html">SAP SuccessFactors Learning</a>, to deliver these capabilities.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="boost-employee-skills-while-helping-ensure-compliance-with-sap-successfactors-learning">Boost employee skills while helping ensure compliance with SAP SuccessFactors Learning</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/corporate-lms.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>These investments are part of a broader strategy to help our customers focus on accelerated skills growth and build a <a href="/2023/09/new-integrated-learning-experience-sap-successfactors">future-ready workforce</a>. Recently, we released a redesigned <strong>integrated learning experience</strong> that can deliver an entirely new way for people to experience learning at work. The highly personalized experience can guide the learner to not only accomplish compliance trainings – what they “have to learn” – and organizational goals – what they “need to learn” – but also helps to drive an intrinsic culture of learning around what they “want to learn,” tapping into each individual’s needs, aspirations, interests, or preferences based on their growth profile.</p>
  <p>Furthermore, <strong>the AI-powered</strong> <strong><a href="/2023/10/skills-based-organization-talent-intelligence-hub">talent intelligence hub</a></strong> is now available across all SAP SuccessFactors solutions. It is a framework that helps organizations understand the skills their employees have today, the gaps that exist, and how to close those gaps. With this intelligence, SAP SuccessFactors Learning can continue to deliver even more personalized learning and development recommendations.</p>
  <p>“The level of innovation within the learning systems market continues to accelerate rapidly – specifically around AI and skills,” said David Wilson, founder and CEO of Fosway Group. “As a major vendor in this space, SAP continues to invest significantly in innovating its learning and talent capabilities, reflecting its focus on enhancing the value it delivers to learning buyers as well as its wider HCM audience.”</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d02d983db0796a8aed17039c36d19de9b713748b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d02d983db0796a8aed17039c36d19de9b713748b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1d02d983db0796a8aed17039c36d19de9b713748b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_1d02d983db0796a8aed17039c36d19de9b713748b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="768">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>Source: 2024 Fosway 9-GridTM for Learning Systems. Click to enlarge.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Both multinational and midsize companies leverage <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/corporate-lms.html">SAP SuccessFactors Learning</a>, along with our partner ecosystem, to help drive upskilling and reskilling and create a culture of continuous learning.</p>
  <p><a href="/2023/07/san-pablo-farmacia-employees-brand-ambassadors">San Pablo Farmacia</a>, a Mexico-based pharmacy retail chain, created an intuitive and engaging training experience that employees can consume at their convenience. By integrating the learning solution with other talent management applications, it can design personal training and development plans in line with its growth strategies and the individual needs of the entire workforce. The company delivered certified training to 1,800 employees without the need to transport its people to a training location and take them away from their pharmacy stores.</p>
  <p>Delta is also embracing AI to drive upskilling and personalized development opportunities. “We are incorporating disruptive technologies like our AI-driven skills ontology that automatically incorporates industry trends with embedded intelligence,” said Tim Gregory, managing director of HR Innovation and Workforce Technology at <a href="/2023/10/skills-based-organization-talent-intelligence-hub">Delta</a>. “We can say which skills are most important to Delta Air Lines and the employee can easily combine those with their current capabilities, strengths and styles, and aspirations to create a personal career path. All of the content is based on Delta-specific skills and personalized to each employee’s career goals.”</p>
  <p>Looking ahead, we will continue to deliver more learning-specific enhancements and new AI capabilities throughout 2024 across all SAP SuccessFactors solutions so leaders can hire the best talent and grow their personal skills with individualized plans while building up the compliance and strategic skills needed by the organization.</p>
  <p><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/corporate-lms.html">Learn more about SAP SuccessFactors Learning.</a></p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Vinita Venkatesh is vice president of Product Management for SAP SuccessFactors Learning.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-learning</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sales Performance Management: Empowering Sales Teams for Better Outcomes]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/sap-north-america-sales-performance-management-customer-summit-better-outcomes</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/sap-north-america-sales-performance-management-customer-summit-better-outcomes</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[At the SAP Sales Performance Management Customer Summit, customers shared how to optimize sales compensation for better business results.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_151d6d5f5e440d033f2105cfba96ee66afebd464e.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_151d6d5f5e440d033f2105cfba96ee66afebd464e.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_151d6d5f5e440d033f2105cfba96ee66afebd464e.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Sales Performance Management: Empowering Sales Teams for Better Outcomes" src="./media_151d6d5f5e440d033f2105cfba96ee66afebd464e.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sales-performance-management-empowering-sales-teams-for-better-outcomes">Sales Performance Management: Empowering Sales Teams for Better Outcomes</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>In today’s dynamic business environment, organizations need highly efficient sales teams to generate revenue and stay ahead of the competition. But while advances in AI-powered tools have accelerated the sales process, they have also increased the value of soft skills and the relationship-building acumen that talented salespeople bring to their jobs. That’s why savvy organizations are more committed than ever to keeping their sales teams engaged and productive.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="accelerate-business-outcomes-with-sales-performance-management-products-from-sap">Accelerate business outcomes with sales performance management products from SAP</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/sales-performance-management.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>High-performing sales teams are using <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/sales-performance-management.html">sales performance management</a> solutions from SAP SuccessFactors to manage and optimize sales compensation and incentives – rewarding sales reps for their performance – while streamlining sales processes and using real-time insights to improve operational efficiency and drive revenue.</p>
  <p>“There’s this renewed emphasis on efficiency,” said Rahul Iyer, general manager, Sales Performance Management, SAP SuccessFactors, speaking to SAP customers at the <a href="https://events.sap.com/us/sap-north-america-spm-customer-summit-2024/en/home">SAP North America Sales Performance Management Customer Summit</a>, held February 13-14, 2024, in Dallas, Texas. “Customers want faster, simpler outcomes – and they want to provide a great seller experience, as well. At SAP SuccessFactors, we’ve threaded the intelligence of connected cloud applications throughout the SPM solution portfolio. This allows us to deliver the efficiency, transparency, and rich experience of SAP in a comprehensive platform that covers a full range of end-to-end processes in sales compensation.”</p>
  <h2 id="together-for-success">Together for Success</h2>
  <p>Under the banner “Together we can make it better,” the summit event provided a venue for SAP customers – some of whom came from as far away as South America – to meet one-on-one with experts and gain valuable knowledge from product road maps, demos, and deep dive sessions, as well as learn from one another’s experiences in customer sessions.</p>
  <p>Iyer affirmed SAP’s commitment to deliver the advanced innovations customers need to be competitive: “As a strategic partner to our customers, we have the moral responsibility to help them receive progressively more out of technology innovations, while accelerating with the best-in-class capabilities SAP has to offer. We are simplifying from every angle to make it easy for our customers to adopt, so they can achieve business outcomes faster.”</p>
  <p>Barbara Rubis Linning, SAP SuccessFactors global vice president, Product and Engineering, presented the latest innovations and features across the sales performance management solution set, which includes <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/incentive-compensation-management.html">SAP SuccessFactors Incentive Management</a>, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/territory-and-quota.html">SAP SuccessFactors Territory and Quota</a>, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/agent-lifecycle-mgmt.html">SAP SuccessFactors Agent Lifecycle Management</a>, and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/agent-performance-management.html">SAP SuccessFactors Agent Performance Management</a>. With features like territory planning and incentive compensation, SAP sales performance management solutions enable organizations to optimize their sales performance for better business results. The solutions use advanced features – for tasks such as drive time analysis and mapping to optimize territories – to streamline processes and make workflows easier so that customers realize value faster. The ongoing introduction of the <a href="https://community.sap.com/t5/technology-blogs-by-sap/sap-fiori-evolution-horizon-now-generally-available-in-ui-technologies-and/ba-p/13532969">Horizon</a> visual theme on key administrative pages delivers a fresh, modern user interface (UI) for an elevated user experience.</p>
  <p>“We want our customers to have winning sales teams,” said Linning. “Their success is why we continuously look for new ways to build innovations and relevant features into the portfolio to accelerate business outcomes. SAP is building intelligence that is relevant, responsible, and reliable because we believe it leads to smarter, data-driven decision making and results in better sales performance. Our new intuitive UI helps simplify tasks and puts people at the center of business for improved productivity.”</p>
  <p>SAP SuccessFactors solutions deliver <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/ai-assistant.html">Joule</a>, SAP’s natural language processing AI copilot, to help people be more productive in their jobs using SAP business solutions.</p>
  <p>The integration of sales performance management solutions with <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform.html">SAP Business Technology Platform</a> and <a href="/2023/03/sap-datasphere-power-of-business-data">SAP Datasphere</a> enables seamless access to real-time data and analytics, empowering organizations to make informed decisions and drive sales success.</p>
  <h2 id="winning-with-sales-compensation">Winning with Sales Compensation</h2>
  <p>As the all-important link between an organization’s products and services and its customers, the sales team is a principal driver of bottom-line growth for the whole organization. Correctly incenting sales teams requires the use of proven strategies and solutions to align the pay program with organizational goals, said David Cichelli, revenue growth advisor at <a href="https://www.alexandergroup.com/">The Alexander Group</a>, who presented “Leading the Sales Design Compensation Project.”</p>
  <p>He advised sales compensation leaders adopt an annual review process that includes assessment, strategic alignment, taskforce design, and comprehensive communication phases. “Sales compensation design needs to reflect the consensus of key stakeholders: sales, finance, product management, and HR,” he said. “By following a proven design process, you can develop a strategically aligned, effective, and motivational pay program.”</p>
  <h2 id="supporting-customer-success-for-better-outcomes">Supporting Customer Success for Better Outcomes</h2>
  <p>The summit showcased the SAP ecosystem with sponsorships and informative sessions from <a href="https://spectrumtek.com/">SpectrumTek</a>, <a href="https://canidium.com/">Canidium</a>, <a href="https://www.opensymmetry.com/">OpenSymmetry</a>, <a href="https://www.cahabaconsultinggroup.com/">Cahaba Consulting Group</a>, <a href="https://www.thelcfirm.com/">The LC Firm</a>, and <a href="https://www.aspiredigital.com/">Aspire Digital</a>.</p>
  <p>SAP experts highlighted SAP’s message of ongoing support for customer success: “We’re here for you,” said Tak Kusano, global chief operating officer of SAP SuccessFactors. “SAP has a tight-knit community of sales performance management experts that bring deep domain knowledge to this niche space. That’s why we’re able to work so closely with customers to gain consensus on the road map and product innovations, like AI. We’re passionate about bringing the best of technology to SAP customers.”</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/sales-performance-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Total Workforce Management Evolution: How OG&E and Brightspeed Manage Employees and Contingent Workers]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/oge-and-brightspeed-manage-employees-contingent-workers</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/oge-and-brightspeed-manage-employees-contingent-workers</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[OG&E and Brightspeed highlight the importance of strategic planning and the effective use of technological tools in managing the workforce.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/contingent-workforce-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fieldglass</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>news-tag/total-workforce-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Game-Changing Role of Incentive Compensation Automation in the Retail Industry]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/incentive-compensation-automation-in-retail</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/incentive-compensation-automation-in-retail</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With SAP SuccessFactors Incentive Management, retailers can incorporate key performance indicators into their incentive structure.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10fff8c20499512be48a61b55b1b6ecdb00d8656a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10fff8c20499512be48a61b55b1b6ecdb00d8656a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_10fff8c20499512be48a61b55b1b6ecdb00d8656a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="The Game-Changing Role of Incentive Compensation Automation in the Retail Industry" src="./media_10fff8c20499512be48a61b55b1b6ecdb00d8656a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="the-game-changing-role-of-incentive-compensation-automation-in-the-retail-industry">The Game-Changing Role of Incentive Compensation Automation in the Retail Industry</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>In the dynamic world of retail, staying ahead means adapting to evolving customer expectations and embracing innovative solutions. The era of omnichannel retailing has ushered in demand for seamless, personalized shopping experiences, compelling businesses to think outside the box to support seamless experiences and minimize friction by providing the right product at the right time in the right place. Moreover, recognizing the intricate dance between employee satisfaction and customer experience, businesses are weaving a narrative where a better employee experience becomes the cornerstone for elevating customer delight.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>At the recent <a href="/topics/nrf">NRF event</a>, the world’s largest retail conference, the mantra of “adjust and adapt” echoed through the halls. AI and digital acceleration took the center stage, making innovation the heart of the conversation. Retailers also highlighted a crucial focus on a motivated workforce, emphasizing how an empowered workforce is critical to delivering exceptional customer experiences.</p>
  <p>In a landscape challenged by high turnover rates, retailers showcased their commitment to navigating complexity through strategic investments in their most valuable asset – their people. One of the pivotal elements that drives employee motivation and engagement in the retail industry is incentive compensation, where associates are often paid on commission.</p>
  <p>During NRF, Daniel Jasper from Neiman Marcus shared insights into how incentive compensation automation transformed the company’s commission payment process. With over 40 stores and a complex commission structure, Neiman Marcus faced challenges in managing incentive compensation. Its previous incentive management system was cumbersome and complex, which led to errors, delays, and frustration among sales associates. Implementing <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/sales-performance-management.html#products">the SAP SuccessFactors Incentive Management solution</a> helped streamline the process, providing real-time monitoring of commission calculations. This allowed Neiman Marcus to identify and resolve issues proactively, resulting in improved accuracy and timeliness of commission payments. “Rather than waiting to hear from associates that something is wrong, we can monitor the calculations in real-time and resolve issues in advance,” said Jasper. This shift has been a game-changer for Neiman Marcus, driving better sales and revenue growth.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="empower-sales-teams-with-the-tools-they-need-to-create-effective-sales-experiences">Empower sales teams with the tools they need to create effective sales experiences</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/sales-performance-management.html">Find out how</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP SuccessFactors Incentive Management is one of the sales performance management solutions in the SAP SuccessFactors portfolio, and it offers a sophisticated platform for tailoring incentive programs to suit the unique needs of retail associates. With powerful analytics, embedded intelligence, and built-in workflows, this solution can revolutionize compensation management. Its intelligent design can not only foster trust but also ignite motivation among store associates. Through a user-friendly mobile app, retail customers can enjoy a comprehensive and easily accessible view of both store and individual performance metrics, promoting transparency and a unified understanding of team dynamics and trends. Personalized recommendations, relevant insights, and interactive monitoring help enhance the user experience, while the mobile app helps ensure that store associates can access their incentives anytime, anywhere, from any device.</p>
  <p>The solution’s agility helps facilitate a swift rollout of new and updated compensation plans, offering the flexibility to manage broadly or tailor plans to individual needs. With a steadfast commitment to accuracy and traceability, associates can trust the fairness of calculations, fostering a positive work environment. The effective dating functionalities help further empower organizations, allowing seamless management of associate promotions and transfers.</p>
  <p>“Retail businesses more than ever need the ability to design and manage incentive plans that align with ever-changing organizational goals, with a focus on store-level personalization and granularity that allow for improved accuracy and timeliness of commission payments,” said Rahul Iyer, general manager of Sales Performance Management at SAP. “With SAP SuccessFactors Incentive Management, retailers can incorporate key performance indicators, such as sales per hour and units per sale, into their incentive structure. The mobile app can provide visibility and transparency into individual and store performance, effectively motivating and ensuring optimal performance from their associates.”</p>
  <p>In essence, SAP SuccessFactors Incentive Management emerges as an indispensable tool, helping to empower retail customers to optimize workforce performance and drive sustained success. Displaying key performance indicators and incentives has proven to be a game changer, helping to drive focus on store and individual performance. The result? Associates are more attentive to customers, guiding them through purchasing decisions and enhancing overall satisfaction.</p>
  <p>In the always-changing retail world, success comes down to three things: using better technology, having happy employees, and keeping customers in focus. The story of Neiman Marcus proves that automating incentives can be a game changer. It shows how a motivated and well-connected team can not just boost how things work but also bring in more sales and money.</p>
  <p>To stay ahead in retail, you need to be ready for change and invest in both tech and your team. This is a clear lesson for retailers planning for the future. Learn more about how <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2023/03/509d257a-677e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">sales performance management can simplify the retail industry</a>. To learn more about how sales performance management solutions can support your organization, visit the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/sales-performance-management.html">sales performance management product page on sap.com</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Kevin Coxwell is vice president of GTM for Sales Performance Management at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-sap-news-on-linkedin">Connect with SAP News on LinkedIn</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news">Follow us</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-engagement</category>
            <category>news-tag/nrf</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
            <category>news-tag/sales-performance-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Eastman Energizes HR Reporting to Deliver One-Stop Insights to Leaders]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/eastman-hr-reporting-deliver-insights-to-leaders</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/eastman-hr-reporting-deliver-insights-to-leaders</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Eastman accelerated HR reporting for improved efficiency and insights using story reports in SAP SuccessFactors People Analytics. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>topic/data-analytics</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-preferred-success</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-employee-central</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-people-analytics</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-recruiting</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Top Retailers Using Tech to Build Lifelong Customer Relationships]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/retail-sap-customers-using-tech-to-build-lifelong-relationships</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/retail-sap-customers-using-tech-to-build-lifelong-relationships</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP customers in retail leverage tech to drive meaningful customer experiences, adopt sustainability, and position for success. Read more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/nrf</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-analytics</category>
            <category>product/sap-commerce-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[CallidusCloud to SAP: Evolution to Running Better Smarter and Faster]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/calliduscloud-to-sap-evolution</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/calliduscloud-to-sap-evolution</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is excited to help CallidusCloud customers make the strategic move to the SAP SuccessFactors portfolio. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sales-performance-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-hana</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central Payroll Natively Supports 50 Locales]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/sap-successfactors-employee-central-payroll-supports-50-locales</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/sap-successfactors-employee-central-payroll-supports-50-locales</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is thrilled to announce SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central Payroll natively supports 50 locales across the globe. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central Grows to 6,000 Customers]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/sap-successfactors-employee-central-6000-customers</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/sap-successfactors-employee-central-6000-customers</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is thrilled to announce more than 6,000 organizations have chosen SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central to elevate their core HR operations.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1dfaa5052208192ed8d56df80f5f16592b8c93bf7.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1dfaa5052208192ed8d56df80f5f16592b8c93bf7.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1dfaa5052208192ed8d56df80f5f16592b8c93bf7.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central Grows to 6,000 Customers" src="./media_1dfaa5052208192ed8d56df80f5f16592b8c93bf7.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-successfactors-employee-central-grows-to-6000-customers">SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central Grows to 6,000 Customers</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Today, SAP is thrilled to announce more than 6,000 organizations have chosen SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central, our cloud HRIS software, to help elevate their core HR operations. This milestone demonstrates strong momentum in the SAP SuccessFactors community, which includes leaders and business users that are driving strategies that put people at the center of business.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>People and culture are increasingly becoming some of the most critical aspects of an organization. It’s what attracts new talent to join and keeps current employees growing and developing. Whether that’s scaling up, diving into a new market segment, or pivoting to meet changing customer demands, having the right people in the right roles determines success.</p>
  <p>From midsize organizations to large enterprises, having a single view of employees across all countries is a differentiator. It’s no longer about just maintaining a system of record. It’s <em>the</em> foundation to manage the total workforce – from setting organizational goals to establishing the talent intelligence that’s needed to build a workforce that is agile and adaptable.</p>
  <p>Organizations of all sizes, industries, and regions use SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central to help improve experiences for managers and employees, automate compliance for more than 100 locales, manage benefits and absence management, and standardize processes across multiple locations. Here’s what some of our customers are saying:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>“SAP SuccessFactors is our people backbone. It provides the common processes, systems, and data that let us create engaging people experiences at scale.” – <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/customer-stories/nestle.html#:~:text=Nestl%C3%A9&#x27;s%20journey%20with%20SAP%20began,to%20workforce%20and%20talent%20management.">Giancarlo Pala, head of IT HR / Nestlé S.A.</a></li>
    <li>“With the SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central solution, the company now has a single HR and payroll system providing a single source of truth, instant access to employee data, automated approval workflows, and enhanced reporting – available on the go, anytime, anywhere.” – <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/customer-stories/emirates-fast-food-company.html">Binay Moktan, senior HR director, Emirates Fast Food Company LLC</a></li>
    <li>“The SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central solution, branded at Woodbridge as Teammate Central, supports the company’s core HR processes and provides teammates with intuitive, fast access to HR self-services. The solution’s localization capabilities support Woodbridge’s operations at 50 locations in more than 10 countries, while its position management feature helps smooth the plant acquisition process.” – <a href="https://www.sap.com/asset/dynamic/2022/11/e4f78c1e-4f7e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Peter Martin, vice president, Total Rewards, The Woodbridge Group</a></li>
    <li>“Using SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central, we have mitigated the need for manual monthly and quarterly data input efforts from our local HR teams and can now automatically generate reports whenever required with access to global workforce data.” – <a href="https://www.sap.com/asset/dynamic/2023/07/b65d2def-827e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Jing Yin, global HR strategy manager, OMRON Corporation</a></li>
  </ul>
  <p>Additional organizations, including <a href="/2023/09/versuni-hxm-cloud-erp-strong-data-foundation">Versuni</a>, <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/customer-stories/roehm.html">Röhm</a>, <a href="https://www.sap.com/asset/dynamic/2023/04/7a53dae4-6c7e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Purolator</a>, <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2022/01/88cc7a19-117e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Taylor’s Education Group</a>, and many more, have chosen SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central to help manage their workforce.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="streamline-core-hr-processes-with-cloud-hris-software-from-sap-successfactors">Streamline core HR processes with cloud HRIS software from SAP SuccessFactors</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/employee-central-hris.html">Discover how</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="continued-improvements-to-enhance-the-employee-experience">Continued Improvements to Enhance the Employee Experience</h2>
  <p>Since SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central was introduced over a decade ago, we have continued to adapt and innovate to help our customers meet the changing expectations of their employees and the rising demands from HR to deliver greater insights and data.</p>
  <p>Customers using SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central can have access to:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>A single foundation for HR, with consistent and standardized HR processes for over 200 countries and territories around the globe</li>
    <li>A proactive approach to worldwide regulatory compliance with localization delivered and maintained for more than 100 locales</li>
    <li>Self-service functionality to help support automation, improve data quality, and elevate HR service delivery with efficient, real-time processes</li>
    <li>A consumer-grade user experience with live insights to help make data-driven decisions</li>
  </ul>
  <p>The newest innovations in the <a href="/2023/10/sap-successfactors-second-half-2023-release">2H 2023 release</a> include:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Simplified self-services allow employees and managers to make updates directly from the SAP SuccessFactors home page. For example, employees can quickly update their chosen name and personal pronouns, while managers can initiate a transfer, promotion, location change, and more</li>
  </ul>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_13adf4267e650d0083629bd18a1e43de019fe85d1.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_13adf4267e650d0083629bd18a1e43de019fe85d1.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_13adf4267e650d0083629bd18a1e43de019fe85d1.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_13adf4267e650d0083629bd18a1e43de019fe85d1.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="576">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>Click to enlarge.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Self-service actions are integrated into the flow of work, including within Microsoft Teams, SAP SuccessFactors Work Zone, and Joule, SAP’s AI-powered copilot. With use cases across the SAP SuccessFactors Human Experience Management (HXM) Suite, such as the ability to clock in and out and to view pay statements from within Microsoft Teams, employees can quickly complete their most critical HR tasks without switching applications.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1586494fbb4371898380235e9a5d919f3e4e587f8.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1586494fbb4371898380235e9a5d919f3e4e587f8.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1586494fbb4371898380235e9a5d919f3e4e587f8.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Screenshot of SAP SuccessFactors task in Microsoft Teams" src="./media_1586494fbb4371898380235e9a5d919f3e4e587f8.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="576">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>Click to enlarge.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Learn more about the latest <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/innovations.html">SAP SuccessFactors product innovations</a> and visit the <a href="https://www.sap.com/events/successconnect/virtual.html?campaigncode=CRM-YI23-HXM-2055448&#x26;source=text-glo-SAPNews">SuccessConnect Virtual</a> event site for a replay of the keynote, expert sessions, and other on-demand content.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Maryann Abbajay is chief revenue officer at SAP SuccessFactors.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-employee-central</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Coles Reimagines Volume Hiring with AI and Automation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/coles-reimagines-volume-hiring-with-ai-and-automation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/coles-reimagines-volume-hiring-with-ai-and-automation</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Coles uses an AI-powered solution integrated with SAP SuccessFactors to help revolutionize its hiring process and gain speed and efficiency.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_149ed3b06f07dcdc3485b441db14e19620bea42c6.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_149ed3b06f07dcdc3485b441db14e19620bea42c6.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_149ed3b06f07dcdc3485b441db14e19620bea42c6.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Coles Reimagines Volume Hiring with AI and Automation" src="./media_149ed3b06f07dcdc3485b441db14e19620bea42c6.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="coles-reimagines-volume-hiring-with-ai-and-automation">Coles Reimagines Volume Hiring with AI and Automation</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><a href="https://www.colesgroup.com.au/home/">Coles Group</a>, one of Australia’s most trusted and iconic brands, is steadfast in delivering on its purpose to help Australians eat and live better every day. Through its core business as a full-service supermarket retailer, Coles engages with millions of customers every week in its 860 supermarkets throughout Australia. The group’s other areas of business include its Click &#x26; Collect online platform, network of liquor stores, and financial services with nearly 1,000 additional retail outlets.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Guided by the organization’s clear <a href="https://colescareers.com.au/au/en/culture">vision, purpose, and strategy</a>, Coles’ team of 120,000 employees is dedicated to making a difference in the lives of customers and the local communities it serves.</p>
  <p>In fiscal year 2020/21, Coles Group hired nearly 30,000 people to deliver on its business needs. Mike Virgo, head of Talent Acquisition for Coles Group, said this hiring volume was necessary to make sure the company was “positioned well to support our customers.”</p>
  <p>The business environment, however, dramatically shifted as the public health crisis of the pandemic unfolded, resulting in repeated lockdowns and restrictions. As a neighborhood retailer dependent on in-person interaction to deliver most of its services, Coles found its workforce impacted by the pandemic. Faced with supply chain disruptions, panic buying behaviors by consumers, high employee absenteeism, and increased turnover, Coles urgently needed to step up its volume and pace of hiring to support its customers.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="create-ai-powered-experiences-that-drive-real-competitive-advantage-with-sap-successfactors">Create AI-powered experiences that drive real competitive advantage with SAP SuccessFactors</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“Around 2020-2021, we started to experience one of the most significant shifts in the employment market we’d ever seen,” Virgo said in a <a href="https://go3.events.sap.com/successconnect/virtual/2023/reg/flow/sap/sc23/catalog/page/catalog/session/1693098679863001ykJ6">session</a> at <a href="https://www.sap.com/events/successconnect/virtual.html?campaigncode=CRM-YI23-HXM-2055448&#x26;source=text-glo-SAPNews">SuccessConnect Virtual</a>. “It started to create huge challenges for organizations around the world – around how we attract, retain, and hire talent.”</p>
  <h2 id="catalyst-for-change-and-a-new-way-of-working">Catalyst for Change and a New Way of Working</h2>
  <p>To meet pressing business demands, Coles doubled its hiring volume from 30,000 to 60,000 people and increased recruitment advertising spend by a factor of three. Its talent acquisition team grew proportionally to manage the increased workload – but then labored under manual transactional activities that slowed processing times. As a result of the huge strain, variability in the candidate and hiring manager experience became noticeable.</p>
  <p>Due to the volume of work, Coles looked for ways to evolve its system to create more speed, efficiency, and scalability. With a list of criteria, Coles began to review technology solutions on the market to find one that could support its vision for a new way of working. “We wanted to reimagine how we recruit for our stores,” Virgo said. “We needed automation and AI to remove a lot of the manual work in our systems. We wanted to create more consistency and uplift the experiences we were giving our candidates and our hiring managers. And ultimately, [the solution] needed to drive commercial benefit for us.”</p>
  <p>As a key requirement, the new solution needed to integrate with <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/what-is-hxm-suite.html">SAP SuccessFactors Human Experience Management (HXM) Suite</a>. In 2020, as part of an organization-wide <a href="/australia/2021/09/08/how-coles-group-is-transforming-hr-during-the-global-pandemic">digital transformation</a> that introduced SAP S/4HANA and SAP Ariba solutions, Coles modernized its HR and payroll processing, replacing a patchwork of outdated systems with SAP SuccessFactors solutions. It became the first organization in the southern hemisphere to launch all modules of the SAP SuccessFactors portfolio in one go. With all HR processes unified on a single platform, Coles benefits from having a single source of truth for people data that is accurate and available in real time for the entire organization.</p>
  <h2 id="two-way-integration-ensures-single-source-of-truth-in-data">Two-Way Integration Ensures Single Source of Truth in Data</h2>
  <p>To help with the project, Coles chose <a href="https://www.phenom.com/">Phenom</a>, an SAP partner whose AI-powered Intelligent Talent Experience platform provides two-way integration with SAP SuccessFactors solutions. Virgo said the two-way integration “allows us to have a holistic view of the candidates that progress through the process, no matter whether the team is operating in Phenom or SAP SuccessFactors, and it allows SAP SuccessFactors to be our single source of truth.”</p>
  <p>There are several key benefits of Phenom’s solution at Coles. One is candidate attraction and engagement, which is achieved primarily through the Coles career site and chatbot. Another is recruiter automation and interview management, which provides automation and process efficiencies from when a job requisition is created in SAP SuccessFactors solutions and replicated into Phenom until a hiring manager chooses a candidate for the job. Once a candidate is chosen, the two-way integration enables the HR team to access the data in SAP SuccessFactors solutions and complete all compliance aspects, such as working rights, contract generation, and onboarding.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-how-phenom-can-compliment-sap-successfactors-recruiting">Learn how Phenom can compliment SAP SuccessFactors Recruiting</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://store.sap.com/dcp/en/product/display-2001007992_live_v1">Find out</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The Coles team gains additional efficiencies in its onboarding programs through the application of robotic process automation (RPA) powered by two bots that work in the background: <em>Ashbotty</em> processes the working rights and <em>Usain Bot</em> processes onboarding and manages pending recruits. “They take a lot of the transactional, manual work that we used to have team members doing. It can do that quickly, accurately, and it can do that 24/7 – which is particularly important for us as a seven-days-a-week business,” Virgo said.</p>
  <h2 id="ai-powered-experiences-for-candidates-and-recruiters">AI-Powered Experiences for Candidates and Recruiters</h2>
  <p>Coles reimagined the candidate experience to launch a modern, tech-enabled career site – which has been chosen as a two-time winner of Australia’s Best Careers Site. The site includes an AI-powered chatbot to guide candidates as they look for information, search relevant job postings, and submit their applications. It also includes Coles’ Expression of Interest, always-on advertising that drives the growth of its talent pool and advances its talent marketing by reducing the need to advertise every role. A Hosted Apply process, facilitated by integrations with Phenom, presents a consistent candidate experience and increases the conversion rate on applications.</p>
  <p>Phenom AI Scheduling, a key part of Coles’ hiring experience, enables candidates to book themselves an available interview slot and automates the coordination of hiring team calendars. The new solution provides a fully mobile-enabled experience to meet the demands of candidates for an omni-channel, real-time experience where they can learn, read, and apply for jobs where and when they want.</p>
  <p>Inundated by nearly 1 million applications each year to review, Coles also took steps to elevate the recruiter experience and increase the speed and accuracy of candidate screening and job matching. It implemented Phenom Fit Score, an AI-powered feature that assesses a candidate’s suitability for an open role, based on location and optimal travel distances, availability, and working rights; then, assigns a fit score and surfaces the most closely matched candidates to the recruiters. In addition, the new solution empowers in-store managers to collaborate with recruiters to review candidates and make quick hiring decisions with confidence.</p>
  <h2 id="talent-pools-grow-with-improvements-to-hiring-speed-and-efficiency">Talent Pools Grow with Improvements to Hiring Speed and Efficiency</h2>
  <p>With the new augmented solution, Coles is experiencing tangible benefits across multiple categories and key metrics for success: time-to-fill is down six days; time-to-hire is down two days, which is impressive considering candidates can book the in-store interview up to two weeks in advance; and advertising spend is down 50%.</p>
  <p>Most notably for Coles as a people-centric organization is the development of its talent pool, now numbering 2 million potential candidates. It achieves an 85% application conversion rate on up to 1 million applications per year. Through its <a href="https://www.colesgroup.com.au/media-releases/?page=coles-group-ranked-1-for-recruitment-of-aussies-with-disabilities">commitment</a> to be a safe, inclusive, and diverse workplace, Coles has applied the new solution to provide greater accessibility for more diverse candidates, resulting in an increase of 24% more hiring for people who identify as having a disability.</p>
  <p>Virgo said that the talent acquisition team will continue to evolve its solution and assess more opportunities for AI and automation to bring value to the recruitment process. Although these technologies are not cure-alls for every recruitment scenario, they can save recruiting teams precious time and resources to focus on more high-touch interactions further down the recruiting funnel. In sharing lessons learned, Virgo noted, “I think the important call out is the level of automation you can inject in your process will likely diminish as the seniority, complexity, and requirements of your roles increase because they are likely to be more high touch, perhaps need more interpretation or judgment calls from your recruiters to identify who the right talent is for your organization.”</p>
  <p>Watch <a href="https://www.sap.com/events/successconnect/virtual.html?campaigncode=CRM-YI23-HXM-2055448&#x26;source=text-glo-SAPNews">SuccessConnect Virtual</a> on demand.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="follow-sap-news-on-linkedin-to-stay-up-to-date">Follow SAP News on LinkedIn to stay up-to-date</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/automation</category>
            <category>industry/consumer-goods-cpg</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>news-tag/recruiting</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
            <category>sap-event/successconnect</category>
            <category>news-tag/talent-acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Built-In Support Coverage Extended for SAP SuccessFactors Solutions]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/built-in-support-for-sap-successfactors</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/built-in-support-for-sap-successfactors</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is now expanding Built-In Support into SAP SuccessFactors solutions, so customers can access support right in the solution. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/built-in-support</category>
            <category>news-tag/real-time-support</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Leveraging SAP SuccessFactors Solutions: Five Ways User Experience Drives DEI&B Success]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/five-ways-sap-successfactors-ux-drives-deib</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/five-ways-sap-successfactors-ux-drives-deib</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP SuccessFactor's focus on UX helps businesses advance DEI&B by offering an interface that can address employee needs in the flow of work.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-employee-central</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-learning</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-performance-goals</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-workforce-analytics</category>
            <category>news-tag/ux</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ATS Connects HR Processes to Build a Future-Ready Workforce]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/ats-connects-hr-processes-future-ready-workforce</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/ats-connects-hr-processes-future-ready-workforce</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[To modernize its core HR and talent management systems, ATS chose SAP SuccessFactors and its next-generation cloud HR technology. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Realizing Employee Potential with HR Technology]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/realizing-employee-potential-with-hr-technology</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/realizing-employee-potential-with-hr-technology</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[HR leaders can improve employee potential practices and enable unbiased decision-making processes with HR technology. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-opportunity-marketplace</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-performance-goals</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Six Ways to Prepare Future-Ready People Managers with SAP SuccessFactors Solutions]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/six-ways-prepare-people-managers-sap-successfactors</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/six-ways-prepare-people-managers-sap-successfactors</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Create engaging experiences, boost productivity, and enhance results by empowering people managers with SAP SuccessFactors solutions.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_102238c9ba8fcf28bb39535e2bf9b2193b8900cdc.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_102238c9ba8fcf28bb39535e2bf9b2193b8900cdc.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_102238c9ba8fcf28bb39535e2bf9b2193b8900cdc.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Six Ways to Prepare Future-Ready People Managers with SAP SuccessFactors Solutions" src="./media_102238c9ba8fcf28bb39535e2bf9b2193b8900cdc.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="six-ways-to-prepare-future-ready-people-managers-with-sap-successfactors-solutions">Six Ways to Prepare Future-Ready People Managers with SAP SuccessFactors Solutions</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>People managers have the potential to make or break the employee experience at an organization. They are responsible for understanding the demands of the business and motivating their team members to meet those requirements. However, the people manager role is evolving due to three crucial factors – hybrid and remote work, automation, and elevated employee expectations.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>To help understand this evolution of the people manager role, the <a href="https://community.sap.com/topics/successfactors/growth-insights-research/growth-insights-team">Growth &#x26; Insights team</a> for SAP SuccessFactors hosted interviews with 31 HR leaders from SAP customer organizations and conducted a survey of 731 people managers and 716 individual contributors from around the globe. Based on the research findings, below are six ways organizations can improve current people managers’ performance and experience with SAP SuccessFactors solutions.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-the-full-research-report">Read the full research report</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/dg/people-management/index.html">Check it out</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="utilize-co-leadership-models">Utilize Co-Leadership Models</h2>
  <p>Organizations look to people managers to execute important initiatives and people practices, leading to an overload of responsibilities. Implementing co-leadership structures, even for a short period of time, can reduce a people manager’s role overload and provide individual contributors with a valuable experiential learning opportunity.</p>
  <p>One way to provide an experiential opportunity is through <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2023/05/bc7c3ca3-727e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">dynamic teams</a>, advanced capabilities available as part of SAP SuccessFactors solutions that can help create and manage cross-functional teams that exist beyond traditional hierarchies. <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2023/05/bc7c3ca3-727e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Statistics</a> reported that 66% of employees who had participated in a dynamic team felt a positive impact on their career, leading to higher engagement. Using dynamic teams can help organizations utilize co-leadership models for projects while also accessing individual contributor potential and incorporating those insights into future succession plans.</p>
  <h2 id="update-people-manager-job-descriptions">Update People Manager Job Descriptions</h2>
  <p>Many organizations have not updated their formal job descriptions for people managers to accurately reflect changes to their roles, leading to unclear performance expectations and ineffective systems for developing and selecting people managers. One way organizations can streamline this process is through <a href="/2023/10/new-sap-successfactors-ai-innovations-successconnect">generative artificial intelligence (AI) in the SAP SuccessFactors Recruiting solution</a>. Hiring managers and recruiters can fine-tune job descriptions with generative AI, which allows them to incorporate supplementary content, identify biased language, and help ensure alignment with business requirements. Instead of starting from scratch every time a new position is created or requirements are updated, recruiters and hiring managers can use AI to help draft job descriptions faster and stay in their normal flow of work. And more importantly, the final content is more meaningful, inclusive, and competitive – presenting a clear and accurate view of the role to attract a larger pool of qualified and interested candidates.</p>
  <h2 id="rethink-career-architecture-and-pathways-to-advancement">Rethink Career Architecture and Pathways to Advancement</h2>
  <p>Without other options for growing, gaining status, or increasing compensation, employees will seek people management roles even if they are not suitable for or interested in this type of role. Developing alternative pathways for advancement, such as specialist career paths, for high-performing individual contributors ensures that employees are entering people manager roles for the right reason – to manage people.</p>
  <p>Sharing career architectures more broadly can also improve managers’ awareness of internal mobility opportunities, which they cited as a top challenge. Talent marketplaces, like the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/opportunity-marketplace.html">SAP SuccessFactors Opportunity Marketplace</a> solution, can improve visibility into development and growth opportunities within the organization. It can provide AI-driven personalized recommendations for learning, mentors, internal roles, and dynamic teams. This allows employees to have experiential learning opportunities and can provide them alternate career paths.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="powerful-cloud-hr-software-empowers-individuals-to-reach-their-full-potential">Powerful cloud HR software empowers individuals to reach their full potential</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="implement-succession-planning-for-all">Implement Succession Planning for All</h2>
  <p>Everyone agrees that people manager roles should become more exclusive, but that also means talent pools will become shallower. Implementing succession planning at all levels of the organization allows organizations to identify “hidden” people manager talent. When developing succession plans, consider that a people manager does not always need to be replaced with an existing people manager – and that a people manager’s next role does not always need to be in management. The <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/succession-development.html">SAP SuccessFactors Succession &#x26; Development</a> solution can make this process easier by helping employees expand their skills and advance their careers with visibility into continuous development dialogue, mentoring opportunities, and AI-powered career planning. It can also optimize succession planning, making it scalable to place the right people in the right roles and helping to secure the “hidden” people manager talent.</p>
  <h2 id="create-a-community-for-people-managers">Create a Community for People Managers</h2>
  <p>People managers consider staying engaged, feeling included, and managing their well-being to be top challenges. Creating a people manager community provides this crucial workforce segment with social support, which research has shown to be a positive driver of the people manger experience. This also offers the organization a clear channel to host two-way communication with people managers. One way to foster a community for people managers is to leverage the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/workzone-hr.html">SAP SuccessFactors Work Zone</a> solution, which is a personalized digital workspace that helps support and encourage collaboration. People managers can create their own community and connect with each other, allowing for more engagement, sharing of best practices, and improvement in the overall employee experience.</p>
  <h2 id="leverage-technology">Leverage Technology</h2>
  <p><a href="/topics/human-resources">Cloud HR technology</a> can help support the strategies recommended here and solve many of managers’ most pressing challenges. With SAP SuccessFactors solutions, organizations can put their people at the center of everything and create AI-powered experiences that can support current people managers while using talent intelligence to help uncover and develop the managers of tomorrow.</p>
  <p>As the expectations of people managers from both employees and organizations undergo constant evolution, the role of people manager will increasingly become more “people-centric” – focusing on support, fostering development, and nurturing a positive culture. It’s important that organizations use the right HR technology to deliver engaging employee experiences, increase productivity, and drive better business outcomes.</p>
  <p>For additional insights on the evolution of the people manager role, read the full report, “<a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/dg/people-management/index.html">Six Best Practices to Prepare People Managers for Today and Tomorrow</a>.”</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Christina Russo is global director of Solution Marketing at SAP SuccessFactors.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-opportunity-marketplace</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-recruiting</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-work-zone</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>