<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/csr/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA["Source from Ukraine" Initiative: The S Stands for Solidarity]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/source-from-ukraine-initiative-s-for-solidarity</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/source-from-ukraine-initiative-s-for-solidarity</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The "Source from Ukraine" initiative aims to activate procurement spend to support Ukrainian suppliers in rebuilding their businesses.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/csr</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/ukraine</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP's “Source from Ukraine” Initiative Boosts Business and Social Responsibility]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/source-from-ukraine-initiative-boosts-business-social-responsibility</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/source-from-ukraine-initiative-boosts-business-social-responsibility</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The "Source from Ukraine" initiative aims to activate procurement spend to support Ukrainian suppliers in rebuilding their businesses.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1be90b8393bfeb6a3a3bdc9a317fa62a7be1e9acb.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1be90b8393bfeb6a3a3bdc9a317fa62a7be1e9acb.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1be90b8393bfeb6a3a3bdc9a317fa62a7be1e9acb.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP’s “Source from Ukraine” Initiative Boosts Business and Social Responsibility" src="./media_1be90b8393bfeb6a3a3bdc9a317fa62a7be1e9acb.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="saps-source-from-ukraine-initiative-boosts-business-and-social-responsibility">SAP’s “Source from Ukraine” Initiative Boosts Business and Social Responsibility</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>SAP’s “Source from Ukraine” initiative, launched in March 2023, has a clear goal: to increase spend with Ukrainian companies while also generating business benefits for SAP. This shows SAP’s deep understanding of social responsibility as an integral part of its commitment to a sustainable future.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The initiative aims to activate <a href="/topics/procurement">procurement</a> spend as a means to support Ukrainian suppliers in rebuilding their businesses. Beyond sourcing for quality goods and services, SAP has a focus on integrating ESG (environmental, social, and governance) principles into decision-making as is standard with its procurement policy.</p>
  <p>It highlights SAP’s commitment not only to sourcing products from Ukraine, but also to promoting social change.</p>
  <h2 id="built-in-sustainability">Built-In Sustainability</h2>
  <p>In implementing the initiative to attract more suppliers from Ukraine, SAP initially focused on the IT sector and conducted a rigorous selection process. So far, suppliers, including industry leaders like Softserve, Unicsoft, and Luxoft, have been selected. SAP’s commitment extends beyond services to include product areas, where notable Ukrainian companies producing innovative environmentally sustainable products have been discovered.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-is-powering-equitable-access-to-economic-opportunity-education-and-employment-and-the-circular-economy">SAP is powering equitable access to economic opportunity, education and employment, and the circular economy</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/our-values/csr.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>At SAP Spend Connect Live in Vienna, Austria, held in October 2023, Ukrainian manufacturers Rekava, Mol’far Tea, and Releaf Paper showcased their sustainable and innovative products. Rekava, for example, specializes in producing biodegradable candles made from recycled coffee grounds, while Mol’far focuses on minimalism and ethical environmental practices in tea production. Releaf Paper is the world’s first manufacturer of paper made from fallen leaves, promoting sustainable products such as paper bags. By supporting these unique Ukrainian companies, SAP is not only contributing to the economic reconstruction of the country, but also sustainability efforts.</p>
  <p>One of SAP’s tier one suppliers, ABC Premium, has taken an important step by offering Rekava candles within its purchasing catalog, available to SAP employees on the SAP Ariba Buying solution.</p>
  <h2 id="strong-alliances-for-reconstruction">Strong Alliances for Reconstruction</h2>
  <p>At the outset of the project, the NGO Impact Ukraine helped SAP connect with Ukrainian suppliers. It focuses on microfinance, procurement, and recruitment from Ukraine. The collaboration is facilitated by the voluntary engagement of professionals from the technology, healthcare, and finance sectors. With Impact Ukraine’s support, SAP and other organizations can further advance their goals regarding procurement from Ukraine.</p>
  <p>SAP’s commitment to promoting innovation, sustainability, and economic growth through partnerships with Ukrainian companies not only fulfills its aspirations for procurement with purpose, but also contributes to making the world a better place.</p>
  <h2 id="helping-the-world-run-better">Helping the World Run Better</h2>
  <p>The “Source from Ukraine” initiative builds on global efforts to integrate social enterprises and diverse suppliers into SAP purchasing opportunities. Beyond SAP’s own internal purchasing efforts, the SAP Corporate Social Responsibility (SAP CSR) team is also investing in social and sustainable procurement ecosystems alongside public, private, and social sector partners like the European Commission, Deloitte, World Economic Forum’s Global Alliance for Social Entrepreneurship, and Social Enterprise World Forum’s People and Planet First verification.</p>
  <p>Consider that US$5.3 trillion in annual commerce is transacted on <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-network.html">SAP Business Network</a>. If we can help create a small shift in procurement spend to organizations prioritizing people and planet like Releaf Paper, we could collectively increase investment in sustainable development in a way that is not possible through corporate philanthropy alone. To join our efforts, please e-mail: <a href="mailto:csr-global@sap.com?subject=Please%20Share%20More%20Collective%20Social%20Procurement%20Investments%20and%20How%20to%20Get%20Involved">csr-global@sap.com</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Elena Parker is chief revenue officer for Intelligent Spend and Business Network, MEE, at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-sap-news-delivered-to-your-inbox-once-a-week">Get the latest SAP news delivered to your inbox once a week</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/nl/sap-news-center-newsletter/index.html">Sign up today</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/csr</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/ukraine</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP CSR's eBook Celebrates a Year of Global Impact]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/sap-csr-ebook-celebrates-global-impact</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/sap-csr-ebook-celebrates-global-impact</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The impact of SAP CSR in 2023 is a testament to the power of collective action and shared vision. Read to find out how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1aa60aead41f035043e44cbfe1f53c8c65e859485.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1aa60aead41f035043e44cbfe1f53c8c65e859485.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1aa60aead41f035043e44cbfe1f53c8c65e859485.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP CSR’s eBook Celebrates a Year of Global Impact" src="./media_1aa60aead41f035043e44cbfe1f53c8c65e859485.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-csrs-ebook-celebrates-a-year-of-global-impact">SAP CSR’s eBook Celebrates a Year of Global Impact</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Reflecting on the past year, one event stands out vividly in my memory: the Social Enterprises World Forum (SEWF) in Amsterdam, the Netherlands. For those unfamiliar, imagine a global assembly where more than 1,500 entrepreneurs from 82 countries dedicated to societal and environmental missions come together. These enterprises prioritize people and the planet, reinvesting their profits to advance their respective causes. Witnessing the energy and innovation in Amsterdam was a powerful reminder of why SAP has emphasized social entrepreneurship for the second consecutive year.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>It makes me proud to think about the 676 SAP colleagues who, in 2023, participated in our pro bono consulting programs, offering their expertise to these visionary social entrepreneurs. As in previous years, this collaboration has proven mutually beneficial, with 74% of our employees reporting a positive, lasting impact on their careers. Furthermore, 96% of the supported organizations and 77% of their beneficiaries have seen significant improvements. These numbers speak volumes about the shared value of our engagement.</p>
  <p>But the 2023 SEWF wasn’t just a personal highlight; it marked the beginning of another significant milestone. We announced our investment in the <strong>Social Enterprise People and Planet First Verification</strong> with Good Market and SEWF. This initiative aims to set a global standard for recognizing organizations prioritizing social and environmental impacts. Social enterprises can now also identify themselves on SAP Business Network, the world’s largest B2B commerce platform. This breakthrough can make it easier for these businesses to explore new business-to-business opportunities while also helping SAP customers achieve their goals of being more environmentally and socially responsible. Saying it’s a win-win situation is a bit cliché, but in this case it’s actually true.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-is-powering-equitable-access-to-economic-opportunity-education-and-employment-and-the-circular-economy">SAP is powering equitable access to economic opportunity, education and employment, and the circular economy</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/our-values/csr.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Working with SEWF shows how much we believe in working together and driving towards collective impact. I’ve said it before and I’ll say it again: we can’t do this by ourselves. Working with others is the key to driving the kind of systemic change our world needs. This idea is a big part of what we stand for at SAP, and is at the heart of our corporate social responsibility (<a href="/topics/csr">CSR</a>) strategy.</p>
  <p>This idea of working together really comes to life in our collaboration with <strong>UNICEF and Generation Unlimited</strong>. In 2023 – the fourth year of our partnership – we set out to make a real difference by not just developing the skills of young people but also finding jobs in the SAP ecosystem. Launching the SAP Educate to Employ program is a big step in that direction. Helping 25 young people get jobs with SAP in each of our pilot countries – Nigeria, Kenya, South Africa, and the Philippines – might not sound like a lot, but it’s a huge deal for each of those young people. For them, it’s a gateway to a sustainable livelihood, offering them not just gainful employment but a chance to build a career, achieve financial stability, and make meaningful contributions to their communities and the broader world. It’s about unlocking their potential and enabling them to participate in the digital and green economy. By the end of the year, we saw amazing results. While more than 2,500 had already passed the aptitude test, over 1,000 young people in Africa finished our “Boost Your Career with SAP Skills” course and more than 500 got through the first big part of their training.</p>
  <p>But, what’s a year recap without some high-level numbers? Let’s dive into some impressive <strong>numbers from 2023</strong>. More than 20,000 of our SAP colleagues volunteered over 140,000 hours. Our initiatives reached over 2.8 million young people – almost half girls – and supported over 41,000 teachers. Our partner network reached 1 billion people in over 140 countries. These stats are just the tip of the iceberg, showing our big reach and impact together with our partners.</p>
  <p>Building on this, our signature partnerships with Africa Code Week, Meet and Code, and Latin Code Week have always been at the heart of our achievements. As we handed over these initiatives in 2023, we took a moment to reflect and evaluate Africa Code Week and Latin Code Week outcomes more deeply. For instance, by empowering 14.6 million participants with the education, knowledge, and ICT skills needed to participate in the digital future, <strong>Africa Code Week</strong> has increased the likelihood that beneficiaries will realize higher earnings during their working lives. Common Good Marketplace estimates that Africa Code Week catalyzed up to US$1 billion in social value for program participants between 2015 and 2022 based on future increased income.</p>
  <p>As we close the chapter on 2023 and look ahead, the journey we’ve embarked upon at SAP CSR is a testament to the power of collective action and shared vision. The stories, numbers, and outcomes shared in our eBook reflect our commitment to making a meaningful difference. <a href="https://d.dam.sap.com/a/Gnggenc/SAP%20CSR%20in%20Review%202023.pdf?rc=10">Read the full eBook.</a></p>
  <p>Thank you to everyone who has been a part of this journey. Your passion, dedication, and commitment are what drive us forward.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Alexandra van der Ploeg is global head of Corporate Social Responsibility at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="follow-sap-news-on-linkedin-to-stay-up-to-date">Follow SAP News on LinkedIn to stay up-to-date</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news">Connect with us</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>non-sap-event/africa-code week</category>
            <category>news-tag/csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/generation-unlimited</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/social-entrepreneurship</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Showing Up in the World Through Pro Bono Consulting]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/showing-up-through-pro-bono-consulting</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/showing-up-through-pro-bono-consulting</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Product Engineering and SAP CSR joined forces to leverage pro bono consulting to develop the next generation of SAP engineering leaders.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/purpose</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reskilling for the Green Transition]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/reskilling-for-the-green-transition</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/reskilling-for-the-green-transition</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[An inclusive green transition could create millions of jobs in the next decade but requires significant investments in reskilling.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/climate-action</category>
            <category>news-tag/climate-change</category>
            <category>news-tag/csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/people-sustainability</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP CSR Launches Third Edition of eBook, Celebrating a Year of Global Impact]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/sap-csr-launches-ebook-third-edition</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/sap-csr-launches-ebook-third-edition</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Corporate Social Responsibility (SAP CSR) launched the third edition of its annual eBook, "Helping the World Run Better – Together."]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-social-sabbatical</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Power of Change Activists: SAP x ChangemakerXchange]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/01/power-of-change-activists-changemakerxchange</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/01/power-of-change-activists-changemakerxchange</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP supported a North America-focused gender and climate action summit with ChangemakerXchange. Read to learn more about the event.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/climate-action</category>
            <category>news-tag/csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/gender-equality</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[What You Didn’t Know You Needed to Know About Entrepreneurship]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/01/what-you-need-to-know-entrepreneurship</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/01/what-you-need-to-know-entrepreneurship</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP's Cindy Fagen spoke with Anastasia Kiku of Reusables about her startup experience and expertise in entrepreneurship. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/entrepreneurship</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-canada</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-labs-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-io</category>
            <category>news-tag/social-entrepreneurship</category>
            <category>news-tag/startups</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Lasting Impact of SAP’s Early College High School Program]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/impact-of-sap-early-college-high-school-program</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/impact-of-sap-early-college-high-school-program</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A survey from SAP and Digital Promise reveals the lasting impact of Early College High School program participants in pursuing STEM.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/education</category>
            <category>industry/higher-education-research</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Organizations Measure the Real Impact of Social Enterprise Programs]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/measure-real-impact-of-social-enterprise-programs</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/measure-real-impact-of-social-enterprise-programs</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Social enterprise programs that educate and train disadvantaged people to address challenges are a force for positive change. Learn how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/circular-economy</category>
            <category>news-tag/climate-change</category>
            <category>news-tag/csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>news-tag/entrepreneurship</category>
            <category>news-tag/esg</category>
            <category>news-tag/pyxera-global</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-social-sabbatical</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Drive Key Business Outcomes through People Sustainability]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/drive-key-business-outcomes-people-sustainability</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/drive-key-business-outcomes-people-sustainability</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[HR has both the opportunity and responsibility to ensure that people are at the center of work. Learn more about people sustainability.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/mental-health-well-being</category>
            <category>news-tag/people-sustainability</category>
            <category>news-tag/well-being-at-work</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Top Five Benefits of Social Sabbaticals]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/top-five-benefits-of-sap-social-sabbatical</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/top-five-benefits-of-sap-social-sabbatical</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Through the SAP Social Sabbatical program, employees experience many benefits, personally and professionally, and gain lifelong skills.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/purpose</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-social-sabbatical</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Retailers Can Trigger Sustainability Growth before Reaching Their Tipping Point]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/04/how-retailers-trigger-sustainability-growth</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/04/how-retailers-trigger-sustainability-growth</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[By integrating sustainability, retailers can better navigate fast-approaching tipping points while performing better than those that do not.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/circular-economy</category>
            <category>news-tag/climate-action</category>
            <category>news-tag/csr</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Buy Social This Holiday Season and All Throughout the Year]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/buy-social-holiday-season</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/buy-social-holiday-season</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Buy social this holiday season, with a gift guide focused on social enterprises. Consider the impact of how you spend.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10aa4e45575e810d5d5561e25409461ec79e91e6d.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10aa4e45575e810d5d5561e25409461ec79e91e6d.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_10aa4e45575e810d5d5561e25409461ec79e91e6d.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Buy Social This Holiday Season and All Throughout the Year" src="./media_10aa4e45575e810d5d5561e25409461ec79e91e6d.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="buy-social-this-holiday-season-and-all-throughout-the-year">Buy Social This Holiday Season and All Throughout the Year</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>The ways in which we choose to spend our money can be powerful, especially this holiday season. Adobe estimates that consumers will spend more than <a href="https://www.zdnet.com/article/us-consumers-to-spend-209-billion-online-during-holiday-season-910-billion-to-be-spent-globally/">$910 billion</a> this season, adding to the $4 trillion spent online during 2021.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>What if we could attribute a portion of that spend to organizations that are delivering quality goods and services alongside positive economic, social, and environmental impact? If you knew where to look would you change the way you spend for good?</p>
  <p>SAP has spent more than a decade building capacity for and working alongside social businesses. In 2020 our commitment to the sector reached new heights by embracing the power of our own spend to accelerate these organizations’ positive global impact. With our social procurement initiative <a href="/2020/10/sap-launches-55by25-purposeful-procurement">5 &#x26; 5 by ’25</a>, we have committed to a shift of five percent in addressable procurement spend with social enterprises and diverse businesses by 2025. With the help of our incredible partners, buying social is something everyone can do. And together, our proven buying power is even more influential than any one company can be alone.</p>
  <p>Individual purchasing decisions around the holidays, or any time through the year, play an important role in supporting social enterprises to continue their work in their respective communities. Whether an organization employs people from marginalized groups, like <a href="https://www.theartfaculty.sg/en-sg/brands/the-animal-project-sg">The Animal Project</a>, or discovers new and creative ways to reduce waste streams, like <a href="https://www.soulbottles.de/">Soulbottles</a> — and everything in between! — your support makes a difference.</p>
  <p>Our money has a greater impact when spent with a business that is centered around a higher purpose.</p>
  <p>To help you on your journey to buy social this holiday season, we have compiled a list of social enterprises and social gifting guides from around the world – there is something for everyone here. While this is not an exhaustive collection of all the wonderful social enterprises where you can make purchases, here are a few places to start.</p>
  <p>Social media is another great place to find businesses making an impact via searching hashtags like #buysocial, #sustainableliving, and #ecofriendly.</p>
  <p>This list also provides some inspiration from businesses doing incredible work, many of which are part of the SAP ecosystem.</p>
  <p>If any social enterprises or gift guides you love are not listed here, tag @SAP4Good on Twitter, Instagram, or Facebook. Let’s build a collective list of businesses to support that truly represent the meaning of the holiday spirit.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <table>
          <thead>
            <tr>
              <th colspan="2">Promo</th>
            </tr>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td>
                <h3 id="video-what-is-5--5-by-25">Video: What is 5 &#x26; 5 by ‘25?</h3>
              </td>
              <td><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/purpose-and-sustainability/social-responsibility/social-entrepreneurship.html?video=2ac819f2-c97d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff#buysocial">Learn more</a></strong></td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
        <h2 id="global-reach">Global Reach</h2>
        <ul>
          <li><a href="https://www.giftsforgood.com/pages/our-impact">Gifts for Good</a> products support the work of over 40 nonprofits and social enterprises in 19 states and 65 countries around the globe—in Africa, Asia, Central and South America, North America, &#x26; Europe.</li>
          <li><a href="https://www.goodmarket.global/">Good Market</a>: An online marketplace and curated community platform for purpose driven businesses. Free to set up a profile for your social enterprise.</li>
          <li>For the U.S., Canada, and the UK, our partner UNICEF has created a <a href="https://www.market.unicefusa.org/">holiday gift guide</a>, where every hand-crafted artisanal gift purchased send lifesaving supplies to children.</li>
        </ul>
        <h2 id="africa">Africa</h2>
        <p><strong>Kenya</strong></p>
        <ul>
          <li><a href="https://sandstormkenya.com/">Sandstorm</a> began by creating canvas bags using leftover tent fabric. They are driven by the Swahili proverb “Haraka haraka haina baraka”, meaning “hurry, hurry has no blessing” or more directly “haste makes waste”. Today, bags are made from local, sustainable materials, and are sewn by people, not machines.</li>
          <li><a href="https://oceansoleonline.com/">Ocean Sole</a> makes art from foam flip flops collected from Kenyan beaches. Ocean Sole removes trash from the oceans, coastlines and makes art to support marine conservation, whilst creating employment opportunities in high-impact areas.</li>
        </ul>
        <p><strong>South Africa</strong></p>
        <ul>
          <li><a href="https://www.mungo.co.za/about-us/">Mungo</a> creates contemporary woven goods from tradition weaving methods. At Mungo, they center people, their livelihoods, and their vision at the heart of what they do.</li>
        </ul>
        <p><strong>Tanzania</strong></p>
        <ul>
          <li><a href="https://www.neemacrafts.com/shop.php">Neema Crafts</a> provides training and employment opportunities for over 120 people with disabilities in the Iringa region of Tanzania. It also aims to change negative attitudes towards people with disabilities in the local society. Products include home décor and accessories.</li>
          <li><a href="https://www.womencraft.org/shop-in-tanzania">WomenCraft</a> is a collection of artisan home décor pieces and accessories made by local women. WomenCraft’s mission is to bring women together in the rural, post-conflict area from the tri-border region of Rwanda, Burundi, and Tanzania to create economic opportunity.</li>
          <li><a href="https://makeitmatter.org/">Make It Matter</a> is a marketplace that provide artisans from across Tanzania with a premium marketplace that they would not normally have access to, and connects artisans to technology and business networks.</li>
        </ul>
        <p><strong>Uganda</strong></p>
        <ul>
          <li><a href="https://www.kimulifashionability.org/">Kimuli Fashionabiliy</a> is a clothing and accessory line that focuses on the environment by using recycled fabrics and creates employment opportunities for people with disabilities.</li>
        </ul>
        <p><strong>Zambia</strong></p>
        <ul>
          <li><a href="https://mulberrymongoose.com/">Mulberry Mongoose</a> employs local craftswomen and makes beautiful jewelry from snare wire that is recovered from poaching traps. Each purchase supports local conservation efforts to protect Zambia’s wildlife.</li>
        </ul>
        <h2 id="asia">Asia</h2>
        <p><strong>India</strong></p>
        <ul>
          <li><a href="https://rangsutra.com/">Rangsutra</a> is a community of over 2,000 artisans across rural India. They connect artisans with global consumers, which develops more sustainable livelihoods and continues the traditions of craftsmanship in India.</li>
        </ul>
        <p><strong>Lebanon</strong></p>
        <ul>
          <li>Through handmade traditional embroidery, <a href="https://www.inaash.org/">Inaash</a> is provides employment opportunities for women in the Palestinian refugee camps of Lebanon.</li>
        </ul>
        <p><strong>Malaysia</strong></p>
        <ul>
          <li><a href="https://earthheir.com/">Earth Heir</a> serves traditional artisans in underserved communities by supporting with market access and education in ethical business operations. This online marketplace sells artisan-made goods, ranging from jewelry and clothing to home accessories.</li>
        </ul>
        <p><strong>Singapore</strong></p>
        <ul>
          <li><a href="https://www.bettrcoffee.com/">Bettr Coffee Co.</a> sells their signature blends online, as well as coffee subscriptions, accessories, and merch. Each purchase supports Bettr Coffee’s initiatives including running vocational programs for marginalized women and at-risk youth.</li>
          <li><a href="https://www.theartfaculty.sg/en-sg/brands/the-animal-project-sg">The Animal Project</a> showcases and supports the abilities of people with special needs, and features work from artists who are differently-abled. All products, such as water bottles and tote bags, feature illustrations of animals created by The Animal Project’s artists.</li>
          <li><a href="https://bamboostrawgirl.com/">Bamboo Straw Girl</a> offers a full range of lifestyle products designed to help consumers reduce waste, including, of course, bamboo straws.</li>
          <li><a href="https://indosole.com.sg/">Indosole</a> repurposes old tires to make high-quality footwear.</li>
          <li><a href="https://www.theclayday.com/">The Clay Days</a> sells handcrafted ceramic homeware and jewelry. They partner with ethical workshops and social enterprises who hire socially disadvantaged artisans.</li>
        </ul>
        <h2 id="australia-and-new-zealand">Australia and New Zealand</h2>
        <table>
          <thead>
            <tr>
              <th colspan="2">Promo</th>
            </tr>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td>
                <h3 id="social-procurement-is-a-powerful-lever-any-organization-can-activate-to-deliver-immediate-social-impact">Social procurement is a powerful lever any organization can activate to deliver immediate social impact</h3>
              </td>
              <td><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/purpose-and-sustainability/social-responsibility/social-entrepreneurship.html#buysocial">Learn more</a></strong></td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
        <ul>
          <li>Ākina has created a list of <a href="https://www.akina.org.nz/news/11-social-enterprises-to-support-this-christmas?rq=christmas">11 social enterprises to support this Christmas</a>. Ākina is a social enterprise that offer a range of consulting and business development services to support businesses in creating positive impact.</li>
          <li><a href="https://herplatformshop.com/">platform</a> offers essential oils, tees and totes. It is an organization that promotes and empowers women. 100% of profits from each sale is invested in mental health and wellbeing programs delivered for free to women experiencing crisis and vulnerabilities.</li>
          <li><a href="https://magpiegoose.com/pages/collections">Magpie Goose</a> is a clothing social impact business that creates new economic and creative opportunities for Aboriginal people around Australia, and provides a platform for people to connect, celebrate and learn from Aboriginal people, culture and stories.</li>
        </ul>
        <h2 id="europe">Europe</h2>
        <p><strong>Germany</strong></p>
        <ul>
          <li><a href="https://beliya.de/">Beliya</a> is a bag label in Germany, every purchase enables a vulnerable child in Africa to attend school for one year. The bags are created in Hamburg from fine leather returns and surpluses from designer houses.</li>
          <li><a href="https://bridgeandtunnel.de/">Bridge &#x26; Tunnel</a> stands for design that changes society. The label produces sustainable and fair clothing and accessories in Hamburg with socially disadvantaged people as well as with refugees who have only recently come to Germany.</li>
          <li><a href="https://www.soulbottles.de/">Soulbottles</a> offer sustainable glass drinking bottles for at home and on the go. The bottles are made in Berlin and consist of up to 80% recycled glass and zero plastic. For every bottle sold, Soulbottles donate € 1 to the organization and support e.g. the construction of wells all over the world.</li>
          <li><a href="https://yourohana.de/">OHANA</a> offers coffee and tea with social impact. OHANA builds a bridge between family-run coffee and tea farms and socially responsible companies. With purchase prices well above the world market and sustainable partnerships, they support the farmers and ensure long-term high quality for their customers.</li>
        </ul>
        <p><strong>UK</strong></p>
        <ul>
          <li>Social Enterprise UK, a network of social enterprises throughout the UK, creates an annual gift shopping guide. The <a href="https://www.socialenterprise.org.uk/campaigns/christmas/">2021 version</a> features over 70 businesses!</li>
          <li><a href="https://www.bigissueshop.com/">The Big Issue Shop</a> is an online marketplace aimed at making ethical shopping accessible. They offer a range of products that put people and planet first.</li>
          <li><a href="https://www.nemiteas.com/">NEMI Teas</a> offer a variety of organic, fair-trade tea blends, and provides employment opportunities for refugees.</li>
        </ul>
        <h2 id="north-america">North America</h2>
        <p><strong>Canada</strong></p>
        <ul>
          <li><a href="https://www.buysocialcanada.com/directories/certified-social-enterprises/">Buy Social Canada</a> has an extensive database for you to find valuable connections in your community and make an impact by doing business with social enterprises.</li>
          <li><a href="https://atira.bc.ca/what-we-do/program/enterprising-women-making-art/">Enterprising Woman Making Art</a> EWMA was launched in 2003 as a development initiative of Atira Women’s Resource Society. It has focused on supporting women in Vancouver’s Downtown Eastside to work together to develop an alternative form of business or employment that is grounded in their needs and realities.</li>
          <li><a href="https://buildfutures.ca/futures-birds/">Futures Birds</a> is a Social Enterprise of Building Futures Employment Society. The Futures Birds Team have been creating these unique custom pieces since 2013 in Lower Sackville. Buying a Futures Birds is not only purchasing a beautiful piece of folk art; it is buying social which supports the very important services we provide for their employees and participants.</li>
          <li><a href="https://www.hivesforhumanity.com/onlineshop">Hives for Humanity (H4H)</a> is a nonprofit society that creates opportunities for connection to community, through nature, bees and the culture of the hive. We foster self-worth and community pride through skills sharing and experiential learning, working with socially and economically vulnerable populations facing barriers to stability.</li>
          <li><a href="https://skwachays.com/">Skwachàys Lodge</a> is Canada’s first Indigenous Arts Hotel and has diligently worked to provide guests with first-class services and a platform to showcase local Indigenous art and culture. At the street level, the Urban Aboriginal Fair Trade Gallery features Indigenous artwork which includes original paintings, framed limited edition prints, jewelry, pottery, wood carvings, giftware and so much more, purchasing most of its original work from local artists.</li>
          <li><a href="https://www.facebook.com/RiverbankGeneral/">Riverbank General Store &#x26; Cafe</a> is a social enterprise operated by Queens Association for Supported Living – an organization that promotes the social and economic inclusion of people with diverse abilities. The Riverbank provides meaningful work-skills training and employment as well as a valuable service to the community.</li>
          <li><a href="https://petstuffonthego.ca/">Petstuff on the Go</a> is a Dartmouth non-profit pet supply business operated by mental health consumers. We supply pet foods and various pet products. Coupled with your patronage, and their work experience, Petstuff on the Go helps mental health consumers become independent members of the community.</li>
          <li><a href="https://inhershoesyw.com/">In Her Shoes</a> is an employment and entrepreneurship training program for women (cis and trans) and gender diverse people who experience barriers to employment. Their goal is to help women and gender-diverse people reach financial stability through building career management skills, real work experience and developing their own business.</li>
        </ul>
        <p><strong>U.S.</strong></p>
        <ul>
          <li>REDF invests in and advises high-impact social enterprises to employ and empower people overcoming barriers to work. We believe that individuals who are striving to overcome adversity, including those who have historically faced discrimination, deserve the opportunity to work and contribute their skills and talents to our country and our economy. You can find their Social Enterprise Gift Guide <a href="http://socialenterprisegiftguide.com/">here</a>.</li>
          <li><a href="https://plantingjustice.org/">Planting Justice</a> has the biggest Selection of the Best Plants for a Good Cause. Their mission is to empower people impacted by mass incarceration and other social inequities with the skills and resources to cultivate food sovereignty, economic justice, and community healing.</li>
          <li><a href="https://packedwithpurpose.gifts/">Packed with Purpose</a> thoughtfully sources from purveyors are what make Packed with Purpose gifts unique and filled with impact. They have a large selection of curated, personal, and corporate gifts from Minority-Owned, Women-Owned, B-Corp, and BIPOC companies with products that are made in the U.S., Eco-Friendly, and Small Batch.</li>
          <li><a href="https://www.toastinggood.com/">Toasting Good</a> is an online shopping guide platform and community resource celebrating all things social enterprise! Their mission is to empower purchasers to create change with your everyday actions. Through their social impact blog and seasonal gift guides, they have the product recommendations, information, and practical tips you need to start making an impact in your daily life.</li>
        </ul>
        <h2 id="south-and-central-america">South and Central America</h2>
        <p><strong>Brazil</strong></p>
        <ul>
          <li><a href="https://loja.nakau.com.br/">Na’kau</a> makes chocolates sourced from a network of family farmers that produce organic cocoa in the Amazon floodplains. Alongside enabling family farmers to farm cocoa sustainably, Na’kau also works with communities to conserve the forest around them.</li>
        </ul>
        <p><strong>Mexico</strong></p>
        <ul>
          <li><a href="https://someonesomewhere.mx/">Someone Somewhere</a> works with 180 artisans, 98% of whom are women. Through fair trade, Someone Somewhere contributes to artisans’ wellbeing, the development of small businesses, and preservation of traditional crafting techniques by providing secure incomes and community.</li>
          <li><a href="https://mexi-ha.com/en/">Mexi-HA</a> is known for their hand-painted accessories. They support local artists by providing income and promoting Mexican art.</li>
        </ul>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/social-enterprise</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Booting Up for the Future with Brooks Crossing Innovation Lab]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/brooks-crossing-innovation-lab-learning-digital-skills</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/brooks-crossing-innovation-lab-learning-digital-skills</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Nov 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A new program with Brooks Crossing Innovation Lab furthers SAP's commitment to preparing youth for success in a digital world.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14233399a10f4a2a7bfd4dbc3c97eb61be96447d1.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14233399a10f4a2a7bfd4dbc3c97eb61be96447d1.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_14233399a10f4a2a7bfd4dbc3c97eb61be96447d1.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Booting Up for the Future with Brooks Crossing Innovation Lab" src="./media_14233399a10f4a2a7bfd4dbc3c97eb61be96447d1.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="booting-up-for-the-future-with-brooks-crossing-innovation-lab">Booting Up for the Future with Brooks Crossing Innovation Lab</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-young-thinkers-enabling-youth-to-shape-the-world">SAP Young Thinkers: Enabling youth to shape the world</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/innovation/next-gen-innovation-platform/young-thinkers.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Our youth may be poised to shape tomorrow’s world, but we have to let them do it. That’s why at SAP, we’re committed to putting children in position for success now, devoting time, resources, and energy to education that will empower them later.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Today, we are furthering that commitment through a new program with Brooks Crossing Innovation Lab. The Newport News, Va.-based after-school instructional hub is dedicated to learning driven by science, technology, engineering, and mathematics (STEM) and grounded in team building and collaboration. At the lab, students of all ages, abilities, and disciplines learn valuable skills by designing creative solutions to real-world problems.</p>
  <p>“SAP’s support for Brooks Crossing Innovation Lab will not only boost a love for learning,” said Mia Joe, the lab’s director, “it will also make a generational impact on workforce development by providing more access to specialized educational resources and more opportunity for children during early and impressionable developmental stages.”</p>
  <p>The alliance is yet another logical outgrowth of <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/innovation/next-gen-innovation-platform/young-thinkers.html">SAP Young Thinkers</a>, a community for youth all over the world who are passionate about innovation and technology — and who want to influence the way our digital world will take shape. SAP works with colleagues, ambassadors, and a global network of diverse institutions to provide students with the opportunity to learn and practice their skills every day, all around the world.</p>
  <p>At <a href="https://www.nnva.gov/2509/Innovation-Lab">Brooks Crossing Innovation Lab</a> — the result of a collaboration among Newport News Shipbuilding, Old Dominion University, and the City of Newport News — SAP’s participation will lead to:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Integration of SAP Young Thinkers learning modules that encourage creative learning and social innovation</li>
    <li>Professionals from all participating organizations teaching workshops for K-12 and adult learners</li>
    <li>Increased collaboration on curriculum offerings and industry-led design thinking activities</li>
  </ul>
  <p>The program officially got rolling with a kick-off event in Newport News last month, highlighting a day in the life of the lab’s students and allowing them to create a game that was presented to SAP executives.</p>
  <p>“Meeting the instructor and the kids in this program was a powerful testament to the good that can be accomplished in our community,” said SAP Regulated Industries Chief Operating Officer Scott Thatcher. “The night was energetic and engaging, and it was thrilling to see the kids so locked in.”</p>
  <p>This is only the beginning of the relationship between SAP and Brooks Crossing Innovation Lab, but Thatcher is eagerly anticipating the children’s continued growth, whether it be in coding skills or social skills.</p>
  <p>“It was incredible getting to meet the people directly involved in this initiative and to see those in the community show up and invest of themselves,” he said. “This is going to have a real lifelong impact on these kids and their confidence, and I can’t wait to watch it happen.”</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Social Shifters Redefine Business Priorities, One Enterprise at a Time]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/social-shifters-redefine-business-priorities</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/social-shifters-redefine-business-priorities</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP supported the 2021 Social Shifters Global Innovation Challenge, showcasing the importance of social enterprises and entrepreneurs.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Meet Africa Code Week’s Youth Ambassador]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/africa-code-week-youth-ambassador</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/africa-code-week-youth-ambassador</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Africa Code Week’s 2021 Youth Ambassador is 17-year-old Nigerian student Victory Yinka-Banjo, who is eager to empower young African minds.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1da3fe95137eee9f68d07672d3baa31b3eaaada98.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1da3fe95137eee9f68d07672d3baa31b3eaaada98.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1da3fe95137eee9f68d07672d3baa31b3eaaada98.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Meet Africa Code Week’s Youth Ambassador" src="./media_1da3fe95137eee9f68d07672d3baa31b3eaaada98.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="meet-africa-code-weeks-youth-ambassador">Meet Africa Code Week’s Youth Ambassador</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Speaking to Victory Yinka-Banjo is like drinking a fizzy drink; she bubbles with ideas and confidence. It’s no wonder that this 17-year-old Nigerian was chosen to be this year’s youth ambassador for Africa Code Week, the continent’s biggest digital skills youth initiative.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Even at her young age, Victory is no stranger to publicity. Earlier this year, she was offered 19 full scholarships to study at North American universities (She ended up picking MIT). But hers is no rags-to-riches story. The eldest daughter of two smart parents, a university lecturer mother and a father who works in procurement and supply chain management, Victory has always pushed herself to the limit. “My mother taught me how to hustle, and without this scholarship I could never have afforded to study in the U.S.,” she points out.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-africa-code-week">Learn more about Africa Code Week</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://africacodeweek.org/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="youth-ambassador-and-it-role-model-for-girls">Youth Ambassador and IT Role Model for Girls</h2>
  <p>Victory is looking forward to getting involved in this year’s <a href="https://africacodeweek.org/">Africa Code Week</a>, of which she is the official youth ambassador. Girls in science, technology, engineering, and mathematics (STEM) have traditionally lagged behind boys, which is why SAP and Camden Education Trust, the founders of Africa Code Week, are on a mission to make a difference – one African community at a time. Now in its seventh year, the program was proud to report 47% female participation in 2020. The event, which includes the popular AfriCANCode Challenge, has an enormous reach of 54 countries, with millions of children and youth participating. Last year, the program completely shifted to the exciting online world due to <a href="/covid-19">COVID-19</a>.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f25f5e30155c3b5c3c58d16be04bb33c57c10f19.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f25f5e30155c3b5c3c58d16be04bb33c57c10f19.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1f25f5e30155c3b5c3c58d16be04bb33c57c10f19.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Victory Yinka-Banjo headshot" src="./media_1f25f5e30155c3b5c3c58d16be04bb33c57c10f19.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="241" height="300">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p><em>Victory Yinka-Banjo</em></p>
  <p>“I participate in digital youth skills initiatives like Africa Code Week because I am passionate about empowering young people in underserved communities,” she says. Last year, she created an educational video encouraging children to learn computer programming with Scratch, MIT’s free online learning tool for coding. “Scratch is how I was introduced to coding,” she says, mentioning all its various applications that make it fun for kids, from interactive stories and games to animations. Scratch forms an integral part of Africa Code Week, encouraging teachers and African governments to see how easy it is to get kids into coding and fast-track them to the 21<sup>st</sup> century. To date, nine countries have adopted coding as a school subject thanks to the ongoing awareness, support, and contributions from the Africa Code Week program.</p>
  <p>A proud, female code representative, Victory wears many hats and keeps herself busy with multiple projects. In addition to Africa Code Week, she is actively involved with <a href="https://coderina.org/">Coderina</a>, a nonprofit organization that promotes ICT development, youth innovation, and entrepreneurship across Africa.</p>
  <p>“My first introduction to Coderina was during the pandemic last year. I helped facilitate the Lifelong Learning Program (LLP) sessions where young people were able to learn from a virtual space about everything digital skills related, from coding to 3D printing. I also taught a class during this period on design thinking and innovation. This year, I was a coach to the First Lego League (FLL) team comprising of a group of girls in secondary school in Nigeria. FLL is an exciting international robotics competition that is largely driven by Coderina.”</p>
  <h2 id="passionate-about-finding-solutions">Passionate About Finding Solutions</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="advancing-digital-skills-when-needed-most">Advancing Digital Skills When Needed Most</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/08/advancing-digital-skills-when-needed-most-sap-young-professionals-program">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>When asked what she likes about coding, Victory is unequivocal: she wants to find solutions. “I love the challenge of being given a problem and using technology to find a way to solve it,” she says. In 2019, she was part of the winning African team in the global mobile app building competition, Technovation. “The problem we had to solve was double parking, which is common in Nigeria,” she explains. “We developed an app that uses location sensors to enable your phone to pick up whenever another car parks you in, so you can step outside and speak to the owner or can communicate with the owner via instant messaging on the app.”</p>
  <p>It is this same passion for solving problems that has made her pursue a career in computer science and molecular biology. “There are so many different applications of these novel, overlapping fields, from aspects of synthetic biology to RNA sequencing in bioinformatics,” she says. Some of the questions that interest her are whether DNA can be used to store digital data and what machine learning tools can be used to model a vaccine to tackle the next variant of the coronavirus.</p>
  <p>One thing she’s sure about is that she doesn’t want to be put in a box. “Too many young people are fixated about their future career, wanting to become a doctor, engineer, or lawyer,” she says. “So many things are unconventional now. Rather than having a fixed profession, I want to say, ‘I do computational biology and it allows me to proffer solutions to this and that.’” Having a problem-solving mindset will elevate young Africans to be the change they want to see in the world, she believes – with a little bit of help from technology, of course.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Adam Hunter is EMEA communications lead for SAP CSR.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>non-sap-event/africa-code week</category>
            <category>news-tag/csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Can Immersive Technology Level the Playing Field in Education?]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/skill-immersion-lab-technology-level-education-playing-field</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/skill-immersion-lab-technology-level-education-playing-field</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP's Skill Immersion Lab program helps ensure young learners have access to the tools to build critical early career skills.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c30980ec516a74d1b752723b0ac090b5e63af4fc.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c30980ec516a74d1b752723b0ac090b5e63af4fc.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1c30980ec516a74d1b752723b0ac090b5e63af4fc.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Can Immersive Technology Level the Playing Field in Education?" src="./media_1c30980ec516a74d1b752723b0ac090b5e63af4fc.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="can-immersive-technology-level-the-playing-field-in-education">Can Immersive Technology Level the Playing Field in Education?</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>When I reflect on my 25 years in the technology industry, a moment I often think back to is when I first arrived in Silicon Valley. After numerous rounds of interviews, I was hired into a role that provided the opportunity for a tremendous amount of growth, managing hundreds of people in the early years of the tech boom.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>It was with the help of my manager — who would go on to become my mentor and lifelong friend — that I not only thrived in the role, but learned several invaluable skills, particularly around leadership and effective communication. The insights I gleaned in that first big role helped shape me into the leader I am today.</p>
  <p>Just as I was able to in the early years of my career, SAP wants to ensure young learners have access to the tools to build critical early career skills. Soft skills have been and continue to be incredibly important; a <a href="https://www.naceweb.org/talent-acquisition/candidate-selection/the-attributes-employers-seek-on-students-resumes/">2021 survey by the National Association of Colleges and Employers</a>, which looked at hiring projections for the class of 2021, found working in a team, communication, and leadership skills were more sought after than others like computer skills or even having a strong work ethic. We also know CEOs and hiring managers are <a href="https://www.pwc.com/gx/en/services/people-organisation/workforce-of-the-future/workforce-of-future-appendix.pdf">finding these skills</a> difficult to come by.</p>
  <p>To help, SAP created a new program called the <strong>Skill Immersion Lab</strong>. At its core, this program uses virtual reality to teach students communication skills and effective leadership techniques.</p>
  <p>To learn more about the Skill Immersion Lab and the results of its rollout, I sat down with Katie Booth, SAP North America’s head of Corporate Social Responsibility. Below is an edited version of our conversation.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="empowering-equity-in-education-with-virtual-reality-and-immersive-learning">Empowering Equity in Education with Virtual Reality and Immersive Learning</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/07/skill-immersion-lab-education-equity">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="q-to-get-started-would-you-introduce-yourself-and-share-your-role-at-sap">Q: To get started, would you introduce yourself and share your role at SAP?</h2>
  <p><strong>A:</strong> My name is Katie Booth and I oversee SAP’s North America Corporate Social Responsibility (CSR) program. We have three prominent focus areas in CSR: building digital skills, accelerating best run nonprofits and social enterprises, and connecting employees with purpose.</p>
  <p>In practice, this means supporting and enabling our employees to give back in their local communities; working hand-in-hand with our amazing nonprofit partners, such as the Network for Teaching Entrepreneurship and GENYOUth; and building out programs for students that promote and improve technical know-how and digital literacy to better equip them for the future.</p>
  <h2 id="what-is-the-skill-immersion-lab-and-where-was-it-launched">What is the Skill Immersion Lab and where was it launched?</h2>
  <p>The Skill Immersion Lab is a new program we launched in partnership with JFFLabs, a unit of JFF, a national nonprofit that works to drive transformation in the American workforce and education system. In short, our aim was to use virtual reality as an effective teaching tool. <a href="https://www.pwc.com/us/en/services/consulting/technology/emerging-technology/vr-study-2020.html#:~:text=In%20our%20study%2C%20VR%2Dtrained,training%20and%20have%20better%20outcomes.">According to PwC</a>, people who are taught using virtual reality technology are 3.75 times more emotionally connected to the content and four times more focused than their e-learning peers, which helps students improve their employability skills. We specifically wanted to work with learners in communities that do not typically get first access to technology like this.</p>
  <p>The Skill Immersion Lab integrates immersive learning via virtual reality with instructor guidance and discussion. The curriculum was developed by spatial computing company Talespin.</p>
  <p>In July we concluded the first round of learning with our community partners. It ran from four to six weeks, and we rolled it out at three locations across the U.S.: BTECH High School in New York City, Boys and Girls Club in St. Paul, and Quad YouthBuild in Louisiana. In all, about 50 learners aged 14 to 20 participated.</p>
  <p>We chose these sites very intentionally. They’re in different and diverse parts of the country, ranging from urban to rural, and in different education programs and pathways. This meant learners with different backgrounds, experiences, and environments participated. We’ve known from the start that this program is centered on learner feedback, so a variety of learners is essential.</p>
  <h2 id="why-is-there-a-need-for-a-program-like-this">Why is there a need for a program like this?</h2>
  <p>We want to help young learners not only get jobs but have successful careers. Communication and durable, or “soft,” skills are crucial for both of these. We all know that. What’s interesting is how it seems these skills are becoming even more important.</p>
  <p>The World Economic Forum, for example, <a href="http://www3.weforum.org/docs/WEF_Future_of_Jobs_2020.pdf">published a study</a> in October of last year in which it highlighted the top 15 skills employers see as increasing in demand by 2025. Among this list are skills like emotional intelligence, leadership and social influence, and persuasion and negotiation. PwC raises and interesting idea in the <em><a href="https://www.pwc.com/gx/en/services/people-organisation/workforce-of-the-future/workforce-of-the-future-the-competing-forces-shaping-2030-pwc.pdf">Workforce of the future</a></em> study. The concept is that with automation replacing certain occupations, machines may in fact “amplify the comparative advantage” of workers that have strong skills like problem solving, leadership, emotional intelligence, empathy, and creativity. In short, soft skills may be future employees’ unique advantage.</p>
  <p>We believe the Skill Immersion Lab serves a significant purpose in normal times, but might be critical during a <a href="/covid-19">pandemic</a>, with the decrease in face-to-face communications and the rise of remote learning. <a href="https://www.mckinsey.com/industries/public-and-social-sector/our-insights/covid-19-and-student-learning-in-the-united-states-the-hurt-could-last-a-lifetime">McKinsey sites data from Curriculum Associates</a> suggesting that only 60% of low-income students are consistently logging into online instruction compared to 90% of high-income students.</p>
  <p>Nearly 90% of the learners said, in post-program feedback, that this technology was fun to use and that it was a more exciting way to learn. We believe this can play an important role not just in learning the content but also in retaining it—and our results did indicate this.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11790ba0d48cff908c518395f8807c7fc989bf901.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11790ba0d48cff908c518395f8807c7fc989bf901.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_11790ba0d48cff908c518395f8807c7fc989bf901.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_11790ba0d48cff908c518395f8807c7fc989bf901.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="360" height="200">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_140a007b6bc36f35ef82d6f8716f02aad0285181c.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_140a007b6bc36f35ef82d6f8716f02aad0285181c.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_140a007b6bc36f35ef82d6f8716f02aad0285181c.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_140a007b6bc36f35ef82d6f8716f02aad0285181c.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="360" height="200">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="what-does-the-curriculum-structure-focus-on">What does the curriculum structure focus on?</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-saps-csr-efforts">Learn more about SAP's CSR efforts</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/csr.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The immersive learning curriculum by Talespin is broken into two series: Leading Through Uncertainty and Effective Feedback.</p>
  <p>Leading Through Uncertainty consists of five modules designed to empower leaders to apply and practice fundamental communication and interpersonal skills in difficult situations, in which the story line and skills build on top of each other. Effective Feedback includes three modules that provide an immersive learning experience for leaders and managers to further develop critical communication skills.</p>
  <p>It’s important to state that this curriculum is not specifically designed for youth; this is a program built for mid- to high-level managers in a corporate setting, and we had students aged 14 to 20 years old using it to learn.</p>
  <h2 id="now-that-the-initial-program-results-are-rolling-in-what-did-you-learn">Now that the initial program results are rolling in, what did you learn?</h2>
  <p>We had a high degree of confidence that the outcomes would be broadly similar to what we see in adults with immersive technology, and we were right.</p>
  <p>Our results showed that immersive learning helps build confident communicators. In post-program feedback, 85% of our learners said they are more confident speaking with others and an equal amount said their ability to express an idea improved during the program. We also found that it helped to improve empathetic communication. Seventy-nine percent of learners reported that they felt an improvement in their ability to understand others’ opinions and 83% felt an improvement with communicating with those with different opinions.</p>
  <p>We also saw that virtual reality provided an optimal environment for fostering perseverance and resilience. Eighty-eight percent of learners agreed that when they had difficulty they kept trying. Our results showed that immersive learning provided formative feedback loops, facilitating deliberate practice in students. On average, our learners had a higher number of attempts on modules they received a below-acing score on in their first attempt. Also, 90% acknowledged that they went back to check their answers to see how they could improve when they finished a lesson.</p>
  <p>Of course, this program was more than teaching students via virtual reality. We found that an effective approach was in the guided discussions instructors at each site facilitated. Our results indicated that this guidance was an influential factor in students learning the content. That is one unique element of this program: when students are going through the program, instructors play the role of a coach, while Talespin’s software acts more like the teacher and role play partner, offering students guidance, real-time feedback for skill development, and the opportunity to fail in a safe space and try again.</p>
  <p>One instructor summed the typical student response as: “I never thought about other people’s feelings before or what they might be going through and how that could impact their work, but I do now.” Other success stories echoed this sentiment.</p>
  <h2 id="was-there-anything-that-took-you-by-surprise">Was there anything that took you by surprise?</h2>
  <p>In some cases, yes. Probably most important is our goal to offer different program tracts to help learners achieve their goals. One site noted how much more impactful the program would have been if it had a customer service focus to it, since some of the students were in a customer service facing youth training program. The above data suggests that immersive learning is impactful, but a critical next step in scaling access to this technology is having different program tracts and customizable content. That’s something we’re currently looking into.</p>
  <h2 id="whats-next-for-the-skill-immersion-lab-program">What’s next for the Skill Immersion Lab program?</h2>
  <p>We want to ensure we’re getting this technology into as many learners’ hands as possible. Virtual reality is not a new technology, but many people have not experienced it firsthand. I hope with this program we can begin to make the case for investing in this learning model, particularly in communities that may not have the resources to do so.</p>
  <p>We’re looking at different models as we enter the second phase. We hope to develop models using what we’ve learned that can be more easily scaled, and I believe we’re nearing the turning point on that. That’s also one reason we’re publicly sharing these results, so others can follow in our footsteps. We need other organizations to step-up to the table and invest in this for their communities.</p>
  <p>That’s our vision for the Skill Immersion Lab. It’s more than letting students play with innovative technology. It’s a road map for how innovation, multi-sector partnerships, and collaboration can support young learners. It’s an innovation intended to benefit all, not just those who can afford it.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Stephanie Nashawaty is chief customer innovation officer for SAP North America.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Teaming Up to Make Data Science a Priority]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/data-science-for-everyone-coalition-sap-49ers</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/data-science-for-everyone-coalition-sap-49ers</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A Data Science For Everyone panel covered how education strengthens communities and workforces, and how SAP and the 49ers are making change.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18eaa0ffb768dab870dc015fb7a7a513d8799b857.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18eaa0ffb768dab870dc015fb7a7a513d8799b857.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_18eaa0ffb768dab870dc015fb7a7a513d8799b857.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Teaming Up to Make Data Science a Priority" src="./media_18eaa0ffb768dab870dc015fb7a7a513d8799b857.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="teaming-up-to-make-data-science-a-priority">Teaming Up to Make Data Science a Priority</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-how-sap-university-alliances-is-building-the-talent-of-the-future">Learn how SAP University Alliances is building the talent of the future</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/innovation/next-gen-innovation-platform/university-alliances.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>The math curriculum taught to today’s high school students is out of sync with the current landscape and our everyday use of technology. A <a href="https://freakonomics.com/podcast/math-curriculum/">podcast by <em>Freakonomics</em> author Steven Levitt</a> discusses the current “geometry sandwich” of Algebra I/Geometry/Algebra II, which was designed to prepare students for the Space Race of the 1950s, not where we are today.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Data Science for Everyone found that 90% of the world’s data was created in the last two years. However, only 11% of high school students take a statistics course. Data science jobs have seen a 650% growth since 2012 and reports show that seven of 10 careers with the fastest growth are data-centric. In order to prepare students for the future, a change needs to be made with their relationship with data.</p>
  <p>Data Science for Everyone is a <a href="https://www.datascience4everyone.org/about">national movement for advancing data literacy in the U.S.</a> among students, comprised of a coalition of more than 160 educators, policymakers, and industry leaders. Earlier this year, Data Science for Everyone submitted a letter to the Biden administration urging to make data literacy a national priority. They have created actionable steps and gathered resources for educators to implement into their curriculum.</p>
  <p>To date, states including California, Oregon, and Ohio are working to update their current curriculum to meet the growing demand. Additionally, UCLA’s Introduction to Data Science course is taught in 26 school districts nationwide. This is still not enough; additional advocacy is needed to help ensure that the issue of data literacy remains part of the conversation surrounding education.</p>
  <p>Last month, Data Science for Everyone held a virtual Commitments Campaign event to bring together all stakeholders who are working to make a change in data literacy. The event garnered 272 commitments from companies, education leaders, and policymakers that impact more than 3 million students, 25,000 teachers, and 500 school districts.</p>
  <p>Dr. Karina Edmonds, senior vice president and head of Academies and <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/innovation/next-gen-innovation-platform/university-alliances.html">SAP University Alliances</a> for SAP, spoke to how data science education strengthens our communities and workforce: “We absolutely have to get everyone at the table as the growth of data science jobs continues to skyrocket. We can’t afford to leave a great part of our society behind.”</p>
  <p>The <a href="https://www.datascience4everyone.org/commitments-event-2021?wix-vod-video-id=5f4d3c8871784f06a4d86981aab2c1ac&#x26;wix-vod-comp-id=comp-kqjzhw47">49ers and SAP have committed to offer rich educational data science resources</a> for K-12 students over the next year. SAP and the 49ers Foundation plan to launch a new data science course by next year that will include data modules focused on using football data to make data science more relevant to students. The two phased program will be comprised of virtual lessons for middle school students, along with a high school curriculum and field trips for grades 9-12.</p>
  <p>We can each play a role with bringing this movement to life. Individuals can make their own personal commitment to help ensure that students have access to data literacy skills. Simple things like the following:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Parents and adults must encourage children’s curiosity around data science and math. Projecting negative past experiences with math and science can influence children’s relationship with data science in the future. Remove negative self-talk — things like “I hate math” or “I’m not good with numbers” — that are only hurting the curiosity we want youth to have.</li>
    <li>Contact decision-makers and initiate conversations in your community to find support for modern standards that reflect the data-centric world. This can include contacting the Department of Education, state legislators, or the local school board and district superintendent. These policymakers influence curriculum, course offerings, and teachers’ professional development, so engaging these leaders and getting them excited about data science can unlock the potential of new courses and better trained teachers.</li>
    <li>Get personally involved as a volunteer. Not all programs rely on volunteer support, but there is great importance in students hearing from experts in the topic being discussed. The SAP Corporate Social Responsibility team has partners across North America that can host employees for speaking opportunities. Check out organizations like <a href="https://www.csforallteachers.org/">Computer Science for All Teachers</a> and <a href="https://www.techgirlz.org/volunteer/">Tech Girlz</a>.</li>
  </ul>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>news-tag/education</category>
            <category>news-tag/purpose</category>
            <category>news-tag/redefining-youth</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Amazing Inclusion Story Behind India's Digital Transformation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/05/code-unnati-inclusion-story-india-digital-transformation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/05/code-unnati-inclusion-story-india-digital-transformation</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Since SAP Labs India launched Code Unnati four years ago, the program has trained more than 1 million students in digital literacy.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15ab812331322b95cc220a54a291b18fd8d726639.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15ab812331322b95cc220a54a291b18fd8d726639.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_15ab812331322b95cc220a54a291b18fd8d726639.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="The Amazing Inclusion Story Behind India’s Digital Transformation" src="./media_15ab812331322b95cc220a54a291b18fd8d726639.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="the-amazing-inclusion-story-behind-indias-digital-transformation">The Amazing Inclusion Story Behind India’s Digital Transformation</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>As a young woman living in a rural area of Karnataka, a state located in the south western region of India, Manjula Naganur knew that education was critical to achieving her dream of a career in government administration. After completing training and education courses at <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tBRu7qwrtNk">Code Unnati</a>, she joined a fintech company and now is pursuing her post-graduate studies.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“I gained a greater understanding of what organizations expect from job candidates,” said Naganur. “The courses in software development, marketing, communications, English, banking, and problem-solving have provided me with valuable knowledge to stand out in a competitive market, giving me greater career opportunities.”</p>
  <p>Naganur is among the over 1 million students educated at Code Unnati since <a href="https://www.sap.com/india/about/labs-india.html">SAP Labs India</a> launched the program four years ago. So far, it has trained over 1 million students ages 10 to 16 years in digital literacy; 65% of these children and adolescents were girls.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="explore-how-sap-is-working-to-make-sustainability-profitable-and-profitability-sustainable">Explore how SAP is working to make sustainability profitable and profitability sustainable</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/purpose-and-sustainability.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="partnerships-scale-equitable-digital-training">Partnerships Scale Equitable Digital Training</h2>
  <p>Code Unnati is among SAP’s global <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/sustainability-csr.html">corporate social responsibility (CSR)</a> programs, in this case, supporting India’s digital readiness commitment. SAP Labs India works with partners in government as well as the non-profit and private sectors, including customers and education, to bridge the immense digital divide between people in the country’s urban and rural communities. In addition to a digital-rich learning curriculum, the program offers students the opportunity for internships and employment at SAP.</p>
  <p>“We have the incredible opportunity to help transform India from a developing to a developed economy,” said Sindhu Gangadharan, senior vice president and managing director of SAP Labs India. “We’re driving significant engagements to support the digital-first mindset that’s reflected across numerous government initiatives. Code Unnati builds digital literacy among youth and equips them with employable skills for workforce readiness, particularly beyond large, metropolitan areas.”</p>
  <p>A total of over 6,000 youth have participated in the vocational curriculum, which includes learning future IT skills, such as data science and analytics, and next-gen technologies like <a href="https://insights.sap.com/what-is-artificial-intelligence/">artificial intelligence (AI)</a> and <a href="https://insights.sap.com/what-is-machine-learning/">machine learning</a>. Most importantly, an average of over 40% of program graduates obtain jobs after program completion.</p>
  <h2 id="responsible-inclusive-use-of-technology">Responsible, Inclusive Use of Technology</h2>
  <p>Code Unnati reflects just about every one of the Indian government’s “digital readiness for the next billion” commitment, notably talent development, amped up investments in research and development, innovations for both India and the world, and inclusiveness. <a href="https://nasscom.in/">The National Association of Software and Service Companies (NASSCOM)</a> is among the groups leading this initiative, working with the government and companies like SAP.</p>
  <p>“We want to leverage technology as best as possible to solve some of India’s biggest challenges,” said Debjani Ghosh, president of NASSCOM. “As we bring technology into pretty much everything we do, it can become an equalizer, as long as we start at the design stage to make sure that it’s truly inclusive across sectors, regardless of rural or urban, gender, culture, or religion.”</p>
  <h2 id="digital-literacy-for-indias-specific-needs">Digital Literacy for India’s Specific Needs</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="at-goodwill-wine-procurement-with-a-purpose">At Goodwill Wine, Procurement with a Purpose</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/05/goodwill-wine-procurement-with-purpose">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Although India is digitally transforming like the rest of the world, the magnitude of its revolution is much bigger in scale and scope compared to many other regions. Ghosh said that talent development is among the government’s highest priorities, helping to build the population’s digital skills through public-private sector partnerships that provide training and education, mentoring, and internships.</p>
  <p>“Whether you call it a challenge or an opportunity, India has an amazing diversity of socioeconomic levels, cultures, religions, and languages,” she said. “We’re committed to partnering with the government and companies like SAP to build and foster ecosystems that use accelerators, mentorships, hackathons, and other opportunities to drive the IT charter for India.”</p>
  <h2 id="community-wide-purpose-plus-business-profit">Community-Wide Purpose Plus Business Profit</h2>
  <p>More than anything, Code Unnati reflects a commitment to purposeful business that positively impacts people’s lives.</p>
  <p>“It’s not just about bringing technology into pretty much everything we do to make things easier and personalized, but also that we build and use the technology responsibly,” said Ghosh.</p>
  <p>Democratizing technology education is also central to SAP’s purpose-driven mission, helping organizations become intelligent enterprises using <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/intelligent-technologies.html">SAP Business Technology Platform</a>. Spearheading Code Unnati with funds and resources from customers, partners, and its own employees, SAP is also at the forefront of India’s mission to provide disadvantaged students with digital skills for their future, as well as India’s.</p>
  <p>“We’ve been able to quickly scale and achieve meaningful business outcomes with partners focusing on purpose plus profit,” said Gangadharan. “We’re helping everyone lift up society for the sustainable change that’s much needed in India.”</p>
  <p>In this context, Naganur’s singular educational experience is a shining example of the tremendous opportunities in store for India’s next billion people with digital empowerment.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Follow me: @smgaler</em><br><em><a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2021/05/04/the-amazing-inclusion-story-behind-indias-digital-transformation/?sh=49137a2c47b5">This story originally appeared on SAP BrandVoice on Forbes</a></em>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-education</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-labs-network</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP at Globe Series: Procurement to Build Back Better]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/05/globe-series-procurement-build-back-better</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/05/globe-series-procurement-build-back-better</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[At this year’s Globe Series conference, SAP’s market-leading stance in social procurement was represented. Learn more about its impact.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17dce12da2b6c019eb6ba2370ab59f02b5426145a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17dce12da2b6c019eb6ba2370ab59f02b5426145a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_17dce12da2b6c019eb6ba2370ab59f02b5426145a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP at Globe Series: Procurement to Build Back Better" src="./media_17dce12da2b6c019eb6ba2370ab59f02b5426145a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-at-globe-series-procurement-to-build-back-better">SAP at Globe Series: Procurement to Build Back Better</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>At this year’s Globe Series conference, SAP Labs Canada Chief Operating Officer Agnes Garaba represented SAP’s market-leading stance in social procurement. During her session, <a href="https://capital.globeseries.com/agenda/session/499305">Leverage Your Purchasing Power: Procurement to Build Back Better</a>, she helped the audience explore both why and how social procurement creates holistic economic, social, and environmental impact.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Every purchase has an economic, environmental, and/or social impact — whether intended or not. <a href="/2020/10/social-procurement-better-way-grow">Social procurement</a> is the practice of bringing together buyers with suppliers that not only have a quality good or service, but one that delivers on the promise of social and/or environmental impact. Often, these intentional positive contributions are reinvested into the local economy and add to the economic equity and vibrancy of the community. Social enterprises are business that practice social procurement as part of their mission to culturally and operationally change the world. They are founded and governed based on a clear social or environmental mission and they reinvest most of their profit back into this mission.</p>
  <p>SAP understands the importance of prioritizing social procurement. As Garaba noted: “Seventy-seven percent of the world’s transactions run through an SAP system. It puts us in a unique place to have the opportunity, and also the responsibility, to drive positive changes. SAP’s social purchasing strategy began more than a decade ago with the inclusion of social enterprises in our Canadian supply chain. Today, our global ecosystem of partners focused on scaling social procurement, in addition to those inspiring new ideas and accelerating social ventures, collectively impact more than 1 billion beneficiaries across the globe.”</p>
  <p>The commitment of SAP’s social procurement implementation is a two-pronged approach. The first relies on an initial top-down mandate, with executives and the Board supporting it, including putting resources behind it. The other aspect is, as Garaba explains, “a bit of a grassroots approach. We have established a ‘Procurement with Purpose’ ambassador network; these are people both within the procurement organization and others who are also making strategic buying decisions. They are the multipliers and they are the ones who help the organization identify opportunities for positive change.”</p>
  <p>Sustainable procurement has been a central part of the public sector agenda for some time, which is game changing since Canadian governments alone spend $200 billion on procurement. It is also gaining traction in the private sector, as businesses recognize that integrating social value into purchasing and supply chain decisions makes them more competitive and sustainable. SAP has a demonstrated commitment to scaling the sector through social procurement. Notably, SAP <a href="/2020/10/sap-launches-55by25-purposeful-procurement">launched a 5 &#x26; 5 by ‘25 initiative</a>, aiming to spend five percent of addressable spend with diverse enterprises, which are defined as businesses that are at least 51% owned and operated by an individual or group that is traditionally underrepresented, and social enterprises by 2025, and encouraging organizations across industries to join the pledge.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="the-time-has-come-for-procurement-with-purpose">The time has come for procurement with purpose</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.ariba.com/about/procure-with-purpose">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="sap-and-buy-social-canada">SAP and Buy Social Canada</h2>
  <p>SAP co-innovates and co-develops programs with corporate social responsibility (CSR) partners, accelerating change and driving sustainable impact. Beyond internal commitments and Procurement with Purpose ambassadors, SAP fosters social procurement in partnership with social enterprise and social procurement intermediary <a href="https://www.buysocialcanada.com">Buy Social Canada</a>, supporting the development of social procurement across the country by working to connect buyers to certified social enterprise business sellers, unleashing the biggest untapped potential to create sustainable impact in our communities and for the planet.</p>
  <p>Buy Social Canada and SAP are working together to advance the social enterprise sector in Canada by collaborating on initiatives, like the <a href="https://www.buysocialcanada.com/services/social-purchasing-partnerships/">Buy Social Pledge</a>, that deliver better access to markets and buyers, as well as creating opportunities for employees to engage in growing the capacity of local social enterprises. One of the barriers preventing large-scale social enterprise investment is that social enterprises are often small businesses, thus lacking the capacity to be providers for large, multi-national companies like SAP. SAP has implemented a pro bono volunteering program to help build capacity for social enterprises, understanding that they need to grow to become true procurement partners.</p>
  <p>“If you don’t start small, there is no way to build capacity. Small steps but consistent steps will lead much further than trying to do really big leaps,” Garaba notes.</p>
  <p>Working with MovingWorlds, SAP launched the <a href="https://movingworlds.org/social-enterprise-revenue-accelerator">Sustainable Growth of Revenues for International Development</a> (S-GRID) program. The program recently acknowledged as an <a href="https://blog.movingworlds.org/world-changing-idea/">honorable mention for Fast Company’s 2021 World Changing Ideas</a>, helps social enterprises build revenue partnerships with the corporate sector to become more integrated into global value chains.</p>
  <h2 id="looking-ahead">Looking Ahead</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-launches-5--5-by-25-initiative">SAP Launches 5 &#x26; 5 by ’25 Initiative</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2020/10/sap-launches-55by25-purposeful-procurement">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Within the SAP existing procurement spend and purchasing power, the potential for change is massive. With increasing focus on consumerism, it is important to buy and sell responsibly. Where can doing good coincide with doing good business? With time, the hope is that by buying goods and services from organizations with a purpose-driven mission the cycle of good is perpetuated.</p>
  <p>Although there is a growing interest from corporations like SAP to “buy social,” the current supply is not strong enough to meet the global demand. As a result, we work with organizations like Buy Social Canada and invest in programs such as MovingWorld’s S-GRID to help ensure that more enterprises around the world are procurement-ready and can sustainably grow their revenue streams.</p>
  <p>This is not an overnight process. SAP has spent more than a decade accelerating and scaling the work of social entrepreneurs and it is only the beginning. SAP will continue to diligently invest in this for the foreseeable future; in 2021 specifically through partnerships and collaborative work with a continued focus on capacity-building ventures within the sector and expanding access to markets and buyers.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/csr</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/purpose</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-canada</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Empowering Women in Rwanda]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/videos/empowering-women-in-rwanda</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/videos/empowering-women-in-rwanda</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Resonate trains women in Rwanda, like Odette, how to gain confidence and bring about change in their families and communities.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/video</category>
            <category>news-tag/csr</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Adapting to Climate Change in Rwanda]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/videos/adapting-to-climate-change-in-rwanda</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/videos/adapting-to-climate-change-in-rwanda</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Africa Development Consultant (ADC) helps Rwandan farmers in the Ntende Rice Cooperative, like Beatrice, develop and adapt to changing conditions such as global warming.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_162d49da17e14495ac40498ecaff5632adce58fac.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_162d49da17e14495ac40498ecaff5632adce58fac.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_162d49da17e14495ac40498ecaff5632adce58fac.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Adapting to Climate Change in Rwanda" src="./media_162d49da17e14495ac40498ecaff5632adce58fac.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="adapting-to-climate-change-in-rwanda">Adapting to Climate Change in Rwanda</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_162d49da17e14495ac40498ecaff5632adce58fac.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_162d49da17e14495ac40498ecaff5632adce58fac.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_162d49da17e14495ac40498ecaff5632adce58fac.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Adapting to Climate Change in Rwanda" src="./media_162d49da17e14495ac40498ecaff5632adce58fac.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UJa-2dG_Yt4">Adapting to Climate Change in Rwanda</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Africa Development Consultant (ADC) helps Rwandan farmers in the Ntende Rice Cooperative, like Beatrice, develop and adapt to changing conditions such as global warming.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/video</category>
            <category>news-tag/climate-change</category>
            <category>news-tag/csr</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>