<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/sap4good/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Take Small Steps and Create Big Impact Through Volunteering]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/small-steps-big-impact-volunteering-maggie-ramaiah</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/small-steps-big-impact-volunteering-maggie-ramaiah</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Enabling others to make their mark creates lasting impact. SAP employee Maggie Ramaiah integrates CSR activities to build that mindset.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/leadership</category>
            <category>news-tag/pro-bono-for-economic-equity</category>
            <category>news-tag/purpose</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-employee-profile</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Empowering Anthems: A Playlist for International Youth Day]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/international-youth-day-2023-anthems</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/08/international-youth-day-2023-anthems</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[For International Youth Day 2023, get the playlist you need to inspire us all to work better together to protect people and planet.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/redefining-youth</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Transform Your Career and the World Around You Through Volunteering]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/transform-career-world-through-volunteer-pro-bono-work</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/transform-career-world-through-volunteer-pro-bono-work</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP employees are transforming the world through their volunteer and pro bono consulting work. Learn more about their efforts.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_151aa28cc4c3b93ece1704e100b04d40a6cf71ac9.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_151aa28cc4c3b93ece1704e100b04d40a6cf71ac9.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_151aa28cc4c3b93ece1704e100b04d40a6cf71ac9.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Transform Your Career and the World Around You Through Volunteering" src="./media_151aa28cc4c3b93ece1704e100b04d40a6cf71ac9.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="transform-your-career-and-the-world-around-you-through-volunteering">Transform Your Career and the World Around You Through Volunteering</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-csr-at-sap">Learn more about CSR at SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/our-values/csr.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>If you were given the opportunity to help others, build your professional skills, gain confidence, and feel more energized in your life and career, would you take it? SAP has dedicated over <a href="https://www.sap.com/dmc/exp/2017_03_46558/enUS/impact/">a decade to exactly that</a>: creating volunteer and pro bono consulting programs that not only help the world run better and improve people’s lives, but also benefit employees, their teams, and the company as well.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Karen Vergara, from the Global Learning Services Enablement Program Management for SAP Concur, is an alumni participant from several SAP-driven pro bono consulting programs, as well as a mentor, trainer, and SAP Corporate Social Responsibility (SAP CSR) fellow.</p>
  <p>Vergara always knew she wanted to help other people become successful and has taken that passion, along with the development of her own professional skills, to a new level. She began her career in education, but found that while she was making a difference, she wanted to do more. She leveraged her educational foundation to move into various roles at Microsoft, Accenture, and most recently SAP, earning a higher salary that allowed her to donate more to the causes she was passionate about but offered her less time for traditional, hands-on volunteering. Vergara decided to seek out opportunities within her professional role to make an impact in new ways.</p>
  <p>What started as a way to get involved soon turned into so much more. With each experience, Vergara gained more than she expected.</p>
  <p>“I’ve found that I’ve taken away as much as I’ve given, maybe sometimes even more,” she says. Volunteering, particularly skills-based volunteer experiences, provided her with the ability to do good and to keep learning and growing both personally and professionally at the same time.</p>
  <p>From helping students find success to changing her career and making an impact through volunteerism and pro bono consulting as a part of the SAP community, Vergara’s journey is showing no signs of slowing down. Over the past six months, she has been working on a fellowship with the SAP CSR team to position every type of volunteering offered at SAP, particularly pro bono engagements, as an opportunity for learning, career, and leadership development.</p>
  <p>“If you are already volunteering, it is a just a bonus and a way to think more intentionally about your professional development,” Vergara shares. “You can do good and learn, taking skills away from it and gaining experience that will help you in your own career.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-more-stories-and-coverage-about-csr-efforts-at-sap">Read more stories and coverage about CSR efforts at SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/topics/sap-csr">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In fact, Vergara has taken this one step further, becoming a leader and champion for employee volunteering. She shared one anecdote from an SAP employee who was looking to gain specific experience to advance to a new role. Vergara pointed them to skills-based volunteering, and when it came time for the interview for the new role, the employee was able to share examples of the experience they gained through participation in these kinds of activities – experience that they otherwise would not have had – putting them in a better position to obtain the new role.</p>
  <p>Thanks to Vergara’s work during her fellowship, as well as her own lived experiences as a corporate volunteer and pro bono consultant, she has demonstrated that utilizing skills and concepts through volunteering and pro bono consulting <em>is</em> career development.</p>
  <p>Through volunteering in any capacity, there is always an opportunity to explore career interests and find a path forward utilizing the right opportunities. CSR activities represent an alternative form of experiential learning; it benefits every professional, whether employee or manager, to consider how they can be incorporated into our professional development plans and goal setting. Vergara’s work has highlighted that intentional and well thought-out engagement in these types of offerings can lead to the acquisition of new skills and chances to practice skills someone may have learned in an academic setting. It also provides an opportunity to learn from others, share one’s own skills, and build a network.</p>
  <p>Everyone who participates in CSR activities stands to gain from the work that Vergara has done in defining how volunteering contributes to career growth beyond social impact. When thinking about volunteerism, often what comes to mind is doing good, serving others, giving back to our communities, and making a positive social and environmental impact. Beyond these more obvious benefits, there are powerful takeaways for the volunteer as well. Traditional activities are a fantastic way to build community with others who are like-minded and share common interests. Skills-based volunteering and pro bono consulting offers an opportunity to build a professional network, while practicing skills such as collaboration, creative problem-solving, and inclusive leadership behaviors. Like Vergara, many employees seek fulfillment beyond their day-to-day roles. Her story is one example of taking the initiative to make a societal impact and gaining so much more. She has found community in her career, opportunities to lead, and a renewed commitment to continue helping the world run better and improving people’s lives.</p>
  <p><strong>Join Us</strong></p>
  <p>With a <a href="https://www.sap.com/dmc/exp/2017_03_46558/enUS/impact/">decade of success</a> engaging employees like Karen Vergara, SAP, together with EY, MovingWorlds, TRANSFORM, and Unilever, continue to partner on the TRANSFORM Support Hub, connecting employees everywhere to social entrepreneurs anywhere through pro bono consulting, coaching, and more. If you feel inspired to build your skills as well as a more sustainable world, we invite you to <a href="https://movingworlds.org/transform/corporates">join us</a>!</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/moments-of-service</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Breaking Barriers Through Education: SAP's Partnership with University of the People]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/breaking-barriers-through-education-sap-university-of-the-people</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/breaking-barriers-through-education-sap-university-of-the-people</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP has partnered with University of the People, helping provide global access to higher education. Read the stories of two refugee students.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning-for-life</category>
            <category>news-tag/purpose</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
            <category>news-tag/ukraine</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Social Sabbatical: Resiliency and Impact in Action]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/sap-social-sabbatical-resiliency-and-impact-in-action</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/sap-social-sabbatical-resiliency-and-impact-in-action</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Pro bono consulting programs like SAP Social Sabbatical build immense impact for employees, social sector partners, and SAP overall.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/purpose</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-social-sabbatical</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Act Now, Together, Through Pro Bono Consulting]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/together-act-now-pro-bono-consulting</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/together-act-now-pro-bono-consulting</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Together Act Now was the theme for the 2022 UN International Volunteer Day. Learn how SAP employees participate.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/life-at-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-social-sabbatical</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
            <category>news-tag/un-sdgs</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fostering Diversity and Inclusion Through Immersive Pro Bono Consulting]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/immersive-pro-bono-consulting-fostering-diversity-inclusion</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/immersive-pro-bono-consulting-fostering-diversity-inclusion</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Pro bono consulting programs like the SAP Social Sabbatical foster diversity and cultivate an inclusive mindset for participants. Learn how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17c7e0cc1436024ff2536a47add3bf4d172041915.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17c7e0cc1436024ff2536a47add3bf4d172041915.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_17c7e0cc1436024ff2536a47add3bf4d172041915.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Fostering Diversity and Inclusion Through Immersive Pro Bono Consulting" src="./media_17c7e0cc1436024ff2536a47add3bf4d172041915.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="fostering-diversity-and-inclusion-through-immersive-pro-bono-consulting">Fostering Diversity and Inclusion Through Immersive Pro Bono Consulting</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Global Diversity Awareness Month is a time to reflect and honor diversity in all its facets – nationality, race, sex, gender, country of origin, and language, just to name a few.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>This is celebrated each year in October; however, at SAP, diversity is something we honor throughout the year. Within our 110,000+ strong company, we have employees from all over the world, with many of our teams working from multiple locations together to reinvent how the world runs as a network of intelligent, sustainable enterprises. Through global teamwork, employees are exposed to different cultures, diverse ways of thinking, and building skills that grow empathy and resiliency. Not only is diversity and inclusion good for employees, but it is also good for business.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-how-sap-is-powering-equitable-access">Learn how SAP is powering equitable access</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/our-values/csr.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="diversity-in-action-through-pro-bono-consulting">Diversity in Action through Pro Bono Consulting</h2>
  <p>As a global organization with employees representing more than 150 nationalities, we are constantly seeking various ways to incorporate diversity and inclusion proactively, both within our workplace and in the markets we serve.</p>
  <p>One of the ways SAP has prioritized a diversity mindset for employees over the past decade is through <a href="https://www.sap.com/socialsabbatical">SAP Social Sabbatical</a>. In this program, SAP employees from around the world can share their skills, knowledge, and professional expertise with innovative non-profit organizations and social enterprises in emerging markets to help them solve their business challenges. The program has been run in over 52 countries with participants representing 64 different nationalities. This highlights our commitment to bring together different perspectives, amplifying the power of diversity of thought and experience, which creates positive impact for both the organizations and participating SAP employees.</p>
  <p>Meera Shenoy, founder of SAP Social Sabbatical host client <a href="https://www.youth4jobs.org/">Youth4Jobs</a>, shared how her organization benefited from the team’s diversity of professional experience: “The volunteers came from three different countries, and each had a different specialty. They quickly adopted our passion for inclusion and became part of the larger Youth4Jobs family, understanding our challenges and transformational work. They also gave us a peek into the amazing SAP processes in several areas. For example, the team shared the SAP neurodiversity training with us, and we got to learn the techniques that a corporation like SAP uses for neurodiversity inclusion in the workplace.”</p>
  <p>When diversity is incorporated through pro bono consulting programs like SAP Social Sabbatical, organizations are able to tap into the varied perspectives and approaches that each individual employee brings to the <a href="https://www2.deloitte.com/us/en/insights/focus/human-capital-trends/2014/hc-trends-2014-diversity-to-inclusion.html">workplace</a>. Research shows that diversified teams can lead to an increase in innovation, improve problem-solving, and boost decision-making. This can heighten performance by <a href="https://diversity-inclusion-speakers.com/news/tips-and-tricks/benefits-diversity-inclusion-workplace-statistics/#:~:text=%E2%80%9CRacially%20diverse%20teams%20report%20a,key%20factor%20in%20any%20workplace.">at least 35%</a>, which not only accelerates innovation within SAP but also helps the host client organization anticipate and fulfill the needs of diverse customers.</p>
  <h2 id="the-employee-advantage">The Employee Advantage</h2>
  <p>For employee participants, we know that the pro bono consulting benefits include skill development, networking opportunities, gaining new perspectives, and cultural immersion, among others. For example, a participant from India stated, “It gives you a whole new perspective that we don’t get in our day-to-day work.”</p>
  <p>From a recent <a href="https://www.sap.com/dmc/exp/2017_03_46558/enUS/impact/">long-term impact study</a> that we conducted in partnership with impact measurement social enterprise <a href="https://60decibels.com/">60 Decibels</a>, 88% of SAP employees who have participated in SAP Social Sabbatical reported that the program benefited them personally. Additionally, 86% of employees said their ability collaborate with global and diverse colleagues improved by their participation.</p>
  <p>“It allowed me to dive into a new world for weeks. You gain experience you have never had before. It brings you to a new level culture-wise, and you meet many talented people from SAP across the world,” said one participant from Germany.</p>
  <p>Another employee commented, “In my personal life, I am more aware of differences in people and better at understanding peoples’ challenges. These differences go beyond age, gender, geography and race but also diversity of thought, upbringing, values and perspectives. Understanding these differences is key to solving problems and empowering others.”</p>
  <h2 id="focusing-on-sustainable-long-term-impact">Focusing on Sustainable Long-Term Impact</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="explore-what-sap-is-doing-to-accelerate-social-businesses">Explore what SAP is doing to accelerate social businesses</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/our-values/csr.html#accelerate">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In addition to the diversity benefits for participants and social sector partners, the long-term impacts have gone beyond the SAP Social Sabbatical program. These principles of diversity as a building block of the program have supported the evolution of new initiatives that address social challenges and build equity, while leveraging pro bono consulting as a tool. In learning from our success over the past 10 years, we developed the Pro Bono for Economic Equity program in North America, which was launched in 2021 in partnership with <a href="https://www.pyxeraglobal.org/">PYXERA Global</a>, as part of SAP’s overall response to the social justice movement with an aim to foster economic equity for Black-owned business and social enterprises.</p>
  <p>The program allows SAP employees to leverage their professional skills and expertise as pro bono volunteer consultants for under-resourced businesses and social enterprises and help them address systemic and business challenges. Within the first year, the program expanded internationally to the UK, Brazil, and South Africa. Based on the success of the program, we have extended the cohorts to have a focus on Indigenous-owned businesses in Canada. <a href="/2022/05/pro-bono-for-economic-equity-impact">Learn more about the program here</a>.</p>
  <h2 id="cultivating-an-inclusive-mindset">Cultivating an Inclusive Mindset</h2>
  <p>At SAP, diversity and inclusion are not simply goals to strive for; they are strategic components of our corporate culture that fuel innovation and help us turn our purpose to action.</p>
  <p>We recognize that continuously bolstering the diversity, equity, and inclusion mindset is crucial when it comes to shaping the next generation of leaders in our company. Not only will this support employee engagement today, but it means that they will build a more inclusive environment when it comes to how they work in teams, how they hire, and how they engage colleagues who are different from them, now and into the future.</p>
  <p>For more information about SAP Social Sabbatical, visit <a href="https://www.sap.com/socialsabbatical">sap.com/socialsabbatical</a> and to learn about how SAP is empowering Black- and Indigenous-owned businesses and social enterprises, read <a href="/topics/pro-bono-for-economic-equity">more stories about the Pro Bono Economic Equity program here</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Hemang Desai is global program director for SAP Corporate Social Responsibility.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/life-at-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-social-sabbatical</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Community Holiday Shopping Guide: Ideas to Excite, Inspire, and Make an Impact]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/holiday-gift-guide-shopping-ideas-sap-community</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/holiday-gift-guide-shopping-ideas-sap-community</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Review our new holiday gift guide, a one-stop resource for all your shopping needs this holiday season, and all throughout the year.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/purpose</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
            <category>news-tag/social-enterprise</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Lasting Impact of SAP’s Early College High School Program]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/impact-of-sap-early-college-high-school-program</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/impact-of-sap-early-college-high-school-program</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A survey from SAP and Digital Promise reveals the lasting impact of Early College High School program participants in pursuing STEM.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/education</category>
            <category>industry/higher-education-research</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Named Best Corporate Steward by U.S. Chamber of Commerce Foundation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/sap-named-best-corporate-steward</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/sap-named-best-corporate-steward</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP has been named Best Corporate Steward by U.S. Chamber of Commerce Foundation for its commitment to a more inclusive, sustainable economy.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_158bc723afdf76ef6718b04ea6166dfa5dfcfab7a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_158bc723afdf76ef6718b04ea6166dfa5dfcfab7a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_158bc723afdf76ef6718b04ea6166dfa5dfcfab7a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Named Best Corporate Steward by U.S. Chamber of Commerce Foundation" src="./media_158bc723afdf76ef6718b04ea6166dfa5dfcfab7a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-named-best-corporate-steward-by-us-chamber-of-commerce-foundation">SAP Named Best Corporate Steward by U.S. Chamber of Commerce Foundation</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>The U.S. Chamber of Commerce Foundation named SAP “Best Corporate Steward: Large Business” at the 23rd annual Citizens Awards in Washington D.C. The recognition is given to the company that best demonstrates itself as a “responsive and responsible member of society, whose overall values, operational practices, and decision-making exemplify shared value.”</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1675116b99aa002c87c7da6d2f5648b6307bbba33.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1675116b99aa002c87c7da6d2f5648b6307bbba33.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1675116b99aa002c87c7da6d2f5648b6307bbba33.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_1675116b99aa002c87c7da6d2f5648b6307bbba33.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2252" height="2552">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p><em>SAP’s Jennifer Beason, Carmen Krueger, Jim Sullivan, Robin Manherz, Kevin Richards</em></p>
  <p>It was accepted on behalf of SAP by Global Chief Operating Officer Robin Manherz.</p>
  <p>SAP technology helps companies embed sustainability into core business processes, which, combined with an industry-leading social responsibility strategy, is delivering global solutions to unlock a more inclusive and sustainable economy.</p>
  <p>Manherz shared that this award means a lot to her personally and to the company. “This is such a tremendous and important honor for me to represent SAP tonight,” she said. “From the planes in the sky to the electricity on the grid, we run most of the world with our technology. We take that responsibility very seriously and look forward to working with you today and every day to make sure we are living up to our purpose.”</p>
  <p><a href="https://www.uschamberfoundation.org/citizens-awards/2022-winners">Meet all the Citizens Awards winners here</a>.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-how-the-sap-csr-team-is-working-toward-ensuring-an-inclusive-recovery-and-equal-opportunities-for-all">Learn more about how the SAP CSR team is working toward ensuring an inclusive recovery and equal opportunities for all</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/our-values/csr.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="helping-the-world-run-better-together">Helping the World Run Better, Together</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-what-life-looks-like-at-sap">Learn more about what life looks like at SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/careers/who-we-are.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP’s mission is to help every business become a sustainable, intelligent enterprise. In practice, that means we create solutions to manage the most mission-critical business operations, like finance, human resources, and manufacturing, that, at the same time, address some of the most profound economic, social, and environmental challenges of our time.</p>
  <p>For example, SAP Cloud for Sustainable Enterprises helps companies manage their carbon footprint and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/responsible-design-and-production.html">reduce material waste</a>. In addition to the <a href="https://www.sap.com/sustainability.html">sustainability</a> portfolio, SAP is investing in supply chain transparency through SAP Ariba and SAP Business Network to promote human rights, circularity, and socially responsible procurement standards. With more than $3 trillion traded across SAP Business Network, SAP has an opportunity to help companies shift procurement spend from traditional trading partners to companies like <a href="https://www.forthebluedot.com/">Blue Dot Way</a>, <a href="https://auticon.com/">Auticon</a>, and <a href="https://televerde.com/">Televerde</a>. Procuring quality goods and services from organizations like these increases investment in economic equity, social impact, and environmental sustainability in a way that cannot be done through corporate philanthropy alone.</p>
  <p>“SAP’s vision to help the world run better and improve people’s lives is evident through its investments and innovative technology to make a profound impact on the most vulnerable populations,” said Marc DeCourcey, senior vice president of the U.S. Chamber of Commerce Foundation. “Their purpose-driven culture serves as a model for companies around the world.”</p>
  <p>As DeCourcey affirms, technology by itself is not the answer. That is why SAP is also investing in equitable access to economic opportunity, education, and employment, as well as a green, circular economy.</p>
  <p>“As a company, we have an unwavering commitment to innovation and to the communities around the U.S. and the world where we operate,” shared Lloyd Adams, president of SAP North America. “This award belongs to our employees, customers, and partners who have committed to sustainable and equitable business practices that focus on supporting people and protecting the planet.”</p>
  <p>These values are embedded throughout the leadership culture at SAP, along with the way we engage and develop future talent. Adams, for example, personally champions the Autism at Work program and spearheads SAP North America’s Emerging Talent Advisory Board. In the past year alone, Adams and the North America leadership team engaged 30 next-generation leaders in the <a href="https://drive.google.com/file/d/1i4u5GiU8qCAwrssBcdVvQS51J1Q2Nbbs/view">Acceleration Collective</a>, a virtual pro bono consulting initiative, solving strategic business challenges for B2B social enterprises tackling issues of plastics and waste, inclusion, and responsible supply chains. And there are plans to continue embracing experiential learning through pro bono across North America in the future.</p>
  <p>In 2021, SAP Corporate Social Responsibility programs and partnerships trained more than 119,000 teachers, educated 3.5 million youth, 50% of whom were girls, and impacted more than 8.3 million lives. More than 20,000 employees globally engage in skills-based volunteerism through SAP, representing a $20 million in-kind contribution to impact organizations through pro bono consulting in the last decade.</p>
  <p>Looking ahead, SAP has reinforced its partnership with <a href="https://www.unicef.org/partnerships/sap-unicef-genu-help-young-people-gain-skills-for-employment">UNICEF</a> and Generation Unlimited, announcing the <a href="/2022/09/sap-unicef-global-youth-employment-coalition">SAP Educate to Employ initiative</a>, a program that supports learning-to-earning pathways in the digital and green economies for youth in need. Additionally, to help combat the global refugee crisis, SAP is fulfilling associate and bachelor’s degree scholarships with <a href="https://www.uopeople.edu/about/worldwide-recognition/press-releases/sap-providing-50-scholarships-for-ukrainian-refugees-at-uopeople/">University of the People</a>, the first nonprofit, tuition-free, American-accredited online university dedicated to providing global access to higher education.</p>
  <p>Based on SAP’s own success engaging employees and partners, SAP — together with EY, MovingWorlds, TRANSFORM, and Unilever — partnered to launch the <a href="https://movingworlds.org/transform/social-enterprises?utm_source=sap&#x26;utm_medium=email&#x26;utm_campaign=transformlaunch_0422">TRANSFORM Support Hub</a>, helping employees everywhere connect to social enterprises anywhere, through pro bono consulting, coaching, and more. The open, online platform is a place where new and existing partners can come together to expedite world-changing solutions. If you share our commitment to building a more sustainable world, we hope you will <a href="https://movingworlds.org/transform/corporates">join us</a>!</p>
  <p>To learn more about SAP and its purpose in action, visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/csr">www.sap.com/csr</a> and follow us on social media using @SAP4Good.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/life-at-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The "S" in ESG: A Business Imperative]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/esg-business-imperative</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/esg-business-imperative</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The "S" in a company's ESG (environmental, social, and governance) investment strategy is now a business imperative. Learn why.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-social-sabbatical</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Small Step in Space Exploration, a Giant Leap for Youth]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/flynn-doherty-redefining-youth-space-exploration-leap</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/flynn-doherty-redefining-youth-space-exploration-leap</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Flynn Doherty is among the thousands of inspiring participants from the Young ICT Explorers program, run by SAP. Read his story.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/redefining-youth</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Code Unnati: Inspiring Bright Futures through Digital Inclusion]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/code-unnati-digital-inclusion</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/code-unnati-digital-inclusion</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Code Unnati aims to impart digital literacy among adolescents, citizens, and children as well as employable IT skills among youth. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-education</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/redefining-youth</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Meet and Code: Closing Europe’s Digital Skills Gap One Student at a Time]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/meet-and-code-closing-digital-skills-gap</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/meet-and-code-closing-digital-skills-gap</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP’s Meet and Code initiative has helped non-profits introduce young people to the exciting world of technology and coding. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/redefining-youth</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Top Five Benefits of Social Sabbaticals]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/top-five-benefits-of-sap-social-sabbatical</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/top-five-benefits-of-sap-social-sabbatical</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Through the SAP Social Sabbatical program, employees experience many benefits, personally and professionally, and gain lifelong skills.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/purpose</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-social-sabbatical</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Businesses Can Accelerate the Work of Social Entrepreneurs to Change the World]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/sap-social-sabbatical-social-sector-partners-change-the-world</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/sap-social-sabbatical-social-sector-partners-change-the-world</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Through SAP Social Sabbatical , global social sector partners experience long-term benefits directly and in the communities they serve.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/purpose</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-social-sabbatical</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[World Refugee Day: SAP Accelerates Global Partnerships to Boost Education for Displaced Youth]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/06/world-refugee-day-sap-partnerships-education-for-displaced-youth</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/06/world-refugee-day-sap-partnerships-education-for-displaced-youth</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[This World Refugee Day, SAP CSR shines a light on our strategic initiatives that power access to education for refugees and displaced youth.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning-for-life</category>
            <category>news-tag/purpose</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How to Develop Tomorrow’s Purpose-Driven Leaders Today]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/06/developing-purpose-driven-leaders-sap-social-sabbatical</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/06/developing-purpose-driven-leaders-sap-social-sabbatical</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP has been developing purpose-driven leaders through 10 years of the SAP Social Sabbatical. Learn more about the program's impact.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-social-sabbatical</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Forward Together for an Equitable Future]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/forward-together-equitable-future</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/forward-together-equitable-future</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Moving "forward together," the SAP Corporate Social Responsibility team is embarking on a refreshed strategy. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/moments-of-service</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Women Empowering Women: Catalyzing Globally-Minded Leaders for Long-Term Impact]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/women-empowering-women-leaders-long-term-impact</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/women-empowering-women-leaders-long-term-impact</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP's Gina McNamara shares her SAP Social Sabbatical experience in Kenya and how it spurred her passion and effort around women empowerment.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/business-womens-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/purpose</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-social-sabbatical</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
            <category>news-tag/women-at-sap</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Impact of SAP's Pro Bono for Economic Equity Program]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/pro-bono-for-economic-equity-impact</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/pro-bono-for-economic-equity-impact</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP launched Pro Bono for Economic Equity in 2021 to help Black-owned businesses and social enterprises. Learn more about its impact.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/pro-bono-for-economic-equity</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hitachi Is Making the Decarbonization of Society a Reality]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/04/hitachi-making-decarbonization-a-reality</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/04/hitachi-making-decarbonization-a-reality</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Through its sustainable business practices and public-private partnerships, Hitachi catalyzes climate action from the inside out. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/climate-action</category>
            <category>news-tag/climate-change</category>
            <category>non-sap-event/cop26</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Acceleration Collective: Small Contribution, Big Impact]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/02/acceleration-collective-small-contribution-big-impact</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/02/acceleration-collective-small-contribution-big-impact</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Through the Acceleration Collective, SAP colleagues apply their skills to organizations that lead through sustainable business practices.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_110aa5b25939256a2229893d1150931d9f8a01a23.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_110aa5b25939256a2229893d1150931d9f8a01a23.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_110aa5b25939256a2229893d1150931d9f8a01a23.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Acceleration Collective: Small Contribution, Big Impact" src="./media_110aa5b25939256a2229893d1150931d9f8a01a23.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="acceleration-collective-small-contribution-big-impact">Acceleration Collective: Small Contribution, Big Impact</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-how-sap-is-powering-opportunity-for-all-people-through-digital-inclusion">Learn how SAP is powering opportunity for all people through digital inclusion</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/csr.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Sometimes the things you consider to be a small contribution can amount to big impact. In 2021, I had the honor of being asked to coach a young entrepreneur as part of the <strong>Acceleration Collective</strong>, a <a href="https://movingworlds.org/partner/sap/acceleration-collective-employees">virtual pro bono consulting experience from SAP</a>, powered by MovingWorlds.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In the corporate world, you hear a lot about supporting the future of business. This program flips that concept on its head, and instead focuses on the opportunity for SAP employees to connect with and support the “business of future,” a phrase referring to next-generation leaders and organizations that operate as social enterprises.</p>
  <p>Acceleration Collective matches the skills and expertise of SAP employees everywhere with social entrepreneurs anywhere. The <a href="/2021/07/possibilists-study-youth-lead-post-pandemic-world">young social innovators</a> — or <a href="https://thepossibilists.org/">Possibilists</a> as they are also called — need support to solve critical business challenges. SAP employees offer that support to them in two ways: as certified coaches and as pro bono consultants also known as “experteers,” each volunteer position playing a critical role in support of the enterprises.</p>
  <p>In my case, I worked as a coach with <a href="/topics/we-are-family-foundation">We Are Family Foundation</a> Global Teen Leader <a href="https://www.wearefamilyfoundation.org/gtl-2021/angela-busheska">Angela Busheska</a><u>,</u> the founder of <a href="https://www.enroute-app.com/">En Route</a>. Angela has personally experienced the impact of climate change, recently losing her aunt as a result of extreme air pollution. “I wasn’t committed until I saw the negative impact of pollution firsthand. I knew I had to do something.” The death of Angela’s aunt is not an isolated event in her home country of <a href="https://www.aljazeera.com/gallery/2021/4/21/in-pictures-air-pollution-in-north-macedonia">North Macedonia</a>, and she wants that to change.</p>
  <p>Her answer to a better future is En Route, a tech startup that educates children about their carbon footprints through an interactive, gamified app that makes being environmentally responsible fun. Their aim is simple: build a community that will save the planet.</p>
  <p>“COVID has turned the world into a global village. I use technology to not only connect to organizations that can help me [We Are Family Foundation, SAP], but also to connect to others. I want to transform the people who don’t care,” Angela offered.</p>
  <p>Angela knew she wanted to grow her organization, reach more children, and make a bigger impact. But where to start? Through a couple of coaching exercises that help the client identify and rank priorities, Angela quickly realized that funding for growth was the essential next step. Backing out of the funding goal she identified all the necessary steps to find donors. She did the work and it paid off. I was delighted to learn that Angela had this to say about our coaching experience together: “I was working with Allison on what’s next for me and En Route. Her support ultimately helped me create the strategic connections I needed for my business.”</p>
  <p>Through coaching, Angela tapped into all the answers that were already within her. In early January she shared the following: “I am so happy to inform you that our sessions were a success and we ended up being funded by <a href="https://storymaps.arcgis.com/stories/085f4052608944abb6bff76c307b86d8">National Geographic</a>!” I am over the moon excited for this young entrepreneur, and frankly for all of the young leaders who are inspiring global change. Angela told me that she got started because she was tired of everyone blaming others for what was wrong. She wanted to do something. Her engagement with me and this program is another example that she does not just talk about making the change, she gets to work.</p>
  <p>I started coaching in 2017, and it has become one of the most rewarding experiences of my life. Helping clients discover the answers within themselves and seeing them grow, accomplish goals, and thrive is truly an amazing experience. When clients successfully realize their potential through coaching, there is nothing.</p>
  <p>This experience in particular was an opportunity to push the envelope of what is possible through coaching. I’m proud to know that my efforts helped someone who is truly making a difference in the world. En Route teaches children the importance of their carbon footprint, and helps them form sustainable habits at an early age. The potential impact of such an effort is exciting.</p>
  <p>Sustainability topics have long been of interest to me, and this opportunity allowed me to combine my love of coaching with a meaningful cause — a win-win for me. My small contribution to the Acceleration Collective has resulted in a positive impact on Angela, her organization, and hopefully the world.</p>
  <p>You can learn more about the Acceleration Collective and other SAP Corporate Social Responsibility programs by visiting <a href="http://www.sap.com/csr">sap.com/csr</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Allison Gapter is vice president of Global Strategic Ecosystem Marketing at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/moments-of-service</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
            <category>news-tag/we-are-family-foundation</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP and University of the People: Educate the Leaders of Tomorrow]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2022/02/sap-university-of-the-people-educate-leaders</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2022/02/sap-university-of-the-people-educate-leaders</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In partnership with University of the People, SAP is establishing 100 higher education scholarship for refugees and displaced youth.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/executive-blog</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning-for-life</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Volunteering Now for Our Common Future]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/international-volunteer-day-common-future</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/12/international-volunteer-day-common-future</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In the wake of International Volunteer Day, get the highlights on how SAP employees support their communities worldwide.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b93f175ced05c33ccf0725f22369911d25972fc8.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b93f175ced05c33ccf0725f22369911d25972fc8.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1b93f175ced05c33ccf0725f22369911d25972fc8.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Volunteering Now for Our Common Future" src="./media_1b93f175ced05c33ccf0725f22369911d25972fc8.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="volunteering-now-for-our-common-future">Volunteering Now for Our Common Future</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Each year on December 5, the United Nations (UN) Volunteers organization hosts International Volunteer Day with the goal of <a href="https://www.un.org/en/observances/volunteer-day">recognizing and promoting the dedication of volunteers</a> around the world.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Most of the world’s volunteering happens informally and cannot be tracked, but the <a href="https://swvr2022.unv.org/">documented economic contribution</a> of time and support that volunteers deliver globally is estimated to represent the work of approximately 61 million full-time workers monthly.</p>
  <p>In a world struggling to combat seemingly insurmountable issues like climate change, a global health crisis, and growing inequality, even millions of volunteers are not enough. While it is easy to focus on the problems, International Volunteer Day represents an important opportunity to appreciate and reflect on the efforts of the incredible commitment and passion of <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/csr.html#connect">those at SAP who dedicate their time and talents as volunteers</a> to help the world run better and improve people’s lives.</p>
  <p>As non-profit partners in residence working with the SAP Corporate Social Responsibility (CSR) team, we offer a unique perspective on days like this. While we live and breathe the value of volunteering, we know that our experience is not shared by everyone. Volunteering helps others while also promoting learning, personal growth, and community. Together we bring our non-profit organizations’ — <a href="https://www.realizedworth.com/">Realized Worth</a> and <a href="https://www.handsonbayarea.org/">HandsOn Bay Area</a> — extensive experience in social impact and volunteer management alongside our own, collaborating for sustainability with employees directly.</p>
  <p>As the newest members of the SAP CSR team, we have learned so much in a short time about what it means when companies like SAP provide skills-based volunteering services to non-profits and social enterprises, and just how valuable it is to the underserved communities that SAP volunteers support across <a href="https://joom.ag/rUVC/p6">113 countries</a>.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="how-sap-csr-empowers-employees-to-take-action-on-causes-they-care-about">How SAP CSR empowers employees to take action on causes they care about</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/csr.html#connect">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="why-volunteering-matters">Why Volunteering Matters</h2>
  <p>A common misconception about volunteering, especially skills-based volunteering, is that the engagement only delivers value to the organization and its respective clients being served.</p>
  <p>One of the most significant reasons why corporate volunteering matters is that it is an experiential leadership opportunity. It offers employees a chance to build new skills and put current expertise into action while also satisfying a non-profit or community need. Ultimately, this helps employees explore and fulfill career goals, and gain exposure to different perspectives as well as business-relevant experiences to grow personally and professionally.</p>
  <p>Beyond personal growth, corporate volunteering is good business. Companies benefit from employee participation in many ways. For example, when employees volunteer through work, they can become more engaged and connected and experience greater personal fulfillment.</p>
  <p>The various skills-based volunteer opportunities available at SAP all offer meaningful ways to strengthen inclusive and empathetic leadership, communication, and teamwork among so many other important career- and company-building skills.</p>
  <p>Chris Jarvis, co-founder and chief strategy officer of Realized Worth, confirms this: “The contribution of time and other resources to charities and their communities is profoundly valuable. Without these contributions, our world would have a grave deficit of social, human, and physical capital. But the power of volunteering lies in more than its utilitarian application. As passionate volunteers will profess, it is not the transaction that motivates them; rather, it is the transformation that occurs in their own lives.”</p>
  <p>This year, after more than 15 years of focused volunteer engagement each October, SAP evolved its signature volunteer campaign to <a href="/2021/08/moments-of-service-impactful-employee-engagement">Moments of Service</a>. With the shift, SAP is enabling its more than 105,000 employees with varied and valuable skills to connect to causes that matter to them personally. Through skills-based volunteering opportunities, they can create sustainable, long-lasting change in their communities and across the SAP ecosystem.</p>
  <h2 id="volunteering-now-at-sap">Volunteering Now at SAP</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="moments-of-service-a-re-energized-approach-to-impactful-employee-engagement">Moments of Service: A Re-Energized Approach to Impactful Employee Engagement</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/08/moments-of-service-impactful-employee-engagement">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Building on more than a decade of success in our pro bono volunteering portfolio, we are honored to work alongside the SAP CSR team to diligently transform programs like SAP Social Sabbatical and grow new ones including Pro Bono for Economic Equity, a response to SAP’s social justice commitments, and the virtual pro bono Acceleration Collective initiative.</p>
  <p>“Working alongside <a href="https://movingworlds.org/">MovingWorlds</a> to serve young social entrepreneurs from the <a href="https://changemakerxchange.org/">ChangemakerXChange</a>, <a href="https://socialshifters.co/">Social Shifters</a>, and <a href="https://www.wearefamilyfoundation.org/">We Are Family Foundation</a> communities, we are hopeful that we can improve the experience and most importantly the social impact of virtual pro bono volunteering,” shares Jennifer Beason, global program director of SAP CSR. “We are honored that more than 60 expert volunteers and certified coaches are working with us to accelerate the success of 25 outstanding social businesses like <a href="http://www.durian.org.ng/">Durian</a>, a Nigeria-based social enterprise that is building communities of the future – circular, creative, and empowered by rural women.”</p>
  <p>The company’s longest running pro bono portfolio, <strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/dmc/exp/2017_03_46558/enUS/index.html">SAP Social Sabbatical</a></strong>, which is executed in partnership with <a href="https://www.pyxeraglobal.org/">PYXERA Global</a>, has embraced local roles for employees to help tackle global goals right in their own backyard. By keeping employees and programs closer to home, SAP volunteers were able to continue delivering impact despite the pandemic. Working with diverse teams and matched with nonprofits and social enterprises, employees like Esteban Samartin dedicated an estimated $450,000 (estimated USAID value) in pro bono consulting services to solve strategic business assignments in 2021.</p>
  <p><strong><a href="https://sap.sharepoint.com/sites/124545">Pro Bono for Economic Equity</a></strong>, also in partnership with PYXERA Global, follows a similar structure to SAP Social Sabbatical. Small teams of SAP employees are paired with Black-owned businesses to provide their professional skills as pro bono volunteer consultants. At a recent closing event for the U.S. arm of the program, a key theme was that SAP groups offered frameworks and scalable solutions that the businesses can use again and again. A favorite example was a team that developed marketing strategies and templates for baking mix company <a href="https://sugarlessketo.com/">Sugarless Keto</a>. Initially launched in the U.S., the program expanded to Brazil, South Africa, and the UK in the second half of 2021.</p>
  <p>Joining the SAP CSR team with nonprofit backgrounds, our view of corporate volunteerism was very different than the reality of what we now experience and observe every day. The global scale at which SAP’s portfolio of programs and partnerships operate is greater than we imagined.</p>
  <p>It might be difficult to comprehend the difference that SAP employees are making to the more than 1,500 organizations they are serving, but the connections being made are providing the building blocks for more resilient communities. We have seen firsthand that impactful and meaningful work through volunteerism does not just benefit the recipient non-profit organizations – one employee’s contributions to one project can affect thousands of people.</p>
  <p>‘Tis the season for good news and it brings us great joy knowing the work that we are a part of is changing lives for the better. To share how you are making difference, tag us on social media using #SAP4good and share how you are helping your community run better.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Heidi Pio and Atalanta Kyriazi are non-profit partners in residence with the SAP CSR team.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/moments-of-service</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Regenerative by Design: New Video from The Circular Design Project]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/regenerative-design-circular-design-project-video</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/regenerative-design-circular-design-project-video</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Executives from SAP, the London Design Festival, and Ellen MacArthur Foundation discussed regenerative design and the circular economy.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/circular-economy</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Meet Africa Code Week’s Youth Ambassador]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/africa-code-week-youth-ambassador</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/africa-code-week-youth-ambassador</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Africa Code Week’s 2021 Youth Ambassador is 17-year-old Nigerian student Victory Yinka-Banjo, who is eager to empower young African minds.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1da3fe95137eee9f68d07672d3baa31b3eaaada98.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1da3fe95137eee9f68d07672d3baa31b3eaaada98.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1da3fe95137eee9f68d07672d3baa31b3eaaada98.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Meet Africa Code Week’s Youth Ambassador" src="./media_1da3fe95137eee9f68d07672d3baa31b3eaaada98.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="meet-africa-code-weeks-youth-ambassador">Meet Africa Code Week’s Youth Ambassador</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Speaking to Victory Yinka-Banjo is like drinking a fizzy drink; she bubbles with ideas and confidence. It’s no wonder that this 17-year-old Nigerian was chosen to be this year’s youth ambassador for Africa Code Week, the continent’s biggest digital skills youth initiative.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Even at her young age, Victory is no stranger to publicity. Earlier this year, she was offered 19 full scholarships to study at North American universities (She ended up picking MIT). But hers is no rags-to-riches story. The eldest daughter of two smart parents, a university lecturer mother and a father who works in procurement and supply chain management, Victory has always pushed herself to the limit. “My mother taught me how to hustle, and without this scholarship I could never have afforded to study in the U.S.,” she points out.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-africa-code-week">Learn more about Africa Code Week</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://africacodeweek.org/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="youth-ambassador-and-it-role-model-for-girls">Youth Ambassador and IT Role Model for Girls</h2>
  <p>Victory is looking forward to getting involved in this year’s <a href="https://africacodeweek.org/">Africa Code Week</a>, of which she is the official youth ambassador. Girls in science, technology, engineering, and mathematics (STEM) have traditionally lagged behind boys, which is why SAP and Camden Education Trust, the founders of Africa Code Week, are on a mission to make a difference – one African community at a time. Now in its seventh year, the program was proud to report 47% female participation in 2020. The event, which includes the popular AfriCANCode Challenge, has an enormous reach of 54 countries, with millions of children and youth participating. Last year, the program completely shifted to the exciting online world due to <a href="/covid-19">COVID-19</a>.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f25f5e30155c3b5c3c58d16be04bb33c57c10f19.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f25f5e30155c3b5c3c58d16be04bb33c57c10f19.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1f25f5e30155c3b5c3c58d16be04bb33c57c10f19.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Victory Yinka-Banjo headshot" src="./media_1f25f5e30155c3b5c3c58d16be04bb33c57c10f19.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="241" height="300">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p><em>Victory Yinka-Banjo</em></p>
  <p>“I participate in digital youth skills initiatives like Africa Code Week because I am passionate about empowering young people in underserved communities,” she says. Last year, she created an educational video encouraging children to learn computer programming with Scratch, MIT’s free online learning tool for coding. “Scratch is how I was introduced to coding,” she says, mentioning all its various applications that make it fun for kids, from interactive stories and games to animations. Scratch forms an integral part of Africa Code Week, encouraging teachers and African governments to see how easy it is to get kids into coding and fast-track them to the 21<sup>st</sup> century. To date, nine countries have adopted coding as a school subject thanks to the ongoing awareness, support, and contributions from the Africa Code Week program.</p>
  <p>A proud, female code representative, Victory wears many hats and keeps herself busy with multiple projects. In addition to Africa Code Week, she is actively involved with <a href="https://coderina.org/">Coderina</a>, a nonprofit organization that promotes ICT development, youth innovation, and entrepreneurship across Africa.</p>
  <p>“My first introduction to Coderina was during the pandemic last year. I helped facilitate the Lifelong Learning Program (LLP) sessions where young people were able to learn from a virtual space about everything digital skills related, from coding to 3D printing. I also taught a class during this period on design thinking and innovation. This year, I was a coach to the First Lego League (FLL) team comprising of a group of girls in secondary school in Nigeria. FLL is an exciting international robotics competition that is largely driven by Coderina.”</p>
  <h2 id="passionate-about-finding-solutions">Passionate About Finding Solutions</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="advancing-digital-skills-when-needed-most">Advancing Digital Skills When Needed Most</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/08/advancing-digital-skills-when-needed-most-sap-young-professionals-program">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>When asked what she likes about coding, Victory is unequivocal: she wants to find solutions. “I love the challenge of being given a problem and using technology to find a way to solve it,” she says. In 2019, she was part of the winning African team in the global mobile app building competition, Technovation. “The problem we had to solve was double parking, which is common in Nigeria,” she explains. “We developed an app that uses location sensors to enable your phone to pick up whenever another car parks you in, so you can step outside and speak to the owner or can communicate with the owner via instant messaging on the app.”</p>
  <p>It is this same passion for solving problems that has made her pursue a career in computer science and molecular biology. “There are so many different applications of these novel, overlapping fields, from aspects of synthetic biology to RNA sequencing in bioinformatics,” she says. Some of the questions that interest her are whether DNA can be used to store digital data and what machine learning tools can be used to model a vaccine to tackle the next variant of the coronavirus.</p>
  <p>One thing she’s sure about is that she doesn’t want to be put in a box. “Too many young people are fixated about their future career, wanting to become a doctor, engineer, or lawyer,” she says. “So many things are unconventional now. Rather than having a fixed profession, I want to say, ‘I do computational biology and it allows me to proffer solutions to this and that.’” Having a problem-solving mindset will elevate young Africans to be the change they want to see in the world, she believes – with a little bit of help from technology, of course.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Adam Hunter is EMEA communications lead for SAP CSR.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>non-sap-event/africa-code week</category>
            <category>news-tag/csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Launching the Wheel of Purpose with UNCTAD]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/unctad-wheel-of-purpose</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/unctad-wheel-of-purpose</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP's collaboration on the Wheel of Purpose with UNCTAD provides a powerful example of purpose-driven public-private partnership.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15a8d984f3057fba51e82e2f1a29e4bd2d6e8dfa0.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15a8d984f3057fba51e82e2f1a29e4bd2d6e8dfa0.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_15a8d984f3057fba51e82e2f1a29e4bd2d6e8dfa0.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Launching the Wheel of Purpose with UNCTAD" src="./media_15a8d984f3057fba51e82e2f1a29e4bd2d6e8dfa0.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="launching-the-wheel-of-purpose-with-unctad">Launching the Wheel of Purpose with UNCTAD</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>What if you had a “blueprint to achieve a better and more sustainable future for all?” Would you execute on it? And how would you leverage the power of collaboration to scale and accelerate your efforts?</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In 2015, the United Nations (UN) General Assembly provided humanity with this <a href="https://sdgs.un.org/goals">blueprint for a better and more sustainable future</a> through a collection of 17 goals, known today as the UN Sustainable Development Goals (<a href="/topics/un-sdgs">SDGs</a>). They include ending poverty, promoting good health and well-being, reducing inequalities, supporting responsible consumption and production, and more.</p>
  <p>The 17th SDG, “partnerships for the goals,” urgently calls on the public and private sectors, non-governmental organizations (NGOs), and citizens to come together to strengthen the implementation of the SDGs.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="saps-purpose-is-to-help-the-world-run-better-and-improve-peoples-lives-with-sustainability-at-the-core">SAP’s purpose is to help the world run better and improve people's lives with sustainability at the core</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/purpose-and-sustainability.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="public-and-private-sector-collaboration">Public and Private Sector Collaboration</h2>
  <p>At SAP, in alignment with <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/purpose-and-sustainability.html">our purpose</a> to help the world run better and improve people’s lives, with sustainability at the core, we value the opportunity to work alongside organizations driving meaningful impact.</p>
  <p>Our commitment to a more sustainable future inspired the sustainability team and a team of designers and engineers at SAP to develop a gamified, educational experience tied to the SDGs: the <a href="https://unctad.org/wheelofpurpose">Wheel of Purpose</a>. This innovative showcase, which runs on SAP technology, brings to life SAP’s commitment to the SDGs and encourages purpose-driven conversations among employees, customers, and partners.</p>
  <p>The <a href="https://unctad.org/">UN Conference on Trade and Development</a> (UNCTAD) expressed interest in the Wheel of Purpose because of its ease of use and ability to engage users virtually. This led to a public-private partnership to further develop and amplify the reach of the Wheel of Purpose, using it to showcase UNCTAD’s vision to bring about sustainable prosperity for all through trade.</p>
  <p>In the upcoming UNCTAD Youth Forum (September 16-17), the UNCTAD 15 Conference in Barbados (October 3-7), and the World Investment Forum (October 18-22), organizers will embed the Wheel of Purpose into virtual programming.</p>
  <p>“Sustainable development is a complex challenge, but it is a responsibility shared by everyone,” says Arlette Verploegh, UNCTAD chief of communications and external relations. “We need tools that humanize and explain different pathways to sustainability. The Wheel of Purpose does that. Applied to UNCTAD’s work, it showcases what we do in a simple, gamified way. The wheel is at once educational and inspirational to our audiences and reinforces our commitment to the 2030 Agenda.”</p>
  <h2 id="technology-as-a-tool-for-change">Technology as a Tool for Change</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="build-sustainability-directly-into-your-core-business-processes-with-sap">Build sustainability directly into your core business processes with SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/sustainability.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>At SAP, we make sustainability core to business and we believe in the disruptive power of innovative technology and its critical role in creating tangible impact for the UN SDGs. Not only can SAP solutions enable the integration of sustainability insights into business processes, but they can also educate the public, raise awareness, and help us achieve joint sustainability goals alongside our global ecosystem of customers and partners.</p>
  <p>“Our collaboration on the Wheel of Purpose with UNCTAD provides a powerful example of purpose-driven partnership between the public and private sector,” says Daniel Schmid, chief sustainability officer, SAP. “We are excited to amplify the reach of this engaging digital showcase and inform others about how UNCTAD and SAP engage in meaningful efforts to accelerate the UN’s global agenda.”</p>
  <p>Explore the <a href="https://unctad.org/wheelofpurpose">Wheel of Purpose here</a>, and share it with your network to spark the conversations that motivate tangible action for the SDGs. Only in partnership can we create the transformational change required to bring about “peace and prosperity for people and the planet.”</p>
  <p>For more information on the SDGs:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Read the <a href="http://www.sap.com/unglobalgoals">SAP &#x26; UN Global Goals</a> web book, which launched in 2016, to explore tangible examples of how SAP, our customers, and our partners leverage the enabling power of digitalization to contribute to the SDGs.</li>
    <li>Sign up for a free openSAP course, <a href="https://open.sap.com/courses/sbi2">Sustainability Through Digital Transformation</a>, which covers sustainability frameworks, including the SDGs, and how companies can use digitization to contribute to achieving them.</li>
  </ul>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
            <category>news-tag/un-sdgs</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Interconnected Nature of Profitability and Sustainability]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/sustainability-journey-profitability-interconnected-nature</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/sustainability-journey-profitability-interconnected-nature</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Companies that commit to a sustainability journey today will be the ones that remain competitive and relevant tomorrow. Learn why.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_128b56351e31d3f600b1103bd3d2cb09d32e35259.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_128b56351e31d3f600b1103bd3d2cb09d32e35259.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_128b56351e31d3f600b1103bd3d2cb09d32e35259.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="The Interconnected Nature of Profitability and Sustainability" src="./media_128b56351e31d3f600b1103bd3d2cb09d32e35259.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="the-interconnected-nature-of-profitability-and-sustainability">The Interconnected Nature of Profitability and Sustainability</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>At SAP, we often discuss the link between profitability and sustainability, asking, “Are companies that are more sustainable also more profitable?” But upon further reflection, the better question is “Can a company that is not sustainable be successful long term?”</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>I believe that companies that commit to their sustainability journeys today will be the ones that remain competitive and relevant tomorrow. To explore the link between profitability and sustainability in more depth, we need to consider the <strong>time frame</strong>, the way we define <strong>success</strong>, and how we <strong>measure</strong> a company’s value.</p>
  <p>These factors accelerate the paradigm shift from profit maximization to value optimization.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="chasing-zero-aspire-to-a-world-with-zero-emissions-zero-waste-and-zero-inequality">Chasing Zero: Aspire to a world with zero emissions, zero waste, and zero inequality</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/purpose-and-sustainability.html#chasing-zero">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="time-frame">Time Frame</h2>
  <p>As companies recover from <a href="/covid-19">COVID-19</a>, business leaders must consider short-term financial profitability and maximizing shareholder value alongside environmental and social factors that could affect the business’ success in the future. It comes back to the question: “Can a company that is not sustainable be successful long term?”</p>
  <p>Fortunately, even in the short term, a clear link exists between sustainability and profitability. For example, the replacement of business travel with remote collaboration enhances sustainability and cuts down on travel costs. At SAP, a focus on climate action has contributed to a cumulative cost avoidance of €354.3 million in the past three years. However, we achieved 92% of this cost avoidance in 2020, when we were forced to rethink business as usual, illustrating the immense possibility for large-scale impact.</p>
  <p>Nevertheless, sustainability can sometimes require investing today in the long-run profitability of a company and incurring costs that will pay off later. Companies already make many investments with the hopes of “returns” at a future date, such as marketing campaigns or <a href="/2021/03/mental-health-day-sap-employees">giving employees an extra day off</a> to boost their motivation, improve well-being, and increase productivity. Employee training offers another example of an initial investment with payoff down the line.</p>
  <p>In 2019, SAP joined the <a href="/2019/08/value-balancing-alliance-sap-founding-member">Value Balancing Alliance</a> (VBA) to better understand the entire value contribution of our business, which will be further explored below. According to the VBA, our global employee training programs were valued at €1.3 billion, but much of this payoff will be seen years from now through employee output, retention, and satisfaction.</p>
  <p>Broadening the time frame through which you view business success can enable more strategic decision making that sets the company up to thrive not just today, but tomorrow and for years to come.</p>
  <h2 id="redefining-success">Redefining Success</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-more-stories-about-the-chasing-zero-initiative">Read more stories about the Chasing Zero initiative</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/topics/chasing-zero">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Long-term profitability and sustainability present the opportunity to question historical definitions of business success. Profit maximization and increasing shareholder value alone will no longer suffice. The concept of <a href="https://www.sharedvalue.org/about/what-is-shared-value/">shared value</a> presents an alternative way to define success, one that uses core business processes to drive societal change.</p>
  <p>In Harvard Business School’s <em>Sustainable Business Strategy</em> concept, the “wheel of change” illustrates how large-scale transformation occurs across entire industries, starting with shared value. When businesses “do well and do good” through legitimate, innovative practices, it can inspire industry-wide cooperation that alters consumer, investor, and state behavior. This encourages companies to adopt more sustainable practices, ultimately redefining success in a way that considers the entire value creation of an entity.</p>
  <p>Consumer, investor, and state behaviors play a critical role in holding the private sector accountable for prioritizing shared value. Consumers and employees want to support and work for purpose-driven companies. Investors demand that companies disclose not only financial performance but also environmental, social, and governance (ESG) performance to properly assess risk and make investment decisions. And governments increasingly implement climate-related regulations, taxes, and policies, as well as workplace safety procedures, extended producer responsibility (EPR) schemes, anti-discrimination laws, and more.</p>
  <p>For businesses, it will be critical to consider a holistic view of their performance, one that integrates positive and negative impacts on the economy, society, and the environment. Research shows that a <a href="https://www.responsible-investor.com/storage/inline/ESG%20Study%202018%20-%20Digging%20deeper%20-%20112018.pdf">strong correlation exists between ESG performance and operational performance</a>.</p>
  <h2 id="measurement">Measurement</h2>
  <p>Redefining success to include sustainability requires measurements that capture this element of performance. For business leaders to make the appropriate decisions and set the strategy for a company’s long-term success, they need access to comprehensive data and metrics that go beyond financial measurements. This enables holistic steering and reporting, with the visibility required to mitigate negative ESG impact and increase positive ESG impact.</p>
  <p>As mentioned previously, SAP joined the VBA in an effort to transform the way businesses measure and value their societal impact. The VBA develops and tests methodologies that assign a monetary value to the impact of any decision, translating environmental and social impacts into comparable financial data. The VBA equips decision-makers with the knowledge to decide and act consciously.</p>
  <p>Profitability is a necessary condition for sustainability but alone is insufficient. Business can positively impact planet and people, but not if limited planetary resources run out. Unfortunately, the earth’s resources do not align with earnings cycles or CEO tenures, and sooner or later we will suffer the consequences.</p>
  <p>Paul Polman recognized this early on and launched Unilever’s <a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/us-sustainbility-unilever-ceo-idUSBRE8A11FH20121102">Sustainable Living Plan</a> (SLP) to help ensure that his business would be around 50, 100, or 200 years from now. The SLP shifted Unilever’s focus from solely meeting investor’s quarterly earnings to putting environmental and social impact top of mind. Similarly, Kering developed an <a href="https://www.kering.com/en/sustainability/measuring-our-impact/our-ep-l/what-is-an-ep-l/">Environmental Profit and Loss Account</a> to effectively measure its environmental footprint and convert it into monetary value. Utilizing this measurement tool provides a holistic approach to reporting that guides business decisions and respects natural resources.</p>
  <p>Unilever and Kering know that the successful businesses of the future will integrate sustainability into core business operations today.</p>
  <p>By adopting a long-term perspective, redefining success, and adjusting how we measure it, we can inspire a paradigm shift from profit maximization to value optimization, altering the status quo at our own companies and throughout the world. Innovation, business model transformation, and cross-industry collaboration will fuel this change. Wherever your business is today, this transition is a journey.</p>
  <p>You may not be there yet, but it’s time to start by putting this question front and center: “Can a company that is not sustainable be successful long-term?”</p>
  <p>At SAP, we believe it cannot.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Daniel Schmid is chief sustainability officer of SAP SE.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/chasing-zero</category>
            <category>news-tag/economics</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[To the Young People Who Move Us Forward]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/international-youth-day-young-people-move-us-forward</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/international-youth-day-young-people-move-us-forward</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[On International Youth Day, SAP thanks the future of business who are shaping the business of future. Learn more about our gratitude.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_105fe4b2ea2df77b44006256013330a86b5c479a0.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_105fe4b2ea2df77b44006256013330a86b5c479a0.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_105fe4b2ea2df77b44006256013330a86b5c479a0.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="To the Young People Who Move Us Forward" src="./media_105fe4b2ea2df77b44006256013330a86b5c479a0.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="to-the-young-people-who-move-us-forward">To the Young People Who Move Us Forward</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>To young people worldwide, on International Youth Day, I offer my gratitude to you on behalf of our 103,000 colleagues at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>To the doers, the dreamers, and those like <a href="https://vimeo.com/446987417">Teevyah</a> and <a href="https://vimeo.com/431802348">Veenadhari</a> who are <a href="https://www.un.org/en/observances/youth-day">transforming food systems</a>, we honor you. To all The Possibilists who dare businesses to do things differently, we hear you. We see you. You are not just the future of business; you are shaping the business of future!</p>
  <p>For every Greta, Malala, or Simone making global headlines, there are thousands of young changemakers like you, <a href="/2021/08/african-refugee-camps-youth-inspire-change">Avina</a>, <a href="/2021/07/possibilists-study-youth-lead-post-pandemic-world">Ryan</a>, and <a href="/2021/08/the-world-within-us-passion-travel-purpose">Anina</a>, who are making a world of difference in communities and countries alike. The successes and struggles documented in <a href="https://thepossibilists.org/">The Possibilists</a>, a recent report by an alliance of 16 of the world’s leading youth social innovation networks, is a reminder to all of us that you can’t be stopped. And if we can unite business, government, and the social sector around your work, we will succeed in accelerating (your) solutions to the world’s most challenging problems.</p>
  <p>While traditional business has much to learn from social innovators, we also have a lot to offer you.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="in-a-post-pandemic-world-youth-take-center-stage-and-lead">In a Post-Pandemic World, Youth Take Center Stage and Lead</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/07/possibilists-study-youth-lead-post-pandemic-world">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="accessing-networks-build-bridges-not-silos">1. Accessing Networks: Build Bridges, Not Silos</h2>
  <p>Many of the solutions the world needs already exist, but gaining access to the right people and organizations to share those solutions with is not as easy. More than 94% of Possibilists shared that they lack the personal or business access needed to move their organization forward. And yet, combined with financial and mental hardships, they forge on with their work because they are intrinsically motivated to do the right thing for the world. So how can corporations create space for leaders like you to bring game changing ideas to the table? It might be easier than you think.</p>
  <p>In 2020, SAP formally launched “Youth To The Table” in partnership with <a href="https://www.wearefamilyfoundation.org/">We Are Family Foundation</a>, giving skilled experts like Riddhima Yadav, a young climate and sustainability finance expert, a seat at c-suite level decision making tables at SAP. Riddhima joined SAP’s External Sustainability Advisory Council this year, joining the ranks of tenured sustainability leaders. Together, the council members provide formal outside-in guidance on SAP’s sustainability journey. Like many of The Possibilists, Riddhima formed her first organization as a teenager. Although still “early” in her career, she is an outstanding representative for both her field of expertise and her generation.</p>
  <p>A program like Youth To The Table should not only exist within one company, and perhaps we can help change that. I challenge you to approach the business leaders and companies operating in your field of interest or expertise. Reach out to their sustainability or corporate social responsibility leaders on social media as a place to start. If that doesn’t work, connect with intermediaries like <a href="https://changemakerxchange.org/">ChangemakerXChange</a> or We Are Family Foundation, which have formal youth-to-corporate programs. This is an opportunity for all of us if we focus more on building bridges, and a little less on our erecting own silos.</p>
  <h2 id="accelerating-business-keep-the-promise">2. Accelerating Business: Keep the Promise</h2>
  <p>Once you know who is (or could be) in your extended network, be sure you know how you can partner with them. During the <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Vx5O0ECmr2g">presentation of The Possibilists results</a>, we heard innovators request support like, “We need help. We’re looking for an expert who can help us do the work.” Rest assured, there is help out there.</p>
  <p>Helping businesses run better is what we do, but SAP is not alone in that work when it comes to supporting the work of social entrepreneurs. Unilever, EY, and Ikea are a few awesome corporations that come to mind. We all have programs that will provide you with skilled business experts or financial support, usually in partnership with social sector organizations like <a href="https://movingworlds.org/organization">MovingWorlds</a>, <a href="https://acumen.org/covid-19-response/">Acumen</a>, <a href="https://www.pyxeraglobal.org/">PYXERA Global</a>, and <a href="https://www.yunussb.com/">Yunus Social Business</a>. We are constantly innovating together through initiatives like the <a href="https://www.weforum.org/covid-alliance-for-social-entrepreneurs">COVID Response Alliance for Social Entrepreneurs</a> to help improve the way we connect you with valuable resources.</p>
  <p>So you’re probably asking yourself, “Why would companies share their resources with you?” It’s a win-win for us, too. As employees connect with topics that matter to them, they also flex their leadership skills, build empathy and cross-cultural understanding, and gain exposure to ‘what’s next’ from leaders like you.</p>
  <p>If you are looking for skilled support, know that you don’t have to go it alone. SAP and MovingWorlds are inviting social innovators ages 18 to 30 to <a href="https://movingworlds.org/partner/sap/acceleration-collective-organizations">join the Acceleration Collective</a>, a new pro bono consulting experience launching in September. Beyond pro bono consulting, the Acceleration Collective includes access to certified business coaching, and bridges access to other SAP partners’ service offerings like <a href="https://acumenacademy.org/">Acumen Academy</a>. Unilever and EY, with the support of the COVID Response Alliance, are also offering resources through their market-leading program <a href="https://www.transform.global/resources/">TRANSFORM</a>.</p>
  <p>Keeping the promise to organizations of all kinds is just another day at the office for many of us. Do your research to see who is willing to help. (Hint: we are!) If you are not sure where to begin, join Social Shifters and SAP at <a href="https://sewfonline.com/events/2021-events/youth-forum/">Social Enterprise World Forum’s Youth Forum on September 27</a>.</p>
  <h2 id="recognizing-your-value-tell-it-like-it-is">3. Recognizing Your Value: Tell It Like It is</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-more-sap4good-stories">Read more SAP4Good stories</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/topics/sap4good">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>It is true that with age comes wisdom, but age is not synonymous with the value you bring forward as a leader. Innovation starts with all of us! Last year, I was working on a speaker series, and I approached a young social entrepreneur to speak at the event on SAP’s behalf. Her response was one you should take note of. “I’d gladly speak to your audience, but preparing and speaking for you comes at an opportunity cost for my organization. Will you compensate me for my time?” I was momentarily speechless. She further explained to me, “The moderator is likely getting paid, along with the caterer and the venue. They are all providing a service to you, and so am I.” This young person was respectfully challenging my originally unpaid request. She was right to do so — and you are too!</p>
  <p>My ask was not one of ill intention, rather ignorance, though it’s still no excuse. Throughout a decade working in marketing for SAP, I often asked business leaders to speak on our company’s behalf. The difference? They were all being paid by their organization for their time. Young innovators can be exploited and showcased on both virtual and physical stages globally, but you can change that.</p>
  <p>If you are being asked for something, know your worth and how to leverage it. Be bold and ask for the support you need in return. It may not always be financial compensation, rather it might be access to people or networks or could also include personal skill-building or revenue generation opportunities for your organization.</p>
  <p>Lastly, I want to revisit a topic I touched on briefly above. The Possibilists shared that many of you sacrifice your mental and financial well-being in the pursuit of a better world. While I’m grateful for your efforts, I’m also here to remind you that you will never be able to successfully deliver on your goals if you don’t also prioritize your own well-being. Breathe, find a coach, join a peer support group, pay yourself: whatever it is, invest in your own well-being. You are worth it!</p>
  <h2 id="so-what">So What?</h2>
  <p>Am I asking you to start your own youth movement within the corporate world? No. Am I trying to do that? Perhaps. Do I expect that every organization has the same support structure as SAP to embrace young leaders like you? Probably not. But I hope I’m giving you the courage to connect, learn, and lead with people and organizations like mine.</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Reach out and connect with those who can help you. I promise there are more of us who want to help!</li>
    <li>Learn from the experts and teach them a few things along the way. We don’t know it all, I assure you.</li>
    <li>Speak up! Keep leading the way doing exactly what you are doing. You are creating the change we all need to see in the world, and I can’t wait to see more of you in board rooms around the world.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>Thank you for all that you do to keep moving us forward. We owe you one.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Jennifer Beason is global program director of Social Entrepreneurship for Corporate Social Responsibility at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/redefining-youth</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
            <category>news-tag/social-entrepreneurship</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>