<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/life-at-sap/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Empowering Africa's Future: Bridging the Teacher Gap through Digital Education and Upskilling]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/teacher-gap-africa-world-teachers-day-2023</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/teacher-gap-africa-world-teachers-day-2023</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[For World Teachers' Day 2023, SAP shines a spotlight on Africa Code Week and the importance of honoring all educators. Read more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>non-sap-event/africa-code week</category>
            <category>news-tag/life-at-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/un-sdgs</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Gears Up for UNGA 78]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/sap-unga-78</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/sap-unga-78</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn how SAP is preparing for UNGA 78, which signifies the midpoint toward the 2030 target for implementing the UN SDGs.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/life-at-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-at-unga</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-educate-to-employ</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Finishes 2022 with 154 Employer of Choice Awards]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/01/2022-employer-of-choice-awards</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/01/2022-employer-of-choice-awards</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is celebrating its 2022 employer of choice awards, which include more than 150 recognitions worldwide. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/life-at-sap</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Act Now, Together, Through Pro Bono Consulting]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/together-act-now-pro-bono-consulting</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/together-act-now-pro-bono-consulting</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Together Act Now was the theme for the 2022 UN International Volunteer Day. Learn how SAP employees participate.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/life-at-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-social-sabbatical</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
            <category>news-tag/un-sdgs</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fostering Diversity and Inclusion Through Immersive Pro Bono Consulting]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/immersive-pro-bono-consulting-fostering-diversity-inclusion</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/immersive-pro-bono-consulting-fostering-diversity-inclusion</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Pro bono consulting programs like the SAP Social Sabbatical foster diversity and cultivate an inclusive mindset for participants. Learn how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17c7e0cc1436024ff2536a47add3bf4d172041915.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17c7e0cc1436024ff2536a47add3bf4d172041915.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_17c7e0cc1436024ff2536a47add3bf4d172041915.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Fostering Diversity and Inclusion Through Immersive Pro Bono Consulting" src="./media_17c7e0cc1436024ff2536a47add3bf4d172041915.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="fostering-diversity-and-inclusion-through-immersive-pro-bono-consulting">Fostering Diversity and Inclusion Through Immersive Pro Bono Consulting</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Global Diversity Awareness Month is a time to reflect and honor diversity in all its facets – nationality, race, sex, gender, country of origin, and language, just to name a few.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>This is celebrated each year in October; however, at SAP, diversity is something we honor throughout the year. Within our 110,000+ strong company, we have employees from all over the world, with many of our teams working from multiple locations together to reinvent how the world runs as a network of intelligent, sustainable enterprises. Through global teamwork, employees are exposed to different cultures, diverse ways of thinking, and building skills that grow empathy and resiliency. Not only is diversity and inclusion good for employees, but it is also good for business.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-how-sap-is-powering-equitable-access">Learn how SAP is powering equitable access</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/our-values/csr.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="diversity-in-action-through-pro-bono-consulting">Diversity in Action through Pro Bono Consulting</h2>
  <p>As a global organization with employees representing more than 150 nationalities, we are constantly seeking various ways to incorporate diversity and inclusion proactively, both within our workplace and in the markets we serve.</p>
  <p>One of the ways SAP has prioritized a diversity mindset for employees over the past decade is through <a href="https://www.sap.com/socialsabbatical">SAP Social Sabbatical</a>. In this program, SAP employees from around the world can share their skills, knowledge, and professional expertise with innovative non-profit organizations and social enterprises in emerging markets to help them solve their business challenges. The program has been run in over 52 countries with participants representing 64 different nationalities. This highlights our commitment to bring together different perspectives, amplifying the power of diversity of thought and experience, which creates positive impact for both the organizations and participating SAP employees.</p>
  <p>Meera Shenoy, founder of SAP Social Sabbatical host client <a href="https://www.youth4jobs.org/">Youth4Jobs</a>, shared how her organization benefited from the team’s diversity of professional experience: “The volunteers came from three different countries, and each had a different specialty. They quickly adopted our passion for inclusion and became part of the larger Youth4Jobs family, understanding our challenges and transformational work. They also gave us a peek into the amazing SAP processes in several areas. For example, the team shared the SAP neurodiversity training with us, and we got to learn the techniques that a corporation like SAP uses for neurodiversity inclusion in the workplace.”</p>
  <p>When diversity is incorporated through pro bono consulting programs like SAP Social Sabbatical, organizations are able to tap into the varied perspectives and approaches that each individual employee brings to the <a href="https://www2.deloitte.com/us/en/insights/focus/human-capital-trends/2014/hc-trends-2014-diversity-to-inclusion.html">workplace</a>. Research shows that diversified teams can lead to an increase in innovation, improve problem-solving, and boost decision-making. This can heighten performance by <a href="https://diversity-inclusion-speakers.com/news/tips-and-tricks/benefits-diversity-inclusion-workplace-statistics/#:~:text=%E2%80%9CRacially%20diverse%20teams%20report%20a,key%20factor%20in%20any%20workplace.">at least 35%</a>, which not only accelerates innovation within SAP but also helps the host client organization anticipate and fulfill the needs of diverse customers.</p>
  <h2 id="the-employee-advantage">The Employee Advantage</h2>
  <p>For employee participants, we know that the pro bono consulting benefits include skill development, networking opportunities, gaining new perspectives, and cultural immersion, among others. For example, a participant from India stated, “It gives you a whole new perspective that we don’t get in our day-to-day work.”</p>
  <p>From a recent <a href="https://www.sap.com/dmc/exp/2017_03_46558/enUS/impact/">long-term impact study</a> that we conducted in partnership with impact measurement social enterprise <a href="https://60decibels.com/">60 Decibels</a>, 88% of SAP employees who have participated in SAP Social Sabbatical reported that the program benefited them personally. Additionally, 86% of employees said their ability collaborate with global and diverse colleagues improved by their participation.</p>
  <p>“It allowed me to dive into a new world for weeks. You gain experience you have never had before. It brings you to a new level culture-wise, and you meet many talented people from SAP across the world,” said one participant from Germany.</p>
  <p>Another employee commented, “In my personal life, I am more aware of differences in people and better at understanding peoples’ challenges. These differences go beyond age, gender, geography and race but also diversity of thought, upbringing, values and perspectives. Understanding these differences is key to solving problems and empowering others.”</p>
  <h2 id="focusing-on-sustainable-long-term-impact">Focusing on Sustainable Long-Term Impact</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="explore-what-sap-is-doing-to-accelerate-social-businesses">Explore what SAP is doing to accelerate social businesses</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/our-values/csr.html#accelerate">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In addition to the diversity benefits for participants and social sector partners, the long-term impacts have gone beyond the SAP Social Sabbatical program. These principles of diversity as a building block of the program have supported the evolution of new initiatives that address social challenges and build equity, while leveraging pro bono consulting as a tool. In learning from our success over the past 10 years, we developed the Pro Bono for Economic Equity program in North America, which was launched in 2021 in partnership with <a href="https://www.pyxeraglobal.org/">PYXERA Global</a>, as part of SAP’s overall response to the social justice movement with an aim to foster economic equity for Black-owned business and social enterprises.</p>
  <p>The program allows SAP employees to leverage their professional skills and expertise as pro bono volunteer consultants for under-resourced businesses and social enterprises and help them address systemic and business challenges. Within the first year, the program expanded internationally to the UK, Brazil, and South Africa. Based on the success of the program, we have extended the cohorts to have a focus on Indigenous-owned businesses in Canada. <a href="/2022/05/pro-bono-for-economic-equity-impact">Learn more about the program here</a>.</p>
  <h2 id="cultivating-an-inclusive-mindset">Cultivating an Inclusive Mindset</h2>
  <p>At SAP, diversity and inclusion are not simply goals to strive for; they are strategic components of our corporate culture that fuel innovation and help us turn our purpose to action.</p>
  <p>We recognize that continuously bolstering the diversity, equity, and inclusion mindset is crucial when it comes to shaping the next generation of leaders in our company. Not only will this support employee engagement today, but it means that they will build a more inclusive environment when it comes to how they work in teams, how they hire, and how they engage colleagues who are different from them, now and into the future.</p>
  <p>For more information about SAP Social Sabbatical, visit <a href="https://www.sap.com/socialsabbatical">sap.com/socialsabbatical</a> and to learn about how SAP is empowering Black- and Indigenous-owned businesses and social enterprises, read <a href="/topics/pro-bono-for-economic-equity">more stories about the Pro Bono Economic Equity program here</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Hemang Desai is global program director for SAP Corporate Social Responsibility.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/life-at-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-social-sabbatical</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Named Best Corporate Steward by U.S. Chamber of Commerce Foundation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/sap-named-best-corporate-steward</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/sap-named-best-corporate-steward</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP has been named Best Corporate Steward by U.S. Chamber of Commerce Foundation for its commitment to a more inclusive, sustainable economy.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_158bc723afdf76ef6718b04ea6166dfa5dfcfab7a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_158bc723afdf76ef6718b04ea6166dfa5dfcfab7a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_158bc723afdf76ef6718b04ea6166dfa5dfcfab7a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Named Best Corporate Steward by U.S. Chamber of Commerce Foundation" src="./media_158bc723afdf76ef6718b04ea6166dfa5dfcfab7a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-named-best-corporate-steward-by-us-chamber-of-commerce-foundation">SAP Named Best Corporate Steward by U.S. Chamber of Commerce Foundation</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>The U.S. Chamber of Commerce Foundation named SAP “Best Corporate Steward: Large Business” at the 23rd annual Citizens Awards in Washington D.C. The recognition is given to the company that best demonstrates itself as a “responsive and responsible member of society, whose overall values, operational practices, and decision-making exemplify shared value.”</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1675116b99aa002c87c7da6d2f5648b6307bbba33.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1675116b99aa002c87c7da6d2f5648b6307bbba33.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1675116b99aa002c87c7da6d2f5648b6307bbba33.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_1675116b99aa002c87c7da6d2f5648b6307bbba33.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2252" height="2552">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p><em>SAP’s Jennifer Beason, Carmen Krueger, Jim Sullivan, Robin Manherz, Kevin Richards</em></p>
  <p>It was accepted on behalf of SAP by Global Chief Operating Officer Robin Manherz.</p>
  <p>SAP technology helps companies embed sustainability into core business processes, which, combined with an industry-leading social responsibility strategy, is delivering global solutions to unlock a more inclusive and sustainable economy.</p>
  <p>Manherz shared that this award means a lot to her personally and to the company. “This is such a tremendous and important honor for me to represent SAP tonight,” she said. “From the planes in the sky to the electricity on the grid, we run most of the world with our technology. We take that responsibility very seriously and look forward to working with you today and every day to make sure we are living up to our purpose.”</p>
  <p><a href="https://www.uschamberfoundation.org/citizens-awards/2022-winners">Meet all the Citizens Awards winners here</a>.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-how-the-sap-csr-team-is-working-toward-ensuring-an-inclusive-recovery-and-equal-opportunities-for-all">Learn more about how the SAP CSR team is working toward ensuring an inclusive recovery and equal opportunities for all</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/our-values/csr.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="helping-the-world-run-better-together">Helping the World Run Better, Together</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-what-life-looks-like-at-sap">Learn more about what life looks like at SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/careers/who-we-are.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP’s mission is to help every business become a sustainable, intelligent enterprise. In practice, that means we create solutions to manage the most mission-critical business operations, like finance, human resources, and manufacturing, that, at the same time, address some of the most profound economic, social, and environmental challenges of our time.</p>
  <p>For example, SAP Cloud for Sustainable Enterprises helps companies manage their carbon footprint and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/responsible-design-and-production.html">reduce material waste</a>. In addition to the <a href="https://www.sap.com/sustainability.html">sustainability</a> portfolio, SAP is investing in supply chain transparency through SAP Ariba and SAP Business Network to promote human rights, circularity, and socially responsible procurement standards. With more than $3 trillion traded across SAP Business Network, SAP has an opportunity to help companies shift procurement spend from traditional trading partners to companies like <a href="https://www.forthebluedot.com/">Blue Dot Way</a>, <a href="https://auticon.com/">Auticon</a>, and <a href="https://televerde.com/">Televerde</a>. Procuring quality goods and services from organizations like these increases investment in economic equity, social impact, and environmental sustainability in a way that cannot be done through corporate philanthropy alone.</p>
  <p>“SAP’s vision to help the world run better and improve people’s lives is evident through its investments and innovative technology to make a profound impact on the most vulnerable populations,” said Marc DeCourcey, senior vice president of the U.S. Chamber of Commerce Foundation. “Their purpose-driven culture serves as a model for companies around the world.”</p>
  <p>As DeCourcey affirms, technology by itself is not the answer. That is why SAP is also investing in equitable access to economic opportunity, education, and employment, as well as a green, circular economy.</p>
  <p>“As a company, we have an unwavering commitment to innovation and to the communities around the U.S. and the world where we operate,” shared Lloyd Adams, president of SAP North America. “This award belongs to our employees, customers, and partners who have committed to sustainable and equitable business practices that focus on supporting people and protecting the planet.”</p>
  <p>These values are embedded throughout the leadership culture at SAP, along with the way we engage and develop future talent. Adams, for example, personally champions the Autism at Work program and spearheads SAP North America’s Emerging Talent Advisory Board. In the past year alone, Adams and the North America leadership team engaged 30 next-generation leaders in the <a href="https://drive.google.com/file/d/1i4u5GiU8qCAwrssBcdVvQS51J1Q2Nbbs/view">Acceleration Collective</a>, a virtual pro bono consulting initiative, solving strategic business challenges for B2B social enterprises tackling issues of plastics and waste, inclusion, and responsible supply chains. And there are plans to continue embracing experiential learning through pro bono across North America in the future.</p>
  <p>In 2021, SAP Corporate Social Responsibility programs and partnerships trained more than 119,000 teachers, educated 3.5 million youth, 50% of whom were girls, and impacted more than 8.3 million lives. More than 20,000 employees globally engage in skills-based volunteerism through SAP, representing a $20 million in-kind contribution to impact organizations through pro bono consulting in the last decade.</p>
  <p>Looking ahead, SAP has reinforced its partnership with <a href="https://www.unicef.org/partnerships/sap-unicef-genu-help-young-people-gain-skills-for-employment">UNICEF</a> and Generation Unlimited, announcing the <a href="/2022/09/sap-unicef-global-youth-employment-coalition">SAP Educate to Employ initiative</a>, a program that supports learning-to-earning pathways in the digital and green economies for youth in need. Additionally, to help combat the global refugee crisis, SAP is fulfilling associate and bachelor’s degree scholarships with <a href="https://www.uopeople.edu/about/worldwide-recognition/press-releases/sap-providing-50-scholarships-for-ukrainian-refugees-at-uopeople/">University of the People</a>, the first nonprofit, tuition-free, American-accredited online university dedicated to providing global access to higher education.</p>
  <p>Based on SAP’s own success engaging employees and partners, SAP — together with EY, MovingWorlds, TRANSFORM, and Unilever — partnered to launch the <a href="https://movingworlds.org/transform/social-enterprises?utm_source=sap&#x26;utm_medium=email&#x26;utm_campaign=transformlaunch_0422">TRANSFORM Support Hub</a>, helping employees everywhere connect to social enterprises anywhere, through pro bono consulting, coaching, and more. The open, online platform is a place where new and existing partners can come together to expedite world-changing solutions. If you share our commitment to building a more sustainable world, we hope you will <a href="https://movingworlds.org/transform/corporates">join us</a>!</p>
  <p>To learn more about SAP and its purpose in action, visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/csr">www.sap.com/csr</a> and follow us on social media using @SAP4Good.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/life-at-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap4good</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Receives 100 Employer of Choice Awards]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/2022-q3-employer-of-choice-awards</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/2022-q3-employer-of-choice-awards</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is celebrating its 2022 Q3 employer of choice awards, which include an all-time high of 20 recognitions for equality. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/life-at-sap</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Receives 75 Employer of Choice Awards in the First Half of 2022]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/2022-q1-q2-employer-of-choice-awards</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/2022-q1-q2-employer-of-choice-awards</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is celebrating its 2022 Q1 and Q2 employer of choice awards, which include 75 different recognitions worldwide. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/life-at-sap</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Business Women's Network at SAP: Empowerment through Connection]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/04/business-womens-network-empowerment-connection</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/04/business-womens-network-empowerment-connection</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The mission of the Business Women’s Network (BWN) at SAP is to help women advance their careers and the company’s business.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/business-womens-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/life-at-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/women-at-sap</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Certified as a Top Employer in 17 Countries in 2022]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/01/sap-certified-top-employer-17-countries-2022</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/01/sap-certified-top-employer-17-countries-2022</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP has been recognized as a Top Employer in 17 countries and two regions in 2022 by Top Employers Institute.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_115a0935d58ec15411f38621a11904c84b0333969.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_115a0935d58ec15411f38621a11904c84b0333969.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_115a0935d58ec15411f38621a11904c84b0333969.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Certified as a Top Employer in 17 Countries in 2022" src="./media_115a0935d58ec15411f38621a11904c84b0333969.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-certified-as-a-top-employer-in-17-countries-in-2022">SAP Certified as a Top Employer in 17 Countries in 2022</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-what-life-looks-like-at-sap">Learn more about what life looks like at SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/careers/who-we-are/life.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>SAP has been recognized as a Top Employer in 17 countries and two regions in 2022 by Top Employers Institute.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Being certified as a Top Employer showcases an organization’s dedication to a better world of work and exhibits this through excellent human resources (HR) policies and people practices.</p>
  <p>SAP’s two biggest regions, North America and Europe, have achieved Regional Top Employer status. With offices in 130 countries, SAP considers itself a truly global company and is pleased that its people practices have been recognized in locations including Canada, China, Colombia, France, Germany, Greece, India, Israel, Italy, Mexico, Poland, Portugal, Russia, South Africa, Spain, Turkey, and the U.S.</p>
  <p>SAP is delighted to be certified again as an employer of choice, especially in times where organizations and employees are still adapting to the pandemic. In 2022, SAP remains committed to employees more than ever, continuing to expand flexible work policies, assist employees in maintaining their physical and mental well-being, investing in learning and development, evolving into an even more inclusive workplace, and continuing to attract the best and most diverse talent.</p>
  <p>Sophie Bieber, head of Global Employer Branding, said, “A flexible and trust-based workplace is the norm, not the exception, at SAP. We help the world run better — and that includes doing what’s best for our employees. Our unique culture is built on trust, respect, purpose, inclusion, and team spirit.”</p>
  <p>The Top Employers Institute program certifies organizations based on the participation and results of its HR Best Practices Survey. The survey covers six HR domains consisting of 20 topics, including people strategy, work environment, talent acquisition, learning, well-being, diversity and inclusion, and more. The program has certified and recognized more than 1,857 Top Employers in 123 countries and regions across five continents.</p>
  <p>To learn more about the recognition that SAP has achieved in best workplaces, diversity and inclusion, work-life balance, and more, visit the <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/careers/who-we-are/employer-awards.html">Employer Awards section of sap.com</a>.</p>
  <p>Follow #LifeAtSAP on <a href="https://www.instagram.com/lifeatsap/">Instagram</a>, <a href="https://www.facebook.com/lifeatsap/">Facebook</a>, <a href="https://twitter.com/LifeatSAP">Twitter</a> and <a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/lifeatsap">YouTube</a> to receive regular news and updates about careers at SAP.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/life-at-sap</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Named Glassdoor Best Places to Work in Five Countries]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/01/sap-glassdoor-2022-best-places-to-work-five-markets</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/01/sap-glassdoor-2022-best-places-to-work-five-markets</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is among Glassdoor's 2022 Best Places to Work in Canada, France, Germany, the UK, and the U.S. Learn more about life at SAP.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a0ee123fbd2ba51fb2ad1b7b4bc334a1a2422db4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a0ee123fbd2ba51fb2ad1b7b4bc334a1a2422db4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1a0ee123fbd2ba51fb2ad1b7b4bc334a1a2422db4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Named Glassdoor Best Places to Work in Five Countries" src="./media_1a0ee123fbd2ba51fb2ad1b7b4bc334a1a2422db4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-named-glassdoor-best-places-to-work-in-five-countries">SAP Named Glassdoor Best Places to Work in Five Countries</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-what-life-looks-like-at-sap">Learn more about what life looks like at SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/careers/who-we-are/life.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>We are pleased to share that SAP is among the winners of the annual Glassdoor Employees’ Choice Awards, a list of the <a href="https://www.glassdoor.com/Award/Best-Places-to-Work-LST_KQ0,19.htm">Best Places to Work in 2022</a>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The Employees’ Choice Awards, now in its 14th year, are based solely on the input of employees who elect to provide anonymous feedback by completing a company review about their job, work environment, and employer on <a href="https://www.glassdoor.com/">Glassdoor</a>, the worldwide leader on insights about jobs and companies. Unlike other awards, there is no self-nomination or application process — it is entirely based on the feedback of employees.</p>
  <p>For 2022, SAP is named as a Best Place to Work in Canada, France, Germany, the U.S., and the UK, receiving the maximum five Glassdoor awards in major markets. This is a huge success following last year’s rankings, where SAP was listed in four markets. Full ranking below:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><a href="https://www.glassdoor.com/Award/Best-Places-to-Work-LST_KQ0,19.htm">Canada: #9</a></li>
    <li><a href="https://www.glassdoor.fr/R%C3%A9compense/Meilleurs-Employeurs-France-LST_KQ0,27.htm">France: #9</a></li>
    <li><a href="https://www.glassdoor.de/Award/Beste-Arbeitgeber-Deutschland-LST_KQ0,29.htm">Germany: #6</a></li>
    <li><a href="https://www.glassdoor.co.uk/Award/Best-Places-to-Work-UK-LST_KQ0,22.htm">UK: #19</a></li>
    <li><a href="https://www.glassdoor.com/Award/Best-Places-to-Work-LST_KQ0,19.htm">U.S.: #42</a></li>
  </ul>
  <p>Glassdoor’s Best Places to Work were determined using company reviews shared by employees between October 20, 2020, and October 18, 2021. During the year-long eligibility period, employers considered for the large list must have received at least 75 ratings for each of the nine workplace attributes taken into account as part of the awards algorithm: overall company rating, career opportunities, compensation and benefits, culture and values, diversity and inclusion, senior management, work-life balance, recommend to a friend, and six-month business outlook.</p>
  <p>We thank all our employees who took the time to share their perspective on what it is like to work at SAP. We appreciate their valuable feedback as it only helps us improve.</p>
  <p>To learn more about the our certifications like best workplace awards, early talent certifications, and other accolades that validate SAP as a great place to work, please visit the <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/careers/who-we-are/employer-awards.html">Employer Awards section of sap.com</a>.</p>
  <p>Follow #LifeAtSAP on <a href="https://www.instagram.com/lifeatsap/">Instagram</a>, <a href="https://www.facebook.com/lifeatsap/">Facebook</a>, <a href="https://twitter.com/LifeatSAP">Twitter</a>, and <a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/lifeatsap">YouTube</a> to receive regular news and updates about careers or <a href="https://jobs.sap.com/">new opportunities at SAP</a>.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/life-at-sap</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Closes Out 2021 with 160 Employer of Choice Awards!]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/01/2021-q4-employer-of-choice-awards</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/01/2021-q4-employer-of-choice-awards</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is celebrating its 2021 and Q4 employer of choice awards, which include more than 20 recognitions worldwide. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/life-at-sap</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Recognized Among World's Best Workplaces 2021]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/sap-worlds-best-workplaces-2021</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/sap-worlds-best-workplaces-2021</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP has been recognized among the World’s Best Workplaces in 2021 according to Great Place to Work and Fortune magazine. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ce9352661f9122ef37ae004c622cc62115a9ade7.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ce9352661f9122ef37ae004c622cc62115a9ade7.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1ce9352661f9122ef37ae004c622cc62115a9ade7.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Recognized Among World’s Best Workplaces 2021" src="./media_1ce9352661f9122ef37ae004c622cc62115a9ade7.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-recognized-among-worlds-best-workplaces-2021">SAP Recognized Among World’s Best Workplaces 2021</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-what-life-looks-like-at-sap">Learn more about what life looks like at SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/careers/who-we-are/life.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Great Place to Work and Fortune magazine have honored SAP as one of the World’s Best Workplaces in 2021.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP was selected out of more than 10,000 organizations that participated in the survey process, representing the voices of almost 20 million employees worldwide.</p>
  <p>The 25 World’s Best Workplaces stood out for creating globally exceptional employee experiences, high-trust relationships, and workplaces that are fair and equal for all. In that survey, <strong>91% of SAP’s employees said this is a great place to work</strong>.</p>
  <p>To be eligible for the list, a company must be named to five or more national Best Workplaces lists across Great Place to Work’s global offices, have 5,000 employees or more worldwide, and at least 40% of the company’s workforce — or 5,000 employees — must be based outside of the country in which the company is headquartered.</p>
  <p>SAP has qualified as a result of its success in appearing in Great Place to Work Best Workplaces lists in the following countries: Argentina, Australia, Brazil, Canada, Chile, Greater China, Colombia, Costa Rica, Japan, Peru, Switzerland, the UK, and the U.S. In 2021 alone, SAP has received more than 35 nods as a best workplace in categories such as for Women, Inclusion, Mental Wellness, Millennials, Technology, Parents, Diversity, and LGBTQ+ equality in Canada and the U.S.</p>
  <p>“We are honored to have earned this recognition for building and maintaining an inclusive culture that is focused on supporting our people and providing them an environment where differences are celebrated,” says DJ Paoni, president of SAP North America.</p>
  <p>“Earning a place among the World’s Best Workplaces is a great accomplishment for us as a company,” says Sabine Bendiek, chief people and operating officer and member of the Executive Board of SAP SE. “It is thanks to our dedicated employees from all around the globe that we have been a part of this list. It is people who make working at SAP a truly special experience every day. We celebrate them for all they do to earn this incredible honor.”</p>
  <p>SAP is proud to be recognized by Great Place to Work and our employees as creating one of the World’s Best Workplaces. We put our people at the very top of our greatest assets and focus on providing an exceptional employee experience for all. This recognition reflects the efforts and values of our company so we thank each of you for helping to make SAP so special.</p>
  <p>Join the conversation by sharing the news on your social channels with the hashtags #LifeAtSAP and #WorldsBestWorkplaces, and follow and engage with @LifeAtSAP on <a href="https://www.instagram.com/lifeatsap/">Instagram</a>, <a href="https://www.facebook.com/lifeatsap/">Facebook</a>, <a href="https://twitter.com/LifeatSAP">Twitter</a>, and <a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/lifeatsap">YouTube</a>. And to learn more about the diversity and inclusion awards, best workplace awards, early talent certifications, and other accolades that validate SAP as a great place to work, please visit the <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/careers/who-we-are/employer-awards.html">Employer Awards section of sap.com</a>.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/life-at-sap</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Celebrates 22 Employer of Choice Awards in Third Quarter of 2021]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/2021-q3-employer-of-choice-awards</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/2021-q3-employer-of-choice-awards</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is celebrating its Q3 employer of choice awards, which include more than 20 recognitions worldwide. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1fdc6152b9ae2eba1b41f327fb2674c16f9b4bd76.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1fdc6152b9ae2eba1b41f327fb2674c16f9b4bd76.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1fdc6152b9ae2eba1b41f327fb2674c16f9b4bd76.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Celebrates 22 Employer of Choice Awards in Third Quarter of 2021" src="./media_1fdc6152b9ae2eba1b41f327fb2674c16f9b4bd76.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-celebrates-22-employer-of-choice-awards-in-third-quarter-of-2021">SAP Celebrates 22 Employer of Choice Awards in Third Quarter of 2021</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Heading into fall of 2021, SAP is proud to be recognized for 22 employer awards globally in the third quarter of 2021. This includes eight for equality, seven for early career talent, four for work-life-balance, and three for best workplace.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>With a <a href="/2021/07/q2-employer-of-choice-awards">grand total of 114 awards thus far in 2021</a>, the past exciting quarter included various awards for career starters and young professionals, such as Best Workplaces for Millennials, and underlines our diverse culture with recognition of a company that cares and gives back.</p>
  <p>“We are happy and proud to receive so many recognitions underlining different aspects of employee experience quarter after quarter,” said Elke Manjet, global head of Talent Attraction at SAP. “Employer of choice awards express our power as a talent magnet and we take this as an incentive to continue our efforts in creating a desirable workplace that attracts employees who help the world run better and improve people’s lives.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-what-life-looks-like-at-sap">Learn more about what life looks like at SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/careers.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="third-quarter-award-highlights">Third Quarter Award Highlights</h2>
  <ul>
    <li>Best Workplaces for Millennials by Fortune</li>
    <li>PEOPLE’s Companies That Care by Great Place to Work</li>
    <li>Top 100 Internship Programs by WayUp</li>
    <li>Best Workplaces for Giving Back by Great Place to Work</li>
    <li>Best Place to Work for Disability Inclusion by Disability:IN</li>
    <li>Top Employer for students in IT by Tendence Institut GmbH</li>
    <li>Asia’s Best Workplaces by Great Place to Work</li>
  </ul>
  <p>SAP is proud of the recognition received for a high commitment to both our employees and a unique company culture, which reflects the efforts and values of our company.</p>
  <p>To learn more about the diversity and inclusion awards, best workplace awards, early talent certifications, and other accolades that validate SAP as a great place to work, please visit the <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/careers/who-we-are/employer-awards.html">Employer Awards section of sap.com</a>.</p>
  <p>Follow #LifeAtSAP on <a href="https://www.instagram.com/lifeatsap/">Instagram</a>, <a href="https://www.facebook.com/lifeatsap/">Facebook</a>, <a href="https://twitter.com/LifeatSAP">Twitter</a>, and <a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/lifeatsap">YouTube</a> to receive regular news and updates about careers or <a href="https://jobs.sap.com/">new opportunities at SAP</a>.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/life-at-sap</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Setting Our Minds to Being Kind]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/setting-our-minds-to-being-kind</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/setting-our-minds-to-being-kind</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[For the second year in a row, SAP stands proud with Born This Way Foundation and its #BeKind21 campaign to foster kindness worldwide.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_12ba02c059d9104e356e1deda2511e1412227046c.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_12ba02c059d9104e356e1deda2511e1412227046c.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_12ba02c059d9104e356e1deda2511e1412227046c.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Setting Our Minds to Being Kind" src="./media_12ba02c059d9104e356e1deda2511e1412227046c.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="setting-our-minds-to-being-kind">Setting Our Minds to Being Kind</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>One of my favorite quotes ever shared is from Maya Angelou: “People will forget what you said, people will forget what you did, but people will never forget how you made them feel.”</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>We have reached a critical point in humanity where we need to collectively take pause – as individuals, communities, companies, societies at large – and think about how our actions, or lack thereof, make others feel. We must ask ourselves the tough questions: Are we making people feel valued? Appreciated? Loved? Heard? Empowered? Inspired? Confident? Hopeful? In order to create a sustainable future where our economy, environment, and society prosper for years to come, everyone must search within themselves and do their part to create a better world for all.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="kindness-is-the-contagion-that-brings-us-together">Kindness Is the Contagion That Brings Us Together</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2020/09/bekind21-campaign-kindness-contagious">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="bekind21-in-2021">#BeKind21 in 2021</h2>
  <p>For the <a href="/2020/09/bekind21-campaign-kindness-contagious">second year</a> in a row, SAP stands proud with <a href="https://bornthisway.foundation/">Born This Way Foundation</a> (BTWF) and its <a href="https://bornthisway.foundation/bekind21/">#BeKind21 campaign</a>. BTWF was founded by Lady Gaga and her mom, Cynthia Germanotta. The foundation supports the mental health of young people, with a mission of creating a kinder, braver world. At SAP, our purpose is to help the world run better and improve people’s lives. With a caring work culture grounded in psychological safety, SAP aspires to a world with zero inequality where people genuinely care about each other and feel a sense of belonging. We see it as our responsibility to <a href="http://www.sap.com/mentalhealth">lead by example</a> in removing the stigma around mental health disorders in the workplace, and kindness is a powerful lever to help get us there.</p>
  <h2 id="the-science-of-kindness">The Science of Kindness</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="a-healthy-business-starts-with-healthy-people">A healthy business starts with healthy people</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="http://www.sap.com/mentalhealth">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Kindness has the power to turn darkness into light, cold into warmth, loneliness into connection. Acts of kindness – whether random or deliberate, small or large, simple or complex – make everyone involved feel good: the giver, the recipient, and even the observer. <a href="https://www.mayoclinichealthsystem.org/hometown-health/speaking-of-health/the-art-of-kindness">Science shows</a> that kindness benefits our minds and our bodies. In fact, it tends to be contagious.</p>
  <p>The healing powers of kindness are well documented and recognized by the world’s foremost <a href="https://www.cedars-sinai.org/blog/science-of-kindness.html">medical experts</a>. Did you know that performing – and even witnessing – small, simple acts of kindness can produce oxytocin, also known as “the love hormone,” and can improve our overall health and well-being? Kindness is also known to release dopamine, a feel-good brain chemical, and boost serotonin, a neurotransmitter that helps regulate mood. Similar to the type of high we feel when we exercise, being kind can lead to a “<a href="https://www.psychologytoday.com/us/blog/emotional-nourishment/201711/why-random-acts-kindness-matter-your-well-being">helper’s high</a>.”</p>
  <p>Imagine if we could spread kindness farther, wider, and faster than the speed of <a href="/covid-19">COVID-19</a>. Do we have the power – as all of humankind – to counter the negative effects of the pandemic by killing it with kindness? I believe we do if we set our minds to it.</p>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div>.<a href="https://twitter.com/ZequeMa?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@ZequeMa</a> 🇦🇷 is kicking off <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/BeKind21?src=hash&#x26;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#BeKind21</a> by showing kindness to his best friend and donating to a charity that helps others like him! <a href="https://twitter.com/SAPLatinAmerica?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@SAPLatinAmerica</a> <a href="https://t.co/Rq1a4pK8Fx">pic.twitter.com/Rq1a4pK8Fx</a></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div>— Life at SAP (@LifeatSAP) <a href="https://twitter.com/LifeatSAP/status/1433006798819180545?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">September 1, 2021</a></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="join-us-lifeatsap">Join Us @LifeatSAP</h2>
  <p>From September 1st through the 21st, we’re curating acts of kindness from SAP employees all around the world and sharing them on our social channels.</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Follow along with us on <a href="https://www.instagram.com/lifeatsap/">Instagram</a>, <a href="https://twitter.com/LifeatSAP">Twitter</a>, and <a href="https://www.facebook.com/lifeatsap">Facebook</a>, or through the hashtags #LifeAtSAP and #BeKind21.</li>
    <li>Make the #BeKind21 pledge. Sign up and <a href="https://bornthisway.foundation/current-programs/bekind21/">generate your own #BeKind21</a> calendar to share on your personal accounts with the hashtags #LifeAtSAP and #BeKind21.</li>
  </ul>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Julie Barrier is global vice president of Purpose and Sustainability Marketing at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/covid-19</category>
            <category>news-tag/life-at-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/mental-health-well-being</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Celebrates 41 Employer of Choice Awards in the Second Quarter]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/q2-employer-of-choice-awards</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/q2-employer-of-choice-awards</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is celebrating its Q2 employer of choice awards, which include more than 40 different recognitions worldwide. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e282c0638127caa390428a0d5e24f8c1a44a1ab5.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e282c0638127caa390428a0d5e24f8c1a44a1ab5.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1e282c0638127caa390428a0d5e24f8c1a44a1ab5.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Celebrates 41 Employer of Choice Awards in the Second Quarter" src="./media_1e282c0638127caa390428a0d5e24f8c1a44a1ab5.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-celebrates-41-employer-of-choice-awards-in-the-second-quarter">SAP Celebrates 41 Employer of Choice Awards in the Second Quarter</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>In the second quarter of 2021, SAP is proud to have received 41 employer awards globally, including 16 recognitions for best workplaces, 14 for equality, three for early talent, and two for work-life-balance.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Building on more than 50 <a href="/2021/04/sap-celebrates-q1-employer-awards">awards received in the first quarter</a>, this exciting quarter included Christian Klein being named a top CEO, ranking as one of LinkedIn’s Top Companies 2021, and various awards related to Pride month.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-life-at-sap">Learn more about life at SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/careers.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="second-quarter-award-highlights">Second Quarter Award Highlights</h2>
  <ul>
    <li>100 Best Big Companies to Work for by Fortune</li>
    <li>America’s Best Employer for Diversity by Forbes &#x26; Statista</li>
    <li>Top Companies in US, CA, BR, GER and GC by LinkedIn</li>
    <li>Top CEO in FRA and GER by Glassdoor</li>
    <li>German Diversity Index DAX 30 by Beyond Gender Agenda</li>
    <li>Germany’s Most Popular Employer Among Students by Handelsblatt</li>
    <li>Best Employer in Bulgaria by Kincentric</li>
    <li>Best Employers for New Graduates by Forbes</li>
  </ul>
  <p>SAP is proud of the recognition received for a high commitment to both our employees and a unique company culture, which reflects the efforts and values of our company.</p>
  <p>To learn more about the diversity and inclusion awards, best workplace awards, early talent certifications, and other accolades that validate SAP as a great place to work, please visit the <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/careers/who-we-are/employer-awards.html">Employer Awards section of sap.com</a>.</p>
  <p>Follow #LifeAtSAP on <a href="https://www.instagram.com/lifeatsap/">Instagram</a>, <a href="https://www.facebook.com/lifeatsap/">Facebook</a>, <a href="https://twitter.com/LifeatSAP">Twitter</a>, and <a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/lifeatsap">YouTube</a> to receive regular news and updates about careers at SAP.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/life-at-sap</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Glassdoor Names Christian Klein a Top CEO in 2021]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/06/glassdoor-names-christian-klein-top-ceo-2021</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/06/glassdoor-names-christian-klein-top-ceo-2021</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP CEO Christian Klein has been acknowledged as a top CEO in Germany and France by Glassdoor, with an approval rating of 96%.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1cbfc53de6444e8aa82313cbc8457262f0c9abf49.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1cbfc53de6444e8aa82313cbc8457262f0c9abf49.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1cbfc53de6444e8aa82313cbc8457262f0c9abf49.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Glassdoor Names Christian Klein a Top CEO in 2021" src="./media_1cbfc53de6444e8aa82313cbc8457262f0c9abf49.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="glassdoor-names-christian-klein-a-top-ceo-in-2021">Glassdoor Names Christian Klein a Top CEO in 2021</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Every year, Glassdoor, a platform for job seekers and employee reviews, recognizes outstanding employers and leaders throughout the world with the Employees’ Choice Awards. SAP is proud that our CEO Christian Klein has won a Glassdoor Employees’ Choice Award honoring the <a href="https://www.glassdoor.co.uk/Award/Top-CEOs-UK-LST_KQ0,11.htm">top CEOs in 2021</a>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Based entirely on anonymous employee feedback from the past year, Klein has been acknowledged as a leading CEO in <a href="https://www.glassdoor.de/Award/Beliebteste-Manager-Deutschland-LST_KQ0,31.htm">Germany</a> and <a href="https://www.glassdoor.fr/R%C3%A9compense/Le-Top-Des-PDG-France-LST_KQ0,21.htm">France</a> with an approval rating of 96%. Among the chief executives recognized by Glassdoor in France, Klein was ranked number one on the list.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_147875454ac4adff6abf9308da4f932e2fbddfdbd.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_147875454ac4adff6abf9308da4f932e2fbddfdbd.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_147875454ac4adff6abf9308da4f932e2fbddfdbd.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_147875454ac4adff6abf9308da4f932e2fbddfdbd.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="512">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p><em>Click to enlarge</em></p>
  <p>“Our colleagues are the heart of our success, and they make SAP the great company it is,” said Klein. “Of all the things that motivate me to give my best every day, it is undoubtedly the people I have the privilege to work with all over the world. I am grateful to be able to work with such outstanding colleagues, and they inspire me continually with their dedication, ingenuity, and passion.”</p>
  <p><a href="https://www.glassdoor.com/sap">Glassdoor</a>, the worldwide leader in insights about jobs and companies, provides employees with an opportunity to give feedback on their company’s environment, culture, and senior leaders. Across the approximately 1.5 million employers reviewed on Glassdoor, the average CEO approval rating is 73%.</p>
  <p>To learn more about the diversity and inclusion awards, best workplace awards, early talent certifications, and other accolades that validate SAP as a great place to work, please visit the <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/careers/who-we-are/employer-awards.html">Employer Awards section of sap.com</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <hr>
        <table>
          <thead>
            <tr>
              <th colspan="2">Promo</th>
            </tr>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td>
                <h3 id="sap-recognized-as-worlds-best-workplaces-2020-by-great-place-to-work">SAP Recognized as World’s Best Workplaces 2020 by Great Place to Work</h3>
              </td>
              <td><strong><a href="/2020/10/best-workplaces-2020-great-place-to-work">Learn more</a></strong></td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
        <h3 id="see-all-the-2021-winners">See All the 2021 Winners</h3>
        <table>
          <thead>
            <tr>
              <th colspan="2">Section Metadata</th>
            </tr>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td>Style</td>
              <td>Additional Reading</td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="https://www.glassdoor.fr/R%C3%A9compense/Le-Top-Des-PDG-France-LST_KQ0,21.htm">25 Top CEOs – France</a></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="https://www.glassdoor.de/Award/Beliebteste-Manager-Deutschland-LST_KQ0,31.htm">25 Top CEOs – Germany</a></p>
        <table>
          <thead>
            <tr>
              <th colspan="2">Section Metadata</th>
            </tr>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td>Style</td>
              <td>Additional Reading</td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
        <hr>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/life-at-sap</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP on Fortune's 100 Best Companies to Work For, Best Big Companies to Work For 2021 Lists]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/sap-fortune-100-best-companies-to-work-for-2021</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/sap-fortune-100-best-companies-to-work-for-2021</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 12 Apr 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is among the Fortune 100 Best Companies to Work For 2021 list and is one of the Best Big Companies to Work For in 2021. Read the news!]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10719adb01d3c8025c6952d413fbd7b8b28c30c60.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10719adb01d3c8025c6952d413fbd7b8b28c30c60.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_10719adb01d3c8025c6952d413fbd7b8b28c30c60.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP on Fortune’s 100 Best Companies to Work For, Best Big Companies to Work For 2021 Lists" src="./media_10719adb01d3c8025c6952d413fbd7b8b28c30c60.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-on-fortunes-100-best-companies-to-work-for-best-big-companies-to-work-for-2021-lists">SAP on Fortune’s 100 Best Companies to Work For, Best Big Companies to Work For 2021 Lists</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-life-at-sap">Learn more about life at SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/careers.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Great Place to Work and Fortune have honored SAP America, which has been selected for the Fortune 100 Best Companies to Work For 2021 list and additionally is one of the Best Big Companies to Work For in 2021.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>This is SAP’s fifth consecutive year named to the prestigious list, this time coming in at <a href="https://www.greatplacetowork.com/certified-company/1001312">#29</a> and earning a spot that means it is among the best companies to work for in the country.</p>
  <p>SAP North America President DJ Paoni expressed his congratulations to U.S. colleagues, saying, “I don’t have to tell you that <a href="/covid-19">last year was like no other</a>. It tested our resolve and it proved our resilience and determination to work through it — together. Our teams demonstrated this in the countless ways they handled whatever came their way this year. They kept the promise to have the backs of our customers, of their families, and of one another.”</p>
  <p>The Fortune 100 Best Companies to Work For 2021 list honors the most heroic companies supporting their people and communities in the U.S. during a year deeply impacted by the pandemic. Great Place to Work surveyed more than half a million employees on issues including how trustworthy, caring, and fair the company is in times of crises; employees’ physical, emotional, and financial health; and the company’s broader community impact.</p>
  <p>Based on analysis of survey responses from more than 39,000 current employees across the U.S., 94% said SAP is a great place to work, which is 35 percentage points higher than the average U.S. company. On April 9, SAP America was also named by Great Place to Work and Fortune to the Best Workplaces in Technology 2021 list for the fifth consecutive year.</p>
  <p>SAP is extremely proud of the recognition received for its high commitment to employees and for the company’s unique culture. This reflects the company’s efforts and values, and could not be done without its people as well as the commitment of SAP to invest in its people.</p>
  <p>To learn more about the results, please visit the <a href="https://www.greatplacetowork.com/best-workplaces/100-best/2021">rankings at greatplacetowork.com</a>.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>To learn more about the diversity and inclusion awards, best workplace awards, early talent certifications, and other accolades that validate SAP as a great place to work, please visit the <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/careers/who-we-are/employer-awards.html">Employer Awards section of sap.com</a>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/life-at-sap</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Celebrates 51 Employer of Choice Awards in First Quarter of 2021]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/sap-celebrates-q1-employer-awards</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/sap-celebrates-q1-employer-awards</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is celebrating its Q1 employer awards: more than 50 across 25 regions and countries! Learn more about the highlights so far this year.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b93ac5e22659ac35f2f07908e8887184db7768af.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b93ac5e22659ac35f2f07908e8887184db7768af.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1b93ac5e22659ac35f2f07908e8887184db7768af.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Celebrates 51 Employer of Choice Awards in First Quarter of 2021" src="./media_1b93ac5e22659ac35f2f07908e8887184db7768af.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-celebrates-51-employer-of-choice-awards-in-first-quarter-of-2021">SAP Celebrates 51 Employer of Choice Awards in First Quarter of 2021</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>You may have seen some exciting news this year on our <a href="https://twitter.com/search?q=%23LifeAtSAP">#LifeAtSAP</a> social channels. In the first quarter, SAP was recognized as a 2021 Top Employer in 20 key markets, a Best Place to Work in four countries according to Glassdoor, and a “Best Place to Work for LGBTQ Equality.” That was only the beginning.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>So far this year, SAP has received a total of 51 employer awards across 25 regions and countries, including 32 for best employer, six for equality, one for work-life, and four for early talent.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-life-at-sap">Learn more about life at SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/careers.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="first-quarter-award-highlights">First Quarter Award Highlights</h2>
  <ul>
    <li>
      <ul>
        <li><a href="/2021/01/sap-global-top-employer-2021">Global Top Employer by Top Employer Institute</a></li>
        <li>Bloomberg Gender-Equality Index by Bloomberg Finance L.P.</li>
        <li>Most Valuable German Brands by BrandZ</li>
        <li><a href="/2021/01/sap-glassdoor-2021-best-places-to-work-four-markets">Best Place to Work in Germany, France, the UK, and Canada by Glassdoor</a></li>
        <li>America’s Best Large Employers by Forbes</li>
        <li>Top Employers for Young People in Canada by MediaCorp Inc.</li>
        <li>Best Places to Work for LGBTQ Equality by Human Rights Campaign</li>
        <li>Campus Forward Honoree in U.S. by RippleMatch</li>
        <li>30 Best Employers for People With Autism by Applied Behaviors Analysis</li>
      </ul>
    </li>
  </ul>
  <p>Fostering a good work environment enhances SAP’s reputation with customers, prospective customers, investors, and – most importantly – employees.</p>
  <p>We are extremely proud of the recognition received for our high commitment to employees and our unique culture, which reflects the efforts and values of our company.</p>
  <p>To learn more about the diversity and inclusion awards, best workplace awards, early talent certifications, and other accolades that validate SAP as a great place to work, please visit the <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/careers/who-we-are/employer-awards.html">Employer Awards section of sap.com</a>.</p>
  <p>Follow #LifeAtSAP on <a href="https://www.instagram.com/lifeatsap/">Instagram</a>, <a href="https://www.facebook.com/lifeatsap/">Facebook</a>, <a href="https://twitter.com/LifeatSAP">Twitter</a>, and <a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/lifeatsap">YouTube</a> to receive regular news and updates about careers at SAP.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/life-at-sap</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Recognized as a Global Top Employer in 2021]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/01/sap-global-top-employer-2021</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/01/sap-global-top-employer-2021</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is one of 16 companies with Global Top Employer 2021 status for outstanding people policies and practices. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/life-at-sap</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Is Among Glassdoor's 2021 Best Places to Work in Four Markets]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/01/sap-glassdoor-2021-best-places-to-work-four-markets</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/01/sap-glassdoor-2021-best-places-to-work-four-markets</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is among Glassdoor's 2021 Best Places to Work in France (#3), Germany (#7), Canada(#8), and the UK (#9). Learn more about life at SAP.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e5a7f7b4548009f6307ffbd3d0fa8ada45c8d093.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e5a7f7b4548009f6307ffbd3d0fa8ada45c8d093.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1e5a7f7b4548009f6307ffbd3d0fa8ada45c8d093.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Is Among Glassdoor’s 2021 Best Places to Work in Four Markets" src="./media_1e5a7f7b4548009f6307ffbd3d0fa8ada45c8d093.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-is-among-glassdoors-2021-best-places-to-work-in-four-markets">SAP Is Among Glassdoor’s 2021 Best Places to Work in Four Markets</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-what-life-looks-like-at-sap">Learn more about what life looks like at SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/careers.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Glassdoor, the worldwide leader on insights about jobs and companies, has revealed its annual list of Best Places to Work. For the fifth consecutive year, SAP is honored to be recognized as a recipient of 2021 Best Places to Work awards in multiple markets.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>This year, the company is one of only three employers that are being recognized in four out of five markets.</p>
  <ul>
    <li><a href="https://www.glassdoor.fr/R%C3%A9compense/Meilleurs-Employeurs-France-LST_KQ0,27.htm">SAP France: #3</a></li>
    <li><a href="https://www.glassdoor.com/Award/Beste-Arbeitgeber-Deutschland-LST_KQ0,29.htm">SAP Germany: #7</a></li>
    <li><a href="https://www.glassdoor.ca/Award/Best-Places-to-Work-Canada-LST_KQ0,26.htm">SAP Canada:#8</a></li>
    <li><a href="https://www.glassdoor.co.uk/Award/Best-Places-to-Work-UK-LST_KQ0,22.htm">SAP UK: #9</a></li>
  </ul>
  <p>The rankings are decided based on employee reviews and ratings and are conducted by Glassdoor’s awards team.</p>
  <p>While rankings may fluctuate, SAP has held a consistent place on Glassdoor Employees’ Choice Award, recognizing the 2021 Best Places to Work. The Employees’ Choice Awards program is based on the input of employees who elect to provide feedback on their jobs, work environments, and companies on <a href="https://www.glassdoor.com/sap">Glassdoor.com</a>.</p>
  <p>On <a href="https://www.glassdoor.com/mz-survey/employer/collectReview_input.htm?i=10471&#x26;j=true&#x26;y=&#x26;c=PAGE_INFOSITE_TOP">Glassdoor</a>, current and former employees voluntarily and anonymously share insights and opinions about their work environments by sharing a company review, designed to capture an authentic inside look at what a specific job may be like at a particular company. When sharing a company review on Glassdoor, employees are asked to rate their satisfaction with the company overall, along with key workplace factors like career opportunities, compensation and benefits, culture and values, senior management, and work/life balance.</p>
  <p>SAP’s unique culture is valued by its employees around the world. The company appreciates the valuable feedback and insights of its employees and remains committed to listening and acting on feedback while creating an amazing employee experience to foster a workplace of excellence.</p>
  <p>To learn more about the diversity and inclusion awards, best workplace awards, early talent certifications, and other accolades that <a href="/2021/01/sap-2020-employer-awards">validate SAP as a great place to work</a>, visit the <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/careers/who-we-are/employer-awards.html">Employer Awards section of sap.com</a>.</p>
  <p>For more, follow #LifeAtSAP on <a href="https://www.instagram.com/lifeatsap/">Instagram</a>, <a href="https://www.facebook.com/lifeatsap/">Facebook</a>, and <a href="https://twitter.com/LifeatSAP">Twitter</a>. SAP employees can provide a <a href="http://www.glassdoor.com/sap">review on Glassdoor.com</a>.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/life-at-sap</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Celebrates 2020 Employer Recognition]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/01/sap-2020-employer-awards</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/01/sap-2020-employer-awards</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn about SAP's 2020 employer awards, which included recognition for 125 unique employer of choice awards across 37 countries and regions.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11366c53fd1c671e999db90d6f56b11d5e726c66c.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11366c53fd1c671e999db90d6f56b11d5e726c66c.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_11366c53fd1c671e999db90d6f56b11d5e726c66c.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Celebrates 2020 Employer Recognition" src="./media_11366c53fd1c671e999db90d6f56b11d5e726c66c.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-celebrates-2020-employer-recognition">SAP Celebrates 2020 Employer Recognition</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-what-life-looks-like-at-sap">Learn more about what life looks like at SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/careers/who-we-are.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Last year was one like no other. To say 2020 was challenging would be a significant understatement. In addition to the human cost, the <a href="/covid-19">pandemic</a> has fundamentally disrupted the way people work and has transformed the ways we interact and connect with each other.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Nevertheless, SAP finished the year on a high and is proud of how its employees have dealt with the many challenges.</p>
  <p>As of the end of 2020, the company was recognized around the world for 125 unique employer of choice awards, certifications, and rankings across 37 countries and regions. This includes 30 awards for best workplaces, 22 awards for equality, 10 awards for work-life balance, and nine recognitions related to early talent.</p>
  <p>Highlights of awards from the fourth quarter include:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>World’s Best Workplaces by Great Place to Work (GPTW)</li>
    <li>Best Global Brands by Interbrand</li>
    <li>Best Workplaces for Women in Germany by Brigitte</li>
    <li>DAX 30 LGBT+ Diversity Index by UHLALA Group</li>
    <li>Best Workplace for Parents in the U.S. by GPTW</li>
    <li>Best Workplaces for Today’s Youth in Canada by GPTW</li>
    <li>Gold Certification in Japan by Work with Pride</li>
    <li>Best Software Company to Work for in Israel by BDI</li>
  </ul>
  <p>The recognition helps SAP to attract more candidates, boosts employee morale, and supports retention of top talent by driving employee engagement with participation. It also helps the company to benchmark itself against other leading organization to make sure it continues to offer employees great benefits, work-life flexibility, learning and development, and more.</p>
  <p>Fostering a good work environment enhances SAP’s reputation with customers, prospective customers, investors, and–most importantly–employees.</p>
  <p>We are extremely proud of the ongoing recognition in 2020, which reflects the efforts and values of our company, received both for our commitment to employees and our unique culture.</p>
  <p>To learn more about the diversity and inclusion awards, best workplace awards, early talent certifications, and other accolades that validate SAP as a great place to work, please visit the <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/careers/who-we-are/employer-awards.html">Employer Awards section of sap.com</a>.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/life-at-sap</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>