<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/product/sap-business-technology-platform/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Four SAP Customers Are Successfully Driving Transformation in Their Businesses]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-sapphire-sap-customers-drive-business-transformation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-sapphire-sap-customers-drive-business-transformation</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In their SAP Sapphire keynote, Scott Russell and Thomas Saueressig talked to four customers about using SAP to deliver high-value results.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c4521f798d991573b94b36fd1f60cfe20d3399cf.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1c4521f798d991573b94b36fd1f60cfe20d3399cf.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1c4521f798d991573b94b36fd1f60cfe20d3399cf.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="How Four SAP Customers Are Successfully Driving Transformation in Their Businesses" src="./media_1c4521f798d991573b94b36fd1f60cfe20d3399cf.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="how-four-sap-customers-are-successfully-driving-transformation-in-their-businesses">How Four SAP Customers Are Successfully Driving Transformation in Their Businesses</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>This week at SAP Sapphire, four industry-leading companies joined SAP Executive Board Members Scott Russell and Thomas Saueressig on stage in Orlando to discuss how they are using SAP technology to deliver high-value results for their businesses.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="taking-business-to-the-next-level-in-the-era-of-ai">Taking Business to the Next Level in the Era of AI</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/events/sapphire/news-guide.html">Read the news guide</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Russell told the crowd that customer stories and conversations is what SAP Sapphire is all about, saying that what makes the event special is having “a collective group that comes together, both here in the room and virtually, and being able to understand how SAP can bring out your best.”</p>
  <p>Russell emphasized that the news from SAP Sapphire is a “demonstration of our commitment to continually innovate, to continually strive to bring more creative value to your business.”</p>
  <p>He noted that a perfect example of this is the announcement that <a href="/2024/06/sap-enters-agreement-to-acquire-walkme">SAP has entered into an agreement to acquire WalkMe</a>, a leader in digital adoption platforms. Reflecting on the acquisition, Russell said “We are obsessed not only about great applications and great platforms to deliver value for your business, we also care passionately about the transformation journey to get there.”</p>
  <p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/live/ZZ1yFoALzAs?si=mbPWUzgttHga-_PR">Embed from www.youtube.com</a></p>
  <p>As Chief Revenue Officer, Russell noted that every day 300 million people log on to SAP cloud applications to run their businesses. “And obviously we can never take that for granted,” he said. “You have choice, you have options. We strive to be at our best to help you be at yours. The way we measure success is in your terms, because ultimately [as a] market leader in business AI, we hold ourselves to the highest standards. Why? Because that’s what you expect.”</p>
  <p>A big part of the transformation journey many customers are taking is moving to the cloud with RISE with SAP. “We are super proud of our cloud journey and [that] we are helping you transform your business,” Russell said. “More than 6,000 customers have already moved to RISE with SAP. Of those 6,000 customers in the last 12 months, over 1,000 have already gone live.”</p>
  <h2 id="puretech-scientific-speed-and-scalability-is-key">PureTech Scientific: Speed and Scalability is Key</h2>
  <p>Russell was first joined on stage by Brian Hardee, CIO of <a href="https://www.puretechscientific.com/">PureTech Scientific LLC</a>, a global leader in the production of glycolic acid used in a variety of industries and applications. As a recent carve-out by a private equity owner from a much larger global manufacturer, PureTech had to quickly migrate its operations to its own systems. But without an IT team of its own this was initially a daunting challenge. The new company chose SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition because of its many benefits.</p>
  <p>“For us, it was an easy choice because first, we have no IT team,” Hardee said. “We have no internal training team, and we also had a very tight timeline with respect to the exit. So, we needed a solution that would enable us to move forward with speed, efficiency, and scalability. I could be confident that the infrastructure was being managed and secure. And that left us with an awesome choice for growth as well.”</p>
  <p>Scalability and rapid implementation were key factors in the choice of GROW with SAP, Hardee noted: “It was a great fit and gave us a platform for scalability for future bolt-ons, acquisitions, and so forth. So that’s the main reason. And SAP has an awesome suite of tools that enable that rapid implementation. And there was no other way we were going to do it without an internal IT team and without the access to the training material and the testing and so on.”</p>
  <p>And speaking of rapid implementation, PureTech went live on SAP in just 15 weeks, standardizing a business with an 85-year history on a common platform. Hardee gave some advice on how to make a project successful: “Use the tool set that SAP provides – SAP Activate methodology does work! And if you have the opportunity, sign up for the SAP Preferred Success program because it gives you a direct line to someone in SAP so that if you or your integrator doesn’t know the answer, SAP can point you to the right direction very quickly. So that helps with the speed of transformation.”</p>
  <h2 id="tropicana-brands-group-all-about-agility-and-time">Tropicana Brands Group: All About Agility and Time</h2>
  <p>Tropicana is a household name to many consumers, known chiefly for its juice and other beverage products. But while the brand is more than 75 years old, <a href="https://www.tropicanabrandsgroup.com/">Tropicana Brands Group</a> is just a bit over two years old, having been recently spun-off as a stand-alone group.</p>
  <p>Jeff Lischett, CIO of the US$3 billion organization, joined Russell to talk about how his company relied on RISE with SAP to make its “Project Harvest” IT separation and transformation project successful.</p>
  <p>Lischett noted that speed and agility was the key value proposition for the project. “We needed a platform that was able to accelerate, move with us, pivot with us, as we were going through this in a very accelerated timeline,” he said. “When you bring the technology and couple it with the unified business architecture powered by SAP, the choice for us was clearly RISE with SAP. Tropicana really needed a fit for purpose. Where we came from was going to be entirely different than where we were going, and this modern ERP, in terms of leaner, simpler, more streamlined ways of working, was really at the core of what we needed across the value chain.”</p>
  <p>Tropicana Brands Group took its European business operations live on SAP just 11 months after it started the design work, followed by North America three months later. “That was pressure testing!” Lischett said. “In just over a year, we had a fully implemented, end-to-end digital core and technology foundation for Tropicana Brands. We have a technology and a platform now that is really going to – no pun intended – rise to meet the challenge of our growth ambition.”</p>
  <p>“Ruthless prioritization” and change management were key to the project’s success, Lischett said. “I’m the biggest evangelist and advocate of change management,” he said. “You need it. You need it at the front, you need it during, you need it at the end. One thing that I would’ve probably done slightly differently is [to have] stayed with it longer at the end.”</p>
  <p>Tropicana is already seeing the impact of the project and specifically its focus on a clean core. “The most impactful value we’ve seen [goes] back to that clean core,” Lischett said. “Just in the months that followed, the ability to … bring the development forward, to build on top of the core that we have with enhancements and optimizing at a speed ratio that you just haven’t seen.”</p>
  <p>When asked about what role AI will play in his company, Lischett focused mainly on the human side of the technology. “Ironically, from the standpoint of being a technologist … AI in my mind, in terms of how I lead it, [needs to be] human-centered first and foremost, ensuring that we’ve got the right culture, responsible use, and effective use,” he said. “The gift of time is really the value creator that I see in AI and being able to work more efficiently and being able to take that time and translate it into what matters to you.”</p>
  <h2 id="responsibly-enabling-critical-systems">Responsibly Enabling Critical Systems</h2>
  <p>Russell handed over the stage to Saueressig, who recently launched the <a href="/2024/04/cloud-transformation-adoption-revolution-expectations-outcomes-meet">new Customer Services &#x26; Delivery Board area</a>. Saueressig noted that 25% of the world’s commerce already runs through more than 6,000 RISE with SAP customers worldwide, and that SAP supports the most critical business processes on the planet.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <picture>
          <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1dc5f09272052858aaeb01a0eec06423efb162249.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
          <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1dc5f09272052858aaeb01a0eec06423efb162249.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
          <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1dc5f09272052858aaeb01a0eec06423efb162249.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
          <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_1dc5f09272052858aaeb01a0eec06423efb162249.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="683">
        </picture>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>With that comes “the responsibility and the accountability to provide you with the most reliable and secure infrastructure,” Saueressig said. “That’s the reason why we co-engineered together with our partners from AWS, Microsoft Azure, Google Cloud Platform, and many others, to ensure that you have the highest level of quality and availability.”</p>
  <p>Echoing the theme of speed and adaptability, he noted that fast adoption of technology is critical. “Today, it’s not about the big fish that eats the small fish, it’s about the fast fish that eats the slow,” he cited. “At the end of the day, [our] ambition is to transform your system landscape to create a more flexible architecture, which enables fast adoption of innovations and ultimately, value realization. … And we take our responsibility seriously to really help you thrive in this ever-changing environment.”</p>
  <h2 id="fresenius-se-from-complexity-to-standardization">Fresenius SE: From Complexity to Standardization</h2>
  <p>Ingo Elfering, CIO of global healthcare conglomerate <a href="https://www.fresenius.com/">Fresenius</a>, knows something about speed: his team migrated 29 system landscapes containing more than 134 systems in less than 15 months. He joined Saueressig on stage to provide some insights into his company’s transformation project.</p>
  <p>As a company that has grown through many acquisitions, Fresenius had a highly heterogenous IT landscape. “We never quite integrated them,” Elfering said. “So, a really complex landscape …, [with] all sorts of interfaces and other applications attached to it. That was our starting point.”</p>
  <p>Fresenius’ management realized the company needed to change and become more efficient and effective to set itself up for ongoing success. It went all-in, doing four major transformations at the same time. As Elfering noted, “We not only did the RISE with SAP migration, we also did a complete cloud migration of our data centers worldwide; an outsourcing with a partner to become a more global team; and a global change of our network, including a whole bunch of security additions into our space.”</p>
  <p>Since it works in the healthcare and pharmaceutical space, Fresenius has a lot of regulatory requirements that it must adhere to, making the project more challenging than it might be in other industries. “You do a lot more technical documentation, testing, and so forth. So, from that perspective, regulations like GxP, good manufacturing or critical infrastructure, they were new to SAP in that instance in RISE with SAP. And we did it together. And I find that quite remarkable.”</p>
  <p>The <a href="/2023/06/fresenius-rise-with-sap-moves-sap-systems-cloud">new system has now been live</a> for just over a year and the company has seen many benefits. “We have a better speed on the underlying systems,” Elfering said. “We have a new infrastructure stack that works well. The main benefit for us will come as we [reinvent] the company. … We have some systems that doubled and tripled in size. So, it’s possible to leverage SAP quite quickly in these types of environments. From that perspective, I’m very happy with where we are. … We now have all the foundations in place to be able to execute our next phase of changes, our consolidation, our simplification, and in the cloud.”</p>
  <p>Finally, Elfering believes that healthcare is an area where AI can make a significant difference. “Healthcare always has been data-rich and insights-poor. … And the only way to get there, in our opinion at least, is to be on a cloud-based infrastructure in the first place. Because otherwise you don’t have the same performance or capabilities.”</p>
  <h2 id="clean-core-drives-agility">Clean Core Drives Agility</h2>
  <p>The idea of a “clean core” and a unified, simplified system underlies all these customer transformation stories. And it’s even more important in the context of agility and adaptability when it comes to taking advantage of the latest innovations in AI.</p>
  <p>“It’s super important for us to be clear that the clean core is not just for the sake of the clean core,” Saueressig said. “It’s a means to get to an innovation- and upgrade-ready system to be able to embrace these innovations. Because at the end of the day, legacy systems often have this technical depth that limits agility.”</p>
  <p>Saueressig admitted that even SAP has struggled with this, noting that the company had millions of lines of custom code in its systems. An internal analysis of all SAP customers showed that more than 65% of their custom code was unused in the past 12 months. “Code is also a liability, not just an asset,” he said. “And this is something we need to actively work against.”</p>
  <h2 id="hitachi-high-tech-corporation-clean-and-simple-benefits">Hitachi High-Tech Corporation: Clean and Simple Benefits</h2>
  <p>Saueressig invited Takuya Sakai, general manager of the Digital Transformation Business Group at <a href="https://www.hitachi-hightech.com/">Hitachi High-Tech</a>, on the stage to talk more about the benefits of system simplification and clean core. In 2019, Hitachi High-Tech <a href="https://www.sap.com/asset/dynamic/2023/07/d237f8b9-7e7e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">initiated a project</a> to simplify its business processes and digitize its management information. With its existing business processes fragmented across overseas sales offices, headquarters, and manufacturing sites, the organization needed to change to accelerate its business and set itself up for future growth. It chose SAP S/4HANA to help it build its new foundation for ongoing growth.</p>
  <p>Hitachi was running SAP R/3 but had significantly customized it with 9,000 add-ons across four instances, resulting in a lot of custom code. This resulted in many errors every day and large operational costs every year, Sakai said. And with the cost of validating so many add-ons, the company only did a major version update once in 12 years.</p>
  <p>To move to a more standardized and flexible system, Hitachi High-Tech adopted a two-tier architecture model. Taking advantage of development flexibility, the company deployed SAP S/4HANA Cloud Private Edition for its headquarters and group companies in Japan and SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition for its overseas sales offices. The adoption of SAP S/4HANA Cloud allows Hitachi High-Tech to take advantage of the functionality offered by SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP) for application development, data management, automation, integration, analytics, and AI.</p>
  <p>With the new system, Hitachi High-Tech reduced its 9,000 add-ons to just 750, allowing it to easily upgrade its ERP core. “Upgrading our old ERP took about a year and a half from the planning stage,” Sakai said. “However, with clean core, we can now do an upgrade every year in about 40 days. An upgrade every year keeps the clean core fresh and means new features can be delivered to our business quickly, like AI or process automation.”</p>
  <p>But achieving – and keeping – a clean core “requires patience,” Sakai said. Executives must understand the purpose of the transformation project and employees must overcome the pain that comes with a transformation project. “This is the most difficult thing,” he said. “The IT department must properly understand the new technology and suggest how to use it correctly. Then together we embark on the journey to the transformation.”</p>
  <h2 id="supporting-business-transformation-and-accelerating-time-to-value">Supporting Business Transformation and Accelerating Time to Value</h2>
  <p>Accelerating and improving time-to-value for customers is very important to SAP, according to Saueressig.</p>
  <p>“We are now bringing together all of our assets … in a seamless, end-to-end tool chain,” he said. “We want to holistically support your business transformation according to the dimensions of applications, data, processes, and people, which means we bring together and fully integrate SAP LeanIX for the IT landscapes and architecture, SAP Signavio for process management, SAP Cloud Application Lifecycle Management for application management and operational aspects, SAP BTP for integrations, and SAP Build for extensions, but also our telemetry tools, which we can leverage in the cloud.”</p>
  <p>Saueressig’s passion and ambition is to help customers drive innovation adoption. He noted that RISE with SAP is more than just a technical migration: it’s an offering for holistic business transformation as a service to accelerate value realization.</p>
  <p>“Ultimately, we want to help you to bring the best out of our entire holistic portfolio,” he said. “We want to help you to transform, realize agility at scale, achieve more across the entire value chain, and fundamentally transform operations with sustainability at the core. And this is something where I feel that we have a huge opportunity together to make that a reality.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-news-and-coverage-from-sap-sapphire-in-2024">Get the latest news and coverage from SAP Sapphire in 2024</h3>
        <p><em><a href="/topics/sap-sapphire">Read more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/grow-with-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[End-to-End Innovation Is Key to Bringing Out Your Best]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-sapphire-innovation-key-to-bring-out-your-best</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-sapphire-innovation-key-to-bring-out-your-best</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In their keynote, Juergen Mueller and Muhammad Alam demoed and discussed the latest innovations out of SAP Sapphire in 2024.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e38256295162fd6aa4582f624a1a9f11f0f8543b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e38256295162fd6aa4582f624a1a9f11f0f8543b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1e38256295162fd6aa4582f624a1a9f11f0f8543b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="End-to-End Innovation Is Key to Bringing Out Your Best" src="./media_1e38256295162fd6aa4582f624a1a9f11f0f8543b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="end-to-end-innovation-is-key-to-bringing-out-your-best">End-to-End Innovation Is Key to Bringing Out Your Best</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>In their SAP Sapphire Orlando keynote, Executive Board Members Muhammad Alam, SAP Product Engineering, and Juergen Mueller, chief technology officer, shared how the latest SAP innovations will help businesses drive true, end-to-end digital transformation and address their toughest business challenges.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="taking-business-to-the-next-level-in-the-era-of-ai">Taking Business to the Next Level in the Era of AI</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/events/sapphire/news-guide.html">Read the news guide</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In the keynote, which featured several real-world product demos by SAP employees, Alam and Mueller touted the value of SAP’s best-of-breed solutions with an outlook of what the next 50 years of innovation by SAP may look like.</p>
  <p>Who better to inspire the keynote than Hasso Plattner, co-founder and recently retired chairman of the SAP Supervisory Board, who both Alam and Mueller invoked during the session. To spell out SAP’s legacy and vision for the future, Mueller quoted <a href="/2024/05/hasso-plattner-olaf-scholz-farewell-tributes">Plattner’s farewell message</a>: “Keep innovating, keep pushing boundaries, and keep making a difference in the lives of our customers and the world at large.”</p>
  <h2 id="keep-innovating">Keep Innovating</h2>
  <p>To kick off his first SAP Sapphire appearance as the head of SAP Product Engineering, Alam began by describing the importance of harnessing innovation to deliver an end-to-end picture across all business functions and unlock true value.</p>
  <p>Simply put, businesses exist to build and deliver products and services to customers, he explained. But the materials, assets, people, and processes that come together to achieve this task is far from simple. “The reality is that each part of the business is deeply and intricately connected to all the others,” Alam said, meaning a pain point in one area impacts the rest. That’s why SAP’s modular cloud ERP approach is so successful: “We allow our customers to drive true digital transformation as opposed to running systems integration projects disguised as digital transformation,” he added.</p>
  <p>Alam presented <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/grow.html">GROW with SAP</a> as an example of this composability and extensibility, as it can work for and scale to many sizes and types of business. And now, SAP Sales Cloud and Concur Expense are natively integrated into GROW with SAP, making the offering even more comprehensive. Sinit Foto, product manager for UX, Cloud ERP at SAP, joined Alam on stage to show how GROW with SAP and SAP Business AI can help achieve integrated processes, demoing use cases such as communicating with customers about sales quotes, creating expense reports, and supporting financial analyses. In fact, Alam announced that SAP is implementing the demoed application internally to manage sales worldwide. And Mueller emphasized: “We are committed to helping you in this transformative AI moment by creating business outcomes that were unthinkable before. That’s why we’re embedding SAP Business AI deeply in our processes and analytics.”</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <picture>
          <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ab1b55bf13f95fe3a6b47084f96d918d20d0b6d4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
          <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ab1b55bf13f95fe3a6b47084f96d918d20d0b6d4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
          <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1ab1b55bf13f95fe3a6b47084f96d918d20d0b6d4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
          <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_1ab1b55bf13f95fe3a6b47084f96d918d20d0b6d4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="683">
        </picture>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="keep-pushing">Keep Pushing</h2>
  <p>AI was woven throughout the entire keynote, with both Alam and Mueller discussing <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence.html">SAP’s strategy and product enhancements in this space</a>. AI must be high value, easy to adopt into the flow of work, and trustworthy for it to truly transform how we do business, Alam said. “Equally important is whether it’s done in a way where it keeps your data secure and private – and is executed in a responsible manner,” he added. “And that is really the core promise of SAP Business AI.”</p>
  <p>There’s no doubt that AI is a powerful technology, which is why it’s essential that businesses view it as a “responsibility” not just an “opportunity,” Alam said. Megan Fife, executive solution advisor for SAP SuccessFactors, showed how SAP executes on its responsible, reliable, and relevant business AI by demoing how SAP’s AI copilot Joule in SAP SuccessFactors HCM can help fill skills gaps and collaborate across teams, among other meaningful tasks. Key to this endeavor is <a href="/2024/06/joule-microsoft-copilot-unified-work-experience">SAP’s expanded partnership with Microsoft announced earlier in the day</a>, which Scott Guthrie, executive vice president of Cloud and AI at Microsoft, discussed with Alam on stage.</p>
  <p>Mueller echoed the importance of responsible AI, saying that the technology depends highly on data that is reliable and that allows customers to look at their business end-to-end. Here, SAP Datasphere and SAP Spend Control Tower – which was demoed by Orla Cullen, product marketing manager for Data and Analytics at SAP – can help simplify data management and view and manage spend and sustainability data holistically.</p>
  <p>This transformation is supported by <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform.html">SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP)</a>, and Mueller demonstrated the newest generative AI features in SAP Analytics Cloud, SAP Integration Suite, and SAP Build solutions. He showed how Joule can help create and summarize financial reports for controlling teams; generate integration flows between SAP and non-SAP applications; and create custom skills and content based on specific business needs. Greater insights, faster reaction times, and increased productivity are the result. Soon, Mueller added, it will even be possible to enhance and extend Joule’s knowledge by creating custom skills using SAP Build and having the copilot interact with data housed in SAP and non-SAP systems, helping businesses run even more efficiently.</p>
  <p>SAP BTP is the key to being “innovation-ready,” maintaining a clean core, and tailoring standard offerings to unique needs, Mueller explained. More than 24,000 companies running live on SAP BTP, including Blue Diamond Growers and Lufthansa Technik, can attest to this.</p>
  <p>“SAP BTP’s extensibility and enterprise automation capabilities can help businesses turn process insights into actual improvements,” Mueller said. Cecilia Huergo, product manager for SAP BTP, showed this in her demo on how identifying improvement opportunities, realizing needed changes while maintaining a clean core, and gaining an up-to-date view of your IT landscape can be enabled with the combined power of SAP Signavio solutions, SAP LeanIX,, SAP BTP, and ABAP Cloud.</p>
  <h2 id="keep-making-a-difference">Keep Making a Difference</h2>
  <p>The innovations demoed and discussed in Alam and Mueller’s keynote, in addition to <a href="/2024/06/sap-sapphire-news-business-ai-enterprise-cloud-portfolio-cutting-edge-partnerships">the many others announced at SAP Sapphire in 2024</a>, are just the latest steps forward in SAP’s journey to bringing out the best in its customers. “The future is here, and it’s defined by those who innovate first,” Mueller said. “And we are here to give you the right tools at hand, such that you can be a leader not just today, but also tomorrow.”</p>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d468a3b0b7b4a96babee63b887b0c66d1bdc61b2.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d468a3b0b7b4a96babee63b887b0c66d1bdc61b2.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1d468a3b0b7b4a96babee63b887b0c66d1bdc61b2.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Why AI Means Being In The Cloud" src="./media_1d468a3b0b7b4a96babee63b887b0c66d1bdc61b2.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://youtu.be/EnxihshouTE">Why AI Means Being In The Cloud</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Gillian Hixson is an integrated communications specialist at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-news-and-coverage-from-sap-sapphire-in-2024">Get the latest news and coverage from SAP Sapphire in 2024</h3>
        <p><em><a href="/topics/sap-sapphire">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/grow-with-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP's New AI Innovations and Partnerships Deliver Real-World Results]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/ai-innovations-partnerships-sap-sapphire</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/ai-innovations-partnerships-sap-sapphire</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Explore the AI capabilities and ecosystem innovations presented at SAP Sapphire in 2024, all aimed at delivering real-world results.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>news-topic/financial-management</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/abap-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/accenture</category>
            <category>news-tag/ai-ethics</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/aws</category>
            <category>news-tag/bcg</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Expands Business AI Portfolio with Meta Open-Source Models]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-business-ai-meta-open-source-models</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-business-ai-meta-open-source-models</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is integrating Meta Llama 2 and Meta Llama 3 models into generative AI hub to enable customers to create dashboards based on rich content.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP’s Partnership with Mistral AI, One of the Leading LLM Makers]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-mistral-ai-leading-llm-maker-partnership</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-mistral-ai-leading-llm-maker-partnership</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The collaboration between SAP and Mistral AI is a symbiotic combination of AI expertise and technology. Learn about the partnership.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How SAP BTP Becomes the Trusted Platform for Business AI]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/sap-btp-strategy-paper-trusted-platform-business-ai</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/sap-btp-strategy-paper-trusted-platform-business-ai</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP BTP will further evolve to become the trusted business AI platform for SAP-centric landscapes. Learn more in the SAP BTP strategy paper.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-build</category>
            <category>product/sap-integration-suite</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP BTP Wins Multiple TrustRadius 2024 Top Rated Awards]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/sap-btp-wins-trustradius-2024-top-rated-awards</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/sap-btp-wins-trustradius-2024-top-rated-awards</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP BTP has received TrustRadius 2024 Top Rated awards, including SAP Build, SAP Integration Suite, and SAP Master Data Governance.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14e8d52807c7569f208a7c3238193ad8862cdb0a4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14e8d52807c7569f208a7c3238193ad8862cdb0a4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_14e8d52807c7569f208a7c3238193ad8862cdb0a4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP BTP Wins Multiple TrustRadius 2024 Top Rated Awards" src="./media_14e8d52807c7569f208a7c3238193ad8862cdb0a4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-btp-wins-multiple-trustradius-2024-top-rated-awards">SAP BTP Wins Multiple TrustRadius 2024 Top Rated Awards</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>SAP’s commitment to customers is steadfast in making SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP) the best platform to extend and personalize SAP applications, integrate and connect landscapes, maximize the value of data, and drive business innovation through artificial intelligence (AI).</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="discover-which-version-of-sap-btp-meets-your-needs">Discover which version of SAP BTP meets your needs</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/pricing.html">Try it today</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>To that end, I am thrilled to announce that <a href="https://www.trustradius.com/">TrustRadius</a>, a leading independent peer research and review platform, has once again recognized SAP BTP, along with multiple solutions that run on our platform, as winners of the 2024 Top Rated awards.</p>
  <p>As a reflection of direct customer feedback, the TrustRadius Top Rated awards offer an authentic measure of a product’s quality and customer satisfaction and highlight those products that have demonstrated excellence in fulfilling clients’ needs and expectations.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <picture>
          <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1bff4785e82312c107ed744772e802bfd657c73b9.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
          <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1bff4785e82312c107ed744772e802bfd657c73b9.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
          <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1bff4785e82312c107ed744772e802bfd657c73b9.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
          <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_1bff4785e82312c107ed744772e802bfd657c73b9.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="530" height="610">
        </picture>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="best-of-awards">Best of Awards</h2>
  <p>SAP customers’ willingness to share their hands-on experience and opinions of SAP BTP is testament to our platform’s services, robustness, and ongoing innovation.</p>
  <p>We are honored that the following solutions have been recognized with Top Rated awards:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform.html">SAP Business Technology Platform</a> on <a href="https://www.trustradius.com/products/sap-business-technology-platform/reviews">TrustRadius</a>: Platform-as-a-Service (PaaS) and Application Infrastructure</li>
    <li><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/application-development.html">SAP Build</a> on <a href="https://www.trustradius.com/products/sap-build/reviews">TrustRadius</a>: Low-Code Development and Robotic Process Automation (RPA)</li>
    <li><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/integration-suite.html">SAP Integration Suite</a> on <a href="https://www.trustradius.com/products/sap-integration-suite/reviews">TrustRadius</a>: Integration Platform-as-a-Service (iPaaS), and API Management</li>
    <li><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/master-data-governance.html">SAP Master Data Governance</a> on <a href="https://www.trustradius.com/products/sap-master-data-governance/reviews">TrustRadius</a>: Master Data Management (MDM) and Data Governance</li>
  </ul>
  <p>“SAP Business Technology Platform’s comprehensive suite of solutions has been recognized with a TrustRadius Top Rated award,” said Allyson Havener, senior vice president of Marketing and Community at TrustRadius. “SAP is committed to delivering innovative technologies that empower businesses to drive digital transformation, and achieve their goals. We congratulate SAP on this achievement, showcasing their continued leadership and excellence in providing cutting-edge enterprise solutions.”</p>
  <h2 id="our-focus-on-customer-success">Our Focus on Customer Success</h2>
  <p>At SAP, customer success and satisfaction are the ultimate measures of our own success. We strive to deliver industry-leading solutions, functionality, and user experience that exceeds customer expectations and unlocks business potential. This is especially important as customers accelerate their digital innovation across business operations while maintaining the agility to adapt to fluctuating market demands. SAP BTP provides this for our customers.</p>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div>SAP Business Technology Platform is the right tool to manage sites, applications, users, and everything you can imagine in the cloud and non-cloud world, from my point of view BTP is very well focused and has everything that a tool has to have.</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div><em><a href="https://www.trustradius.com/reviews/sap-business-technology-platform-2023-11-08-14-00-23">Read the full review by Warner Bros. Discovery on TrustRadius</a></em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>To read what other customers said about SAP BTP, please take a look at <a href="https://www.trustradius.com/products/sap-business-technology-platform/reviews">our TrustRadius review page</a>. We welcome you to <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/pricing.html">try out SAP BTP for yourself too</a>.</p>
  <p>On behalf of the entire SAP BTP team, we sincerely thank TrustRadius for acknowledging SAP BTP in its 2024 Top Rated awards and our dedicated SAP BTP customers for their unwavering support.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>JG Chirapurath is chief marketing and solutions officer for SAP Business Technology Platform.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-build</category>
            <category>product/sap-integration-suite</category>
            <category>product/sap-master-data-governance</category>
            <category>news-tag/trustradius</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Extends Contract with Chief Technology Officer Juergen Mueller]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-extends-contract-with-cto-juergen-mueller</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-extends-contract-with-cto-juergen-mueller</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP has extended the contract of CTO Juergen Mueller for three years through 2027. Mueller joined the company in 2013 and the Board in 2019.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d4256f3133f0b4e05056896b40ac385c7299de26.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d4256f3133f0b4e05056896b40ac385c7299de26.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1d4256f3133f0b4e05056896b40ac385c7299de26.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Extends Contract with Chief Technology Officer Juergen Mueller" src="./media_1d4256f3133f0b4e05056896b40ac385c7299de26.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-extends-contract-with-chief-technology-officer-juergen-mueller">SAP Extends Contract with Chief Technology Officer Juergen Mueller</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced that it has extended the contract of Dr. Juergen Mueller, Chief Technology Officer (CTO) of SAP SE, for another three years until the end of 2027. Mueller joined SAP in 2013 and has been a member of the Executive Board of SAP SE since 2019.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As CTO, he leads the Technology &#x26; Innovation Board area at SAP and has successfully established SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP) as the platform for SAP and as an external business unit. In his mandate as CTO, he will prepare SAP for its accelerated cloud growth. In addition to SAP BTP, he is responsible for architecture decisions and innovations across SAP as well as Business Transformation Management with SAP Signavio and SAP LeanIX. Global security and cloud compliance are also part of his responsibility.</p>
  <p>“I would like to thank the Supervisory Board for their trust and am thrilled to continue shaping SAP’s technology strategy and driving innovation for our customers around the world,” Mueller said. “Together with our teams, I will continue working with the clear goal of being the number one enterprise application and business AI company.”</p>
  <p>“In recent years, Juergen Mueller and his team have successfully developed SAP BTP and established it as the platform of choice for our customers,” said Professor Hasso Plattner, chairman of the Supervisory Board of SAP SE. “We thank Juergen Mueller for his successful work to date and are convinced that he will continue to ensure SAP’s innovation capabilities in the future.”</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="http://news.sap.com/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Media Contact:</strong><br>Marcus Winkler, +49 6227 767497, <a href="mailto:marcus.winkler@sap.com">marcus.winkler@sap.com</a>, CEST<br><a href="http://www.news-sap.com/press-room/">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>This document contains forward-looking statements, which are predictions, projections, or other statements about future events. These statements are based on current expectations, forecasts, and assumptions that are subject to risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results and outcomes to materially differ. Additional information regarding these risks and uncertainties may be found in our filings with the Securities and Exchange Commission, including but not limited to the risk factors section of SAP’s 2023 Annual Report on Form 20-F.<br>© 2024 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Combine the Power of AI with Business Context Using SAP HANA Cloud Vector Engine]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2024/04/sap-hana-cloud-vector-engine-ai-with-business-context</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2024/04/sap-hana-cloud-vector-engine-ai-with-business-context</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The latest quarterly release introduces the SAP HANA Cloud vector engine, enhancing capabilities with AI technology to tackle complex issues.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/executive-blog</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP and NVIDIA to Accelerate Generative AI Adoption Across Enterprise Applications Powering Global Industries]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/sap-and-nvidia-to-accelerate-generative-ai-adoption</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/sap-and-nvidia-to-accelerate-generative-ai-adoption</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Together, SAP and NVIDIA will bring custom generative AI to thousands of enterprises around the world. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b3fcf19084a91c9721f2b9169c59bd16f3f8e1b6.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b3fcf19084a91c9721f2b9169c59bd16f3f8e1b6.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1b3fcf19084a91c9721f2b9169c59bd16f3f8e1b6.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP and NVIDIA to Accelerate Generative AI Adoption Across Enterprise Applications Powering Global Industries" src="./media_1b3fcf19084a91c9721f2b9169c59bd16f3f8e1b6.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-and-nvidia-to-accelerate-generative-ai-adoption-across-enterprise-applications-powering-global-industries">SAP and NVIDIA to Accelerate Generative AI Adoption Across Enterprise Applications Powering Global Industries</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Customers Can Harness Their Business Data in Cloud Solutions from SAP Using Customized LLMs Deployed with NVIDIA AI Foundry Services and New NVIDIA NIM Microservices</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <table>
          <thead>
            <tr>
              <th>Text Large</th>
            </tr>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td>
                <p><strong><em>WALLDORF and SANTA CLARA, Calif.</em></strong></p>
                <hr>
                <p><a href="http://www.nvidia.com">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) and <a href="http://www.nvidia.com">NVIDIA</a> (NASDAQ: NVDA) today announced a partnership expansion focused on accelerating enterprise customers’ ability to harness the transformative power of data and generative AI across SAP’s portfolio of cloud solutions and applications.</p>
              </td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
        <p>The companies are collaborating to build and deliver SAP Business AI, including scalable, business-specific generative AI capabilities inside the Joule copilot from SAP and across SAP’s portfolio of cloud solutions and applications – all of which are underpinned by the SAP generative AI hub. The generative AI hub facilitates relevant, reliable and responsible business AI and provides instant access to a broad range of large language models (LLMs).</p>
        <p>As part of SAP’s ongoing initiative to build generative AI directly into the applications that power the world’s businesses, the partnership aims to help customers adopt generative AI capabilities at scale across their organizations. SAP will use <a href="https://www.nvidia.com/en-us/ai-data-science/generative-ai/">NVIDIA’s generative AI foundry service</a> to fine-tune LLMs for domain-specific scenarios and deploy applications with new <a href="https://nvidianews.nvidia.com/news/generative-ai-microservices-for-developers">NVIDIA NIM</a>™ microservices. SAP and NVIDIA plan to make the new integrated capabilities available by the end of 2024.</p>
        <p>“Enterprise customers want to leverage state-of-the-art technology that delivers real business value,” said Christian Klein, CEO and Member of the Executive Board of SAP SE. “Strategic technology partnerships, like the one between SAP and NVIDIA, are at the core of our strategy to invest in technology that maximizes the potential and opportunity of AI for business. NVIDIA’s expertise in delivering AI capabilities at scale will help SAP accelerate the pace of transformation and better serve our customers in the cloud.”</p>
        <p>“SAP is sitting on a gold mine of enterprise data that can be transformed into custom generative AI agents to help customers automate their businesses,” said Jensen Huang, founder and CEO of NVIDIA. “Together, NVIDIA and SAP will bring custom generative AI to the thousands of enterprises around the world that rely on SAP to power their operations.”</p>
        <h2 id="harnessing-business-data-and-generative-ai-to-advance-customer-insights">Harnessing Business Data and Generative AI to Advance Customer Insights</h2>
        <p>SAP and NVIDIA plan to collaborate to integrate generative AI into cloud solutions from SAP, which include the latest release of the SAP Datasphere solution, SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP) and RISE with SAP.</p>
        <p>SAP plans to build additional generative AI capabilities within SAP BTP using NVIDIA’s generative AI foundry service, featuring <a href="https://www.nvidia.com/en-us/data-center/dgx-cloud/">NVIDIA DGX™ Cloud</a> AI supercomputing, <a href="https://www.nvidia.com/en-us/data-center/products/ai-enterprise/">NVIDIA AI Enterprise</a> software and NVIDIA AI Foundation models. These new capabilities are designed to be the basis of SAP’s development and deployment of generative AI for customers and is expected to be accessible in the generative AI hub in SAP AI Core and SAP Datasphere.</p>
        <p>Additional generative AI initiatives include:</p>
        <ul>
          <li><strong>New capabilities for the Joule copilot</strong>: Joule can leverage <a href="https://blogs.nvidia.com/blog/2023/11/15/what-is-retrieval-augmented-generation/">retrieval-augmented generation</a> (RAG) capabilities built by NVIDIA and SAP, which can be deployed on leading hyperscalers or SAP’s own cloud environments. As a natural-language, generative AI copilot, Joule helps customers unlock the potential in their business by automating time-consuming tasks and quickly analyzing business-critical data to deliver more intelligent, personalized experiences.</li>
          <li><strong>Innovative use cases leveraging SAP S/4HANA Cloud, SAP SuccessFactors and SAP Signavio</strong>: SAP and NVIDIA are exploring more than 20 generative AI use cases where the companies can combine assets to simplify and enhance digital transformation. Among these are generative AI features that can automate enterprise resource planning with intelligent invoice matching in SAP S/4HANA Cloud; improve human resources use cases leveraging SAP SuccessFactors; and accelerate new generative AI insights from SAP Signavio to better process business recommendations and optimize SAP’s customer support processes.</li>
          <li><strong>Unifying AI data sources with SAP Datasphere</strong>: Built on SAP BTP, SAP Datasphere enables integration and a unified view of semantically rich SAP data with third-party data across the enterprise landscape to help customers adapt faster to market changes and make more efficient and better informed decisions. With SAP Datasphere, customers can confidently access a high-quality data fabric using AI and machine learning (ML) models. To accelerate SAP’s federated machine learning (FedML) capabilities for SAP Datasphere, NVIDIA and SAP are facilitating easier access to data for data scientists and enhancing ML workload performance with the support of NVIDIA accelerated computing platforms and NVIDIA AI Enterprise data science software such as <a href="https://developer.nvidia.com/rapids">NVIDIA RAPIDS</a>™.</li>
          <li><strong>Using LLMs for the ABAP programming language</strong>: To aid developers in creating domain-specific language code, SAP plans to use NVIDIA AI foundry services to assist in fine-tuning LLMs. This will build on SAP’s use of generative AI models to assist developers who use ABAP through the company’s ABAP Cloud model and SAP Cloud Application Programming model.</li>
        </ul>
        <h2 id="nvidia-ai-enterprise-powers-production-grade-generative-ai-across-cloud-solutions-from-sap">NVIDIA AI Enterprise Powers Production-Grade Generative AI Across Cloud Solutions from SAP</h2>
        <p>Once models are ready for deployment in cloud solutions from SAP, SAP plans to use NVIDIA AI Enterprise software, including NVIDIA NIM inference microservices and NVIDIA NeMo Retriever™ microservices. NVIDIA NIM can be used to accelerate and maximize inference performance across the accelerated infrastructure from SAP. Using NVIDIA NeMo Retriever microservices, SAP plans to add RAG capabilities that enable generative AI applications to more securely access data running on SAP software to improve accuracy and insights. Customers can plan to use RAG on both SAP and third-party data.</p>
        <p>To learn more about the SAP and NVIDIA partnership, <a href="https://www.nvidia.com/gtc/keynote/">watch the replay of Huang’s GTC keynote address</a>.</p>
        <p>Visit the <a href="/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
        <h2 id="about-nvidia">About NVIDIA</h2>
        <p>Since its founding in 1993, <a href="https://www.nvidia.com/">NVIDIA</a> (NASDAQ: NVDA) has been a pioneer in accelerated computing. The company’s invention of the GPU in 1999 sparked the growth of the PC gaming market, redefined computer graphics, ignited the era of modern AI and is fueling industrial digitalization across markets. NVIDIA is now a full-stack computing infrastructure company with data-center-scale offerings that are reshaping industry. More information at <a href="https://nvidianews.nvidia.com/">https://nvidianews.nvidia.com/</a>.</p>
        <table>
          <thead>
            <tr>
              <th>Text Large</th>
            </tr>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td><strong>About SAP</strong></td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
        <p>SAP’s strategy is to help every business run as an intelligent, sustainable enterprise. As a market leader in enterprise application software, we help companies of all sizes and in all industries run at their best: SAP customers generate 87% of total global commerce. Our machine learning, Internet of Things (IoT), and advanced analytics technologies help turn customers’ businesses into intelligent enterprises. SAP helps give people and organizations deep business insight and fosters collaboration that helps them stay ahead of their competition. We simplify technology for companies so they can consume our software the way they want – without disruption. Our end-to-end suite of applications and services enables business and public customers across 26 industries globally to operate profitably, adapt continuously, and make a difference. With a global network of customers, partners, employees, and thought leaders, SAP helps the world run better and improve people’s lives. For more information, visit <a href="http://www.sap.com">www.sap.com</a>.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="revolutionize-how-you-interact-with-sap-business-system-while-simplifying-your-day-to-day-with-faster-work-smarter-insights-and-better-outcomes">Revolutionize how you interact with SAP business system while simplifying your day-to-day with faster work, smarter insights and better outcomes</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/ai-assistant.html">Meet Joule</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><strong>Note to editors:</strong><br>To preview and download broadcast-standard stock footage and press photos digitally, please visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/photos">www.sap.com/photos</a>. On this platform, you can find high-resolution material for your media channels.</p>
  <p><strong>For customers interested in learning more about SAP products:</strong> Global Customer Center: +49 180 534-34-24<br>United States Only: 1 (800) 872-1SAP (1-800-872-1727)</p>
  <p><strong>For further information, contact:</strong><br>SAP: Scott Malinowski, +1 (617) 538-6297, <a href="mailto:scott.malinowski@sap.com">scott.malinowski@sap.com</a><br><a href="mailto:SAP%20Press%20Room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a><br>NVIDIA: Shannon McPhee, +1 (310) 920-9642, <a href="mailto:smcphee@nvidia.com">smcphee@nvidia.com</a></p>
  <p>Certain statements in this press release including, but not limited to, statements as to: the benefits, impact, performance, features, and availability of NVIDIA’s products and technologies, including NVIDIA’s generative AI foundry service, NVIDIA NIM microservices, NVIDIA DGX Cloud AI supercomputing, NVIDIA AI Enterprise software, and NVIDIA AI Foundation models, NVIDIA accelerated computing platforms, NVIDIA AI Enterprise data science software such as NVIDIA RAPIDS, RAPIDS cuDF and cuML, NVIDIA NeMo Retriever microservices; NVIDIA’s partnership with SAP, the benefits and impact of such partnership, and the features and availability of its services and offerings; SAP sitting on a gold mine of enterprise data that can be transformed into custom generative AI agents to help customers automate their businesses; and NVIDIA and SAP bringing custom generative AI to the thousands of enterprises around the world that rely on SAP to power their operations are forward-looking statements that are subject to risks and uncertainties that could cause results to be materially different than expectations. Important factors that could cause actual results to differ materially include: global economic conditions; our reliance on third parties to manufacture, assemble, package and test our products; the impact of technological development and competition; development of new products and technologies or enhancements to our existing product and technologies; market acceptance of our products or our partners’ products; design, manufacturing or software defects; changes in consumer preferences or demands; changes in industry standards and interfaces; unexpected loss of performance of our products or technologies when integrated into systems; as well as other factors detailed from time to time in the most recent reports NVIDIA files with the Securities and Exchange Commission, or SEC, including, but not limited to, its annual report on Form 10-K and quarterly reports on Form 10-Q. Copies of reports filed with the SEC are posted on the company’s website and are available from NVIDIA without charge. These forward-looking statements are not guarantees of future performance and speak only as of the date hereof, and, except as required by law, NVIDIA disclaims any obligation to update these forward-looking statements to reflect future events or circumstances.</p>
  <p>This document contains forward-looking statements, which are predictions, projections, or other statements about future events. These statements are based on current expectations, forecasts, and assumptions that are subject to risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results and outcomes to materially differ. Additional information regarding these risks and uncertainties may be found in our filings with the Securities and Exchange Commission, including but not limited to the risk factors section of SAP’s 2023 Annual Report on Form 20-F.</p>
  <p>© 2024 SAP SE and NVIDIA Corporation. All rights reserved.</p>
  <p>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p>NVIDIA, the NVIDIA logo, DGX, NVIDIA NeMo Retriever, NVIDIA NIM, and RAPIDS are trademarks and/or registered trademarks of NVIDIA Corporation in the U.S. and/or other countries. Other company and product names may be trademarks of the respective companies with which they are associated. Features, pricing, availability, and specifications are subject to change without notice.</p>
  <p>Please consider our <a href="https://www.sap.com/corporate/en/legal/privacy.html">privacy policy</a>. If you received this press release in your e-mail and you wish to unsubscribe to our mailing list please contact <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a> and write Unsubscribe in the subject line.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
            <category>product/sap-datasphere</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Biggest Opportunity for Businesses Today: Using the Right Business Data]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2024/03/business-opportunity-use-the-right-business-data</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2024/03/business-opportunity-use-the-right-business-data</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Having a central hub for data is more critical than ever. Updates to SAP Datasphere empower businesses with more innovations.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10cb3ea6ef420b80f58847074323ded1ddf40b734.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10cb3ea6ef420b80f58847074323ded1ddf40b734.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_10cb3ea6ef420b80f58847074323ded1ddf40b734.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="The Biggest Opportunity for Businesses Today: Using the Right Business Data" src="./media_10cb3ea6ef420b80f58847074323ded1ddf40b734.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="the-biggest-opportunity-for-businesses-today-using-the-right-business-data">The Biggest Opportunity for Businesses Today: Using the Right Business Data</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>There is no doubt that generative AI for business will transform every aspect of how business is done. But the reality is that generative AI is only as good as the data that it’s trained on.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>While data may be the fuel powering the engine of AI, it’s good data that’s the real game changer. With good data, a company can automate processes — freeing up their people to do the most impactful work — and analyze the most important variables facing their business to create intelligent insights.</p>
  <p>That’s where a datasphere comes in. It makes data more complete and logical by understanding the different relationships within a company’s data. And that’s what can truly bring out the best in any business today.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="deliver-seamless-and-scalable-access-to-mission-critical-business-data">Deliver seamless and scalable access to mission-critical business data</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/datasphere.html">Explore SAP Datasphere</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Having a central hub for data is more critical than ever. It allows our customers to better model their business across all SAP business applications. That’s exactly why we introduced <strong>SAP Datasphere</strong> last year to empower businesses with insights they need – based on the right data – in the context of their business. Since then, generative AI has disrupted and simplified even more business processes, and data capture is no different. This week <a href="/2024/03/future-of-data-driven-business-new-sap-datasphere-capabilities">we announced new generative-AI features in SAP Datasphere that will transform enterprise planning</a> through simplified data landscapes and more-intuitive data interaction.</p>
  <p>Why is this important? Because having a unified data view that simplifies the data landscapes while retaining context and logic is what enables businesses to adapt faster to market changes and make better decisions. It’s also a more efficient way of working. Because while you’re busy pulling data together, competitors are circling your customers.</p>
  <p>I am constantly speaking with our customers about the value of SAP Datasphere. It’s a data architecture that harmonizes mission-critical data across an organization. I hear amazing outcomes they’re able to achieve: from PwC breaking down silos in the different countries where it stores sensitive data so its workforce can access it more efficiently and securely for customers, to the Lufthansa Group taking data from different parts of its operations like aircraft, HR, and procurement, to see how decisions from one could impact the other.<br><br>With our additional news this week, such as making our generative AI copilot Joule available in SAP Analytics Cloud and expanding our partnership with Collibra to help our customers meet compliance, privacy, and regulatory requirements related to AI as they evolve, we’re making it easier to find the right data and use it to drive deeper insights, more efficiencies, faster growth, and more trust in their business.</p>
  <p>While PwC and Lufthansa show what’s possible today with a simplified data fabric, imagine what is about to become possible when you infuse it with the power of generative AI that understands your business – and then learns from that data. This has the potential to deliver exponential value from your data.</p>
  <p>Or think of it this way: years ago, the biggest differentiators for businesses were price, location, products, and services. Today, and especially in the years ahead, it could very well be how effectively a business is training their AI models. That’s why building the right data fabric is one of the most important investments any business can make today.</p>
  <p>It’s been said that the best way to predict the future is to invent it. And in an era where data is being created exponentially, I believe that those businesses that can separate the signal from the noise when it comes to their data will be the ones that invent the future in an AI-first world.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Scott Russell is a member of the Executive Board of SAP SE.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="take-a-guided-tour-and-experience-firsthand-the-power-of-business-data-with-sap-datasphere">Take a guided tour and experience firsthand the power of business data with SAP Datasphere</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/datasphere/guided-experience.html">Start now</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/blog/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/blog/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/blog/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/blog/article-read-more</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/executive-blog</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-datasphere</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[HomeMade: Self-Service Home Care Because There Is No Place Like Home]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/homemade-self-service-home-care-sap-btp</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/homemade-self-service-home-care-sap-btp</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[HomeMade, an Australian startup working to empower its customers in the home care sector, used SAP BTP to help scale, grow, and innovate.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_132610f4998fda9f546e77509f74312e342bbea68.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_132610f4998fda9f546e77509f74312e342bbea68.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_132610f4998fda9f546e77509f74312e342bbea68.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="HomeMade: Self-Service Home Care Because There Is No Place Like Home" src="./media_132610f4998fda9f546e77509f74312e342bbea68.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="homemade-self-service-home-care-because-there-is-no-place-like-home">HomeMade: Self-Service Home Care Because There Is No Place Like Home</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>People over age 65 made up 16% of the Australian population in 2020, and they’re on track to represent more than 22% by 2026. This growing cohort is increasingly forgoing traditional facility care models to remain at home. The Australian government offers financial support to qualifying citizens, who can use those funds to support in-home care.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>These government funds are typically managed by a traditional provider who establishes a plan within the customer’s budget and assigns caregivers. They offer limited to no choice regarding providers and little transparency on how the funds are being spent. This inefficient and costly approach reduces available funds for actual care with limited and often unfamiliar providers.</p>
  <p>Enter HomeMade, a startup looking to disrupt the home care sector with a transformative solution that would empower customers to not only stay in their own homes but also to oversee their spending and self-select their providers. With an initial staff of only six, HomeMade set out to create a <a href="/topics/business-technology-platform">technology platform</a> that would deliver efficiency, flexibility, transparency, and ease of use for customers and a scalable model that would grow and evolve with the company.</p>
  <h2 id="a-rock-solid-technology-foundation-for-a-digitally-native-startup">A Rock-Solid Technology Foundation for a Digitally Native Startup</h2>
  <p>Technology is at the heart of HomeMade’s business model, so choosing the right technology partner and the right digital platform was essential. “We wanted a solution that would give us that ability to scale rapidly and with confidence knowing that the rails weren’t going to fall off, because to be digitally enabled is what makes us different,” <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/laura-westhorpe/?originalSubdomain=au">Laura Westhorpe</a>, HomeMade general manager, said.</p>
  <p>HomeMade found the perfect partner in Bourne Digital, part of Accenture, which steered the startup to <a href="http://sap.com/btp">SAP Business Technology Platform</a> (SAP BTP). In choosing the platform, HomeMade benefits from a locally hosted, high-performance cloud architecture that can scale across its network. As a React Native open-source Cloud Foundry runtime service, the HomeMade application is intuitive, user-friendly, and easy for the company to maintain and support long term. Add SAP Integration Suite and SAP HANA data storage into the mix and HomeMade emerged with a secure, integrated, and scalable technology foundation to offer efficient care and support to Australia’s at-home care population.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="bring-out-your-best-with-data-and-ai-from-sap-btp">Bring out your best with data and AI from SAP BTP</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="young-company-makes-an-outsize-impact">Young Company Makes an Outsize Impact</h2>
  <p>In just two years, HomeMade has grown its business to 2,500 customers and reduced new user onboarding time from 14 days to 48 hours. The company has empowered qualifying citizens to manage their budgets and choose their care while saving 14 million Australian dollars and counting.</p>
  <p>Customers and families rave about the solution’s functionality and ease of use. HomeMade’s team members, who have grown to over 100, can happily focus on the customer instead of the endless paperwork they might find in traditional care management. Service providers appreciate timely payment, and another critical stakeholder – the Australian government – conducted a regulatory compliance audit and found that HomeMade scored 100% across 42 requirements for the Age Care Quality Safety Standards.</p>
  <p>And this is only the beginning for a new company already making an appreciable impact. “As the needs of HomeMade grow and evolve, the platform will grow and evolve with HomeMade,” <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/selimahmed/?originalSubdomain=au">Selim Ahmed</a>, managing director of Bourne Digital, part of Accenture, explained. For example, Ahmed continued, “We leverage AI business services to read documents…and we’re feeling really confident that those AI services will continue to play a part in the future evolution of HomeMade as the company moves more and more towards automation and self-service.”</p>
  <h2 id="adding-value-through-innovation">Adding Value Through Innovation</h2>
  <p>An SAP Innovation Award winner in 2023, HomeMade continues to grow and think creatively about how its foundational SAP BTP-based technology can enable it to continue to innovate and add value for customers. “There are endless opportunities,” Westhorpe said, from increasing efficiency to leveraging data to identify falls or other incidents to using large language models to recognize clinical deterioration in users and launch preventative interventions.</p>
  <p>For other startups looking to build technology solutions that will make a dramatic impact, Westhorpe offered to consider, “You want to build everything and you’ve got all these grand ideas, but what are the biggest things that will add value for customers?” Ahmed adds that resilience, a strong partnership, and hard work are critical: “Adapt, learn, grow together, and accept feedback…To build something innovative, you must be prepared to roll up your sleeves.”</p>
  <h2 id="the-full-episode">The Full Episode</h2>
  <p>Special thanks to <a href="https://apphaus.sap.com/">SAP AppHaus</a>, a hub for fostering human-centered innovation, for collaborating on this <a href="https://www.sap.com/programs/btp-better-together-customer-series.html">Better Together: Customer Conversations</a> on SAP Business Technology Platform episode. Learn more about how HomeMade built a better solution for qualifying citizens:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Thought leadership podcast:</strong> Thulium’s CEO <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/tamaramccleary/">Tamara McCleary</a> sat down with Westhorpe and Ahmed to discuss the change in caring for older adults, home-based care, and how technology can deliver on a promise dedicated to purpose.</li>
    <li><strong>Practitioners’ video</strong>: Westhorpe, Ahmed, and I discussed the challenges and opportunities in creating a world-class digital solution for a small but rapidly scaling startup.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>Explore more success stories of customers leveraging SAP BTP to help optimize processes for the sake of people and purpose:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/asset/dynamic/2023/04/ac38cbd6-6d7e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Colsubsidio</a></strong>: This nonprofit provider of wide-ranging social services chose SAP BTP and SAP HANA Cloud to enable extensive solution integrations, helping deliver better data connectivity and operational efficiency.</li>
    <li><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2023/07/b457bfbe-837e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Heartland Dental</a></strong>: Administratively supporting over 1,700 dental practices, Heartland Dental leverages SAP BTP to help improve the business assistant’s user experience, increase productivity, and reduce turnover.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>For the full episode and the on-demand Better Together: Customer Conversations series, visit <a href="https://www.sap.com/programs/btp-better-together-customer-series.html">sap.com/btp</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Timo Elliott is vice president and a global innovation advocate for SAP BTP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>industry/healthcare</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-apphaus</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>sap-award/sap-innovation-awards</category>
            <category>news-tag/startups</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP AppHaus Network to Onboard New Partners in North America]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/sap-apphaus-network-new-partners-in-north-america</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/sap-apphaus-network-new-partners-in-north-america</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP AppHaus Network announced its plans to establish additional partner-driven locations in North America. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/human-centered-innovation</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-apphaus</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-apphaus-network</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unleashing the Latest SAP Data and Analytics Innovations]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/latest-sap-data-and-analytics-innovations-sap-data-unleashed</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/latest-sap-data-and-analytics-innovations-sap-data-unleashed</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP has shared the latest innovations in data and analytics. Read on to learn more about the company's transformative announcements.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1025728cedc072568e25830043a6185f08eca8f64.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1025728cedc072568e25830043a6185f08eca8f64.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1025728cedc072568e25830043a6185f08eca8f64.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Unleashing the Latest SAP Data and Analytics Innovations" src="./media_1025728cedc072568e25830043a6185f08eca8f64.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="unleashing-the-latest-sap-data-and-analytics-innovations">Unleashing the Latest SAP Data and Analytics Innovations</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Today at <a href="/">SAP Data Unleashed</a>, SAP proudly announced the latest innovations in data and analytics.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Read on to learn more about these transformative announcements, which will enable businesses to unlock new potential in the areas of data management, AI-driven planning, and analytics.</p>
  <h2 id="access-insights-wherever-your-data-resides">Access Insights Wherever Your Data Resides</h2>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>SAP Datasphere Knowledge Graph</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP Datasphere knowledge graph will enable organizations to better represent their real-world use of data, leading to more effectively leveraging it for generative AI and better reasoning.</p>
  <p>As data is onboarded, transformed, and integrated in SAP Datasphere, SAP Datasphere knowledge graph automatically creates an ontology representing the relationships in the data, including the inherent business context from SAP application sources like SAP S/4HANA. This is then available to be extended and augmented via an ontology editor to reflect specific attributes within an organization. Finally, the data in SAP Datasphere is automatically applied to this ontology to create a knowledge graph that allows the data to be processed as a semantic web of relationships, drawing new insights from connections that are otherwise difficult to follow.</p>
  <p>These knowledge graphs are better suited for answering complex, often open-ended questions. For example, a marketing manager might ask a question like: “What type of campaign for mountain bikes works best for my highest performing cities with a population over 1 million?”</p>
  <p>Knowledge graphs can provide better context to large language models (LLMs) and prevent AI-generated “hallucinations.” SAP Datasphere knowledge graph will enable organizations to unleash the power of AI for even the most complex queries.</p>
  <p>The effort and cost of manually creating knowledge graphs is typically very high. SAP Datasphere knowledge graph overcomes this by pre-populating the knowledge graphs using all the valuable content already available in SAP Datasphere. The knowledge graph can then be used with Joule, SAP’s generative AI co-pilot, allowing business users to ask both open-ended and specific questions and get instant and well-documented answers. Sign up for a preview of SAP Datasphere knowledge graph via the link below.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15c1af20ba8e68937af5d24f99fac41cebc44dce7.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15c1af20ba8e68937af5d24f99fac41cebc44dce7.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_15c1af20ba8e68937af5d24f99fac41cebc44dce7.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_15c1af20ba8e68937af5d24f99fac41cebc44dce7.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="576">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>Auto-generated knowledge graphs enable AI to answer complex, open-ended questions</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>SAP HANA Cloud Vector Engine</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>With the next release of SAP HANA Cloud, a vector capability will be added to existing multi-model capabilities, allowing customers to gain value from all relevant types of business data using a single database. The inclusion of a vector engine further enables customers to build <a href="https://pages.community.sap.com/topics/hana/intelligent-data-applications">intelligent data applications</a> that combine the natural intuition of human interaction with powerful machine learning and multi-model processing capabilities.</p>
  <p>The vector engine in SAP HANA Cloud provides the ability to store and compare vectors using SQL. Determining similarity between vectors enables use cases such as retrieval-augmented generation (RAG), recommendations, classifications, clustering, and more. Key benefits of SAP HANA Cloud vector engine include:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Simplify data architecture and security with a single multi-model database with SQL interaction</li>
    <li>Gain new insights by combining spatial, graph, JSON, and relational data with vector queries</li>
    <li>Easily incorporate vector use cases in solutions based on the HANA Cloud ecosystem (clients, Python libraries, CAP, etc.)</li>
    <li>Integrate with open-source community tools such as LangChain via plug-ins</li>
  </ul>
  <p>SAP HANA Cloud vector engine is currently in public preview and is planned for general availability in late Q1 2024.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Simplified Consumption of Data Products in SAP Datasphere</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Data products facilitate self-service access to data as a product and enable data sharing across application boundaries. Data consumers need an easy way to explore, understand, and activate the data needed to perform their tasks — and data providers need an easy way to publish their assets and make them available to data consumers.</p>
  <p>SAP is innovating in this space with an improved user experience that drives data sharing at scale. This starts with published data products, whether produced by SAP line-of-business applications, industry solutions, or third parties, and follows with simple consumption in SAP Datasphere.</p>
  <p>In SAP Datasphere, customers will find ready access to SAP and non-SAP data products and easily install them into their SAP Datasphere instance. The procedure establishes relevant connections and creates the necessary artifacts in SAP Datasphere without the user having to enter those details. Key to this is making data provisioning easier via metadata, which are described via the Open Resource Directory (ORD) protocol. The experience will be harmonized within SAP Datasphere by bringing catalog and the data product installation closely together. Visit <a href="https://roadmaps.sap.com/board?range=FIRST-LAST&#x26;PRODUCT=73555000100800002141&#x26;q=data%20products#Q1%202024">SAP Road Map Explorer</a> for the latest updates.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15b1605af3a6110198283ea2725e4e982d88adc28.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15b1605af3a6110198283ea2725e4e982d88adc28.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_15b1605af3a6110198283ea2725e4e982d88adc28.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_15b1605af3a6110198283ea2725e4e982d88adc28.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="576">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>Data products available in catalog enhances the experience and productivity of data users</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>SAP Datasphere Semantic Onboarding Enhancements</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Semantic onboarding provides a seamless import of semantically rich objects from SAP S/4HANA and SAP BW/4HANA into SAP Datasphere. Now, we are taking the next step by adding support for SAP HANA Cloud and SAP data products through the same unified onboarding experience.</p>
  <p>Customers will be able to combine their SAP HANA Cloud modeling approach with SAP Datasphere by importing calculation views into the data layer of SAP Datasphere. This preserves the semantic information such as measures, attributes, hierarchies, aggregations, and currencies/units, while keeping SAP HANA Cloud and SAP Datasphere objects in sync — allowing customers to leverage their prior investments in SAP HANA modeling.</p>
  <p>Likewise, semantic onboarding of SAP data products will enable inheritance of business context from SAP line-of-business applications and industry solutions. By providing the semantics of the source systems and transferring that into the business data fabric as a foundation, SAP Datasphere drastically improves the analytic workflow and accelerates and simplifies data-driven insights.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Collibra AI Governance Integration with SAP Solutions</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The SAP and Collibra partnership enables end-to-end data governance and delivers trusted data to all users across the business data fabric. As more tasks and decisions are automated by AI within critical business processes, the need to extend governance to AI has also become apparent.</p>
  <p>The partnership with Collibra is being expanded to address the data and AI governance needs of joint customers via Collibra AI Governance. We will build tailored integrations between Collibra AI Governance and SAP solutions to connect the data used for AI with the models themselves in a single platform, allowing enterprises to track and manage their AI development efforts.</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Customers will better understand data lineage and metadata of SAP data that is utilized in AI modeling. With that, users can see what data their AI models were trained on to ensure that the data is accurate and from a trusted source.</li>
    <li>Customers will benefit from a single view to understand what AI models exist in their organization, and what data is being used to power them. AI/machine learning models created with SAP technology will be registered with the Collibra AI Governance platform.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>This extension of the SAP partnership with Collibra will increase transparency and accountability for organizations, and help ensure that regulatory, compliance, and privacy policies are being met. More importantly, it will build user trust by preventing biased decision-making, inaccurate recommendations, and other risks arising from AI.</p>
  <p>Together, SAP and Collibra will help joint customers address the data and AI governance needs across their organizations. Collibra AI Governance was <a href="https://www.collibra.com/us/en/company/newsroom/press-releases/collibra-introduces-collibra-ai-governance">launched last week</a> and is available to interested customers.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>SAP Datasphere Confluent Integration</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Core to the SAP data strategy is providing customers with the ability to interoperate with the world’s leading data and AI vendors through an open data ecosystem. To this end, the newly enhanced Confluent integration enables real-time streaming of data to and from SAP Datasphere.</p>
  <p>First, the outbound capabilities were extended by taking advantage of Confluent’s proprietary schema registry capabilities. Second, the Confluent schema registry will be used to enable seamless consumption of Confluent data within SAP Datasphere.</p>
  <p>The integration is specifically tailored to Confluent and provides a superior user experience for joint customers. It allows connections on the application level without additional custom application development. The integration is a pre-established replication flow in SAP Datasphere, which already includes delta and real-time processing natively. This makes the process very efficient as it does not force customers to load all the data at every step, but only when data has changed.</p>
  <p>The first integration for data ingestion into Kafka and Confluent is generally available. Additional capabilities for Confluent specific outbound and inbound integration will be generally available at the end of Q1 and Q3, respectively.</p>
  <h2 id="transform-planning-with-a-business-data-fabric">Transform Planning with a Business Data Fabric</h2>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>SAP Analytics Cloud for Planning Deep Integration to SAP Datasphere</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP Datasphere and SAP Analytics Cloud for planning will be more closely integrated to expand the business data fabric to planning use cases. SAP Analytics Cloud planning models can be deployed into SAP Datasphere, bringing plan and actuals data together for real-time steering.</p>
  <p>Through a reduction in both data footprint and modeling efforts, SAP Analytics Cloud extends planning functionality via SAP Datasphere and its native capabilities for transformation and integration. This reduces the complexity and risk inherent in storing multiple copies of data which is prevalent today.</p>
  <p>SAP Analytics Cloud for planning will have live access to actual and plan data for extended planning and analysis scenarios, including the live usage of master data. With this, SAP Datasphere will become the platform on which planning processes and tools can integrate.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14d5d8f4cd6ea2a14b3cb7d88fc159719e39722c7.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14d5d8f4cd6ea2a14b3cb7d88fc159719e39722c7.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_14d5d8f4cd6ea2a14b3cb7d88fc159719e39722c7.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_14d5d8f4cd6ea2a14b3cb7d88fc159719e39722c7.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="558">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>In this example, third-party inflation data from the World Bank (blue box) is provisioned through Datasphere to help planners do scenario planning with SAP Analytics Cloud compass</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP is the only vendor to offer a business data fabric that seamlessly integrates planning and therefore covers the entire technology stack required to transform data into insights and future actions. Visit <a href="https://roadmaps.sap.com/board?PRODUCT=67838200100800006884&#x26;q=seamless&#x26;range=CURRENT-LAST#;INNO=1FA75F34ABA51EDEADDAB4FD3ACC8288">SAP Road Map Explorer</a> for the latest updates.</p>
  <h2 id="foster-trusted-ai-across-your-business">Foster Trusted AI Across Your Business</h2>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>SAP Analytics Cloud Generative AI Co-Pilot</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP customers will embrace the power of generative AI to create and simulate business plans in SAP Analytics Cloud. With the power of Joule, planning and analytics professionals can leverage generative AI capabilities in a wide range of business processes. Activities such as data discovery, dashboard creation, planning model maintenance, and more are benefitting from a boost in core capabilities and an unmatched user experience.</p>
  <p>With the power of natural language processing, end users can easily run analytical queries, simulate driver impacts, plan resource allocations, and auto-generate dashboards and calculations. For example, a business user seeking to understand why gross margins declined in the latest version of a plan could query Joule, which could automatically look through previous plan iterations and attached comments, and uncover the fact that planners were estimating higher commodity costs.</p>
  <p>SAP’s investment in AI and its understanding of the context of business data provides truly limitless potential in unleashing the world of planning and analytics.</p>
  <p>A preview of Joule co-pilot functionality in SAP Analytics Cloud is planned to be available in Q2 2024. Sign up for the preview via the link below.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_135bdf52547a43026234fdf26c84defd9f04f1334.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_135bdf52547a43026234fdf26c84defd9f04f1334.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_135bdf52547a43026234fdf26c84defd9f04f1334.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_135bdf52547a43026234fdf26c84defd9f04f1334.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="574">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>With Joule co-pilot, planning and analytics professionals can prompt Joule to analyze all aspects of extended planning and create new analytical views on the fly, provisioned specially for individual user types</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>SAP Analytics Cloud Compass</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In an increasingly volatile business climate, it is essential to create operational and financial plans and provision BI insights with risk mitigation in mind. This requires the ability to simulate uncertainties and the probability of their impact. Knowing how uncertainties in commodity prices, labor costs, or production volumes will hit your operational expenses or revenue means that companies can quickly prepare and plan counter measures for any scenario.</p>
  <p>SAP Analytics Cloud compass provides Monte Carlo simulation capabilities with a business user-friendly interface. This enables non-technical users to perform real-time multi-variate analysis without prior IT setup or advanced statistical skills.</p>
  <p>Users can perform business simulations directly in SAP Analytics Cloud at a fraction of the time and effort required to perform similar analysis manually. Scenario modeling capabilities will allow comparisons between assumptions, and the reporting of impact variances provides real-time insight, concept validation, and reveals the sensitivity of the drivers chosen. Now customers can identify their major drivers and combinations over time, enabling a better understanding of the dynamics between the data, and how to continuously simulate better and faster. With compass, customers can face the future with confidence.</p>
  <p>A preview of SAP Analytics Cloud compass is planned to be available at the end of Q3 2024. Sign up for the preview via the link below.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b407deea790db28d0775959ab3574632b1f5e085.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b407deea790db28d0775959ab3574632b1f5e085.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1b407deea790db28d0775959ab3574632b1f5e085.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_1b407deea790db28d0775959ab3574632b1f5e085.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>SAP Analytics Cloud compass showing distribution of impact probability on the operating income based on a simulation of uncertainty in inputs such as inflation or other relevant drivers.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="get-started-today">Get Started Today</h3>
  <p>Begin your path toward unlocking the full potential of your business data with SAP Datasphere. Embrace the opportunity to seamlessly integrate and activate your data landscape, propelling your business into a new era of insights and efficiency. Start now and transform how your organization leverages data with SAP Datasphere.</p>
  <p>Start your journey today to bring out your best with SAP data and AI:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><a href="https://www.sap.com/registration/trial.4d48ec23-eadf-4399-8595-ac3f9c66c64f.html">Take a complete tour and try the latest features of SAP Datasphere</a> with the 30-day guided experience.</li>
    <li><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/datasphere/migration.html">Begin your SAP Business Warehouse cloud modernization journey</a> with a free assessment and special offers.</li>
    <li><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/oth/business-data-fabric/index.html?campaigncode=CRM-YJ24-BTP-2560577&#x26;source=blog-glo">Save on costs and learn how to implement a business data fabric architecture</a> with the Total Cost of Ownership study and getting started package</li>
    <li><a href="https://events.sap.com/dataunleashed-previews/en/home">Sign up today for an early preview</a> of the upcoming SAP Datasphere and SAP Analytics Cloud features</li>
  </ul>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Irfan Khan is chief product officer and president for SAP HANA Database &#x26; Analytics.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="deliver-seamless-and-scalable-access-to-mission-critical-business-data">Deliver seamless and scalable access to mission-critical business data</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/datasphere.html">Explore SAP Datasphere</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-data-unleashed</category>
            <category>product/sap-datasphere</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Data Unleashed: The Future Belongs to Data-Driven Organizations]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/future-belongs-to-data-driven-organizations-sap-data-unleashed</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/future-belongs-to-data-driven-organizations-sap-data-unleashed</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With the latest updates to SAP Datasphere, SAP is empowering data-driven organizations to bring out their best. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-data-unleashed</category>
            <category>product/sap-datasphere</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Shapes the Future of Data-Driven Business Transformation with Innovations that Equip Customers to Succeed in the Era of AI]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/future-of-data-driven-business-new-sap-datasphere-capabilities</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/future-of-data-driven-business-new-sap-datasphere-capabilities</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New SAP Datasphere capabilities will drive deeper insights, faster growth and more efficiency in the era of AI. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ca92906e5e003a06f25ac5a8b837a5576894477a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ca92906e5e003a06f25ac5a8b837a5576894477a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1ca92906e5e003a06f25ac5a8b837a5576894477a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Shapes the Future of Data-Driven Business Transformation with Innovations that Equip Customers to Succeed in the Era of AI" src="./media_1ca92906e5e003a06f25ac5a8b837a5576894477a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-shapes-the-future-of-data-driven-business-transformation-with-innovations-that-equip-customers-to-succeed-in-the-era-of-ai">SAP Shapes the Future of Data-Driven Business Transformation with Innovations that Equip Customers to Succeed in the Era of AI</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced transformative data innovations that will help customers harness the full power of their data to drive deeper insights, faster growth and more efficiency in the era of AI. New capabilities in the SAP Datasphere solution, including new generative-AI features, transform enterprise planning through simplified data landscapes and more-intuitive data interaction.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“Capturing data to make better decisions is an enterprise technology imperative that’s become increasingly critical as AI – which relies on quality data – revolutionizes every aspect of business,” said Juergen Mueller, SAP Chief Technology Officer and member of the Executive Board. “Our newest SAP Datasphere innovations, as well as an expanded partnership with Collibra, represent a quantum leap in our ability to help customers drive intelligent business transformations through data.”</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="deliver-seamless-and-scalable-access-to-mission-critical-business-data">Deliver seamless and scalable access to mission-critical business data</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/datasphere.html">Explore SAP Datasphere</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>At the heart of these announcements is the business data fabric, an architecture that helps ensure data is not just an asset but also the core underpinning of strategic initiatives. The innovations and partnership announced today equip organizations to deliver meaningful data to data consumers – with business context and logic intact.</p>
  <p>“We have decided to leverage SAP Datasphere for a modern business data fabric architecture in conjunction with our SAP S/4HANA landscape. It allows us to effectively establish a modern data analytics platform that enables a business self service capability on the basis of trusted data and data models,” said Achim Welter, Senior Director ERP, Digital &#x26; IT Strategy, Hershey’s.</p>
  <p>Today’s SAP Datasphere innovations help customers achieve a unified data view that simplifies their data landscapes while retaining context and logic – enabling them to adapt faster to market changes and make more-efficient decisions. From new copilot and vector database capabilities that help ensure business context remains constant in generative AI outputs to a new knowledge graph that helps uncover insights and patterns in complex data, SAP’s data innovations help ensure customers have the full power of their data at their fingertips.</p>
  <p>Today’s key innovations include:</p>
  <h2 id="generative-ai-copilot-and-ai-governance">Generative-AI Copilot and AI Governance</h2>
  <p>SAP’s generative-AI assistant, the <a href="https://www.sap.com/joule">Joule</a> copilot, is now coming to the SAP Analytics Cloud solution to automate the creation and development of reports, dashboards, plans and more. This automation is enabled by the <strong>SAP HANA Cloud vector engine capabilities,</strong> which combine the power of large language models with the relevant data of your organization – helping ensure business context is a constant for generative-AI outputs.</p>
  <p>Incorporating generative AI across the business isn’t possible without trusted and governed data. To provide organizations with a solution to govern the policies, processes and practices of AI, SAP is announcing an <strong>expansion of our partnership with Collibra</strong> to integrate Collibra’s AI Governance with SAP data assets. This can help provide transparency and accountability for organizations and help ensure regulatory, compliance and privacy policies are met.</p>
  <h2 id="discover-hidden-insights-and-patterns-with-knowledge-graph">Discover Hidden Insights and Patterns with Knowledge Graph</h2>
  <p>With the new <strong>SAP Datasphere knowledge graph,</strong> organizations can discover hidden insights and patterns across their applications and systems. This enables both technical and business users to deeply understand the relationships between data, metadata and business processes, as well as boost the effectiveness of machine learning and large language models.</p>
  <h2 id="unified-and-advanced-planning-and-analytics">Unified and Advanced Planning and Analytics</h2>
  <p>The new SAP Datasphere integration with SAP Analytics Cloud offers a single data management system and advanced analytics to power cross-organizational planning. Planners can leverage a single flexible model to break down silos between planning using one tool for data preparation, modeling and planning.</p>
  <p>Additionally, business users can use the <strong>new compass</strong> capability in SAP Analytics Cloud to realize better outcomes in planning and analytics through data-driven simulation. It enables organizations to run complex simulations using a chat interface to evaluate predictive outcomes and continually adjust controllable variables to find the optimal plan.</p>
  <p>This supports customers to transform their planning by unifying financial, operational, supply chain and workforce planning with native connection to SAP applications and third-party data.</p>
  <p>To learn more, please read: <strong><a href="/">Unleashing the Latest SAP Data and Analytics Innovations</a></strong>.</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="take-a-guided-tour-and-experience-firsthand-the-power-of-business-data-with-sap-datasphere">Take a guided tour and experience firsthand the power of business data with SAP Datasphere</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/datasphere/guided-experience.html">Start now</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>About SAP</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP’s strategy is to help every business run as an intelligent, sustainable enterprise. As a market leader in enterprise application software, we help companies of all sizes and in all industries run at their best: SAP customers generate 87% of total global commerce. Our machine learning, Internet of Things (IoT), and advanced analytics technologies help turn customers’ businesses into intelligent enterprises. SAP helps give people and organizations deep business insight and fosters collaboration that helps them stay ahead of their competition. We simplify technology for companies so they can consume our software the way they want – without disruption. Our end-to-end suite of applications and services enables business and public customers across 26 industries globally to operate profitably, adapt continuously, and make a difference. With a global network of customers, partners, employees, and thought leaders, SAP helps the world run better and improve people’s lives. For more information, visit <a href="http://www.sap.com">www.sap.com</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Note to editors:</strong><br>To preview and download broadcast-standard stock footage and press photos digitally, please visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/photos">www.sap.com/photos</a>. On this platform, you can find high resolution material for your media channels.</p>
  <p><strong>For customers interested in learning more about SAP products:</strong><br>Global Customer Center: +49 180 534-34-24<br>United States Only: 1 (800) 872-1SAP (1-800-872-1727)</p>
  <p><strong>For more information, press only:</strong><br>Julia Fargel, +1 (650) 276-8964, <a href="mailto:julia.fargel@sap.com">julia.fargel@sap.com</a>, PT<br>Martin Gwisdalla, +49 (6227) 767 275, <a href="mailto:martin.gwisdalla@sap.com">martin.gwisdalla@sap.com</a>, CET<br><a href="mailto:SAP%20Press%20Room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>This document contains forward-looking statements, which are predictions, projections, or other statements about future events. These statements are based on current expectations, forecasts, and assumptions that are subject to risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results and outcomes to materially differ. Additional information regarding these risks and uncertainties may be found in our filings with the Securities and Exchange Commission, including but not limited to the risk factors section of SAP’s 2023 Annual Report on Form 20-F.<br>© 2024 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.<br>Please consider our <a href="https://www.sap.com/corporate/en/legal/privacy.html">privacy policy</a>. If you received this press release in your e-mail and you wish to unsubscribe to our mailing list please contact <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a> and write Unsubscribe in the subject line.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-data-unleashed</category>
            <category>product/sap-datasphere</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Named Leader in the 2024 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for iPaaS for Fourth Consecutive Time]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/sap-named-leader-2024-gartner-magic-quadrant-ipaas</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/sap-named-leader-2024-gartner-magic-quadrant-ipaas</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP was named a Leader in the 2024 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Integration Platform as a Service (iPaaS) for the fourth consecutive time.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11e0cc32a99eaafa84b0f392021aac0d9ea3ac792.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11e0cc32a99eaafa84b0f392021aac0d9ea3ac792.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_11e0cc32a99eaafa84b0f392021aac0d9ea3ac792.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Named Leader in the 2024 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for iPaaS for Fourth Consecutive Time" src="./media_11e0cc32a99eaafa84b0f392021aac0d9ea3ac792.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-named-leader-in-the-2024-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-ipaas-for-fourth-consecutive-time">SAP Named Leader in the 2024 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for iPaaS for Fourth Consecutive Time</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>We are proud to announce SAP has been recognized as a Leader in the 2024 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Integration Platform as a Service (iPaaS) with SAP Integration Suite for the fourth consecutive time.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>We believe this prestigious recognition is a testament to our current capabilities, ongoing innovation, and commitment to providing world-class integration solutions for customers.</p>
  <h2 id="unparalleled-recognition-in-ipaas">Unparalleled Recognition in iPaaS</h2>
  <p>The Gartner Magic Quadrant provides an overview of the technology vendors in the iPaaS market and positions them according to their Ability to Execute and Completeness of Vision. According to Gartner, “Leaders have a deep understanding of the iPaaS market. They have a record of strong execution and an ability to influence the market’s direction. Leaders have a clear product road map to solidify the product’s position and to help buyers protect their investments. In <a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/dg/integration-platform-as-a-service-leader/index.html">the latest report</a>, SAP is positioned as a Leader again.”</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="unleash-the-power-of-connectivity-and-innovation-with-sap-integration-suite">Unleash the power of connectivity and innovation with SAP Integration Suite</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/integration-suite.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The ability for an organization to connect and automate its business applications faster and in new ways is critical in today’s digital world. SAP customers are seeking a robust integration solution to support their innovation and modernization initiatives. We believe this recognition serves as validation of our commitment to delivering industry-leading solutions that can empower businesses to seamlessly connect their applications, data, and processes.</p>
  <h2 id="a-winning-combination-of-technology-and-expertise">A Winning Combination of Technology and Expertise</h2>
  <p>SAP’s vision for SAP Integration Suite is to connect and automate business processes. As the key integration technology of <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform.html">SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP)</a>, SAP Integration Suite can empower customers to achieve seamless, scalable business processes without disruption. Its user-friendly interface, extensive library of proven prebuilt content for SAP and non-SAP applications, and robust security features help make it easy for customers to jump-start their integrations.</p>
  <p>Organizations across the globe have embraced SAP Integration Suite to help support automation of business processes, streamline operations, and strengthen their collaboration with partners and customers. Take <a href="https://www.sap.com/asset/dynamic/2024/01/6a507734-a27e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Pitney Bowes</a> for example. It wanted a solution to support its transformation from selling stand-alone products to offering holistic solutions that orchestrate physical delivery, installation, and support while minimizing the need for customization and providing growth for the company.</p>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div>Using SAP Integration Suite, part of SAP BTP, to integrate SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition with SAP Sales Cloud and third-party providers, we’re simplifying and standardizing business processes, increasing agility, and supporting our growth ambitions in select countries.</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>Stuart Beadle, Senior Director, Global Order Management, Supply Chain Applications and SAP Service, Pitney Bowes Inc.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Customer experience is one of the criteria evaluated by Gartner in the report for the ability to execute. According to the report, “Relationships, products, and services/programs that enable clients to be successful with the products are evaluated. Specifically, this includes the ways customers receive technical support or account support. This can also include ancillary tools, customer support programs (and the quality thereof), availability of user groups, service-level agreements, and so on.”</p>
  <p>See <a href="https://www.gartner.com/reviews/market/integration-platform-as-a-service-worldwide/vendor/sap/product/sap-integration-suite">Gartner Peer Insights</a> to read the reviews.</p>
  <h2 id="learn-more">Learn More</h2>
  <p><a href="/topics/sap-integration-suite">SAP Integration Suite</a> can accelerate innovation, speed connectivity, and connect everyone to automated processes. We remain steadfast in providing powerful and reliable integration solutions. To learn more:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/dg/integration-platform-as-a-service-leader/index.html">Read the full report</a></li>
    <li>Explore exclusive iPaaS content on <a href="https://gateway.on24.com/wcc/eh/3869277/integration-space">SAP’s integration space</a></li>
    <li><a href="https://discovery-center.cloud.sap/serviceCatalog/integration-suite?region=all&#x26;category=all">Get started for free</a> with SAP Integration Suite</li>
    <li>Learn more about <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/integration-suite.html">SAP Integration Suite</a></li>
  </ul>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>JG Chirapurath is chief marketing and solutions officer for SAP BTP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-sap-news-delivered-to-your-inbox-once-a-week">Get the latest SAP news delivered to your inbox once a week</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/nl/sap-news-center-newsletter/index.html">Sign up today</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Gartner, Magic Quadrant for Integration Platform as a Service 19 February 2024, Keith Guttridge Et Al.<br>Gartner does not endorse any vendor, product or service depicted in its research publications and does not advise technology users to select only those vendors with the highest ratings or other designation. Gartner research publications consist of the opinions of Gartner’s research organization and should not be construed as statements of fact. Gartner disclaims all warranties, expressed or implied, with respect to this research, including any warranties of merchantability or fitness for a particular purpose.<br>GARTNER is a registered trademark and service mark of Gartner and Magic Quadrant is a registered trademark of Gartner, Inc. and/or its affiliates in the U.S. and internationally and are used herein with permission. All rights reserved.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-integration-suite</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Digital Eco-Farming: How SAP Japan Helps Revitalize Rural Communities]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/minano-digital-eco-farm-sap-japan-revitalize-rural-communities</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/minano-digital-eco-farm-sap-japan-revitalize-rural-communities</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The Minano Digital Eco Farm, launched by PSI and SAP Co-Innovation Lab in Japan, is helping the town of Minano revitalize its community.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/agribusiness</category>
            <category>news-tag/digitization</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>news-tag/internet-of-things</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-co-innovation-lab</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Recognized as a Major Player in the IDC MarketScape Experience-Centric Intelligent Digital Workspaces]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/sap-recognized-idc-marketscape-experience-centric-intelligent-digital-workspaces</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/sap-recognized-idc-marketscape-experience-centric-intelligent-digital-workspaces</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In a new MarketScape, IDC has recognized SAP Build Work Zone as a modern, robust solution for digital workplaces. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1bc71d974e0081b3064b32f0acac989c4add119a3.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1bc71d974e0081b3064b32f0acac989c4add119a3.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1bc71d974e0081b3064b32f0acac989c4add119a3.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Recognized as a Major Player in the IDC MarketScape Experience-Centric Intelligent Digital Workspaces" src="./media_1bc71d974e0081b3064b32f0acac989c4add119a3.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-recognized-as-a-major-player-in-the-idc-marketscape-experience-centric-intelligent-digital-workspaces">SAP Recognized as a Major Player in the IDC MarketScape Experience-Centric Intelligent Digital Workspaces</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Today’s digital workplace is constantly evolving, but the way we work is still siloed and complicated. Employees often waste time switching between applications, searching for information, finding data, and seeking recommendations and insights to get work done. They desire an intelligent work experience to boost engagement and productivity.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/workzone.html">SAP Build Work Zone</a> provides a unified, intelligent work experience for the modern workforce.</p>
  <h2 id="idc-marketscape-experience-centric-intelligent-digital-workspaces-recognition">2024 IDC MarketScape: Experience-Centric Intelligent Digital Workspaces Recognition</h2>
  <p>SAP has been recognized as a Major Player in the IDC MarketScape: Worldwide Experience-Centric Intelligent Digital Workspaces 2024 Vendor Assessment (doc # US49741923, January 2024), based on IDC analysts and customer feedback. We believe this recognition acknowledges SAP’s ongoing dedication in delivering a modern, robust digital workplace solution to optimize user engagement and productivity, and to drive overall business agility.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-an-excerpt-of-the-idc-marketscape-report-now">Read an excerpt of the IDC MarketScape report now</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/workzone.html?pdf-asset=c4053575-a87e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b&#x26;page=1">Get the complementary copy</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>IDC defines an intelligent digital workspace as a well-organized system of tools working together to enhance end users’ overall productivity and experiences. This system integrates intentional design, engineering, and artificial intelligence (AI) to provide a customized and seamless view of tools for user tasks. It ensures secure access to resources from any location or device and enables IT and security professionals with complete oversight.</p>
  <p>As stated within this IDC MarketScape report, “Client organizations we interviewed noted that SAP Build Work Zone reinforced the importance of collaboration and knowledge management.”</p>
  <p>Here are the additional highlights on strengths of SAP Build Work Zone noted in the report:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>A unified digital workspace</strong>: SAP Build Work Zone supports building blocks of content, user interface (UI) integration cards, and home page widgets to embed and display SAP or third-party business data in one workspace. Guided experiences sit on top of workflows to guide the user journey.</li>
    <li><strong>Streamlined user tasks</strong>: SAP Task Center is used within SAP Build Work Zone to act as a unified inbox to provide one place for all approvals and to dos. Global announcements can be tracked for reads and to check length of time spent on content items with native SAP analytics, or with third-party tools such as Google Analytics or Qualtrics. Customers have noted that SAP Build Work Zone provided a friendly UI and access to all functionality on the mobile app.</li>
    <li><strong>Seamless connection to a comprehensive product suite</strong>: SAP Build Work Zone is used to connect the SAP suite of capabilities — including SAP S/4 HANA, SAP Success Factors, and SAP Integrated Business Planning solutions — to handle workflow and collaboration of tasks across multiple IT and business users. SAP Build Work Zone offers pre-built workspace templates with public, private, or external access and an impersonation feature to preview workspaces in-context of specific audience segments.</li>
  </ul>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Evolving the Digital Workplace with SAP Build Work Zone</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="unify-experiences-enterprise-wide">Unify Experiences Enterprise-Wide</h3>
  <p>Business users gain centralized access to SAP and non-SAP business applications, processes, and information, including custom-built apps and extensions, from desktop to mobile using SAP Build Work Zone. The solution offers a personalized, role-based user experience, for example, allowing business users to quickly search for applications or information they need, promptly manage tasks and notifications through the integrated inbox, and stay updated on content, apps, workflows, and processes that are seamlessly integrated across the business landscape without constantly switching around applications or leaving their desktops.</p>
  <h3 id="build-workspaces-simpler-and-faster-with-low-code">Build Workspaces Simpler and Faster with Low-Code</h3>
  <p>Business users are empowered to build and customize business sites visually. They can build branded sites, pages, and workspaces for different purposes and complexity. Our pre-built line-of-business content — including home pages, workspaces, integrations, and guided experiences — dramatically accelerates their time-to-value. For example, HR users can create pages for benefits announcements and design workspaces for learning academies. With the flexibility to design a tailored digital experience, business users can organize their work intuitively by bringing together their favorite business applications and unstructured content side-by-side, within a unified environment.</p>
  <p>UI integration cards is a powerful widget to visualize data from back-end systems, allowing business users to quickly gain business insights into, for example, purchasing trends, account receivable overview, or compliance checklist. In addition, guided experiences streamline complex, difficult processes that span multiple systems, transforming them into simple, fast, and error-free experiences. This empowers business users to self-service their way through cross-application processes such as onboarding, returning to work, or submitting parental leave requests with ease and confidence.</p>
  <p>SAP Build Work Zone is part of <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/low-code.html">SAP Build, a portfolio of low-code solutions</a> that enables the people closest to the business problems to create and augment enterprise applications, automation processes, and design workspaces and business sites visually.</p>
  <h3 id="optimize-team-effectiveness-within-and-beyond-the-enterprise">Optimize Team Effectiveness Within and Beyond the Enterprise</h3>
  <p>SAP Build Work Zone is also designed to amplify team effectiveness across internal employees, external customers, partners, and suppliers. Business users can visually create workspaces to facilitate better team engagement through knowledge sharing, streamlined business processes execution, content management, and implementing best practices. They can also leverage surveys, polls, and interactive Q&#x26;A sessions to gather valuable feedback, improving communication and work synergy.</p>
  <p>Many SAP Build Work Zone customers have created purpose-built business sites to actively engage with their external customers, partners, and suppliers. For example, a supplier business site is created for suppliers to self-service various business operations, including supplier onboarding, accessing policies, managing account payables and invoicing processes, and obtaining product knowledge along with Q&#x26;As. By empowering suppliers to address their requirements and needs, not only enhances their engagement and efficiency but also saves internal teams’ time for more impactful, high-value activities.</p>
  <h3 id="unlock-the-future-of-digital-workplaces">Unlock the Future of Digital Workplaces</h3>
  <p>Like many customers and partners, <a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2023/07/b457bfbe-837e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Heartland Dental and Avvale</a> chose SAP Build Work Zone and SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP) to improve more than 5,000 business assistant’s user experience and productivity across more than 1,700 dental practices within the national dental network. Since its initial rollout in 2023, it has been reported that 33 hours per day have been saved across the initial 200 supported offices.</p>
  <p>Looking ahead, SAP remains dedicated to delivering the best-in-class innovations to our customers to enable their business success, such as injecting business AI capabilities by enabling SAP Joule as the digital assistant for intelligent interactions within SAP Build Work Zone.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Learn More</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <ul>
    <li>Read a complimentary excerpt copy of the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/workzone.html?pdf-asset=c4053575-a87e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b&#x26;page=1">IDC MarketScape Experience-Centric Intelligent Digital Workspaces report</a></li>
    <li>Join the <a href="https://community.sap.com/topics/work-zone">SAP Build Work Zone community</a></li>
  </ul>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Sid Misra is vice president for Product Marketing and Solution Management at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><strong>About IDC MarketScape Experience-Centric Intelligent Digital Workspaces</strong><br>This IDC research explores the intelligent digital workspace environment, offering further insights on the pace of adoption, the potential success of technology, and the level of market excitement. This aims to empower IT and business decision-makers to evaluate investments based on their own judgments.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/idc-marketscape</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-build</category>
            <category>product/sap-build-work-zone</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Generative AI for Business Is Creating a New Playbook for Value]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2024/02/how-generative-ai-for-business-is-creating-a-new-playbook-for-value</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2024/02/how-generative-ai-for-business-is-creating-a-new-playbook-for-value</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The promise of generative AI is the value it creates. With it, SAP Sports One supports better scouting. Learn why businesses should care.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/executive-blog</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>industry/sports-entertainment</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cloud Technology Empowers Ugandan Island Community]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/videos/cloud-technology-empowers-ugandan-island-community</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/videos/cloud-technology-empowers-ugandan-island-community</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[KOPGT, which educates farmers on improved agricultural practices, recognized the need for a digital solution to meet the rising demand for palm oil and chose SAP Rural Sourcing Management.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/video</category>
            <category>industry/agribusiness</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-one</category>
            <category>product/sap-rural-sourcing-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP TechEd in 2024: An Expanded Global Program to Meet You Where You Are]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/sap-teched-in-2024-expanded-global-program</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/sap-teched-in-2024-expanded-global-program</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP TechEd in 2024 offers three unique and convenient experiences so customers and partners can easily build skills and meet with experts.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1cd2d1e153edaa50b3c6b55dcda64e30a680ce56f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1cd2d1e153edaa50b3c6b55dcda64e30a680ce56f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1cd2d1e153edaa50b3c6b55dcda64e30a680ce56f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP TechEd in 2024: An Expanded Global Program to Meet You Where You Are" src="./media_1cd2d1e153edaa50b3c6b55dcda64e30a680ce56f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-teched-in-2024-an-expanded-global-program-to-meet-you-where-you-are">SAP TechEd in 2024: An Expanded Global Program to Meet You Where You Are</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>I’m thrilled to share a sneak peek of our <a href="/topics/sap-teched">SAP TechEd</a> program for 2024, which brings together developers, practitioners, enterprise architects, and global IT leaders to explore SAP’s latest innovations and gain hands-on learning.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>This year, we’re offering three unique and convenient event experiences so customers and partners can build skills and meet 1:1 with SAP experts.</p>
  <h2 id="sap-teched-virtual">SAP TechEd Virtual</h2>
  <p>Held October 8-9, 2024, the free two-day virtual event will deliver SAP technology news and announcements via global keynotes, technical and developer enablement, and engaging sessions of live and pre-recorded content for everyone across the globe.</p>
  <h2 id="sap-teched-on-tour">SAP TechEd On Tour</h2>
  <p>Taking place on multiple dates throughout the year, the single-day in-person events hosted across the globe by SAP experts and the SAP Community will deliver deep learning, networking, and hands-on engagement. Locations will range in North America, Europe, the Middle East and Africa (EMEA), Latin America and the Caribbean (LAC), and Asian-Pacific and Japan (APJ) regions.</p>
  <h2 id="asug-tech-connect-in-partnership-with-sap-teched-west-palm-beach-florida">ASUG Tech Connect, in partnership with SAP TechEd, West Palm Beach, Florida</h2>
  <p>From November 12-14, 2024, the major three-day event stopover on the SAP TechEd program tour will deliver visionary keynotes, technical education and enablement, expert-led sessions, and a full-scale show floor community experience with networking, best practices, and hands-on engagement.</p>
  <p>I can’t wait to see everyone at an SAP TechEd event in 2024!</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>JG Chirapurath is chief marketing and solutions officer for SAP BTP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-notified-about-updates-and-news-on-the-2024-sap-teched-program">Get notified about updates and news on the 2024 SAP TechEd program</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/dg/sap-teched-subscription/index.html">Sign up now</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-teched</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Corvias Combines SAP S/4HANA Cloud and SAP BTP to Streamline Efficiency and Maximize Results]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/corvias-sap-streamline-efficiency-maximize-results</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/corvias-sap-streamline-efficiency-maximize-results</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Corvias selected SAP S/4HANA Cloud, private edition and SAP BTP to help modernize its business processes. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16b00da7ad89aecaccd983d3343285162838738c3.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16b00da7ad89aecaccd983d3343285162838738c3.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_16b00da7ad89aecaccd983d3343285162838738c3.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Corvias Combines SAP S/4HANA Cloud and SAP BTP to Streamline Efficiency and Maximize Results" src="./media_16b00da7ad89aecaccd983d3343285162838738c3.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="corvias-combines-sap-s4hana-cloud-and-sap-btp-to-streamline-efficiency-and-maximize-results">Corvias Combines SAP S/4HANA Cloud and SAP BTP to Streamline Efficiency and Maximize Results</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><a href="https://www.corvias.com/">Corvias</a> is known for its unwavering commitment to addressing critical infrastructure challenges. The company’s work isn’t merely about providing housing or energy – it’s about enhancing quality of life and promoting collaboration within communities.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>This vision is underpinned by concrete plans that will help turn it into a reality. That’s why Corvias recently began modernizing its business processes for the future. Together with <a href="https://www.avvale.com">Avvale</a>, the company embarked on a journey that led to the adoption of SAP S/4HANA Cloud, private edition and SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP).</p>
  <h2 id="a-vision-for-optimization">A Vision for Optimization</h2>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15c36d38c8030e9f6e88a0cf9cdb1cdba127470ce.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15c36d38c8030e9f6e88a0cf9cdb1cdba127470ce.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_15c36d38c8030e9f6e88a0cf9cdb1cdba127470ce.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Row of houses. Photo courtesy of Corvias" src="./media_15c36d38c8030e9f6e88a0cf9cdb1cdba127470ce.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="600" height="400">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>Photo courtesy of Corvias</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Before choosing SAP, Corvias was grappling with a complex organizational structure, one characterized by disconnected systems and processes across accounting and purchasing. The allocation process was cumbersome and required redundant updates in multiple parts of the system, causing administrative headaches.</p>
  <p>Executive leadership quickly identified the need to simplify workflows so that they could deliver information to the right stakeholders effectively and quickly and create an integrated system that could move data seamlessly between processes without human intervention.</p>
  <h2 id="choosing-sap-for-success">Choosing SAP for Success</h2>
  <p>To help overcome its challenges, Corvias selected two primary SAP solutions: <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/s4hana-private-edition.html">SAP S/4HANA Cloud, private edition</a> and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform.html">SAP BTP</a>. With them, Corvias hoped to primarily centralize its data, enabling integrated purchasing and accounting capabilities. The implementation also leveraged SAP Fiori to help develop customized applications for allocating segment costs.</p>
  <p>Today, Corvias’ processes are simplified and streamlined, thanks to real-time, actionable information accessible by key members of leadership through SAP. This allows them to be more strategic in their decision-making with greater visibility into real costs and profitability at both the individual and project levels, contributing to a more efficient financial management system for the company overall.</p>
  <h2 id="far-reaching-benefits">Far-Reaching Benefits</h2>
  <p>The adoption of SAP has empowered the company to concentrate on enhancing its working capital through ongoing improvements. This has fostered a culture of innovation and encouraged a proactive approach to operational challenges and enhancements within the organization.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-tailored-to-fit-cloud-erp-that-adapts-to-your-organizations-unique-transformation">Get tailored-to-fit cloud ERP that adapts to your organization’s unique transformation</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/s4hana-private-edition.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In accounts payable, for instance, the implementation of automated purchase order management processes has resulted in a notable decrease in touch points. The accounts payable team has seen a reduction from seven to two touch points in 75% of cases. This not only enhances efficiency but reduces the likelihood that errors will occur as often as they would with manual processes. The streamlined purchase-order management system has become a valuable asset in optimizing the company’s financial workflow.</p>
  <p>Corvias has also embraced a more unified and secure information management system. By standardizing data security roles throughout the entire organization, SAP provided a reliable and protected method for managing information. This consistency has made it easier for site teams to handle administrative tasks, freeing up their time to focus on more strategic initiatives.</p>
  <p>Best of all, these SAP solutions provided a flexible and scalable platform that allows Corvias to seamlessly incorporate acquired or new companies.</p>
  <h2 id="looking-ahead-to-the-future">Looking Ahead to the Future</h2>
  <p>Corvias’ journey with SAP and Avvale showcases the transformative power of streamlined systems and integrated solutions. By addressing the challenges of a complex organizational structure and disparate workflows, Corvias not only achieved operational efficiency but also laid the groundwork for future scalability. The collaboration with Avvale unlocked expert guidance and support throughout the process, highlighting the importance of strategic partnerships in navigating the evolving landscape of technology integration.</p>
  <p>Today, as Corvias continues to oversee diverse projects in partnership with the military, higher education institutions, and communities, the adoption of SAP stands as a testament to the company’s commitment to innovation and excellence across all its mission-critical endeavors.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Mike Kaszuk is SVP and COO for Midmarket at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/sme</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>industry/mining: industry/mill-products</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Self-Sovereign Identity Gives Users Control Over Their Personal Data]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/self-sovereign-identity-gives-control-over-personal-data</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/self-sovereign-identity-gives-control-over-personal-data</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Self-sovereign identity (SSI) is the first technology to give individuals maximum control over their digital persona. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/data-privacy</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-innovation-center-network</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Is a Leader in the 2023 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Financial Planning Software]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/sap-leader-2023-gartner-magic-quadrant-financial-planning-software</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/sap-leader-2023-gartner-magic-quadrant-financial-planning-software</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[We are proud to announce that Gartner has recognized SAP as a Leader in its 2023 Magic Quadrant for Financial Planning Software.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_12c0f62a0c1bea8cebafaf88b1a2478cf4d11b899.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_12c0f62a0c1bea8cebafaf88b1a2478cf4d11b899.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_12c0f62a0c1bea8cebafaf88b1a2478cf4d11b899.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Is a Leader in the 2023 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Financial Planning Software" src="./media_12c0f62a0c1bea8cebafaf88b1a2478cf4d11b899.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-is-a-leader-in-the-2023-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-financial-planning-software">SAP Is a Leader in the 2023 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Financial Planning Software</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>We are proud to announce that Gartner has recognized SAP as a Leader in its <a href="https://www.gartner.com/reprints/?id=1-2FU0XES5&#x26;ct=231206&#x26;st=sb">2023 Magic Quadrant for Financial Planning Software</a>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>At SAP, our commitment extends beyond traditional financial planning and analysis (FP&#x26;A), reaching across the entire enterprise of financial professionals. To achieve a comprehensive FP&#x26;A transformation, organizations need effortless access to crucial finance data, regardless of its location. In a landscape where financial information is dispersed across various applications, files, and systems – both on premise and in the cloud – organizations often expend significant resources on extracting, rebuilding, and integrating their financial data to deliver forecasts and simulations.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-analytics-cloud-make-decisions-without-doubt">SAP Analytics Cloud: Make decisions without doubt</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/cloud-analytics.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>By harnessing cutting-edge FP&#x26;A software tools and adopting strategic approaches, organizations can seamlessly explore, connect, integrate, govern, and orchestrate their planning and analysis. SAP’s solutions for financial planning and analysis can provide a reliable foundation for finance information, delivering trustworthy, pertinent, and timely financial insights. This can streamline finance data, helping to maximize business information potential. Simultaneously, it can foster an analytics-driven approach to planning and decision-making. Our primary solution for financial planning and analysis is <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/cloud-analytics/features/planning.html">SAP Analytics Cloud</a>. This solution is part of <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">SAP Business Technology Platform</a> (SAP BTP).</p>
  <p>Gartner evaluated 16 vendors and named SAP a Leader based on our “ability to execute” and “completeness of vision.” We believe this recognition serves as an acknowledgment of SAP’s continued commitment to providing our customers with world-class financial planning software.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1db92051bee73b9bb29a5433d2213c41cc9f52bab.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1db92051bee73b9bb29a5433d2213c41cc9f52bab.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1db92051bee73b9bb29a5433d2213c41cc9f52bab.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_1db92051bee73b9bb29a5433d2213c41cc9f52bab.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="570" height="592">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>This graphic was published by Gartner, Inc. as part of a larger research document and should be evaluated in the context of the entire document. The Gartner document is available upon request from SAP here. Click to enlarge.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="future-proof-your-organization-with-sap-solutions-for-xpa">Future-Proof Your Organization with SAP Solutions for xP&#x26;A</h2>
  <p>Our focus on accelerating planning and analysis (xP&#x26;A) is achieved by integrating with SAP S/4HANA Cloud and other SAP applications. This integration helps enable swift planning cycles, providing live access to actuals and plans. Customers can use our solutions to help extend their planning and analysis across the enterprise to facilitate seamlessly connected financial, workforce, sales, and supply chain plans. By adopting this approach, SAP customers can react quickly to changes and increase decision-making agility and performance no matter what events unfold.</p>
  <p>A pivotal aspect of our approach involves harnessing the power of artificial intelligence (AI) and machine learning for everyday planning. With a single click, our users can activate predictive analytics, allowing for insights with greater ease and speed. The AI capabilities within SAP Analytics Cloud are helping organizations unlock the full potential of their data and derive greater value from analytics and planning. With these capabilities, planners can model a wide range of scenarios and generate more accurate forecasts and plans.</p>
  <p>We are committed to instilling unwavering confidence in plans by meticulously ensuring the trustworthiness of data. Leveraging the powerful combination of <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/datasphere.html">SAP Datasphere</a> and SAP Analytics Cloud, we go beyond traditional boundaries to help harmonize planning data seamlessly across SAP and third-party sources, presenting natively integrated plans that can form a reliable foundation for strategic decision-making.</p>
  <p>This approach has yielded tangible benefits for organizations such as <a href="https://www.sap.com/asset/dynamic/2023/06/34b2b0e8-797e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Watco</a> and <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/customer-stories/roche.html">F. Hoffmann-La Roche AG</a>. These SAP Analytics Cloud customers have experienced firsthand the transformative impact of having their planning data seamlessly integrated, resulting in enhanced precision and efficacy in their planning and analysis endeavors. With our holistic approach, we help pave the way for you to navigate the complex landscape of financial planning with confidence, working to ensure your business decisions are backed by a foundation of accurate and planning-ready data.</p>
  <h2 id="next-steps">Next Steps</h2>
  <p>SAP is dedicated to advancing financial planning and analysis through our suite of financial planning software tools. Our commitment is reflected in the seamless transformation of financial data into actionable insights at scale for our customers. If you’re poised to unlock the full potential of your financial data and elevate your FP&#x26;A capabilities, explore the next steps with the resources provided:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Visit our <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/financial-management/financial-planning-analysis-fpa.html">financial planning and analysis page</a></li>
    <li>Try the free <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/financial-management/financial-planning-analysis-fpa/guided-experience.html">financial planning and analysis guided experience</a></li>
    <li>Read the full, complimentary <a href="https://www.gartner.com/reprints/?id=1-2FU0XES5&#x26;ct=231206&#x26;st=sb">Gartner Magic Quadrant for Financial Planning Software</a> report</li>
  </ul>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Dan Yu is senior vice president of SAP Business Technology Platform.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Gartner, Magic Quadrant for Financial Planning Software, Regina Crowder, Matthew Mowrey, Vaughan Archer, 5 December 2023<br>Gartner does not endorse any vendor, product or service depicted in its research publications and does not advise technology users to select only those vendors with the highest ratings or other designation. Gartner research publications consist of the opinions of Gartner’s Research &#x26; Advisory organization and should not be construed as statements of fact. Gartner disclaims all warranties, expressed or implied, with respect to this research, including any warranties of merchantability or fitness for a particular purpose.<br>GARTNER is a registered trademark and service mark of Gartner, Inc. and/or its affiliates in the U.S. and internationally, Magic Quadrant is a registered trademark of Gartner, Inc. and/or its affiliates and is used herein with permission. All rights reserved.</p>
  <p>Top image courtesy of SAP employee Laurentia-Iulia Pavel.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/financial-management</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/magic-quadrant</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Recognized as a Leader in 2023 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Data Integration Tools]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/sap-a-leader-gartner-magic-quadrant-data-integration-tools</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/sap-a-leader-gartner-magic-quadrant-data-integration-tools</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[For the 16th consecutive time, Gartner has recognized SAP as a Leader in its Magic Quadrant for Data Integration Tools.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18676e13249083c87480612ffdb6501c1181d00cd.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18676e13249083c87480612ffdb6501c1181d00cd.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_18676e13249083c87480612ffdb6501c1181d00cd.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Recognized as a Leader in 2023 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Data Integration Tools" src="./media_18676e13249083c87480612ffdb6501c1181d00cd.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-recognized-as-a-leader-in-2023-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-data-integration-tools">SAP Recognized as a Leader in 2023 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Data Integration Tools</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>We are proud to announce that Gartner has recognized SAP as a Leader in its 2023 <a href="https://www.gartner.com/reprints/?id=1-2FTDYPZU&#x26;ct=231204&#x26;st=sb">Magic Quadrant for Data Integration Tools</a> for the 16th consecutive time.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-an-engaging-hands-on-experience-with-sap-datasphere">Get an engaging, hands-on experience with SAP Datasphere</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/datasphere/guided-experience.html">Start now</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>To achieve true digital transformation, organizations must have seamless access to their mission-critical business data no matter where it resides. Yet with data landscapes distributed among different applications and systems both in the cloud and on premises, organizations spend countless resources extracting, rebuilding, and integrating their data.</p>
  <p>By leveraging the right data integration tools and strategies, organizations can easily discover, connect, integrate, govern, and orchestrate their data assets. Data integration offerings from SAP deliver trusted, relevant, and timely information to enable customers to simplify their data landscape and unleash the power of business data. Our primary solutions include <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/datasphere.html">SAP Datasphere</a>, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/cloud-platform/capabilities/integration.html">SAP Data Intelligence</a> Cloud, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/data-services.html">SAP Data Services</a>, and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/cloud-platform/capabilities/integration.html">SAP Integration Suite</a>. These offerings are part of <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">SAP Business Technology Platform</a> (SAP BTP).</p>
  <p>Gartner evaluated 21 vendors and named SAP a Leader based on our “ability to execute” and “completeness of vision.” We believe this recognition serves as acknowledgment of SAP’s continued commitment to providing our customers with world-class data integration tools.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b4a7dd1fbccb32babb1428357e9df797fb738917.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b4a7dd1fbccb32babb1428357e9df797fb738917.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1b4a7dd1fbccb32babb1428357e9df797fb738917.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_1b4a7dd1fbccb32babb1428357e9df797fb738917.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="926" height="1024">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>This graphic was published by Gartner, Inc. as part of a larger research document and should be evaluated in the context of the entire document. The Gartner document is available upon request from SAP here.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="unleash-the-power-of-business-data">Unleash the Power of Business Data</h2>
  <p>Data integration is necessary for customers to gain intelligent, relevant, and contextual insights for better decision-making. However, without the right data management approach and technology, companies can face an uphill battle in integrating, processing, curating, governing, and augmenting their data.</p>
  <p>SAP takes a business data fabric approach, which goes beyond a traditional data fabric. A business data fabric is a data management architecture that delivers an integrated, semantically rich data layer over underlying data landscapes to provide users with scalable access to their data without duplication.</p>
  <p>It eliminates the need to recreate the business context that was lost from extracting and replicating data. This gives users the ability to accelerate their decision-making with trust and confidence, knowing they always have the complete picture of their data regardless of where it is stored or how it was designed.</p>
  <p>SAP Datasphere — and its open data ecosystem — is the foundation for a business data fabric. It equips any organization to deliver meaningful data to every data consumer — with business context and logic intact. SAP Datasphere helps customers:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Access authoritative data:</strong> Accelerate time-to-value by automatically reusing the semantical definitions and associations from SAP applications</li>
    <li><strong>Enrich all data projects:</strong> Harmonize heterogeneous data into a business semantic model of diverse data landscape</li>
    <li><strong>Simplify the data landscape:</strong> Access all data across hybrid and cloud environments no matter where it resides</li>
  </ul>
  <p>With a unified experience for data integration, data cataloging, semantic modeling, data warehousing, data federation, and data virtualization, SAP Datasphere enables data professionals to easily distribute authoritative business data — with business context and logic preserved — across the data landscape.</p>
  <p>Since the launch of SAP Datasphere, we have seen tremendous growth of customers innovating with this technology. For example, Messer CIO David Johnston describes his experience with the solution this way:“The business data fabric architecture enables us to bring SAP and non-SAP data together in the seamless and self-service way we’ve been envisioning. SAP Datasphere provided us with a solution to build a harmonized layer, or business data fabric, across SAP and non-SAP, cloud or on-premise data sources, making the best use of our existing investments in SAP, Microsoft Azure, Salesforce, and Oracle.”</p>
  <h2 id="next-steps">Next Steps</h2>
  <p>For over 16 years, data integration tools from SAP have enabled our customers to turn disjoined data assets into actionable business insights at scale. Take the next step and begin your business data fabric journey today:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Visit the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/datasphere.html">SAP Datasphere page</a></li>
    <li>Try the free <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/datasphere/guided-experience.html">SAP Datasphere guided experience</a></li>
    <li>Read the <a href="https://www.gartner.com/reprints/?id=1-2FTDYPZU&#x26;ct=231204&#x26;st=sb">2023 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Data Integration Tools report</a></li>
  </ul>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Kaiser Larsen is vice president of Data and Analytics at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Gartner, Magic Quadrant for Data Integration Tools, Ehtisham Zaidi, Robert Thanaraj, Sharat Menon, Thornton Craig, Roxane Edjlali, Michele Launi, 4 December 2023<br>Gartner does not endorse any vendor, product or service depicted in its research publications and does not advise technology users to select only those vendors with the highest ratings or other designation. Gartner research publications consist of the opinions of Gartner’s Research &#x26; Advisory organization and should not be construed as statements of fact. Gartner disclaims all warranties, expressed or implied, with respect to this research, including any warranties of merchantability or fitness for a particular purpose.<br>GARTNER is a registered trademark and service mark of Gartner, Inc. and/or its affiliates in the U.S. and internationally, Magic Quadrant is a registered trademark of Gartner, Inc. and/or its affiliates and is used herein with permission. All rights reserved.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/data-fabric</category>
            <category>news-tag/data-integration</category>
            <category>news-tag/database-and-data-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/magic-quadrant</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-datasphere</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP and PayPal Collaborate to Simplify Digital Payments Through the PayPal Braintree Platform]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/sap-and-paypal-collaborate-to-simplify-digital-payments-through-the-paypal-braintree-platform</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/sap-and-paypal-collaborate-to-simplify-digital-payments-through-the-paypal-braintree-platform</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[PayPal and SAP have developed a digital payments plug-in for the PayPal Braintree platform built on SAP Business Technology Platform.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ac1ce4a441b54c0d79d5f46a481f6eacec1f4082.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ac1ce4a441b54c0d79d5f46a481f6eacec1f4082.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1ac1ce4a441b54c0d79d5f46a481f6eacec1f4082.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP and PayPal Collaborate to Simplify Digital Payments Through the PayPal Braintree Platform" src="./media_1ac1ce4a441b54c0d79d5f46a481f6eacec1f4082.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-and-paypal-collaborate-to-simplify-digital-payments-through-the-paypal-braintree-platform">SAP and PayPal Collaborate to Simplify Digital Payments Through the PayPal Braintree Platform</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) announced today it has expanded its integration with financial services company, <a href="https://www.paypal.com/us/home">PayPal</a>, through the creation of a digital payments plug-in for the PayPal Braintree platform built on SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP).</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="bring-together-data-and-analytics-ai-application-development-automation-and-integration-on-sap-btp">Bring together data and analytics, AI, application development, automation, and integration on SAP BTP</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP BTP brings together data and analytics, artificial intelligence, application development, automation and integration into one unified environment. Using SAP BTP to build its digital payments processing solution, PayPal now can offer a plug-in for SAP customers to manage payments easily online.</p>
  <p>Many companies in recent years have seen an increase in business and compliance requirements for sending and receiving payments across organizations. As a result, digital wallets, automated clearing houses (ACH) and credit cards are being used for corporate transactions. With the PayPal Braintree Digital Payments connector, SAP customers can use all these funding sources to reduce costs and complexity.</p>
  <p>The PayPal Braintree platform provides SAP customers with more payment choices. It is the only payment platform that supports PayPal, Venmo*, credit and debit cards and popular digital wallets in a single integration. SAP customers who purchased the SAP digital payments add-on can easily connect to PayPal with the plug-in, now available from the <a href="https://help.sap.com/docs/DIGITALPAYMENTS">SAP Help Portal site</a>. Customers will benefit from increased efficiency, cost savings, security and transparency, with the plug-in’s smooth integration with SAP software environments certified through the <a href="https://www.sap.com/partners/partner-program/certify-my-solution.html#software">SAP Integration and Certification Center</a>.</p>
  <p>“The payments space has undergone unprecedented disruption over the past couple years, driving companies to embrace more customer-centric, agile payments environments,” said David Bruce, VP, Channel Partnerships, PayPal. “That’s why PayPal teamed up with SAP to develop the PayPal Braintree digital payments app, providing consistent, standard access for SAP customers to connect with PayPal’s payment processing solutions. We hope this is the first of many adaptors built on SAP BTP.”</p>
  <p>Shane Gorman, Chief Operation Officer, Business Technology Platform, SAP, said: “It’s great to see technology companies like PayPal use SAP BTP to develop standard adaptors that our customers and partners can use during an implementation for a consistent customer experience and reduced complexity.”</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="http://news.sap.com/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <p>*Venmo is available only in the United States.</p>
  <p><strong>Media Contact:</strong><br>Bridget Carroll, +1 (267) 615-3589, <a href="mailto:bridget.carroll@sap.com">bridget.carroll@sap.com</a>, MT<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-us-on-linkedin-for-the-latest-news-and-updates">Connect with us on LinkedIn for the latest news and updates</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news/posts/?feedView=all">Follow SAP News</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>This document contains forward-looking statements, which are predictions, projections, or other statements about future events. These statements are based on current expectations, forecasts, and assumptions that are subject to risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results and outcomes to materially differ. Additional information regarding these risks and uncertainties may be found in our filings with the Securities and Exchange Commission, including but not limited to the risk factors section of SAP’s 2022 Annual Report on Form 20-F.<br>© 2023 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Generative AI-Enabled Developers Are the Architects of the Future]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/generative-ai-enabled-developers-architects-of-the-future</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/generative-ai-enabled-developers-architects-of-the-future</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Generative AI developers are the architects of the future. Learn how SAP is enabling every developer to become a business AI developer.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-build-code</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Data Can Move the Needle on Sustainability]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/data-can-move-the-needle-on-sustainability</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/data-can-move-the-needle-on-sustainability</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Non-profit eXXpedition is collecting data to investigate the causes of and solutions to ocean plastic pollution. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-footprint</category>
            <category>news-tag/circular-economy</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP and Infosys Introduce New Sustainable and Innovative Industry Cloud Solution]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/sap-and-infosys-introduce-sustainable-industry-cloud-solution</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/sap-and-infosys-introduce-sustainable-industry-cloud-solution</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With the SAP-validated partner use case program, Infosys and SAP created a solution to help companies monitor their carbon footprints.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_164f38f864e0733a6806af629b2d24613241a4b15.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_164f38f864e0733a6806af629b2d24613241a4b15.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_164f38f864e0733a6806af629b2d24613241a4b15.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP and Infosys Introduce New Sustainable and Innovative Industry Cloud Solution" src="./media_164f38f864e0733a6806af629b2d24613241a4b15.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-and-infosys-introduce-new-sustainable-and-innovative-industry-cloud-solution">SAP and Infosys Introduce New Sustainable and Innovative Industry Cloud Solution</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>In today’s fast-paced and dynamic business environment, <a href="/topics/sustainability">sustainability</a> is no longer a buzzword; it’s a critical business priority. Investors and customers seek more sustainable business practices from their solution providers and enterprises are keenly focused on integrating sustainability into their operations. This is no easy lift, and it doesn’t happen overnight. Several challenges need to be addressed, including action planning, effective resource allocation, and prioritization.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>For companies to act sustainably, responsibly, and efficiently, they must harness the power of data-driven decisions and advanced technology to reduce their carbon footprint and create sustainable product portfolios. Enter SAP and its broad ecosystem of industry cloud partners with a shared vision to help businesses become strategic, sustainable, intelligent enterprises.</p>
  <h2 id="hack2build-opens-door-for-innovation-and-sustainability">Hack2Build Opens Door for Innovation and Sustainability</h2>
  <p>The <a href="https://events.sap.com/hack2build/en/home">Hack2Build event from SAP</a>, organized by SAP Co-Innovation Lab, is an initiative designed to harness the creativity and speed of prototyping industry cloud solutions by SAP partners in days as opposed to weeks. At a September 2022 Hack2Build event, SAP partner Infosys presented a solution for organizations to identify, track, predict, and refine carbon emissions during sales and operations planning (S&#x26;OP) and make sustainable decisions. The solution, <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2023/08/7affe1f5-847e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Sustainable S&#x26;OP and Carbon Footprint Management</a>, was built using SAP Integrated Business Planning (SAP IBP) for Supply Chain, SAP S/4HANA, SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP), SAP Integration Suite, and SAP Sustainability Footprint Management.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="industry-cloud-solutions-from-sap-and-partners-can-help-you-find-a-competitive-edge">Industry cloud solutions from SAP and partners can help you find a competitive edge</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/industry-cloud.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="framework-for-tracking-emissions-leverages-the-power-of-saps-industry-cloud">Framework for Tracking Emissions Leverages the Power of SAP’s Industry Cloud</h2>
  <p>Infosys’ carbon footprint solution calculates carbon emissions based on greenhouse gas protocols and global warming potential factors across an organization’s procurement, production, and distribution processes. It helps calculate key information, such as estimates of CO2e emissions per order level, thereby helping to make decisions that can ensure a smaller carbon footprint. The solution also provides an innovative framework to help companies identify, track, predict, and refine their carbon emissions numbers throughout the entire supply chain process.</p>
  <h2 id="sap-validated-partner-use-case-program-offers-momentum-to-service-partner-solution">SAP-Validated Partner Use Case Program Offers Momentum to Service Partner Solution</h2>
  <p>Infosys’ solution is part of the SAP-validated partner use case program. The program was established to give SAP service partners the ability to showcase, position, and promote solutions and spotlight their expertise of SAP Business Technology Platform, leveraging the power of SAP’s vast customer base and industry networks.</p>
  <p>The SAP-validated partner use case program offers service partners the ability to:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Get amplified market reach</strong>: Increased visibility enables service partners to target a broader audience, opening doors to new markets and untapped opportunities. Leveraging SAP’s robust platform, partners can position themselves strategically and expand their global reach.</li>
    <li><strong>Collaborate and co-innovate</strong>: Participating in the SAP-validated partner use case program can foster collaboration with SAP experts, industry leaders, and customers.</li>
    <li><strong>Access a dynamic ecosystem</strong>: Partners can benefit from SAP’s ecosystem, where they can collaborate, exchange knowledge, and share best practices with some of the industry’s best leaders.</li>
    <li><strong>Develop customer-centric solutions</strong>: The program helps put the customer at the core of solution development. Service partners can gain valuable customer insights though interactions facilitated by SAP, leading to better-tailored products and services that can precisely address users’ pain points.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>The program presents opportunities for both customers and service partners to flourish. By achieving certification, service partners can earn credibility, expand market reach, and foster collaborative innovation with industry giants. Its streamlined processes help accelerate time-to-market, providing a significant advantage in today’s fast-paced business landscape.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-information-training-tools-and-resources-you-need">Get the information, training, tools, and resources you need</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://partneredge.sap.com/en/welcome.html?pexpRequestedURL=%2Fen%2Flibrary%2Feducation%2Fpsd%2F2023%2Fmar%2Fe_oe_te_w_rnbo_31837.html">Visit the SAP Partner Portal site</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The program unlocks a door to a dynamic ecosystem where partners can learn, grow, and develop customer-centric solutions that can meet industry demands head-on. For partners aiming to thrive in their respective industries, this program is a game changer. Service partners are encouraged to embrace the power of the SAP-validated partner use case program and transform their business.</p>
  <p>“Infosys is delighted to publish the Infosys Sustainable S&#x26;OP and Carbon Footprint Management Solution through the SAP-validated partner use case program,” said Atul Chorbele, AVP at Infosys. “We are confident that customers across industries will benefit from adopting this solution.”</p>
  <p>Holger Brammer, Global Partner Ecosystem vice president at SAP, praised this partner solution and the development process: “It was impressive to see how fast Infosys developed this solution on SAP BTP and integrated it with SAP S/4HANA, SAP IBP, and SAP Sustainability Footprint Management. I’m quite confident that this solution will resonate very well with customers.”</p>
  <p>To learn how to build industry innovation on SAP BTP and the SAP-validated partner use case program or get more information about <a href="mailto:lucca.sperl@sap.com">validated use cases on the SAP PartnerEdge site</a>, contact <a href="mailto:lucca.sperl@sap.com">Lucca Sperl</a>, industry cloud innovation program lead. To learn more about Infosys’ solution, <a href="https://www.infosys.com/campaigns/documents/sop-carbon-footprint-management.pdf">visit here</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>Vidya Gugnani is senior director and industry cloud ecosystem lead for Strategic Partners, North America at SAP.<br>Nitin Majahan is COE lead for SAP Industrial Manufacturing at Infosys.</p>
        <p>Top image courtesy of SAP employee Karsten Hohage</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-emissions</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-footprint</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-integrated-business-planning-for-supply-chain</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>