<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/experience-management/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Agrees to Sell Its Stake in Qualtrics as Part of Qualtrics Acquisition by Silver Lake and CPP Investments]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/sap-agrees-to-sell-its-stake-in-qualtrics</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/sap-agrees-to-sell-its-stake-in-qualtrics</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP SE (NYSE: SAP), today announced it has agreed to sell all of its 423 million shares of Qualtrics International Inc. as part of the ...]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/investor-relations</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/experience-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/qualtrics</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Measuring the Carbon Footprint of Employees Can Help You Make More Informed and Strategic Business Decisions]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/measuring-employee-carbon-footprint-business-decisions</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/measuring-employee-carbon-footprint-business-decisions</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Executives can make informed decisions when considering the social and actual carbon footprint of employees in planning. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/experience-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/people-sustainability</category>
            <category>news-tag/qualtrics</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-product-footprint-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-employee-central</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-people-analytics</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-workforce-analytics</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sustainable Business at Veolia ANZ: A Culture of Employee Engagement]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/veolia-anz-culture-of-employee-engagement</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/veolia-anz-culture-of-employee-engagement</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Aug 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Veolia ANZ builds a culture of employee engagement with SAP solutions as part of its sustainable business mission. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d9756ca8715dfa6172ff87e4a03e6f2be81050f0.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d9756ca8715dfa6172ff87e4a03e6f2be81050f0.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1d9756ca8715dfa6172ff87e4a03e6f2be81050f0.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Sustainable Business at Veolia ANZ: A Culture of Employee Engagement" src="./media_1d9756ca8715dfa6172ff87e4a03e6f2be81050f0.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sustainable-business-at-veolia-anz-a-culture-of-employee-engagement">Sustainable Business at Veolia ANZ: A Culture of Employee Engagement</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Sustainable business is one post-pandemic trend that’s here to stay, especially among global market leaders like <a href="https://www.veolia.com/anz/">Veolia ANZ</a>, a longtime champion of ecological transformation.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>With approximately 4,600 employees in Australia and 182,000 worldwide, Veolia ANZ has extended its sustainable business commitment to both customers and workers. The company’s COVID-19 crisis response team in Australia and New Zealand began using <a href="https://www.qualtrics.com/">Experience Management solutions from SAP and Qualtrics</a> this past year to stay connected with workers and address their challenges.</p>
  <p>“It’s critical that we constantly communicate with employees to understand their challenges and act quickly to address their needs,” said Alexandre Moreau, chief people and safety officer at Veolia ANZ. “We needed a quick and easy solution to keep people connected, whether it was managers and their teams or customers. Qualtrics helped us make sure that our people were okay and receiving the support they needed.”</p>
  <p>Sustainability is in Veolia’s DNA. The company’s business portfolio includes providing environmental solutions across water, waste management, and energy. With operations and treatment facilities nationwide, it serves customers of all sizes – from local cafes and food chains to industrial facilities. One of its business units helps municipal water customers provide safe drinking water for their communities and industrial clients to more sustainably manage water in their operations, while its energy division helps companies build energy resilience and become carbon neutral.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="put-employees-at-the-heart-of-everything-you-do-with-sap-successfactors">Put employees at the heart of everything you do with SAP SuccessFactors</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="listening-translates-employee-feedback-into-engagement">Listening Translates Employee Feedback Into Engagement</h2>
  <p>As a designated essential service during the <a href="/covid-19">pandemic</a>, Veolia ANZ provided the same level of support for customers despite significant challenges, including social distancing, schedule disruptions, and lockdowns. During the height of the crisis, it needed even more flexibility to respond to highly changeable situations. For example, workloads increased in the health sector because of pandemic-related activities. Meanwhile, some employees were working remotely, while others had to be in the field. The company used XM solutions from SAP and Qualtrics to stay in touch with employees.</p>
  <p>Kate Moonen, head of Marketing and Digital Experience at Veolia ANZ, was part of the company’s pandemic response team. Speaking during <a href="https://open.spotify.com/episode/1Xe6n7mvEGJCwKz4A7kOgl">The Best Run Podcast by SAP ANZ</a>, she discussed how short, but targeted surveys helped the company stay in touch with its diverse workforce that includes truck drivers, machine operators, engineers, lawyers, and sustainability experts in urban and remote locations.</p>
  <p>“We really wanted to understand that our people, particularly essential workers, were feeling supported,” she said. “Did they have enough PPE equipment to do their jobs safely? What were their concerns about their mental health and well-being? Based on that feedback, it helped our team formulate what we were going to communicate and what actions we needed to take to continue to support our people.”</p>
  <p>Initially, the team was surprised at the high employee engagement levels with the surveys. Over time, the company rolled out new activities based on the feedback. These included regularly scheduled, anywhere, any device communications with senior leadership through live webinars and question-and-answer sessions. In response to employee requests, executives also sent short video messages that employees could watch on their mobile phones, with personalized stories from company leaders about their lives outside of work and how they adapted to the changed working environment.</p>
  <p>“People felt they wanted to take the opportunity to be heard,” said Moonen. “We would often share regular communications with them about what came out of the latest pulse and what we were going to do about it. If you’re asking people for their time, it’s critical to demonstrate what you’re doing with that feedback to meet their needs.”</p>
  <h2 id="continuous-dialogue-through-employee-surveys">Continuous Dialogue Through Employee Surveys</h2>
  <p>Just like any aspect of sustainable business, employee engagement is not a one-and-done effort.</p>
  <p>“We’re seeing strong employee engagement every time we roll out a new survey,” said Moreau. “Instead of waiting a year to connect with employees, Qualtrics has given us a more agile response tool with a quick pulse check that our people appreciate and we can rely on for updated feedback to make better decisions. We want to know how people are feeling in a fast-changing business environment.”</p>
  <h2 id="go-digital-for-fast-action">Go Digital for Fast Action</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="the-future-of-business-has-feelings">The future of business has feelings</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/experience-management-xm.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Moreau said companies should be explicit about what employees have shared and how they’re taking action. Even if there isn’t an immediate answer, people appreciate the transparency.</p>
  <p>Moonen also advised employers not to overthink the survey process.</p>
  <p>“Sustainable business is all about agility,” she said. “Collecting the feedback and acting quickly is far more valuable than spending months iterating questions. Digital technology gives us the ability to constantly evolve and adapt as customer expectations, market conditions, and employee experiences shift.”</p>
  <h2 id="future-of-work-is-in-employee-experience">Future of Work Is in Employee Experience</h2>
  <p>In the wake of the pandemic, many employees yearn for a greater sense of belonging. They want more help with their individual career goals and to have pride in their workplace. Getting the employee experience right is part of every organization’s transformational journey to sustainable business.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Follow me @smgaler.</em><br><em><a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2021/07/08/sustainable-business-at-veolia-anz-we-make-sure-our-people-are-okay/?sh=5a8244291c0f">This blog also appeared on SAP BrandVoice on Forbes.</a></em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-engagement</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/experience-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/qualtrics</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-anz</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Using Mobile Technology with Hourly Employees: Balancing the Employee Experience and Wage Compliance Risks]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/mobile-technology-hourly-employee-experience-wage-compliance</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/mobile-technology-hourly-employee-experience-wage-compliance</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 13 Aug 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[There's value behind supporting deskless and hourly employees with mobile technology. But what wage compliance risks should be considered?]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/compliance</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/experience-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/mobile</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Essential But Under-Supported: Improving the Deskless Worker Experience]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/essential-but-under-supported-improving-deskless-worker-experience</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/essential-but-under-supported-improving-deskless-worker-experience</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Paying greater attention to the needs of deskless workers will be critical to the business success of companies. Read to learn why.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_13b84fe227b63d2b68747acdb3f8c93f97aa30483.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_13b84fe227b63d2b68747acdb3f8c93f97aa30483.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_13b84fe227b63d2b68747acdb3f8c93f97aa30483.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Essential But Under-Supported: Improving the Deskless Worker Experience" src="./media_13b84fe227b63d2b68747acdb3f8c93f97aa30483.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="essential-but-under-supported-improving-the-deskless-worker-experience">Essential But Under-Supported: Improving the Deskless Worker Experience</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/05/8ae80846-e37d-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Deskless workers</a> are employees whose jobs are performed outside an office, virtual or otherwise. This includes frontline and field employees in retail, manufacturing, utilities, healthcare, transportation, and other industries. The people who perform deskless jobs directly impact our day-to-day lives. They make and deliver the food we eat and clothes we wear, ensure we have power and water in our homes, build and maintain the tools and machines we rely on, and provide care and protection for us and our families.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Most of the employees declared <a href="https://www.epi.org/blog/who-are-essential-workers-a-comprehensive-look-at-their-wages-demographics-and-unionization-rates/">“essential workers”</a> during the <a href="/covid-19">pandemic</a> were in deskless jobs. Yet these essential employees receive little technology support compared to their desk-sitting colleagues.</p>
  <p>Approximately 80% of the world’s employees do not sit at a desk, but <a href="http://desklessworkforce2018.com/">only about 1% of enterprise software investment</a> is focused on deskless workers. We rely on deskless workers for tasks that directly impact the health, happiness, and welfare of ourselves and our loved ones. Yet we give them very little job support compared to their desk-based colleagues. Fortunately, changes in the nature of work are driving investment to improve the employee experience for deskless workers.</p>
  <h2 id="where-we-are-now">Where We Are Now</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="supporting-the-deskless-workforce-a-new-approach-to-understanding-and-improving-todays-employee-experience">Supporting the Deskless Workforce: A New Approach to Understanding and Improving Today’s Employee Experience</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm/insights.html?pdf-asset=8ae80846-e37d-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b&#x26;page=1">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>A recent <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm/insights.html?pdf-asset=8ae80846-e37d-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b&#x26;page=7">study</a> by SAP provides insight into what it is like to be a deskless worker. The study notes the nature of deskless jobs varies depending on things like level of customer interaction, skills specialization, and work environment. When compared to the attitudes of desk-based employees, deskless workers tend to be much less satisfied with wages and bonuses, training and career development, opportunities to share ideas with management, and communication from the company about the business and the performance of themselves and their teams. The highest levels of dissatisfaction are among deskless workers in jobs associated with high turnover located outside of corporate offices, like retail service and health aids, or low levels of customer interaction, like manufacturing and distribution.</p>
  <p>Statistics from this study paint a grim picture of the current state of deskless workers. “Only 33% of deskless workers feel comfortable talking to their manager about their salary. Forty-eight percent of deskless workers could not afford to lose the pay if they stayed home, and only 13% benefit from paid sick leave policies.” Only “61% of deskless workers in the United States intend to stay within their current job” although “69% of deskless workers would be less likely to leave their organization if employee communication would improve.” When confronted with statistics like these, it is little surprise that many industries find it <a href="https://www.npr.org/2021/07/20/1016081936/low-pay-no-benefits-rude-customers-restaurant-workers-quit-at-record-rate">difficult to hire and retain deskless workers</a>.</p>
  <h2 id="why-it-is-changing">Why It Is Changing</h2>
  <p>There are many reasons why deskless work is often seen as less enjoyable and fulfilling than desk-based work. It is often physically demanding, frequently pays less than desk-oriented jobs, and usually requires conforming to fixed work schedules. The fact that deskless workers are away from computers and offices also creates challenges in engaging and communicating with leaders and colleagues. However, three shifts in the nature of jobs are likely to profoundly improve the experience of deskless workers.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="put-employees-at-the-heart-of-everything-you-do-with-sap-successfactors-software">Put employees at the heart of everything you do with SAP SuccessFactors software</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="there-are-no-unskilled-jobs-in-a-digital-world">There Are No “Unskilled Jobs” in a Digital World</h3>
  <p>Historically, many deskless jobs were referred to as “unskilled” because they required no formal educational qualifications or requirements. Calling jobs unskilled led many companies to <a href="https://mitsloan.mit.edu/sites/default/files/2021-07/A%20Backgound%20Note%20on%20Unskilled%20Jobs%20in%20the%20United%20States.IC__0.pdf">devalue their worth</a>. Rather than investing in employee development, companies focused on using automation to make deskless jobs simpler to reduce costs of hiring and training workers. This focus on automation ultimately led to an interesting <a href="https://risnews.com/avocado-roulette-why-store-employees-are-key-online-revenue-growth">turning point that actually increased skill levels associated with deskless work</a>. The role of deskless workers now often focuses on non-routine problems that machines cannot handle or involves doing things that require uniquely human traits and talents, such as displaying empathy. This is making deskless work much more skilled and is increasing the importance of training, developing, and retaining deskless workers.</p>
  <h3 id="job-quality-is-driven-by-employee-experience">Job Quality Is Driven by Employee Experience</h3>
  <p>As the pace of business competition increases, companies rely on deskless employees to be fully engaged in their work, doing things such as paying high levels of attention to manufacturing and maintenance tasks, delivering exceptional customer or patient care, and finding effective solutions to transportation or construction challenges. Employees do not do these things well if they feel <a href="https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/abs/10.1111/j.1559-1816.2012.01017.x">stressed, overworked, or underappreciated</a>.</p>
  <h3 id="there-are-no-walls-in-a-hybrid-world">There Are No Walls in a Hybrid World</h3>
  <p>The events of 2020 created a <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/pulse/creating-hybrid-work-strategies-10-things-know-remote-steve-hunt/?lipi=urn%3Ali%3Apage%3Ad_flagship3_profile_view_base_post_details%3BVeEPxulCT5esEQetDU%2Bvkw%3D%3D">shift toward a more hybrid world</a> that blends remote and on-site work experiences. This initially created <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/pulse/supporting-hourly-production-workers-age-covid-steve-hunt/">tension</a> between deskless workers and their desk-based colleagues who were able to work from home. As the world settles into a new hybrid approach, companies are now seeing opportunities to better engage all employees regardless of their physical location. This is leading to a greater sense of belonging among employees who work outside of corporate offices, which includes deskless workers.</p>
  <p>These shifts create pressure on companies to improve employee experiences for deskless workers. How companies respond will determine whether they become opportunities for growth or threats to survival.</p>
  <h2 id="where-we-are-going">Where We Are Going</h2>
  <p>It has been said that technology is created when we need it. This is true when it comes to <a href="https://d.dam.sap.com/a/V3xSNXZ/76345_OT_76345_enUS.pdf">deskless work solutions</a>. The following are three particularly valuable ways technology allows companies to rethink the nature of deskless work.</p>
  <p><strong>Create shared virtual workspaces where everyone has a voice.</strong> Use mobile technology to ensure deskless workers have access to the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/workzone.html">digital work platforms</a> that support hybrid work. Leverage these platforms to bring deskless and desk-based employees into a “shared workspace in the cloud.” And enable <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm/employee-experience-management.html">employee listening solutions</a> that make it easy for deskless workers to express ideas, opinions, and experiences in a constructive and actionable manner.</p>
  <p><strong>Improve talent management and development in the flow of work.</strong> Implement mobile-enabled <a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2019/01/7837a9fb-6e7d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff.html#:~:text=As%20part%20of%20SAP%20SuccessFactors,conversations%20between%20managers%20and%20employees.">coaching solutions</a> that help managers engage, develop, and support deskless workers. Leverage <a href="https://www.mobietrain.com/partners/sap-hxm-suite/">micro-learning applications</a> that allow deskless workers to integrate training and development activities into ongoing job activities.</p>
  <p><strong>Design more fulfilling jobs.</strong> This involves addressing the lower wages and difficult work schedules historically associated with many deskless jobs. Two technology solutions are highly relevant to overcoming these challenges. First, integrated data solutions enable companies to determine how changes in compensation and scheduling impact operational business metrics such as sales, customer retention, manufacturing productivity, and safety incidents. These <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2021/02/daca9325-d37d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff.html">intelligent enterprise solutions</a> make it possible to balance the costs of paying higher wages with the benefits of improved deskless worker experiences. Second, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/commissions.html">compensation management systems</a> enable the design and delivery of service and sales-based commission plans that help ensure deskless workers are appropriately rewarded for their contributions.</p>
  <p>Given how little technology investment deskless workers have received in the past, it is clear we can and should do more to support them. Paying greater attention to the needs of deskless workers will be critical to the business success of companies. The world is going through a major transition in <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/pulse/creating-new-normal-work-six-assumptions-we-should-question-hunt/">reimagining the nature of what work is</a> and how it should be performed. Rethinking deskless work, whether skilled or “unskilled,” is a critical part of this transformation.</p>
  <p>Interested in hearing more about this topic? Be sure to <a href="https://gateway.on24.com/wcc/eh/1892128/lp/3292118/aug-2021-making-the-connection-with-deskless-workers-an-expert-panel-discussion">register</a> for an upcoming interactive panel discussion exploring the topic of deskless workers on August 11. Or, download the “<a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm/insights.html?pdf-asset=8ae80846-e37d-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b&#x26;page=1">Supporting the Deskless Workforce</a>” white paper.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Steven T. Hunt, Ph.D., is part of Technology &#x26; Work within the SAP Innovation Office.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/experience-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/future-of-work</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Redefining Employee Experience: The Opportunity in ‘X’]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/opportunity-in-x-redefine-employee-experience</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/opportunity-in-x-redefine-employee-experience</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jul 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[To advance human experience management (HXM), businesses must increasingly individualize their employee experience management strategy.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/experience-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/future-of-work</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[2020 Tech Trends: Experience Management]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/videos/2020-tech-trends-experience-management</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/videos/2020-tech-trends-experience-management</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[People-centricity is in! By the end of this year, digitally trustworthy companies will generate 20 percent more online profit than those that are not, according...]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_190e484c1dc1670c83a52830eb96c92df1cb62734.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_190e484c1dc1670c83a52830eb96c92df1cb62734.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_190e484c1dc1670c83a52830eb96c92df1cb62734.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="2020 Tech Trends: Experience Management" src="./media_190e484c1dc1670c83a52830eb96c92df1cb62734.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="tech-trends-experience-management">2020 Tech Trends: Experience Management</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_190e484c1dc1670c83a52830eb96c92df1cb62734.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_190e484c1dc1670c83a52830eb96c92df1cb62734.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_190e484c1dc1670c83a52830eb96c92df1cb62734.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="2020 Tech Trends: Experience Management" src="./media_190e484c1dc1670c83a52830eb96c92df1cb62734.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ebnpt3oDbZg">2020 Tech Trends: Experience Management</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>People-centricity is in! By the end of this year, digitally trustworthy companies will generate 20 percent more online profit than those that are not, according to Garter.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>A study by SAP revealed that customer support is the most defining moment in customer experience. Daniel Newman from Futurum Research shares his insights into what it takes to succeed in 2020.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/video</category>
            <category>news-tag/experience-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/qualtrics</category>
            <category>news-tag/ux</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>