<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/industry/banking/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Power of SAP S/4HANA Cloud: Revolutionizing the Midmarket Banking Industry]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/sap-s4hana-cloud-revolutionizing-midmarket-banking-industry</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/sap-s4hana-cloud-revolutionizing-midmarket-banking-industry</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP S/4HANA Cloud helps revolutionize midmarket banking with tailored simplicity, scalability, and customer-centric innovation. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17356558432084b1ac6f3aff27227d6550342794a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17356558432084b1ac6f3aff27227d6550342794a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_17356558432084b1ac6f3aff27227d6550342794a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="The Power of SAP S/4HANA Cloud: Revolutionizing the Midmarket Banking Industry" src="./media_17356558432084b1ac6f3aff27227d6550342794a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="the-power-of-sap-s4hana-cloud-revolutionizing-the-midmarket-banking-industry">The Power of SAP S/4HANA Cloud: Revolutionizing the Midmarket Banking Industry</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>In the fast-paced world of the midmarket <a href="/topics/banking">banking</a> industry, finding the perfect technology partner is like discovering a gem amidst a sea of stones. It’s about harnessing the power of innovation, scalability, and tailored solutions to meet the ever-evolving needs of both customers and businesses.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Enter <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/grow/industry/banking.html">SAP S/4HANA Cloud</a>, a game changer for the midmarket banking industry. Let’s dive into how this solution can help banks aiming to skyrocket their growth and redefine the future of banking.</p>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14692ed3dc37fd427f9eb5a242dd341d3c1119167.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14692ed3dc37fd427f9eb5a242dd341d3c1119167.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_14692ed3dc37fd427f9eb5a242dd341d3c1119167.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Industry - Banking: Introduction" src="./media_14692ed3dc37fd427f9eb5a242dd341d3c1119167.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Q93o4YvvhjA">SAP Industry – Banking: Introduction</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="tailored-for-the-midmarket">Tailored for the Midmarket</h2>
  <p>SAP S/4HANA Cloud can address the unique challenges and aspirations of midmarket banks. With a laser focus on pre-built functionality and best practices, the solution is designed to fit seamlessly into the specific requirements of midsized financial institutions, helping to ensure a match that caters to their distinct operational demands and strategic visions.</p>
  <h2 id="unleashing-the-power-of-simplicity">Unleashing the Power of Simplicity</h2>
  <p>In the complex maze of banking operations, simplicity is the ultimate sophistication. SAP S/4HANA Cloud offers a user-friendly interface and streamlined processes that can simplify complex banking tasks, helping midmarket players to navigate with ease and efficiency. It’s about fostering a culture of simplicity that can amplify productivity and enhance the overall banking experience.</p>
  <h2 id="scalability-redefined">Scalability Redefined</h2>
  <p>For midmarket banks aiming to scale their operations and expand their market presence, SAP S/4HANA Cloud can serve as the ultimate growth catalyst. With its robust scalability features, the solution can empower banks to seamlessly adapt to evolving market dynamics, embrace new opportunities, and catapult their business to new heights without the fear of outgrowing their technological backbone.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="digital-transformation-is-paving-the-way-for-innovation-in-banking">Digital transformation is paving the way for innovation in banking</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/banking.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="customer-centric-innovation">Customer-Centric Innovation</h2>
  <p>In an era where the customer experience reigns supreme, SAP S/4HANA Cloud helps place the customer at the heart of every banking endeavor. From personalized banking services to real-time insights that can drive meaningful engagements, the solution can enable midmarket banks to create unforgettable customer journeys that can foster long-term relationships and trust, helping to set them apart in a competitive landscape.</p>
  <h2 id="security-fortified">Security Fortified</h2>
  <p>In the age of digital threats and cyber vulnerabilities, the security of financial data is non-negotiable. SAP S/4HANA Cloud comes fortified with robust security features that can safeguard sensitive information, helping ensure data integrity and compliance with regulatory standards. It’s like having an impenetrable fortress protecting the valuable assets and trust of both the bank and its customers.</p>
  <h2 id="embracing-future-ready-technology">Embracing Future-Ready Technology</h2>
  <p>SAP S/4HANA Cloud is not just about meeting the current industry standards; it’s about setting the stage for future innovation and technological advancements. With a forward-thinking approach and integration of cutting-edge technologies like generative artificial intelligence (AI) and data analytics, the solution can empower midmarket banks to stay ahead of the curve and help pave the way for a future-ready banking landscape.</p>
  <p>In conclusion, SAP S/4HANA Cloud stands out as a quintessential choice for the midmarket banking industry, offering a blend of customization, simplicity, scalability, customer-centric innovation, robust security, and future-ready technology. By embracing the power of SAP S/4HANA Cloud, midmarket banks can embark on a transformative journey that can propel their growth, amplify their customer relationships, and set them on a trajectory of unprecedented success in the dynamic world of modern banking.</p>
  <p>To learn more, please visit <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/grow/industry/banking.html">GROW with SAP page for Banking</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Falk Rieker is global head of IBU Banking at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/financial-management</category>
            <category>news-topic/sme</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/banking</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Banking on Mobility: Degroof Petercam’s App for People and the Planet]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/banking-on-mobility-degroof-petercam</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/banking-on-mobility-degroof-petercam</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Bank Degroof Petercam and Flexso Digital focused on employee commutes and transportation for employee satisfaction and retention. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f9bd40a3ab2e823fb03db6d1aaf596a8bd14239b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f9bd40a3ab2e823fb03db6d1aaf596a8bd14239b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1f9bd40a3ab2e823fb03db6d1aaf596a8bd14239b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Banking on Mobility: Degroof Petercam’s App for People and the Planet" src="./media_1f9bd40a3ab2e823fb03db6d1aaf596a8bd14239b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="banking-on-mobility-degroof-petercams-app-for-people-and-the-planet">Banking on Mobility: Degroof Petercam’s App for People and the Planet</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>More than ever, organizations worldwide are seeking to improve employee commutes and transportation with flexible and sustainable options – not only to bring employees back to the office, but to boost employee satisfaction and retention and gain a competitive edge in recruiting new talent.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The HR team at <a href="https://www.degroofpetercam.com/en-be">Bank Degroof Petercam</a> gladly accepted that challenge and raised it, aiming not only to alleviate commuting-associated stress but also to streamline HR processes while incentivizing sustainable transportation alternatives.</p>
  <h2 id="overhauling-employee-transportation-benefits">Overhauling Employee Transportation Benefits</h2>
  <p>With offices in major cities across Belgium and over a thousand employees grappling with a daily commute, Degroof Petercam realized that the bank’s employee transportation benefits needed a significant overhaul. Employees had to choose one mobility plan from limited options and commit to it for four years. The application process was also cumbersome, miring employees and HR staff in time-consuming, manual tasks.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="better-together-customer-conversations-with-bank-degroof-petercam">Better Together: Customer Conversations with Bank Degroof Petercam</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2023/09/b207b37f-8a7e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Watch the video</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Degroof Petercam needed an intuitive, flexible application to maximize employee benefits and meet their commuting preferences while encouraging sustainable commuting and minimizing administrative headaches. The bank reached out to Flexso, whose deep HR business expertise and extensive experience with <a href="/topics/business-technology-platform">SAP Business Technology Platform</a> (SAP BTP) made it the perfect partner.</p>
  <p>Guy Spitaels, head of HR Service Center, Payroll &#x26; Systems, explained: “We started from a blank page, so it was really important to have a sounding board, and Flexso challenged us in each phase of the project…They really played a critical role.” As for the development process, Bert Van Bree, solution architect at Flexso Digital, said, “I think our approach can be summarized as start with design thinking and then scale with architecture thinking” while remembering that “the application must really empower the employee.”</p>
  <h2 id="meeting-the-personal-needs-of-employees-while-helping-the-planet">Meeting the Personal Needs of Employees While Helping the Planet</h2>
  <p>Flexso’s human-centric approach, combined with the power of SAP BTP, resulted in a new mobility app perfectly tailored for the employees and the business. The user-friendly app gives employees the flexibility to spend their yearly commuting budget on an array of options – public transportation, leasing a traditional or electric bike, leasing a gas-powered, hybrid, or electric car, or any combination of the above.</p>
  <p>For example, an employee might choose to drive on days when they are dropping a child off at school or heading straight to the gym after work and then take public transportation at other times. The app allows users to simulate infinite combinations of different transportation scenarios to create their ideal commute. Degroof Petercam employees value “the transparency and the flexibility of our tool,” Kira Zouboff, HR business analyst, said, and the simulations allow them to “play in the tool. They discover all of its features while they are making their own choices, meeting their personal needs.”</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-btp-accelerate-innovation-to-unlock-your-business-potential">SAP BTP: Accelerate innovation to unlock your business potential</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>To reduce the bank’s overall carbon footprint, the new app awards employees a “green bonus” when they choose more sustainable options, a benefit that has increased Degroof Petercam employees’ sustainable commutes by 50%. “We can incentivize the reduction of our carbon footprint while offering a very flexible solution, and the fact that the tool is consolidating all of the data helps us report on long-term sustainability solutions in line with all of the initiatives that are led by our group sustainability manager,” Zouboff explained.</p>
  <h2 id="efficiency-improvements-for-hr">Efficiency Improvements for HR</h2>
  <p>As for the HR team, the new mobility app automatically assigns each employee’s transportation budget and provides a real-time view of employee choices and requests through the user-friendly administrative platform. After the app’s rollout, Degroof Petercam saw a 75% improvement in efficiency around the administration of mobility benefits.</p>
  <p>The mobility app is also a powerful recruitment tool for like-minded top talent. “I think our large and flexible mobility offer is absolutely an asset in the war for talent,” Spitaels said.</p>
  <h2 id="the-full-episode">The Full Episode</h2>
  <p>The guests from Degroof Petercam – <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/guy-spitaels-aa19874/">Spitaels</a>, <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/kira-zouboff/">Zouboff</a>, and <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/bertvanbree/">Van Bree</a> – joined <a href="https://www.sap.com/programs/btp-better-together-customer-series.html">Better Together: Customer Conversations on SAP Business Technology Platform</a>, to discuss the origins and implementation of the app:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><a href="https://techunknownsap.libsyn.com/bank-degroof-petercams-mobility-app-for-people-and-the-planet">Thought Leadership Podcast</a>: Spitaels, Zouboff, and Van Bree shared insights behind Degroof Petercam’s inspiring move to offer sustainable transportation alternatives as a benefit to its employees in an easy-to-use mobility app.</li>
    <li><a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2023/09/b207b37f-8a7e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Practitioners’ Video</a>: Spitaels, Zouboff, and Van Bree continued the conversation and dug deeper into how real-time integrations with mobility providers and an intuitive app interface came together to help employees better understand the impact of their transportation choices.</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="empowering-employees-by-focusing-on-their-well-being">Empowering Employees by Focusing on Their Well-Being</h2>
  <p>A recent Harvard Business Review article argues that a daily commute is an important ritual that can increase employee well-being and job satisfaction. At Degroof Petercam, current and future employees are empowered to create a daily routine that works for them – walking, biking, driving, public transporting, or carpooling to a perfect day.</p>
  <p>Interested in more stories that feature companies innovating for people, productivity, and the planet? Check out:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2020/11/5ea44341-be7d-0010-87a3-c30de2ffd8ff.html">Engaging Employees to Reduce Environmental Impact and Build a More Sustainable future at FRoSTA</a>: As one of Europe’s leading frozen food brands, FRoSTA is committed to sustainability and environmental protection. The company aims to be a digital champion in the frozen food sector by 2025. Ultimately, FRoSTA’s employees will help bring about this change, reduce the company’s environmental impact, and drive its success.</li>
    <li><a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2022/07/3c91d9a0-347e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Quickly Deploying a Renewable Business with a Unified Customer Experience at Cepsa</a>: In 2022, Cepsa presented its new strategic plan for 2030, “Positive Motion,” which projects the company’s ambition to be a leader in sustainable mobility, biofuels, and green hydrogen in Spain and Portugal and become a benchmark in the energy transition. Cepsa places customers at the heart of its business and will work with them to help them advance their decarbonization goals.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>For the full episode and the on-demand Better Together: Customer Conversations series, visit <a href="https://www.sap.com/programs/btp-better-together-customer-series.html">sap.com/btp</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Timo Elliott is vice president and global innovation advocate at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-sap-news-on-linkedin">Connect with SAP News on LinkedIn</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news">Follow us</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/banking</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Standard Chartered Gains Agility with Total Workforce Management]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/standard-chartered-total-workforce-solution</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/07/standard-chartered-total-workforce-solution</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Standard Chartered uses total workforce management with SAP SuccessFactors and SAP Fieldglass for one view of permanent and external workers.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/banking</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/external-workforce-management</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fieldglass</category>
            <category>sap-award/sap-innovation-awards</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-employee-central</category>
            <category>news-tag/total-workforce-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Take: Curbing the Bank Failure Contagion]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/the-take-bank-failures-curbing-contagion</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/the-take-bank-failures-curbing-contagion</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[What could have been done to prevent the recent bank failures in the U.S.? Get SAP's take on how technology could help.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/perspective</category>
            <category>industry/banking</category>
            <category>news-tag/the-take</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Industry Innovation: Turning Supply Chains into Hot Spots for Meaningful Change]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/industry-innovation-supply-chains-meaningful-change</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/industry-innovation-supply-chains-meaningful-change</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The Customer Solution Support & Innovation organization at SAP works with various organizations to support and encourage industry innovation.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/services-support</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/banking</category>
            <category>news-tag/covid-19</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-solution-support-innovation</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>industry/life-sciences</category>
            <category>news-tag/research-development</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-advanced-track-and-trace-for-pharmaceuticals</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-information-collaboration-hub-for-life-sciences</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Collaborative Mindset Makes Rabobank a Leader Among Financial Institutions]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/rabobank-collaborative-mindset-financial-institutions</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/rabobank-collaborative-mindset-financial-institutions</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Read how SAP is enabling Rabobank in its mission to help drive sustainable development and a better future for people and the planet.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/banking</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-extreme-series</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Take: Up Next? A Fed Central Bank Digital Currency]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/the-take-next-cbdcs-central-bank-digital-currency</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/07/the-take-next-cbdcs-central-bank-digital-currency</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Over 60 central banks are exploring the possibility of launching CBDCs, central bank digital currencies. Learn how SAP can support these.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>content-type/perspective</category>
            <category>industry/banking</category>
            <category>news-tag/cryptocurrency</category>
            <category>news-tag/the-take</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Join Us at the SAP and SAP Fioneer Financial Services Forum]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/06/join-us-sap-and-sap-fioneer-financial-services-forum</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/06/join-us-sap-and-sap-fioneer-financial-services-forum</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The SAP and SAP Fioneer Financial Services Forum brings together the best minds in the finance, banking, and insurance worlds. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/banking</category>
            <category>news-tag/financial-services</category>
            <category>industry/insurance</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fioneer</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Banking On a People-Centric Digital Transformation for Continued Success]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/banco-atlantida-people-centric-digital-transformation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/banco-atlantida-people-centric-digital-transformation</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[During COVID-19, Banco Atlántida digitally transformed so customers could continue to complete their financial activities uninterrupted.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/banking</category>
            <category>news-tag/covid-19</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-employee-central</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Vast Bank Is Redefining the Banking Industry with SAP]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/04/vast-bank-redefining-banking-industry</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/04/vast-bank-redefining-banking-industry</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Vast Bank worked with SAP to create a seamless user experience alongside real-time data and analytics. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/banking</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/fintech</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Take: Central Bank Digital Currencies Are Coming]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/01/the-take-central-bank-digital-currencies-cbdcs</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/01/the-take-central-bank-digital-currencies-cbdcs</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[As central banks consider launching central bank digital currencies (CBDCs), commercial banks are preparing for disruption. Get SAP's take.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f83921766312f9737570921ffe3c182d8a447ee3.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f83921766312f9737570921ffe3c182d8a447ee3.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1f83921766312f9737570921ffe3c182d8a447ee3.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="The Take: Central Bank Digital Currencies Are Coming" src="./media_1f83921766312f9737570921ffe3c182d8a447ee3.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="the-take-central-bank-digital-currencies-are-coming">The Take: Central Bank Digital Currencies Are Coming</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>What’s News</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>More than 60 central banks are exploring the possibility of launching central bank digital currencies (CBDCs).</p>
  <p>Among them, the U.S. Federal Reserve Board published a discussion paper on the topic 10 days ago and is inviting public comment on how a CBDC — a digital dollar — might improve the safety and effectiveness of domestic payments.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="reach-more-customers-and-achieve-new-levels-of-trust-with-sap-software">Reach more customers and achieve new levels of trust with SAP software</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/banking.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="saps-take">SAP’s Take</h2>
  <p>As the Fed noted in its invitation for comments, a CBDC could provide a safe, digital payment option for households and businesses as the payments system continues to evolve, and may result in faster payment options between countries. But there may also be downsides, including how to ensure a CBDC would preserve monetary and financial stability as well as complement existing means of payment. Other key policy considerations include how to preserve the privacy of citizens and maintain the ability to combat illicit finance. The Fed’s paper discusses these and other factors in more detail.</p>
  <p>Torsten Hoffmann, chief technology innovation officer for SAP Banking and an expert on CBDCs, cryptocurrencies and other banking issues, notes that CBDCs are quickly gaining traction across the traditional finance landscape.</p>
  <p>Currently, he says, China is actively working on its plan to connect its central bank digital currency to Hong Kong’s Fast Payment system, and Israel is accelerating its study and preparations for the possibility of a digital shekel.</p>
  <p>Indeed Hoffmann believes that the adoption of CBDCs by central banks “has the potential to completely alter the banking landscape,” and that it could result in profound changes not only to the commercial banking system, but also to tax and benefits systems.</p>
  <p>If the central bank becomes of a full-service bank, he says it could be the first step to a central bank digital wallet. Then central banks could provide money directly to people during a crisis — like COVID-19 — and impose limits on what the funds could be used for and dictate how long the funds would be available.</p>
  <p>Similarly, CBDCs could enable central banks to enter the lending business help implement government policy. For example, central banks could help implement a sustainability agenda by only lending to environmentally friendly businesses.</p>
  <p>Hoffmann says the full impact of the introduction of CBDCs will depend on the details. But in the meantime, he notes, bankers appear convinced CBDCs are coming. A recent study from banking security specialist OneSpan found that 84% of banking leaders plan to take steps to prepare for CBDCs over the coming year.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Contact:</strong><br>Joellen Perry, Head of <a href="/press-room">Global Public Relations</a>, SAP<br>+1 (626) 265-0370, <a href="mailto:joellen.perry@sap.com">joellen.perry@sap.com</a>, PST</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/perspective</category>
            <category>industry/banking</category>
            <category>news-tag/financial-services</category>
            <category>news-tag/the-take</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Banking on the Future with FinTech AI]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/01/banking-on-the-future-with-fintech-ai</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/01/banking-on-the-future-with-fintech-ai</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Belarusky Narodny Bank’s (BNB-Bank) chatbot developed with SAP Conversational AI provides a smooth, automated customer experience.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>industry/banking</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/financial-services</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[As Programmable Money Emerges, Central Banks Ramp Up for Tokenized Economy]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/05/programmable-money-tokenized-economy</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/05/programmable-money-tokenized-economy</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[As programmable money gains momentum, central banks are exploring ways to digitally mirror cash in an increasingly tokenized economy.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f83921766312f9737570921ffe3c182d8a447ee3.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f83921766312f9737570921ffe3c182d8a447ee3.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1f83921766312f9737570921ffe3c182d8a447ee3.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="As Programmable Money Emerges, Central Banks Ramp Up for Tokenized Economy" src="./media_1f83921766312f9737570921ffe3c182d8a447ee3.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="as-programmable-money-emerges-central-banks-ramp-up-for-tokenized-economy">As Programmable Money Emerges, Central Banks Ramp Up for Tokenized Economy</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Programmable currency is slowly but surely gaining momentum as countries, social media platforms, and now central banks explore ways to digitally mirror cash money in an increasingly tokenized economy.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Although we’re far from any kind of standardized digital coin of the global realm, public and private sector organizations are examining the major challenges and closing in on potential opportunities, particularly for B2B transactions across complex supply chains. The appeal to governments and business is strong.</p>
  <p>“There’s a global movement among governments, social media platforms, and central banks to develop digital currencies,” said Peter-Antonius Bramm, global head of Central Banks at SAP. “Private companies see this as a race, whereas central banks and public sector agencies approach this more collaboratively. Each participant has unique objectives, factoring in geopolitical issues, customer monetization objectives, and industry-specific exigencies.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="streamline-reconciliation-and-consolidation-processes-and-enable-compliant-reporting-with-sap-software">Streamline reconciliation and consolidation processes and enable compliant reporting with SAP software</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp-financial-management/accounting-financial-close.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="programmable-money-promises-a-frictionless-payment-future">Programmable Money Promises a Frictionless Payment Future</h2>
  <p>In one scenario, central banks can program digital currency with logic so it can be spent only for a designated purpose. For large companies at the helm of complex supply chains, programmable currency promises the instantaneous delivery of payment upon product receipt. This has tremendous potential for greater business efficiencies, including dramatic reductions in <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp-financial-management/accounting-financial-close.html">reconciliation</a> time frames.</p>
  <p>“Programmable money relies on the Internet, making it much easier and accessible to use across previously siloed systems,” said Bramm. “Instead of navigating fragmented organizational and payment provider sites, digital currency would allow frictionless payments at the precise moment goods were received through machine-to-machine payment.”</p>
  <h2 id="machine-to-machine-payments-revolutionize-business">Machine-to-Machine Payments Revolutionize Business</h2>
  <p>Naturally, programmable currency will also transform financial applications software including <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp-financial-management/accounts-receivable-billing.html">accounts payable and receivable</a>, not to mention <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/supply-chain-management.html">supply chain management</a> and payroll. It’s not just about new efficiencies from merging information directly with processes and payment; machine-to-machine payments herald entirely new business models.</p>
  <p>“When a drone or self-driving electric vehicle delivers packages ordered online, programmable currency could not only immediately transfer payment in real time when the goods are delivered, but also send digital funds to recharge that vehicle for the next delivery,” said Alessandro Gasch, senior product specialist at SAP Innovation Center Potsdam. “The machine-to-machine economy will fundamentally change how business gets done.”</p>
  <h2 id="central-banks-look-to-the-next-digital-horizon">Central Banks Look to the Next Digital Horizon</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-customer-centric-products-to-market-faster-and-at-less-cost-with-sap">Get customer-centric products to market faster and at less cost with SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/supply-chain-management.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Spurred in part by growing competitive threats from sovereign nations intent on global growth, as well as big tech platforms looking to monetize enviable user bases, central banks see programmable money as a viable option.</p>
  <p>“What if you could sell a Eurobond outside the EU jurisdiction and receive Euros in digital currency, which represents real central bank money, constituting a claim against the central bank in the same way as cash?” asked Bramm. “This is one way to simplify correspondent banking and provide the seller with a ‘risk free’ position in central bank money.”</p>
  <h2 id="greater-liquidity-for-company-operations">Greater Liquidity for Company Operations</h2>
  <p>Programmable digital currency could forever alter the role of central banks, providing funds for large companies involved in B2B transactions. Instead of opening a line of credit, companies could use an infusion of digital currency from central banks to increase liquidity, freeing up more working capital to optimize operations.</p>
  <p>“If an organization held the money like cash — even if it’s digital, but it’s millions — they could directly lend funds to supply chain suppliers based on pending and expected orders,” said Bramm. “For trusted suppliers, this would keep business moving, especially in times of uncertainty like the post-pandemic world.”</p>
  <p>Reserve auctions are another potential use case for programmable currency. Rather than bringing a certified bank check to an auction for a big ticket item like a piece of property, a company or individual could use programmable money – from any number of separate accounts – that’s earmarked for the sale and only released from each account via a smart contract when the bidder wins the sale. Once complete, the transaction would automatically be recorded on a blockchain-based distributed ledger connected with the government land registry.</p>
  <h2 id="trusted-digital-payments">Trusted Digital Payments</h2>
  <p>Programmable money is very much so a work in progress. One major ongoing challenge, especially with cross-border payments, is the prevention of money laundering, fraud, and terrorist financing. Central bank digital currency (CBDC) can be programmed with anti-money laundering logic to reduce and mitigate fraud.</p>
  <p>“Whether the digital currency is private or CBDC, it has to have the same price stability and level of trust,” said Bramm. “Trusting an organization like a central bank also means trusting that country’s economy.”</p>
  <p>Bramm expects further decisions from central banks throughout the year. <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/michaeldelcastillo/2019/08/27/alibaba-tencent-five-others-to-recieve-first-chinese-government-cryptocurrency/?sh=2410f1811a51">China</a> appears to be among the front-runners, likely followed by central banks in Asia, Europe, and Canada. Recently, the U.S. Office of the Comptroller of the Currency (OCC) gave the green light to national banks and federal savings associations to hold <a href="https://www.occ.gov/news-issuances/news-releases/2021/nr-occ-2021-2a.pdf">stablecoin reserves</a>. Significant progress will depend on evolving regulations, as well as proven technology scalability. For businesses and consumers, what won’t change is the equation between trust and money, whether it’s digitally programmed or not.</p>
  <p><em><a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2021/03/25/as-programmable-money-emerges--central-banks-ramp-up-for--tokenized-economy/?sh=5663745bc402">This story originally appeared on SAP BrandVoice on Forbes</a></em>.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/banking</category>
            <category>news-tag/financial-services</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Takes Top Spot in Internationally Recognized CeFPro Fintech Leaders 2021 Report]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/sap-tops-cefpro-fintech-leaders-2021-report</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/sap-tops-cefpro-fintech-leaders-2021-report</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP took first place in core banking/back-end systems and accounting and treasury management in the Fintech Leaders 2021 Report by CeFPro.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d251fd81e04b0a03c2d6ac045463258ddd42f5c1.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d251fd81e04b0a03c2d6ac045463258ddd42f5c1.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1d251fd81e04b0a03c2d6ac045463258ddd42f5c1.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Takes Top Spot in Internationally Recognized CeFPro Fintech Leaders 2021 Report" src="./media_1d251fd81e04b0a03c2d6ac045463258ddd42f5c1.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-takes-top-spot-in-internationally-recognized-cefpro-fintech-leaders-2021-report">SAP Takes Top Spot in Internationally Recognized CeFPro Fintech Leaders 2021 Report</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="reach-more-customers-and-achieve-new-levels-of-trust-with-sap-solutions-for-banking">Reach more customers and achieve new levels of trust with SAP solutions for banking</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/banking.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced that it took first place in both core banking/back-end systems and accounting and treasury management in the Fintech Leaders 2021 Report by the Center for Financial Professionals (CeFPro), an international research organization. CeFPro also named <a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/banking.html?infl=078fcbaf-dfa2-48c5-b524-b0872eeab725">SAP</a> among the top 20 in the overall fintech ecosystem.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The rankings categorize and evaluate leading fintech companies, vendors and solution providers and are based on data gathered from surveys of practitioners, end users and subject matter experts. The report uses original research and market analysis conducted by CeFPro and backed by an advisory board of 60 international industry professionals.</p>
  <p>“SAP’s inclusion in our global Fintech Leaders 2021 Report is recognition of the great work that SAP is undertaking,” CeFPro Managing Director Andreas Simou said. “The votes cast by the industry in the survey, voting SAP best in accounting and treasury and also in core banking categories, also helped propel their overall position in the ecosystem by several places in the top 20.”</p>
  <p>CeFPro’s Fintech Leaders 2021 Report also includes research on industry trends, priorities and challenges. Key findings highlight advanced analytics and artificial intelligence as leading opportunities. These takeaways underscore the importance of making technology the backbone of fintech strategies for a state-of-the-art <a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/banking.html">intelligent suite and digital platform</a>.</p>
  <p>“We are honored to receive in back-to-back years this prestigious award in the categories of core banking, and accounting and treasury,” SAP Global Head of Banking Falk Rieker said. “It is an acknowledgement of our industry thought leadership, our industry cloud strategy and our focus on delivering new and innovative industry solutions and capabilities that make a difference to our customers.”</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="http://news.sap.com/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP on Twitter at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Media Contacts:</strong> Stacy Ries, SAP, +1 (484) 619-0411, <a href="mailto:stacy.ries@sap.com">stacy.ries@sap.com</a>, ET<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a><br>Amy Greene, CeFPro, UK +44 (0)207 164 6582,<br>US +1 (888) 677-7007, <a href="mailto:amy.greene@cefpro.com">amy.greene@cefpro.com</a>; <a href="http://www.cefpro.com">www.cefpro.com</a>, GMT</p>
  <p>Any statements contained in this document that are not historical facts are forward-looking statements as defined in the U.S. Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995. Words such as “anticipate,” “believe,” “estimate,” “expect,” “forecast,” “intend,” “may,” “plan,” “project,” “predict,” “should” and “will” and similar expressions as they relate to SAP are intended to identify such forward-looking statements. SAP undertakes no obligation to publicly update or revise any forward-looking statements. All forward-looking statements are subject to various risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results to differ materially from expectations. The factors that could affect SAP’s future financial results are discussed more fully in SAP’s filings with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (“SEC”), including SAP’s most recent Annual Report on Form 20-F filed with the SEC. Readers are cautioned not to place undue reliance on these forward-looking statements, which speak only as of their dates.<br>© 2021 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>industry/banking</category>
            <category>news-tag/financial-services</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>