<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/greenhouse-gas-emissions/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Scope 3 Emissions in the Telecommunications Industry: Driving Sustainable Transformation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/emissions-in-telecommunications-industry-sustainable-transformation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/emissions-in-telecommunications-industry-sustainable-transformation</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Addressing scope 3 emissions is vital for telecommunications companies to meet climate goals and lead the transition to a sustainable future.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_174e09b00b05a139cf976c0528b18baf650fa1d08.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_174e09b00b05a139cf976c0528b18baf650fa1d08.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_174e09b00b05a139cf976c0528b18baf650fa1d08.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Scope 3 Emissions in the Telecommunications Industry: Driving Sustainable Transformation" src="./media_174e09b00b05a139cf976c0528b18baf650fa1d08.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="scope-3-emissions-in-the-telecommunications-industry-driving-sustainable-transformation">Scope 3 Emissions in the Telecommunications Industry: Driving Sustainable Transformation</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>The telecommunications business has been revolutionary in its ability to connect individuals worldwide. However, this phenomenal growth has left the sector with a significant portion of the world’s emissions. With increasing data demand, telecommunications companies must prioritize decreasing greenhouse gas emissions throughout their value chain.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Scope 3 emissions from activities across suppliers, product lifecycles, and customer usage comprise the overwhelming majority of emissions for telecommunications companies. While progress has been made on scope 1 and 2 emissions, scope 3 emissions remain a blind spot that demands urgent action. Addressing scope 3 emissions is vital for telecommunications companies to meet climate goals and lead the transition to a sustainable digital future.</p>
  <p>According to the <a href="https://www.wri.org/insights/4-charts-explain-greenhouse-gas-emissions-countries-and-sectors">World Resources Institute</a>, the global telecommunications industry emitted 1.7 billion tons of CO2 equivalent in 2019, representing approximately 2% of total global emissions. Telecommunications companies have an outsized opportunity to drive change and reduce emissions given their scale and influence across global supply chains and billions of customers worldwide.</p>
  <p>Now is the time for telecommunications companies to step up with courageous leadership, collective action across the ecosystem, transparency, and a laser focus on reducing scope 3 emissions.</p>
  <h2 id="understanding-scope-3-emissions-in-telecommunications">Understanding Scope 3 Emissions in Telecommunications</h2>
  <p>Scope 3 emissions encompass the vast majority of emissions across the telecommunications value chain. Key sources include:</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="how-sap-helps-businesses-streamline-their-emissions-declarations">How SAP Helps Businesses Streamline Their Emissions Declarations</h3>
        <p><em><a href="/2023/05/sap-ehs-management-streamline-emissions-declarations">Read the feature</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><strong>Supply chain</strong><br>Manufacturing, transport, and disposal of network equipment makes up the largest share, such as 60% of Verizon’s total scope 3</p>
  <p><strong>Product usage</strong><br>Energy consumption of infrastructure, data centers, and devices</p>
  <p><strong>Customers</strong><br>Emissions from using products and services represent over 20% for leading telecommunications companies</p>
  <p>While methodologies vary, standards like the <a href="https://ghgprotocol.org/">Greenhouse Gas (GHG) Protocol</a> enable consistent and transparent scope 3 accounting. Robust data collection and industry alignment will enhance accuracy over time. The urgency of climate action necessitates that telecommunications companies act now to address primary scope 3 hotspots like supply chain and product usage.</p>
  <p>Success requires transparency, cooperation, and immediate commitment to tackle scope 3 emission sources.</p>
  <h2 id="challenges-in-calculating-scope-3-emissions-in-the-telecommunications-industry">Challenges in Calculating Scope 3 Emissions in the Telecommunications Industry</h2>
  <p>Calculating scope 3 emissions poses major challenges for telecommunications companies, including:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Data limitations</strong>: Telecommunications companies lack visibility into supplier and vendor emissions. Greater transparency and coordination are essential.</li>
    <li><strong>Complex value chains</strong>: Varied reporting mechanisms across the vast partner ecosystem create aggregation difficulties.</li>
    <li><strong>Methodology alignment</strong>: Companies must determine boundaries and allocate shared infrastructure emissions while adhering to accounting standards.</li>
    <li><strong>Rapid technology changes</strong>: Emerging solutions like 5G and the Internet of Things (IoT) require continuous emissions monitoring.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>Robust data collection, industry collaboration, and transparency will be vital to overcome these obstacles. Standardized methodologies guided by established protocols will enhance accuracy over time.</p>
  <p>Above all, open cooperation across telecommunications value chains is crucial to drive scope 3 progress. From suppliers to customers, aligning stakeholders to prioritize emissions reductions will accelerate the sustainability shift, despite near-term uncertainty. Telecommunications companies have the scale and influence to lead the way.</p>
  <h2 id="strategies-for-mitigating-scope-3-emissions">Strategies for Mitigating Scope 3 Emissions</h2>
  <p>Telecommunications companies can mitigate scope 3 emissions through:</p>
  <p><strong>Supplier collaboration</strong><br>Joint research and development (R&#x26;D), audits, and incentive programs enable partners to reduce their supply chain footprint. AT&#x26;T uses a sustainability scorecard to motivate action.</p>
  <p><strong>Renewable energy</strong><br>Shifting infrastructure and operations to clean power significantly decreases emissions. BT Group and Telefónica aim for 100% renewable electricity use.</p>
  <p><strong>Eco-design</strong><br>Prioritizing recyclable and energy-efficient materials and manufacturing reduces lifecycle impacts. Vodafone’s Eco Rating drives more sustainable devices.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="achieve-transparency-and-gain-carbon-neutrality-with-sap-sustainability-data-exchange">Achieve transparency and gain carbon neutrality with SAP Sustainability Data Exchange</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/registration/request-demo.html?campaigncode=CRM-YI23-IMM-1939705&#x26;pageTitle=Climate+Action+Solutions&#x26;countryOfOrigin=en_us&#x26;refererPagePath=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.sap.com%2Fsustainability%2Fclimate-action.html&#x26;refererContentPath=%2Fcontent%2Fsapdx%2Flanguages%2Fen_us%2Fsustainability%2Fclimate-action&#x26;navTitle=Request+a+Demo">Demo it</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><strong>Customer engagement</strong><br>Awareness campaigns, energy-saving tips, and green tariffs incentivize sustainable usage. Orange’s set-top box eco-rating nudges consumers.</p>
  <p><strong>Policy and regulation</strong><br>Scope 3 requirements in markets like the EU also drive telecommunications companies to address value chain emissions through mandated reporting and carbon pricing.</p>
  <p>Additionally, telecommunications companies can further engage customers through expanded recycling and take-back programs to optimize device lifecycles. Services like leasing instead of selling phones can incentivize longevity. Features that track energy consumption also enable users to reduce their footprint.</p>
  <p>There are still challenges, but collective effort across the telecommunications ecosystem can drive progress on scope 3 emissions. Engagement and incentives can accelerate emissions reductions across value chains from suppliers to customers. With their global scale, telecommunications companies must lead the way.</p>
  <h2 id="calculating-and-reporting">Calculating and Reporting</h2>
  <p>To enable accurate and consistent scope 3 accounting, telecommunications companies should:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Adopt recognized standards like the GHG Protocol Corporate Value Chain Standard, which provides comprehensive guidance.</li>
    <li>Improve supplier data collection through surveys and supplier engagement platforms.</li>
    <li>Increase transparency by regularly disclosing scope 3 inventories and strategies in sustainability reports.</li>
    <li>Obtain third-party verification for scope 3 emissions data to ensure reliability.</li>
    <li>Collaborate with industry peers and partners to align methodologies and reporting.</li>
    <li>Continuously refine calculations by incorporating improved data sources and emission factors.</li>
    <li>Supplement inventory accounting with scenario modeling to project future emissions.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>While uncertainties remain, standardized and transparent scope 3 reporting is vital to understand emissions baselines, track progress over time, and hold companies accountable. Investors and customers are increasingly demanding credible disclosure.</p>
  <p>Telecommunications companies should lead the drive towards robust scope 3 accounting and reporting across sectors. Their commitment can catalyze broader adoption of carbon transparency.</p>
  <p>Using SAP Sustainability Data Exchange, telecommunications companies can collaborate with partners, enhance awareness and engagement of stakeholders, gain insights, mitigate risks, and seize opportunities to reduce and offset emissions.</p>
  <p>Ultimately, courageous leadership and collective diligence across telecommunications company value chains are imperative to drive progress. Telecommunications companies have the influence to spearhead robust and transparent scope 3 practices across all sectors. But, success hinges on prioritizing partnerships, integrity, and environmental stewardship above all. The moment for action has come.</p>
  <p>For more information on how SAP helps companies record, report, and act on their sustainability goals, visit <a href="https://www.sap.com/sustainability.html">www.sap.com/sustainability</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Venkata Rao is a business transformation expert at SAP.<br>Mohan Shekar is head of Industry Service at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-emissions</category>
            <category>news-tag/climate-action</category>
            <category>news-tag/greenhouse-gas-emissions</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-data-exchange</category>
            <category>industry/telecommunications</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How SAP Helps Businesses Streamline Their Emissions Declarations]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/sap-ehs-management-streamline-emissions-declarations</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/sap-ehs-management-streamline-emissions-declarations</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP EHS Management helps support teams throughout the process of aggregating, preparing, and analyzing their environmental data.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-emissions</category>
            <category>news-tag/esg</category>
            <category>news-tag/greenhouse-gas-emissions</category>
            <category>product/sap-ehs-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[What Gets Measured, Gets Managed: Record, Report, and Act to Decarbonize Using SAP Sustainability Footprint Management]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/record-report-act-sap-sustainability-footprint-management</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/05/record-report-act-sap-sustainability-footprint-management</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP enables the data visibility and insight needed to decarbonize across value chains with SAP Sustainability Footprint Management.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-accounting</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-emissions</category>
            <category>news-tag/climate-action</category>
            <category>news-tag/decarbonization</category>
            <category>news-tag/green-ledger</category>
            <category>news-tag/greenhouse-gas-emissions</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-footprint-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-sustainability-solutions</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Science Behind Net Zero]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/the-science-behind-net-zero</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/04/the-science-behind-net-zero</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[To limit global temperature rise to 1.5°C in alignment with the Paris Agreement, companies have to set science-based net-zero targets.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-emissions</category>
            <category>news-tag/climate-action</category>
            <category>news-tag/climate-change</category>
            <category>news-tag/greenhouse-gas-emissions</category>
            <category>news-tag/net-zero</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Three Steps to Profitable and Sustainable Energy Management]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/three-steps-profitable-sustainable-energy-management</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/03/three-steps-profitable-sustainable-energy-management</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Energy-intensive industries are exploring new trends for profitable, sustainable business and energy management. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-emissions</category>
            <category>news-tag/decarbonization</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-twin</category>
            <category>news-tag/greenhouse-gas-emissions</category>
            <category>industry/oil-gas-energy</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-io</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Why the Reinvention of the Oil and Gas Industry Begins with Intelligent Enterprise Content Management]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/reinvention-of-oil-and-gas-enterprise-content-management</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/reinvention-of-oil-and-gas-enterprise-content-management</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[More than 65% of oil and gas companies are increasing their investment in enterprise software solutions and cloud migrations. Find out why.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digitalization</category>
            <category>news-tag/esg</category>
            <category>news-tag/greenhouse-gas-emissions</category>
            <category>industry/oil-gas-energy</category>
            <category>news-tag/opentext</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhancing Sustainability with People and Technology: A Transformation Story from SAP]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/enhancing-sustainability-people-technology-21-million-trees</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/07/enhancing-sustainability-people-technology-21-million-trees</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[As part of it's commitment to climate protection, SAP has added the goal of planting 21 million trees by the end of 2025.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14a74ac1e4d51fe757620cf88f165b999289e4684.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14a74ac1e4d51fe757620cf88f165b999289e4684.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_14a74ac1e4d51fe757620cf88f165b999289e4684.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Enhancing Sustainability with People and Technology: A Transformation Story from SAP" src="./media_14a74ac1e4d51fe757620cf88f165b999289e4684.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="enhancing-sustainability-with-people-and-technology-a-transformation-story-from-sap">Enhancing Sustainability with People and Technology: A Transformation Story from SAP</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Climate change is one of the biggest challenges of the 21st century and settling for doing “less harm” is no longer sufficient. It is urgently time to “do more good.” As an enabler and exemplar, SAP is committed to contributing to climate protection and has added the goal of planting 21 million trees by the end of 2025 to a comprehensive portfolio of measures.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Why does this matter? Trees are an essential part of our earth and invaluable in maintaining the stability of our planet. According to the United Nations (UN), over <a href="https://www.un.org/sustainabledevelopment/biodiversity/">80% of terrestrial animals and plants live in forests</a> and approximately 1.6 billion people rely on forests for their daily subsistence. Moreover, forests absorb about <a href="https://www.iucn.org/resources/issues-briefs/forests-and-climate-change">2.6 billion tons of CO<sub>2</sub></a> each year — a third of the CO<sub>2</sub> emissions that are released due to the burning of fossil fuels.</p>
  <p>Forest restoration and protection has become an important pillar of addressing climate change through nature-based solutions. SAP’s goal to restore ecosystems and foster sustainable development by planting 21 million trees before the end of 2025 is therefore an important addition to its portfolio of climate measures and <a href="https://www.weforum.org/agenda/2021/04/carbon-offsetting-climate-crisis/">complements</a> much needed action to avoid emissions in the first place.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-accelerates-climate-protection-to-achieve-carbon-neutrality-by-2023">SAP Accelerates Climate Protection to Achieve Carbon-Neutrality by 2023</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2021/03/sap-carbon-neutrality-goal-2023">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="harnessing-the-power-of-technology">Harnessing the Power of Technology</h2>
  <p>Deforestation and disasters such as wildfires accelerate climate change. However, digital technologies can help fight it: for example, the nongovernmental organization <a href="https://discover.sap.com/mobile-innovation-lab/en-us/rainforest.html">Rainforest Connection is working with SAP and using discarded smart phones, machine learning, and an app</a> to track and stop illegal loggers.</p>
  <p>To scale impact even further, SAP is collaborating with customers and partners to co-innovate solutions that enable systemic change toward a more inclusive, <a href="https://www.ellenmacarthurfoundation.org/publications/completing-the-picture-climate-change">circular, and decarbonized economy</a>. <a href="/2020/06/climate-21-track-greenhouse-gas-emissions">Climate 21</a> was launched to build analytical and transactional capabilities into enterprise applications, which can help customers understand and minimize the greenhouse gas footprint of their products and operations along their value chains. Additional programs focusing on a circular economy and holistic steering and reporting are under way to <a href="/2021/06/sapphire-now-sustainability-management-by-sap">accelerate sustainable business transformation</a> further.</p>
  <h2 id="leading-by-example">Leading by Example</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="build-sustainability-directly-into-your-core-business-processes-with-sap">Build sustainability directly into your core business processes with SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/sustainability.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>To walk the talk, SAP is reducing its own greenhouse gas emissions as well as taking action to protect and restore forests.</p>
  <p>The journey started back in 2009, when SAP set the first goal of reducing its global greenhouse gas emissions to the year-2000 level by 2020. <a href="/2018/03/sap-integrated-report-2020-targets-met-early">This target was met at the end of 2017</a>, despite growing more than fourfold in the interim. The next milestone is in 2023, when SAP aims to become <a href="/2021/03/sap-carbon-neutrality-goal-2023">carbon neutral in its own operations</a> – two years earlier than previously envisaged.</p>
  <p>To achieve this, the company follows a three-pillar approach: <strong>avoid</strong>, <strong>reduce</strong>, <strong>compensate</strong>. The goal is to avoid emissions in the first place; for example, by using virtual telecommunication instead of business flights, a practice that has naturally expanded during the pandemic and was one major driver for SAP overachieving by 43% on its target for reducing net carbon emissions in 2020, generating 135 kilotons (kt) instead of the anticipated 238 kt.</p>
  <p>Secondly, if a share of its greenhouse gas emissions cannot yet be avoided, SAP aims to reduce it through innovations, among others in the areas of building efficiency, data center operations, carpooling, and car sharing, as well as e-mobility. For example, SAP is powering its own data centers and facilities with 100% renewable electricity and working toward 33% e-cars in its global car fleet by 2025. Green IT initiatives foster sustainable IT equipment usage and promote tools such as <a href="https://www.ecosia.org/">Ecosia</a> as default search engine. In 2020, SAP implemented additional energy and climate measures within its operations, ranging from opening a new office with energy-efficient design in Australia and implementing more efficient data center technology in Germany to introducing a bike fleet at SAP Hungary and installing photovoltaic systems in Austria.</p>
  <h2 id="million-trees-by-the-end-of-2025">21 Million Trees by the End of 2025</h2>
  <p>For emissions that cannot yet be reduced or avoided, the company thirdly invests in high-quality carbon credits. For example, SAP has been a long-term investor of the <a href="/2020/08/sap-lcf-investment-livelihoods-carbon-funds">Livelihoods Carbon Funds (LCF)</a> since 2012. In close collaboration with rural communities and partners across the world, these funds realize valuable projects that enable sustainable development and environmental benefits, such as carbon dioxide capture, improved water quality, and habitats for wildlife, as well as income opportunities for rural communities.</p>
  <p>SAP has also donated funds to restore ecosystems and improve people’s lives. In 2020, Eden Reforestation Projects planted over 1.3 million trees in Madagascar, Haiti, Indonesia, and Nepal on behalf of SAP. In 2021, SAP continued to support organizations on a mission to restore native forests. For example, SAP partnered with the <a href="/uk/2021/06/sap-partners-with-the-carbon-community-on-new-scientific-forestry-research-to-drive-climate-change-efficiency">UK charity The Carbon Community</a> on new scientific forestry research to enhance nature-based solutions to climate change and improve the efficiency of carbon removal from the atmosphere. In Australia, ReForest Now planted 20,000 trees for SAP, which will help restore critically endangered subtropical rainforest.</p>
  <p>Yet much more climate action is needed. In support of the <a href="https://www.decadeonrestoration.org/">UN Decade on Ecosystem Restoration 2021-2030</a>, SAP recently joined the <a href="https://www.1t.org/">1t.org corporate alliance</a><u>,</u> which aims to conserve, restore, and grow trees worldwide, with a pledge to plant 21 million trees by the end of 2025.</p>
  <p>As the <a href="https://www.decadeonrestoration.org/join-movement">UN correctly states</a>: “Restoration is a monumental task. Over the next 10 years, every action counts. Every single day. Every country, company, organization, and individual have a role to play.”</p>
  <p>We invite you to join us and the UN Decade for Ecosystem and help build a more sustainable tomorrow.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/carbon-neutrality</category>
            <category>news-tag/greenhouse-gas-emissions</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>