<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/joule/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Elevating the RISE with SAP Experience]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2024/06/elevating-rise-with-sap-experience</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2024/06/elevating-rise-with-sap-experience</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn more about the elevated RISE with SAP experience that is improving services and delivery for customers end-to-end.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16f71bd27ee4db299c2fe36e929f4108d8ce4d936.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16f71bd27ee4db299c2fe36e929f4108d8ce4d936.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_16f71bd27ee4db299c2fe36e929f4108d8ce4d936.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Elevating the RISE with SAP Experience" src="./media_16f71bd27ee4db299c2fe36e929f4108d8ce4d936.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="elevating-the-rise-with-sap-experience">Elevating the RISE with SAP Experience</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>According to Albert Einstein, “Life is like a bicycle. To keep your balance, you must keep moving.” He had a point! The same is true of business.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-sapphire-taking-business-to-the-next-level-in-the-era-of-ai">SAP Sapphire: Taking Business to the Next Level in the Era of AI</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/events/sapphire/news-guide.html">Read the news guide</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Successful businesses keep moving and evolving, especially in times of rapid change and macroeconomic uncertainty. And given the current volatility, business transformation is no longer optional; it’s imperative.</p>
  <p>Knowing this, we launched RISE with SAP in 2021 not as a technical IT migration approach, but as a comprehensive solution designed to drive broad business transformation. With 6,000 customers having selected RISE with SAP, we know we cannot stop moving either. And I was <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZZ1yFoALzAs">thrilled to share at SAP Sapphire this year</a> how we are taking the RISE with SAP experience to the next level and improving services and delivery for customers end-to-end.</p>
  <p>Here are some key takeaways.</p>
  <h2 id="evolving-how-we-engage-with-customers">Evolving How We Engage with Customers</h2>
  <p>Navigating the transformation of today’s complex system landscapes and business processes is like orchestrating a symphony with countless instruments and moving parts. To succeed, we need to keep refining our engagement approach to better manage the intricacies of our customers’ complex architecture at an unprecedented level of detail.</p>
  <p>To this end, we’re making a lot of changes in how we engage with customers, including strengthening the role of the enterprise architect (EA). The EA harmonizes all elements and guides the customer throughout their cloud journey.</p>
  <h2 id="enhancing-methodologies">Enhancing Methodologies</h2>
  <p>We know the biggest challenge for any cloud transformation is to make the system landscape more agile and enable innovation — quickly. We’ve been listening and have introduced solutions. For example, our <strong><a href="/2024/04/transform-confidence-rise-with-sap-methodology">RISE with SAP Methodology</a></strong> is a significant step forward in creating a consistent experience for all RISE with SAP customers, independent of their individual cloud journeys. Now, a dedicated enterprise architect guides customers through the RISE with SAP Methodology to enhance onboarding and provides transparency throughout the project with key milestone checks, q-gates, and checklists that ensure consistent quality and more predictable timelines throughout the implementation process.</p>
  <p>This new offering is included in our <strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/rise.html#migration">SAP RISE Migration and Modernization</a></strong> program, which is designed to give customers the confidence to migrate even the most complex ERP systems to the cloud. By enabling our customers to integrate and extend SAP S/4HANA with a clean core approach, we ensure our customers experience better maintainability and lower total cost of ownership.​ Because legacy ERP systems often carry technical debt and, let’s face it, code is also a liability not just an asset. The more code you have, the more you have to optimize, debug, and modernize. And this is something we all need to actively work against.</p>
  <h2 id="introducing-partner-training-and-validation">Introducing Partner Training and Validation</h2>
  <p>We are also making it easier for RISE with SAP customers to identify partners to help with complex SAP S/4HANA Cloud transformations. It is essential for our partner ecosystem to follow the RISE with SAP Methodology as well. For customers to onboard successfully, there needs to be a close alignment between SAP, the customer, and implementation partner. This is why we are training and validating partners to use the RISE with SAP Methodology and will collaborate closely with partners to provide consistency and quality.</p>
  <p>We are also introducing the <strong>RISE with SAP Validated Partner</strong> recognition, which verifies a partner’s adherence to the RISE with SAP Methodology and our q-gates, giving businesses the confidence to know that they are fully leveraging the potential of cloud-based innovations from SAP. Almost 90% of all SAP implementations are overseen by partners, so training and validating them is a key part of our strategy to ensure consistency and quality for customers.</p>
  <h2 id="building-a-seamless-end-to-end-tool-chain">Building a Seamless End-to-End Tool Chain</h2>
  <p>As a former SAP CIO, I’ve felt the challenges (and pain) of large-scale transformation. I know the pressure CIOs are under to show tangible business outcomes quickly. It’s why true business transformation requires a holistic approach, not a simple technology lift and shift.</p>
  <p>We deliver the most complete business transformation suite in the industry. With the range of capabilities on offer today — including SAP Signavio, SAP LeanIX, and SAP Cloud ALM solutions as well as SAP Business Technology Platform — we have an amazing set of tools to bring out the best in businesses. Now, we are bringing them more closely together as one end-to-end seamless tool chain to make it easier to manage the process, system, and data landscape holistically.</p>
  <p>With our recently announced <a href="/2024/06/sap-enters-agreement-to-acquire-walkme">agreement to acquire <strong>WalkMe</strong></a>, we plan to further strengthen our ability to deliver successful business transformation across applications, processes, systems, and people. ​WalkMe will help us incorporate user-centric adoption, enablement, and productivity capabilities alongside our Business Transformation Management portfolio of SAP Signavio and SAP LeanIX solutions. And WalkMe’s AI capabilities will complement our process AI with user intelligence, improving the capabilities of our <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/ai-assistant.html">generative AI copilot Joule</a> to help people get work done faster.​</p>
  <h2 id="sap-business-ai-new-frontier-for-business-transformation">SAP Business AI: New Frontier for Business Transformation</h2>
  <p>In 2024, SAP Sapphire has been an opportunity for us to showcase how we are introducing in a new era of optimized business operations, with all the IT complexity concealed behind intuitive, AI-powered user experiences.</p>
  <p>We highlighted the progress we are making embedding Joule throughout our enterprise portfolio and the enormous potential we see for AI to support both customers and partners in their RISE with SAP journey. I was thrilled to announce that starting in Q4 of 2024, customers and partners can leverage generative AI-powered assistance for their RISE with SAP clean core success plan.</p>
  <p>We are also bringing new consulting capabilities to Joule, aimed at simplifying SAP implementations for partners. The new consulting capability draws insights from SAP product documentation and the SAP community to provide consultants with vital information and is planned to be available in the second half of this year.</p>
  <h2 id="business-transformation-more-than-an-it-project">Business Transformation: More Than an IT Project</h2>
  <p>At SAP, we understand that true business transformation is more than an IT project. It requires a holistic approach and not a simple technological lift and shift. That’s why we are putting the people, methodologies, financial incentives, tools, partner practices, and SAP Business AI in place to ensure our customers not only have compelling reasons to move to the cloud, but also a compelling experience.</p>
  <p><strong>Learn more:</strong></p>
  <ul>
    <li>Watch the replay of the <strong><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZZ1yFoALzAs">Customer Keynote at SAP Sapphire</a></strong></li>
    <li>Read all the announcements in the <strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/events/sapphire/news-guide.html">SAP Sapphire News Guide</a></strong></li>
  </ul>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Thomas Saueressig is a member of the Executive Board of SAP SE leading Customer Services &#x26; Delivery.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-news-and-coverage-from-sap-sapphire-in-2024">Get the latest news and coverage from SAP Sapphire in 2024</h3>
        <p><em><a href="/topics/sap-sapphire">Read more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/blog/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/blog/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/blog/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/blog/article-read-more</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/executive-blog</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>product/sap-leanix</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-signavio</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[German National Team Relies on SAP Technology at the European Championship]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/german-national-team-dfb-sap-technology-european-championship</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/german-national-team-dfb-sap-technology-european-championship</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The coaches and analysts of the German Football Association (DFB) use SAP Sports One to analyze opponents and share tactics with players.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>topic/data-analytics</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>product/sap-sports-one</category>
            <category>industry/sports-entertainment</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[New Supply Chain and External Workforce Innovations Reduce Organizational Inefficiencies]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/supply-chain-external-workforce-innovations</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/supply-chain-external-workforce-innovations</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[At SAP Sapphire, we introduced supply chain and external workforce innovations to help reduce inefficiency and improve decision-making.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/automation</category>
            <category>news-tag/external-workforce-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fieldglass</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[End-to-End Innovation Is Key to Bringing Out Your Best]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-sapphire-innovation-key-to-bring-out-your-best</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-sapphire-innovation-key-to-bring-out-your-best</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In their keynote, Juergen Mueller and Muhammad Alam demoed and discussed the latest innovations out of SAP Sapphire in 2024.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e38256295162fd6aa4582f624a1a9f11f0f8543b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e38256295162fd6aa4582f624a1a9f11f0f8543b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1e38256295162fd6aa4582f624a1a9f11f0f8543b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="End-to-End Innovation Is Key to Bringing Out Your Best" src="./media_1e38256295162fd6aa4582f624a1a9f11f0f8543b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="end-to-end-innovation-is-key-to-bringing-out-your-best">End-to-End Innovation Is Key to Bringing Out Your Best</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>In their SAP Sapphire Orlando keynote, Executive Board Members Muhammad Alam, SAP Product Engineering, and Juergen Mueller, chief technology officer, shared how the latest SAP innovations will help businesses drive true, end-to-end digital transformation and address their toughest business challenges.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="taking-business-to-the-next-level-in-the-era-of-ai">Taking Business to the Next Level in the Era of AI</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/events/sapphire/news-guide.html">Read the news guide</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In the keynote, which featured several real-world product demos by SAP employees, Alam and Mueller touted the value of SAP’s best-of-breed solutions with an outlook of what the next 50 years of innovation by SAP may look like.</p>
  <p>Who better to inspire the keynote than Hasso Plattner, co-founder and recently retired chairman of the SAP Supervisory Board, who both Alam and Mueller invoked during the session. To spell out SAP’s legacy and vision for the future, Mueller quoted <a href="/2024/05/hasso-plattner-olaf-scholz-farewell-tributes">Plattner’s farewell message</a>: “Keep innovating, keep pushing boundaries, and keep making a difference in the lives of our customers and the world at large.”</p>
  <h2 id="keep-innovating">Keep Innovating</h2>
  <p>To kick off his first SAP Sapphire appearance as the head of SAP Product Engineering, Alam began by describing the importance of harnessing innovation to deliver an end-to-end picture across all business functions and unlock true value.</p>
  <p>Simply put, businesses exist to build and deliver products and services to customers, he explained. But the materials, assets, people, and processes that come together to achieve this task is far from simple. “The reality is that each part of the business is deeply and intricately connected to all the others,” Alam said, meaning a pain point in one area impacts the rest. That’s why SAP’s modular cloud ERP approach is so successful: “We allow our customers to drive true digital transformation as opposed to running systems integration projects disguised as digital transformation,” he added.</p>
  <p>Alam presented <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/grow.html">GROW with SAP</a> as an example of this composability and extensibility, as it can work for and scale to many sizes and types of business. And now, SAP Sales Cloud and Concur Expense are natively integrated into GROW with SAP, making the offering even more comprehensive. Sinit Foto, product manager for UX, Cloud ERP at SAP, joined Alam on stage to show how GROW with SAP and SAP Business AI can help achieve integrated processes, demoing use cases such as communicating with customers about sales quotes, creating expense reports, and supporting financial analyses. In fact, Alam announced that SAP is implementing the demoed application internally to manage sales worldwide. And Mueller emphasized: “We are committed to helping you in this transformative AI moment by creating business outcomes that were unthinkable before. That’s why we’re embedding SAP Business AI deeply in our processes and analytics.”</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <picture>
          <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ab1b55bf13f95fe3a6b47084f96d918d20d0b6d4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
          <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ab1b55bf13f95fe3a6b47084f96d918d20d0b6d4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
          <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1ab1b55bf13f95fe3a6b47084f96d918d20d0b6d4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
          <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_1ab1b55bf13f95fe3a6b47084f96d918d20d0b6d4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="683">
        </picture>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="keep-pushing">Keep Pushing</h2>
  <p>AI was woven throughout the entire keynote, with both Alam and Mueller discussing <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence.html">SAP’s strategy and product enhancements in this space</a>. AI must be high value, easy to adopt into the flow of work, and trustworthy for it to truly transform how we do business, Alam said. “Equally important is whether it’s done in a way where it keeps your data secure and private – and is executed in a responsible manner,” he added. “And that is really the core promise of SAP Business AI.”</p>
  <p>There’s no doubt that AI is a powerful technology, which is why it’s essential that businesses view it as a “responsibility” not just an “opportunity,” Alam said. Megan Fife, executive solution advisor for SAP SuccessFactors, showed how SAP executes on its responsible, reliable, and relevant business AI by demoing how SAP’s AI copilot Joule in SAP SuccessFactors HCM can help fill skills gaps and collaborate across teams, among other meaningful tasks. Key to this endeavor is <a href="/2024/06/joule-microsoft-copilot-unified-work-experience">SAP’s expanded partnership with Microsoft announced earlier in the day</a>, which Scott Guthrie, executive vice president of Cloud and AI at Microsoft, discussed with Alam on stage.</p>
  <p>Mueller echoed the importance of responsible AI, saying that the technology depends highly on data that is reliable and that allows customers to look at their business end-to-end. Here, SAP Datasphere and SAP Spend Control Tower – which was demoed by Orla Cullen, product marketing manager for Data and Analytics at SAP – can help simplify data management and view and manage spend and sustainability data holistically.</p>
  <p>This transformation is supported by <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform.html">SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP)</a>, and Mueller demonstrated the newest generative AI features in SAP Analytics Cloud, SAP Integration Suite, and SAP Build solutions. He showed how Joule can help create and summarize financial reports for controlling teams; generate integration flows between SAP and non-SAP applications; and create custom skills and content based on specific business needs. Greater insights, faster reaction times, and increased productivity are the result. Soon, Mueller added, it will even be possible to enhance and extend Joule’s knowledge by creating custom skills using SAP Build and having the copilot interact with data housed in SAP and non-SAP systems, helping businesses run even more efficiently.</p>
  <p>SAP BTP is the key to being “innovation-ready,” maintaining a clean core, and tailoring standard offerings to unique needs, Mueller explained. More than 24,000 companies running live on SAP BTP, including Blue Diamond Growers and Lufthansa Technik, can attest to this.</p>
  <p>“SAP BTP’s extensibility and enterprise automation capabilities can help businesses turn process insights into actual improvements,” Mueller said. Cecilia Huergo, product manager for SAP BTP, showed this in her demo on how identifying improvement opportunities, realizing needed changes while maintaining a clean core, and gaining an up-to-date view of your IT landscape can be enabled with the combined power of SAP Signavio solutions, SAP LeanIX,, SAP BTP, and ABAP Cloud.</p>
  <h2 id="keep-making-a-difference">Keep Making a Difference</h2>
  <p>The innovations demoed and discussed in Alam and Mueller’s keynote, in addition to <a href="/2024/06/sap-sapphire-news-business-ai-enterprise-cloud-portfolio-cutting-edge-partnerships">the many others announced at SAP Sapphire in 2024</a>, are just the latest steps forward in SAP’s journey to bringing out the best in its customers. “The future is here, and it’s defined by those who innovate first,” Mueller said. “And we are here to give you the right tools at hand, such that you can be a leader not just today, but also tomorrow.”</p>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d468a3b0b7b4a96babee63b887b0c66d1bdc61b2.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d468a3b0b7b4a96babee63b887b0c66d1bdc61b2.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1d468a3b0b7b4a96babee63b887b0c66d1bdc61b2.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Why AI Means Being In The Cloud" src="./media_1d468a3b0b7b4a96babee63b887b0c66d1bdc61b2.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://youtu.be/EnxihshouTE">Why AI Means Being In The Cloud</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Gillian Hixson is an integrated communications specialist at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-news-and-coverage-from-sap-sapphire-in-2024">Get the latest news and coverage from SAP Sapphire in 2024</h3>
        <p><em><a href="/topics/sap-sapphire">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/grow-with-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Enters into Agreement to Acquire WalkMe, Driving Business Transformation by Enhancing the Customer Experience and Enriching SAP Business AI Offerings]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-enters-agreement-to-acquire-walkme</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-enters-agreement-to-acquire-walkme</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is entering into an agreement to acquire WalkMe, a leader in digital adoption platforms. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17c02c58752a8aaaec6051673cfe2308da8b06446.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17c02c58752a8aaaec6051673cfe2308da8b06446.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_17c02c58752a8aaaec6051673cfe2308da8b06446.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Enters into Agreement to Acquire WalkMe, Driving Business Transformation by Enhancing the Customer Experience and Enriching SAP Business AI Offerings" src="./media_17c02c58752a8aaaec6051673cfe2308da8b06446.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-enters-into-agreement-to-acquire-walkme-driving-business-transformation-by-enhancing-the-customer-experience-and-enriching-sap-business-ai-offerings">SAP Enters into Agreement to Acquire WalkMe, Driving Business Transformation by Enhancing the Customer Experience and Enriching SAP Business AI Offerings</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) and WalkMe Ltd. (NASDAQ: WKME) announced today that the companies have entered into a definitive agreement under which SAP will acquire WalkMe, a leader in digital adoption platforms (DAPs).</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>WalkMe’s solutions help organizations navigate constant technology change by providing users with advanced guidance and automation features that enable them to execute workflows seamlessly across any number of applications. This results in higher adoption of the underlying application and as such drives value realization.</p>
  <p>The Executive and Supervisory Boards of SAP SE and the board of directors of WalkMe have approved the transaction for US $14.00 per share in an all-cash transaction, representing an equity value of approximately US $1.5 billion. The offer price represents a 45% premium to WalkMe’s closing share price on June 4, 2024.</p>
  <p>The envisioned combination complements SAP’s Business Transformation Management portfolio around SAP Signavio and SAP LeanIX solutions to help customers on their transformation journeys.</p>
  <p>“Applications, processes, data and people are the four key elements of a successful business transformation,” said Christian Klein, CEO and member of the Executive Board of SAP SE. “By acquiring WalkMe, we are doubling down on the support we provide our end users, helping them to quickly adopt new solutions and features to get the maximum value out of their IT investments.”</p>
  <h2 id="walkme-focus-on-analyzing-adoption-and-business-transformation">WalkMe: Focus on Analyzing Adoption and Business Transformation</h2>
  <p>“We are thrilled to join forces with SAP. This acquisition marks a significant milestone in our journey, providing us with the resources and customer base necessary to enhance our product offerings and expand our market reach,” said Dan Adika, CEO of WalkMe. “By leveraging SAP’s extensive ecosystem, we are poised to unlock substantial growth opportunities and deliver even greater value to our customers. Together, we look forward to a future filled with innovation and exceptional service.”</p>
  <p>WalkMe helps organizations boost enterprise productivity and lower risk by enabling consistent, effective and efficient use of software and the workflows it enables. Its DAP works on top of an organization’s application landscape, detects where people encounter friction and provides the tailored support and automation they need to complete the job to be done, right in the flow of work, across any application. Importantly, WalkMe will continue to fully support non-SAP applications.</p>
  <p>Soon, WalkMe will launch the WalkMe<sup>X</sup> copilot, which will use WalkMe’s contextual awareness and AI to suggest the best next step for any workflow, anywhere. WalkMe<sup>X</sup> has the capability to always be on, serving as an overlay to any application, including copilots from different vendors that companies use in their landscapes. Integrating the strength of WalkMe’s adoption capabilities with SAP’s copilot Joule will boost AI assistant and productivity gains for all SAP customers. Additionally, integrating distinctive e-learning features in the SAP Enable Now solution with WalkMe will form the center of SAP’s people-centric transformation approach going forward.</p>
  <p>The acquisition is subject to customary closing conditions, including the receipt of WalkMe shareholder approval and necessary regulatory clearances, and is expected to close in the third quarter of 2024. The impact of the transaction on SAP’s non-IFRS earnings per share for fiscal 2024 is expected to be immaterial.</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>About WalkMe</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>WalkMe (NASDAQ: WKME), headquartered in Tel Aviv, Israel, pioneered DAP innovations and solutions so companies can effectively navigate the constant change brought on by technology. With WalkMe, organizations drive enterprise productivity and reduce risk by ensuring consistent, responsible, and efficient adoption of software and the workflows it powers. Our AI-driven platform sits on top of an organization’s tech stack, identifies where people experience friction, and delivers the personalized guidance and automation needed to get the job done, right in the flow of work. Customers like IBM, Nestle, ThermoFisher Scientific, and the U.S. Dept. of Defense trust WalkMe to create the people-centric experiences required to boost the effectiveness of their workflows and maximize software ROI.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>About SAP</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As a global leader in enterprise applications and business AI, SAP (NYSE:SAP) stands at the nexus of business and technology. For over 50 years, organizations have trusted SAP to bring out their best by uniting business-critical operations spanning finance, procurement, HR, supply chain, and customer experience. For more information, visit <a href="http://www.sap.com">www.sap.com</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Note to editors:</strong><br>To preview and download broadcast-standard stock footage and press photos digitally, please visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/photos">www.sap.com/photos</a>. On this platform, you can find high resolution material for your media channels.</p>
  <p><strong>For customers interested in learning more about SAP products:</strong><br>Global Customer Center: +49 180 534-34-24<br>United States Only: 1 (800) 872-1SAP (1-800-872-1727)</p>
  <p><strong>For more information, financial community only:</strong><br>Anthony Coletta, +49 6227-7-60437, <a href="mailto:investor@sap.com">investor@sap.com</a>, CEST</p>
  <p><strong>For more information, press only:</strong><br>Joellen Perry, +1 650-445-6780, <a href="mailto:joellen.perry@sap.com">joellen.perry@sap.com</a>, PT<br>Daniel Reinhardt, +49 6227-7-40201, <a href="mailto:daniel.reinhardt@sap.com">daniel.reinhardt@sap.com</a>, CEST<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p><strong>For WalkMe Investor Relations:</strong><br>John Streppa, <a href="mailto:investors@walkme.com">investors@walkme.com</a></p>
  <p><strong>Additional Important Information and Where to Find It</strong> In connection with the proposed transaction, WalkMe will prepare a proxy statement to be delivered to its shareholders and furnished to the Securities and Exchange Commission (the “SEC”). INVESTORS AND SECURITY HOLDERS ARE STRONGLY ADVISED TO READ THE PROXY STATEMENT WHEN IT BECOMES AVAILABLE AND OTHER RELEVANT DOCUMENTS FILED OR FURNISHED TO THE SEC IN CONNECTION WITH THE PROPOSED TRANSACTION OR INCORPORATED BY REFERENCE THEREIN, BECAUSE THE PROXY STATEMENT AND SUCH OTHER RELEVANT DOCUMENTS WILL CONTAIN IMPORTANT INFORMATION ABOUT THE PROPOSED TRANSACTION AND THE PARTIES TO THE PROPOSED TRANSACTION. This press release is not a substitute for the proxy statement or any other document that may be filed or furnished by WalkMe with the SEC.</p>
  <p>The proxy statement and other related documents filed or furnished to the SEC regarding the proposed transaction may be obtained for free from the SEC’s website (<a href="http://www.sec.gov/">www.sec.gov</a>), WalkMe’s website at <a href="http://www.walkme.com">www.walkme.com</a> or by directing such request to WalkMe’s Investor Relations.</p>
  <p><strong>Forward-Looking Statements</strong><br>This press release contains “forward-looking statements” within the meaning of the “safe harbor” provisions of the Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995 and other applicable securities laws. All statements other than statements of historical fact, including statements regarding the proposed acquisition of WalkMe by SAP, the expected timing for completing the proposed transaction and the terms thereof, future financial and operating results, benefits and synergies of the transaction, future opportunities for the combined businesses and any other statements regarding events or developments that may occur in the future, may be “forward-looking statements” for purposes of federal and state securities laws. These forward-looking statements involve a number of risks and uncertainties that could significantly affect the financial or operating results of SAP, WalkMe or the combined company. Words such as “expects,” “anticipates,” “intends,” “plans,” “believes,” “estimates,” “predicts,” “seeks,” “targets,” “would,” “will,” “should,” “may” and variations of such words and similar expressions are intended to identify such forward-looking statements. Such statements are based on management’s expectations as of the date they are first made, are not guarantees of future performance and involve certain risks, uncertainties and assumptions that are difficult to predict. Neither SAP nor WalkMe can give any assurances that the expectations in such forward-looking statements will be attained and, therefore, actual outcomes and results may differ materially from what is expressed or forecasted in such forward-looking statements. For example, these forward-looking statements could be affected by factors including, without limitation, risks associated with the ability to consummate the proposed transaction, the satisfaction of the conditions to the consummation of the proposed transaction, including the receipt of certain regulatory approvals, and the timing of the closing of the proposed transaction; the occurrence of any event, change or other circumstance that could give rise to the termination of the proposed transaction; the potential that WalkMe shareholders may not approve the transaction; the ability to successfully integrate operations and employees; the ability to realize anticipated benefits and synergies of the proposed transaction as rapidly or to the extent anticipated by financial analysts or investors; the potential impact of the announcement of the proposed transaction on operating results, business generally and business relationships, including with employees, customers, suppliers and competitors; unanticipated restructuring costs may be incurred or undisclosed liabilities assumed; actual or threatened legal proceedings that have been or may be instituted against SAP or WalkMe in connection with the proposed transaction or otherwise; the ability and costs related to retaining key personnel and clients; risks related to diverting management’s attention from ongoing business operations; delays, challenges, costs, fees, expenses and charges related to the proposed transaction; actions by competitors; general adverse economic, political, social and security conditions in the regions and industries in which SAP and WalkMe operate, including relating to Israel’s ongoing war with Hamas and other terrorist organizations in the Middle East and general hostilities; exposure to inflation, currency rate and interest rate fluctuations and risks associated with doing business locally and internationally, as well as fluctuations in the market price of SAP and WalkMe’s traded securities; natural catastrophes, any pandemic, epidemic or outbreak of infectious disease, warfare, protests and riots, and terrorist attacks; and those additional risks and factors discussed in reports filed or furnished with the SEC by SAP and WalkMe, including SAP’s and WalkMe’s most recent Annual Reports on Form 20-F and in any subsequent reports on Form 6-K, each of which is on file with or furnished to the SEC and available at the SEC’s website at <a href="http://www.sec.gov/">www.sec.gov</a>. Reports filed or furnished with the SEC by SAP are also available on SAP’s website at <a href="http://www.sap.com/investors/en.html">www.sap.com/investors</a> and by WalkMe on WalkMe’s website at <a href="http://www.walkme.com">www.walkme.com</a>. Moreover, other risks and uncertainties of which SAP or WalkMe are not currently aware or may not currently consider material may also affect each of the companies’ forward-looking statements and may cause actual results and the timing of events to differ materially from those anticipated. The forward-looking statements made in this press release are made only as of the date hereof or as of the dates indicated in the forward-looking statements, even if they are subsequently made available by SAP or WalkMe on their respective websites or otherwise. Neither SAP nor WalkMe undertakes any obligation to update or supplement any forward-looking statements to reflect actual results, new information, future events, changes in its expectations or other circumstances that exist after the date as of which the forward-looking statements were made.</p>
  <p>© 2024 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE and affiliated entities in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p>Please consider our <a href="https://www.sap.com/corporate/en/legal/privacy.html">privacy policy</a>. If you receive this press release in your e-mail and you wish to unsubscribe to our mailing list please contact <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a> and write Unsubscribe in the subject line.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/investor-relations</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>product/sap-leanix</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-signavio</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP's New AI Innovations and Partnerships Deliver Real-World Results]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/ai-innovations-partnerships-sap-sapphire</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/ai-innovations-partnerships-sap-sapphire</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Explore the AI capabilities and ecosystem innovations presented at SAP Sapphire in 2024, all aimed at delivering real-world results.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>news-topic/financial-management</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/abap-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/accenture</category>
            <category>news-tag/ai-ethics</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/aws</category>
            <category>news-tag/bcg</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Generative AI Innovations Take Center Stage at SAP Sapphire in 2024]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-sapphire-generative-ai-center-stage</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-sapphire-generative-ai-center-stage</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A series of generative AI innovations and partnerships announced at SAP Sapphire showcase how SAP is taking business to the next level.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_183c39d6e19efd7774c87954a8bbf7838320ef779.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_183c39d6e19efd7774c87954a8bbf7838320ef779.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_183c39d6e19efd7774c87954a8bbf7838320ef779.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Generative AI Innovations Take Center Stage at SAP Sapphire in 2024" src="./media_183c39d6e19efd7774c87954a8bbf7838320ef779.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="generative-ai-innovations-take-center-stage-at-sap-sapphire-in-2024">Generative AI Innovations Take Center Stage at SAP Sapphire in 2024</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>SAP CEO Christian Klein kicked off SAP Sapphire this week with an upbeat keynote that highlighted the company’s latest business AI innovations, products, and partnerships, which he said will change how people work.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="taking-business-to-the-next-level-in-the-era-of-ai">Taking Business to the Next Level in the Era of AI</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/events/sapphire/news-guide.html">Read the news guide</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“This year is a very special Sapphire,” Klein said. “We are entering a new phase of AI, with endless possibilities for us all.”</p>
  <p>Klein and Chief Marketing and Solutions Officer Julia White used the keynote to outline how AI will deliver real business benefits for different corporate functions and “Bring Out Your Best,” this year’s event theme.</p>
  <h2 id="delivering-on-an-ai-promise">Delivering on an AI Promise</h2>
  <p>Klein emphasized how SAP has delivered on its promise to infuse generative AI throughout its business portfolio, has enabled customers to exploit the potential of business AI, and has positioned the Joule copilot as the new front end for SAP applications.</p>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11a9e312c5b8efe848ea7622ac6bcc8c38c9e5913.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11a9e312c5b8efe848ea7622ac6bcc8c38c9e5913.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_11a9e312c5b8efe848ea7622ac6bcc8c38c9e5913.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Sapphire Opening Keynote: Bring Out the Best in Your Business | 2024" src="./media_11a9e312c5b8efe848ea7622ac6bcc8c38c9e5913.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://youtu.be/gOVQhhm5yO0?si=wkpDopYq0gPK6kWn">SAP Sapphire Opening Keynote: Bring Out the Best in Your Business | 2024</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Together, the two also announced the next evolution and new capabilities in both RISE with SAP and GROW with SAP. Since it was launched over three years ago, more than 6,000 customers have selected RISE with SAP. During his keynote, Klein announced that RISE with SAP will now include a dedicated enterprise architect to guide customers through the RISE with SAP Methodology as well as an integrated tool chain to help manage the process, system, and data landscape holistically across the RISE with SAP life cycle.</p>
  <p>Meanwhile White, broadcasting live from the central showcase on the SAP Sapphire show floor, announced that cloud ERP offering GROW with SAP will now include SAP Sales Cloud and Concur Expense at no additional charge. Whether its managing your finances or managing your expenses, GROW with SAP has you covered, she said.</p>
  <h2 id="ai-momentum">AI Momentum</h2>
  <p>Building on SAP’s business AI momentum, Klein and White also announced a series of expanded partnerships to help companies make the most out of this decisive AI moment. The expanded partnerships include deals with Amazon Web Services (AWS) and Google Cloud. Klein also announced the integration of Microsoft 365 Copilot with Joule, delivering what he described as a “truly differentiated employee experience.”</p>
  <p>Together onstage with customers and SAP Chief AI Officer Philipp Herzig, they showcased how SAP is infusing generative AI throughout the application portfolio and enabling customers to thrive in the AI era.</p>
  <p>“The business AI innovations we’re announcing will not only change how people work with SAP solutions, but how people work overall,” said Klein ahead of his keynote address.</p>
  <h2 id="new-joule-capabilities">New Joule Capabilities</h2>
  <p>Klein announced Joule for consulting capabilities and Joule for ABAP developer capabilities, which will help SAP’s 6-million-strong consultant and developer community to accelerate projects by 30% and implement SAP solutions faster than ever before.</p>
  <p>During his keynote he described business AI as being “an inflection point” and added, “Today’s AI announcements and partnerships build on our commitment to deliver revolutionary technology that drives real-world results, helping customers unleash the agility and ingenuity they need to succeed in today’s fast-moving business landscape.”</p>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16cdfc9fd1fdbbf5cdc9cd5193401b9dfcafd1805.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16cdfc9fd1fdbbf5cdc9cd5193401b9dfcafd1805.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_16cdfc9fd1fdbbf5cdc9cd5193401b9dfcafd1805.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Why Joule Will Change the Way You Work" src="./media_16cdfc9fd1fdbbf5cdc9cd5193401b9dfcafd1805.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://youtu.be/a9j2Q6VVCfM?si=9cdzuqQ27TZ_J3uj">Why Joule Will Change the Way You Work</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“SAP is the only tech company who can infuse AI capabilities right into your business processes and workflows,” he said, saluting the achievements of the 40,000 SAP employees in the Product Development organization.</p>
  <h2 id="shout-out-to-sap-developers">Shout Out to SAP Developers</h2>
  <p>“No other tech company can offer a more powerful platform to transform enterprises to rewrite how business is run.” SAP developers have transformed SAP’s portfolio “from an ERP system that enabled transactions in real time, to a system with modular applications and embedded AI so that you can run intelligent, connected, and sustainable enterprises.”</p>
  <p>“We promised this to you, and we delivered,” Klein told audiences online and the 14,000 customers and partners attending SAP Sapphire in person this week in Orlando. “Now we are using the power of generative AI across our stack to once again revolutionize how businesses run and end users will work in the future.”</p>
  <p>After announcing generative AI copilot Joule in September 2023, Klein confirmed that it will become the new front-end and UX for SAP applications and “will turn your words into action.” Joule is ready for prime time, he declared, “and going forward, it will be embedded out of the box for all our cloud customers.”</p>
  <h2 id="joule-key-to-higher-productivity">Joule: Key to Higher Productivity</h2>
  <p>He predicted that Joule will also become the biggest productivity engine for every SAP end user, and that by the end of the year, 80% of the most used tasks will be managed via Joule and the 300 million end users of SAP products will be 20% more productive.</p>
  <p>While AI is a powerful technology facilitating huge opportunities for business and employees, the SAP CEO emphasized that it is also crucial to offer responsible AI. To that end, he announced that SAP is among the first tech companies to adhere to UNESCO’s AI principles.</p>
  <p>Klein wrapped up the keynote by emphasizing that SAP does not view AI as an end in itself, but rather as a tool to help the world run better and improve people’s lives. “You have my commitment that we will continue to listen to your needs, we will continue to deliver great innovations and we will continue to deliver great outcomes for your company.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-news-and-coverage-from-sap-sapphire-in-2024">Get the latest news and coverage from SAP Sapphire in 2024</h3>
        <p><em><a href="/topics/sap-sapphire">Read more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Joule to Integrate with Microsoft Copilot for a Unified Work Experience]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/joule-microsoft-copilot-unified-work-experience</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/joule-microsoft-copilot-unified-work-experience</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is bringing its generative AI copilot Joule together with Microsoft Copilot for Microsoft 365 for deep bi-directional integration.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>news-tag/microsoft</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Expands Business AI Portfolio with Meta Open-Source Models]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-business-ai-meta-open-source-models</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-business-ai-meta-open-source-models</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is integrating Meta Llama 2 and Meta Llama 3 models into generative AI hub to enable customers to create dashboards based on rich content.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP and Accenture Collaborate on Getting to Value Faster with SAP Business AI]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/accenture-sap-sapphire-business-ai</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/accenture-sap-sapphire-business-ai</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP and Accenture are working together to help their customers make SAP Business AI and data their No. 1 competitive advantage.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/accenture</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>product/sap-leanix</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-signavio</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Infuses Business AI Throughout Its Enterprise Cloud Portfolio and Partners with Cutting-Edge AI Leaders to Bring Out Customers’ Best]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-sapphire-news-business-ai-enterprise-cloud-portfolio-cutting-edge-partnerships</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/sap-sapphire-news-business-ai-enterprise-cloud-portfolio-cutting-edge-partnerships</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New SAP Business AI innovations and collaborations with partners are igniting ingenuity. Read the news from SAP Sapphire Orlando in 2024.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18ff27978e1178b1dce994986e74f4cc1f6087f26.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18ff27978e1178b1dce994986e74f4cc1f6087f26.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_18ff27978e1178b1dce994986e74f4cc1f6087f26.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Infuses Business AI Throughout Its Enterprise Cloud Portfolio and Partners with Cutting-Edge AI Leaders to Bring Out Customers’ Best" src="./media_18ff27978e1178b1dce994986e74f4cc1f6087f26.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-infuses-business-ai-throughout-its-enterprise-cloud-portfolio-and-partners-with-cutting-edge-ai-leaders-to-bring-out-customers-best">SAP Infuses Business AI Throughout Its Enterprise Cloud Portfolio and Partners with Cutting-Edge AI Leaders to Bring Out Customers’ Best</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>SAP Business AI Innovations and Collaborations with Partners including Google Cloud, Meta, Microsoft, Mistral AI and NVIDIA Ignite Ingenuity</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <table>
          <thead>
            <tr>
              <th>Text Large</th>
            </tr>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td><strong><em>ORLANDO</em></strong> — At its annual SAP Sapphire conference, SAP unveiled generative AI innovations and partnerships that showcase how the company is taking business to the next level in the era of AI.</td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="taking-business-to-the-next-level-in-the-era-of-ai">Taking Business to the Next Level in the Era of AI</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/events/sapphire/news-guide.html">Read the news guide</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>By infusing Business AI across an enterprise cloud portfolio that powers the world’s most mission-critical processes and partnering with companies pushing the edge of what’s possible with AI, SAP is igniting a new wave of insight and ingenuity in global business.</p>
  <p>“The Business AI innovations we’re announcing at SAP Sapphire in 2024 will redefine the way businesses run,” says Christian Klein, CEO and member of the Executive Board of SAP SE. “Today’s AI announcements and partnerships build on our commitment to deliver revolutionary technology that drives real-world results, helping customers unleash the agility and ingenuity they need to succeed in today’s fast-moving business landscape.”</p>
  <h2 id="ai-that-means-business">AI That Means Business</h2>
  <p>As SAP embeds Business AI across its enterprise solutions, it puts rich insights at users’ fingertips, empowering them to deliver better outcomes and elevate the creative problem-solving humans do best. Examples include AI-generated reports in SAP SuccessFactors solutions that give people managers responsibly sourced insights for compensation-related discussions as well as forecasting capabilities in SAP Sales Cloud solutions that predict combinations of salespeople and products most likely to drive sales. Meanwhile, the SAP Business Technology Platform is adding large language models from Amazon Web Services, Meta and Mistral AI to its generative AI hub. This capability in the SAP AI Core infrastructure makes it easier to build generative AI use cases for SAP applications.</p>
  <p>SAP’s generative AI copilot Joule, which quickly sorts and contextualizes data from multiple systems to advance automation and improve decision-making, is expanding throughout the company’s solution portfolio. Joule launched in <a href="/2023/09/joule-new-generative-ai-assistant">SAP SuccessFactors solutions last fall</a> and is now embedded into SAP S/4HANA Cloud solutions and others including SAP Build and SAP Integration Suite. Further expansion by year-end will include SAP Ariba and SAP Analytics Cloud solutions. At Sapphire, SAP also announced <a href="/">plans to further broaden Joule’s scope</a> by integrating it with Microsoft Copilot to surface even richer insights. This deep, bi-directional integration gives users a unified experience built right into the flow of work, enabling seamless access to information from interactions with business applications in SAP and Microsoft 365.</p>
  <p>Reflecting Business AI’s increasing importance, SAP is redoubling its commitment to the principles of relevant, reliable, and responsible AI it pioneered. At Sapphire, SAP is adopting the 10 guiding principles of the UNESCO Recommendation on the Ethics of Artificial Intelligence, which aim to ensure that AI technologies are developed and used in ways that respect human rights, promote fairness and contribute to sustainable development.</p>
  <h2 id="partnerships-that-scale-innovation">Partnerships That Scale Innovation</h2>
  <p>SAP is partnering with best-in-class technology leaders to push the limits of what generative AI can do at an enterprise level. In addition to our expanded collaborations with <a href="/2024/05/aws-sap-generative-ai-new-innovation">AWS</a> and Microsoft, partnerships with Google Cloud, Meta, Mistral AI and NVIDIA ensure SAP can harness the power of AI-ready technology to innovate at speed and deliver richer real-world results.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Google Cloud</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP and Google Cloud are expanding their partnership, using Business AI to help enterprises better predict and mitigate supply-chain risks to minimize disruptions and maintain optimal inventory levels. The companies will integrate Joule and the SAP Integrated Business Planning for Supply Chain solution with Google Cloud’s Gemini models AI assistant and Google Cloud Cortex Framework’s data foundation.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Meta</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP will leverage Meta Llama 3 to generate scripts that render highly customized analytics applications in SAP Analytics Cloud. Meta’s next-generation AI model excels at language nuances and contextual understanding, making it an ideal candidate for translating enterprise business requirements into tangible outcomes.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Mistral AI</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP will also add <a href="/">new large language models from Mistral AI</a>, a global company headquartered in Paris specializing in generative AI, to the generative AI hub capability in SAP AI Core.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>NVIDIA</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP and NVIDIA Corporation advance a <a href="https://blogs.nvidia.com/blog/sap-sapphire-ai-omniverse/">cross-product partnership</a> to embed cutting-edge technologies into enterprise-ready business applications:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>As SAP trains Joule to serve as an AI assistant for the RISE with SAP solution implementations, NVIDIA’s state-of-the-art AI models sift through SAP consulting assets to provide relevant and precise answers to implementation-related questions;</li>
    <li>As SAP embeds Joule in the ABAP Cloud model to generate ABAP code for SAP developers, NVIDIA’s accelerated infrastructure will run, scale, and manage SAP’s generative AI model for ABAP code generation;</li>
    <li>As SAP infuses generative AI into the SAP Intelligent Product Recommendation solution, NVIDIA Omniverse Cloud APIs enable the simulation of complex manufacturing products and configurations as industrial digital twins.</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="cloud-technology-that-drives-agility-and-sustainability">Cloud Technology That Drives Agility and Sustainability</h2>
  <p>Business success in the era of AI means being in the cloud. SAP is making the move easier than ever with initiatives that help customers find partners with the expertise needed for complex SAP S/4HANA Cloud transformations. Further cloud innovations at SAP Sapphire include features that help the world’s organizations measure, manage and execute their sustainability strategies. SAP Sustainability Control Tower and SAP Sustainability Footprint Management solutions now track carbon footprints at scale and help businesses meet regulatory standards.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><a href="https://www.sap.com/events/sapphire/news-guide.html">Learn more in the 2024 SAP Sapphire News Guide</a>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Visit the <a href="/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-news-and-coverage-from-sap-sapphire-in-2024">Get the latest news and coverage from SAP Sapphire in 2024</h3>
        <p><em><a href="/topics/sap-sapphire">Read more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>About SAP</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As a global leader in enterprise applications and business AI, SAP (NYSE:SAP) stands at the nexus of business and technology. For over 50 years, organizations have trusted SAP to bring out their best by uniting business-critical operations spanning finance, procurement, HR, supply chain, and customer experience. For more information, visit <a href="http://www.sap.com">www.sap.com</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Note to editors:</strong><br>To preview and download broadcast-standard stock footage and press photos digitally, please visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/photos">www.sap.com/photos</a>. On this platform, you can find high resolution material for your media channels.</p>
  <p><strong>For customers interested in learning more about SAP products:</strong><br>Global Customer Center: +49 180 534-34-24<br>United States Only: 1 (800) 872-1SAP (1-800-872-1727)</p>
  <p><strong>For more information, press only:</strong><br>Joellen Perry, +1 (650) 445-6780, <a href="mailto:joellen.perry@sap.com">joellen.perry@sap.com</a> PT<br>Marcus Winkler, +49 6227-767497, <a href="mailto:marcus.winkler@sap.com">marcus.winkler@sap.com</a> CET<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>This document contains forward-looking statements, which are predictions, projections, or other statements about future events. These statements are based on current expectations, forecasts, and assumptions that are subject to risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results and outcomes to materially differ. Additional information regarding these risks and uncertainties may be found in our filings with the Securities and Exchange Commission, including but not limited to the risk factors section of SAP’s 2023 Annual Report on Form 20-F.<br>© 2024 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.<br>Please consider our <a href="https://www.sap.com/corporate/en/legal/privacy.html">privacy policy</a>. If you receive this press release in your e-mail and you wish to unsubscribe to our mailing list please contact <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a> and write Unsubscribe in the subject line.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/abap-cloud</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-sales-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-footprint-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[NEC Leverages RISE with SAP and AI to Build Business AI in Move to the Cloud]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/nec-move-to-cloud-rise-with-sap-business-ai</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/nec-move-to-cloud-rise-with-sap-business-ai</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[NEC is migrating to SAP S/4HANA Cloud and adopting a clean-core approach to create a sustainable society through digital transformation.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/aws</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How SAP BTP Becomes the Trusted Platform for Business AI]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/sap-btp-strategy-paper-trusted-platform-business-ai</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/sap-btp-strategy-paper-trusted-platform-business-ai</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP BTP will further evolve to become the trusted business AI platform for SAP-centric landscapes. Learn more in the SAP BTP strategy paper.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-build</category>
            <category>product/sap-integration-suite</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP SuccessFactors Takes Home 12 Top Rated Awards from TrustRadius]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/sap-successfactors-12-top-rated-awards-from-trustradius</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/sap-successfactors-12-top-rated-awards-from-trustradius</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[TrustRadius has recognized SAP SuccessFactors with 12 Top Rated awards in 2024. Read to learn more about the recognition.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a157e78734853652179498700d8b366ba88f70cd.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a157e78734853652179498700d8b366ba88f70cd.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1a157e78734853652179498700d8b366ba88f70cd.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP SuccessFactors Takes Home 12 Top Rated Awards from TrustRadius" src="./media_1a157e78734853652179498700d8b366ba88f70cd.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-successfactors-takes-home-12-top-rated-awards-from-trustradius">SAP SuccessFactors Takes Home 12 Top Rated Awards from TrustRadius</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>SAP SuccessFactors has once again been recognized as a leader in human resources software by <a href="https://auth.trustradius.com/login?state=hKFo2SAxeFdmN3FRNFYweERQdWtYOUNrZlBpbXFSZE9QbXZRWqFupWxvZ2luo3RpZNkgVk5pZ3luZ0ZsZ1hGZVFvQjFzRVUwakNMZzlvOXRHTGmjY2lk2SAxQm41NHNobVlWMmpFbE5qZ1NZb2dKNHZWeHZBT3hhSw&#x26;client=1Bn54shmYV2jElNjgSYogJ4vVxvAOxaK&#x26;protocol=oauth2&#x26;prompt=login&#x26;scope=openid%20profile%20email&#x26;response_type=code&#x26;redirect_uri=https%3A%2F%2Ftrustradius.com%2Fapi%2Fauth%2Fcallback&#x26;login_hint=&#x26;customParams=%7B%22visitorId%22%3A%22662c047f7334ebca8f8661aa%22%2C%22visitId%22%3A%2266311414bf33ad1060cf30ff%22%2C%22returnTo%22%3A%22%2Freviews%2Fnew%22%7D&#x26;allow_signup=true&#x26;nonce=hYwbKE36k0mTMvPhuGwjobXr7VnrKjlPTnVy0Kbn5sQ&#x26;code_challenge_method=S256&#x26;code_challenge=0aAJd5l2mbjUn1d0SW7Qvrv5DkDvBp6W-0szabD3FVQ">TrustRadius</a>, earning 12 Top Rated awards in 2024. TrustRadius is a peer research and review platform designed to help business leaders find and select the right software to meet their needs.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“At TrustRadius, we pride ourselves on providing unbiased and transparent insights into the software industry,” said Allyson Havener, senior vice president of Marketing and Community at TrustRadius. “Receiving a TrustRadius Top Rated award is a testament to SAP SuccessFactors HCM’s exceptional performance as validated by unbiased user feedback. This recognition highlights SAP SuccessFactors’ commitment to delivering innovative human capital management solutions that truly meet the needs of businesses.”</p>
  <p>This year, <a href="/topics/human-resources">SAP SuccessFactors</a> earned awards across the following categories: Applicant Tracking, Compensation Management, Talent Management, Workforce Analytics, Sales Incentive Compensation Management, HR Management, Workforce Management, Employee Performance Management, Sales Performance Management, Corporate Learning Management, Succession Planning, and Internal Payroll.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="adopt-the-latest-in-hr-innovation-with-sap-successfactors-hcm">Adopt the latest in HR innovation with SAP SuccessFactors HCM</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>We are grateful to our more than 10,000 global customers whose partnership allows us to help make every employee a success story by harnessing the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/human-resources.html">power of AI</a> to elevate every experience, guide every people decision, and connect HR across every aspect of the business.</p>
  <p>In the past year, SAP has introduced new AI capabilities that span the entire SAP SuccessFactors HCM suite and help transform how organizations unlock individual and collective potential. <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/ai-joule-product-tour.html">Joule</a>, SAP’s natural language generative AI copilot, helps employees and managers work faster and smarter by making it easier to find information and complete common HR tasks. With an embedded AI-driven skills framework, SAP SuccessFactors solutions help power an organization’s learning and talent strategy and address critical skills gaps. The combined force of these innovations helps customers better meet the business challenges of today and tomorrow.</p>
  <p>Below are a few reviews from our customers:</p>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div>We chose SAP SuccessFactors over competitors for its comprehensive HR suite, superior integration capabilities with SAP systems, and global scalability. Its user-friendly interface and extensive analytics stood out, <strong>offering more in-depth insights and a seamless experience compared to other solutions in the market</strong>.</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div><a href="https://www.trustradius.com/reviews/sap-successfactors-2023-12-15-07-43-30">Solution Architect, Barclays</a></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div>“<strong>The benefit of [SAP] SuccessFactors is its flexibility</strong>. I have implemented [SAP] SuccessFactors at companies with as little as 1,500 employees and also with as many as 120,000 users. It can handle the complexities of global requirements while still being able to scale to a small, midsized business in a cost-effective manner.”​</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div><a href="https://www.trustradius.com/reviews/sap-successfactors-2023-10-16-10-44-42">HRIS Manager, Great Lakes Cheese</a></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div>“SAP SuccessFactors has a clean employee view of data and offers a wide range of functionality to <strong>support midsize to large companies</strong>.”​</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div><a href="https://www.trustradius.com/reviews/sap-successfactors-2023-10-21-10-48-58">Software Engineer, John Deere</a></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Learn more about <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm.html?url_id=ctabutton-us-hcm-trustradius-freetrial">SAP SuccessFactors HCM</a> and read our customer reviews on <a href="https://www.trustradius.com/products/sap-successfactors/reviews">TrustRadius</a>. For more information about these recognitions, visit the <a href="https://www.trustradius.com/static/about-trustradius-scoring">TrustRadius scoring FAQ page</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Aaron Green is chief marketing &#x26; solutions officer for SAP SuccessFactors.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors-hcm-suite</category>
            <category>news-tag/trustradius</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP SuccessFactors First Half 2024 Release: Make Every Employee a Success Story]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-successfactors-first-half-2024-release</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-successfactors-first-half-2024-release</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[To help take HR to the next level, the SAP SuccessFactors first half 2024 release delivers more than 250 features and enhancements.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_115cc4b7786cb688433caf45dec5bf248f041afdb.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_115cc4b7786cb688433caf45dec5bf248f041afdb.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_115cc4b7786cb688433caf45dec5bf248f041afdb.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP SuccessFactors First Half 2024 Release: Make Every Employee a Success Story" src="./media_115cc4b7786cb688433caf45dec5bf248f041afdb.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-successfactors-first-half-2024-release-make-every-employee-a-success-story">SAP SuccessFactors First Half 2024 Release: Make Every Employee a Success Story</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Success can take many forms. It’s achieving AI-driven results faster and smarter. It’s unlocking more meaningful and aspirational career development experiences. It’s empowering employees and managers through simple HR-related tasks in the flow of work, freeing up more productive time across the organization.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>And for you and your business, you can tell all those success stories – and more – with the SAP SuccessFactors HCM suite and our first half 2024 release.</p>
  <p>As your organization and employees begin to embrace AI, <a href="/topics/human-resources">HR</a> has the opportunity to drive new levels of employee productivity, engagement, and growth. SAP SuccessFactors HCM can give you everything you need – the global foundation, skills framework, people-first experiences, and purpose-built AI capabilities – to help take HR to the next level. With the SAP SuccessFactors first half 2024 release, we are delivering more than 250 innovative features and enhancements.</p>
  <h2 id="sap-business-ai">SAP Business AI</h2>
  <p>In 1H 2024, we are thrilled to introduce more than 25 new AI capabilities to enable better employee experiences and new levels of productivity.</p>
  <p>Among these capabilities include the ability for applicants to provide skills during the application process. This can enable recruiters to see a skills compatibility for each applicant based on matching the applicant’s skills and the job requisition, helping improve applicant screening and time to hire. Furthermore, personalization in SAP SuccessFactors Opportunity Marketplace is enhanced with new AI-driven recommendation categories, “Ignite Your Role” and “Reach Your Aspirations.” These guided experiences can enable employees to proactively take steps to reach their development goals.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e755ea739e2394a3bec10a53f644e2d9cd718123.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e755ea739e2394a3bec10a53f644e2d9cd718123.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1e755ea739e2394a3bec10a53f644e2d9cd718123.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Screenshot of the assisted screening and skills match capabilities" src="./media_1e755ea739e2394a3bec10a53f644e2d9cd718123.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="803" height="521">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>Assisted screening and skills match available in 1H 2024 release. Click to enlarge.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Generative AI continues to be embedded across the SAP SuccessFactors HCM suite, including new capabilities to help employees create ready-made performance and development goals and AI-assisted writing to help improve the quality, clarity, and conciseness of writing across a variety of areas within SAP SuccessFactors solutions.</p>
  <p>Further, with this release, insights based on an employee’s compensation and job history are available to help support managers in having effective and well-informed compensation discussions.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="the-ai-copilot-that-truly-understands-your-business">The AI copilot that truly understands your business</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/ai-assistant.html">Meet Joule</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>We have also added more than 15 new <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/ai-assistant.html">Joule</a> capabilities in this release to help both managers and employees get work done in a conversational way, such as creating or changing a position, creating spot awards, clocking in and out, and viewing pay statements as well as time capabilities like requesting time off, checking leave balances, and syncing holidays to Outlook calendars while managers can review and approve time off. Further, employees can now clock in and out using Joule, Microsoft Teams, or the SAP SuccessFactors Mobile app.</p>
  <h2 id="sap-successfactors-employee-central">SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central</h2>
  <p>We are excited to unveil two new people profile experiences – the profile preview and the spotlight view. The profile preview can provide a snapshot of key areas of the employee profile, including job, manager, location, and contact details, to quickly view and connect with others. Additionally, the spotlight view can showcase employee skills and competencies, mentoring and target roles, and other relevant personal and organizational information.</p>
  <p>We are also introducing a new org chart experience with a refreshed look and feel. Available on desktop and mobile, users can explore their organizational structure with improved expand and collapse capabilities, which helps provide full accessibility to an employee’s profile preview, with an option to open the new spotlight view.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b181ba5a94a8b936ff644a1c243245079ecbbab4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b181ba5a94a8b936ff644a1c243245079ecbbab4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1b181ba5a94a8b936ff644a1c243245079ecbbab4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Screenshot of the new org chart experience" src="./media_1b181ba5a94a8b936ff644a1c243245079ecbbab4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="576">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>The new org chart experience. Click to enlarge.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Customers can now automatically process new hires from SAP SuccessFactors Recruiting and SAP SuccessFactors Onboarding into SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central. This capability helps further reduce the time to hire, which is especially important with mass, seasonal, and high-volume hiring.</p>
  <h2 id="sap-successfactors-employee-central-global-benefits">SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central Global Benefits</h2>
  <p>With this release, we are pleased to introduce a new benefits enrollment experience for insurance, savings, and pension benefit types. Available on both desktop and mobile, the guided experience for benefits elections can give employees increased convenience with improved navigation and increased confidence with side-by-side plan comparisons and embedded instructional text. Additionally, employees can update dependent information and manage beneficiaries directly from the benefits enrollment process, which helps further streamline the enrollment experience.</p>
  <h2 id="sap-successfactors-time-tracking">SAP SuccessFactors Time Tracking</h2>
  <p>We are thrilled to share the launch of a new time sheet experience that integrates the latest version of My Timesheet in SAP S/4HANA with SAP SuccessFactors. Employees can now record time for payroll, as well as against activities and cost objects, from a single time sheet across applications. This helps organizations leverage real-time connectivity between HR and finance operations to keep track of employee activity and labor costs and to pay employees accurately and on time.</p>
  <p>Additionally, a new monthly calendar view for time sheets can give employees and managers a complete picture of recorded time over a month. Users can drill down into specific days and submit or approve time for pay periods beyond a week, such as biweekly or monthly.</p>
  <p>For managers, a new time approval center helps simplify approvals with a centralized dashboard highlighting anomalies for swift resolution. Managers can monitor team working hours effectively, helping to ensure accurate and timely payroll processing.</p>
  <h2 id="sap-successfactors-onboarding">SAP SuccessFactors Onboarding</h2>
  <p>With enhancements to the onboarding journey experience, new hires can now use the new Your Onboarding Checklist page to reference and complete all tasks – onboarding data collection, compliance tasks, additional onboarding tasks, and exploring the onboarding guide – from one place with a single view. Available for new hires, rehires, internal hires, and employees with global assignments, this improved experience can save time for onboarding participants while helping to ensure productivity from the start.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e12cd49909a64b18778552665ee0147fcacdc707.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1e12cd49909a64b18778552665ee0147fcacdc707.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1e12cd49909a64b18778552665ee0147fcacdc707.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Screenshot of the new onboarding journey experience" src="./media_1e12cd49909a64b18778552665ee0147fcacdc707.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="576">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>The new onboarding journey experience. Click to enlarge.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>And that’s only a fraction of all the innovations we’re bringing to customers in 1H 2024. There’s much more in the release, including new and exciting updates in:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Generative AI and Joule capabilities</li>
    <li>SAP SuccessFactors Opportunity Marketplace</li>
    <li>SAP SuccessFactors Compensation</li>
    <li>SAP SuccessFactors Succession &#x26; Development</li>
    <li>SAP SuccessFactors Incentive Management</li>
    <li>SAP SuccessFactors Work Zone</li>
  </ul>
  <p>Read the <a href="https://www.sap.com/documents/2024/04/300e8c6d-b77e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">SAP SuccessFactors first half 2024 release highlights brochure</a> and watch the <a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2024/04/8c907f14-b77e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">1H 2024 release highlights video</a> to find out more.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Bianka Woelke is group vice president of Application Product Management at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-employee-central</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors-hcm-suite</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-onboarding</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-opportunity-marketplace</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-recruiting</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[2024 HR Trends: The Year of AI]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/2024-hr-trends-the-year-of-ai</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/2024-hr-trends-the-year-of-ai</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP research reveals the latest HR trends and how organizations can stay ahead of the curve with innovative strategies and technology.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ff8cf0ed03433df1c0da682bcb037e6567eeae0d.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ff8cf0ed03433df1c0da682bcb037e6567eeae0d.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1ff8cf0ed03433df1c0da682bcb037e6567eeae0d.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="2024 HR Trends: The Year of AI" src="./media_1ff8cf0ed03433df1c0da682bcb037e6567eeae0d.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="hr-trends-the-year-of-ai">2024 HR Trends: The Year of AI</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Over the past few years, HR has steadily evolved into one of the most critical functions for any organization. HR not only has a seat at the table, but the ability to become a driving force behind organizational change and growth. Most customers I speak with recognize this opportunity, but many have the same question: how can HR make the most impact?</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Each year, the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/resources.html">SAP SuccessFactors Growth &#x26; Insights team</a> conducts in-depth research on the latest trends and predictions impacting the HR function. Our PhD-level organizational psychologists and market intelligence experts aggregate and analyze a mountain of HR trends and predictions data to deliver a list of actionable “meta-trends.” For 2024, a list of 611 individual trends were broken down into nine key themes.</p>
  <p>Above all, there is no question that 2024 is the year of <a href="/topics/ai">artificial intelligence (AI)</a>. No longer just hype or speculation, AI is officially here. Exciting possibilities have become realities and organizations must embrace AI or risk being left behind. And while our number one HR trend is AI, you can also see its effects across every trend.</p>
  <p>Below is a snapshot of the top three 2024 HR meta-trends, with examples of how SAP SuccessFactors solutions can help organizations stay ahead of the curve.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <picture>
          <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d0e8557e1e73aae25728990f5b73d21af5fff939.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
          <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d0e8557e1e73aae25728990f5b73d21af5fff939.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
          <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1d0e8557e1e73aae25728990f5b73d21af5fff939.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
          <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_1d0e8557e1e73aae25728990f5b73d21af5fff939.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="208">
        </picture>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="ai-upends-the-world-of-work-as-we-know-it">1. AI Upends the World of Work as We Know It</h2>
  <p>I don’t go a day – or maybe 10 minutes – without a customer asking for all the latest and greatest on AI innovation. That makes sense, as AI has dominated the 2024 trends discourse and it’s increasingly become seen as a way to augment human work.</p>
  <p>Trends indicate that using all forms of AI to improve day-to-day productivity will be top of mind for organizations in 2024. In particular, self-serve AI tools like copilots are poised to increase employee productivity on various day-to-day tasks. As employee sentiment about using AI tools at work has improved, so has the ability of these tools to make employees more efficient and effective.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="be-ready-for-ai-built-for-business">Be ready for AI built for business</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/ai-assistant.html">Meet SAP’s AI copilot, Joule</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>HR use cases abound, particularly within talent acquisition, but concerns continue about data privacy, ethics, and regulatory compliance. There’s a lot of noise and movement in the space, and regulators and enforcement agencies are acting quickly to keep up.</p>
  <p>With the tech landscape and market realities in mind, the HR leaders who head AI implementation programs, maintain a strong policy posture, and avoid overhyped or underbaked propositions to take advantage of the most valuable capabilities will steer their organizations down the right AI path.</p>
  <p>Embedding an AI copilot in HR solutions, like <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/ai-joule-product-tour.html">Joule in SAP SuccessFactors solutions</a>, can help employees and managers work faster and smarter by making it easier to find information and complete common HR tasks, such as updating personal data, giving feedback, and initiating a promotion.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_102dca27542b692c9688525999ebc7b6cc402f1b5.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_102dca27542b692c9688525999ebc7b6cc402f1b5.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_102dca27542b692c9688525999ebc7b6cc402f1b5.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_102dca27542b692c9688525999ebc7b6cc402f1b5.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="614">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>Joule, SAP’s AI copilot. Click to enlarge.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="skills-become-the-center-of-hr-practices">2. Skills Become the Center of HR Practices</h2>
  <p>As AI needs rise within organizations, many organizations will need to immediately respond to determine what AI skills are needed, who possesses those skills, and how to fill skill gaps – whether build, borrow, buy, or bot. On the other hand, AI capabilities will also drive the ability for organizations to more effectively engage in strategic workforce planning.</p>
  <p>Furthermore, in today’s increasingly complex business environment, traditional top-down human resources approaches fail to address employees’ increasing expectations for flexible and personalized career development. In 2024, HR will need to meet employees’ growing expectations for bespoke career paths while also solving the broader organization’s growing skills gaps and talent shortages, which present a major concern for leaders.</p>
  <p>Looking forward, it will be interesting to see whether the average organization fully engages in long-term, strategic, skills-based workforce planning, which has long been a strategic objective for many but often remains out of reach as they react to immediate priorities. AI skills could work as a forcing function here – and contribute to other trend areas like learning and employee potential.</p>
  <p><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/talent-management.html">SAP SuccessFactors solutions for talent management</a> can drive better employee experiences and business outcomes by using a common skills framework across recruiting, learning, performance management, internal mobility, and development.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d381f1111939f272d8dd076b837ed2de4dd9aa20.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d381f1111939f272d8dd076b837ed2de4dd9aa20.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1d381f1111939f272d8dd076b837ed2de4dd9aa20.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_1d381f1111939f272d8dd076b837ed2de4dd9aa20.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="576">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>Overview of skills and aspirations in a growth portfolio for SAP SuccessFactors. Click to enlarge.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="hybrid-work-returns-to-the-office">3. Hybrid Work Returns to the Office</h2>
  <p>Looking back at our yearly analyses of HR meta-trends, we saw the hybrid work topic shift from a focus on remote work as a reactive tactic to protect employees’ health and safety in 2020, to a focus on flexibility in 2021, to maintaining productivity and collaboration while working flexibly in 2022, and finally to an emphasis on underlying flexibility and the need for and benefit of malleable guidelines and principles in 2023. With the recent increase in partial and full return-to-office (RTO) policies, 2024 trends data suggests that the pendulum has swung back to hybrid, referring specifically to work location versus a broader perspective centered on flexibility.</p>
  <p>Companies in 2024 will continue to experiment with motivating employees to return to the office in ways that promote productivity, collaboration, and cost savings but don’t alienate their top talent. But some organizations are focusing more on redesigning the nature of work rather than just mandating where or when work gets done.</p>
  <p><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/core-hr-payroll.html">SAP SuccessFactors solutions for core HR, time, and payroll</a> help employees adopt a hybrid working model by providing options for common HR tasks regardless of when and where they are working, such as clocking in and out via desktop, mobile, or Microsoft Teams.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16e1bb2544e733655fa31281e9dcd8f5220ded6f8.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16e1bb2544e733655fa31281e9dcd8f5220ded6f8.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_16e1bb2544e733655fa31281e9dcd8f5220ded6f8.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_16e1bb2544e733655fa31281e9dcd8f5220ded6f8.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="576">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>Clock in and out via Microsoft Teams with SAP SuccessFactors solutions. Click to enlarge.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>There are plenty more strategic takeaways in the full report – the entire paper is a must-read for HR leaders to learn more from our research team on the latest trends in:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Diversity, equity, inclusion, and belonging (DEI&#x26;B)</li>
    <li>Employee mental health</li>
    <li>Leadership trust</li>
    <li>HR skills and agility</li>
    <li>Compensation</li>
    <li>Sustainability</li>
  </ul>
  <p>For additional insights, <a href="https://www.sap.com/registration/protected/default-overlay.html?gated_asset_path=%2F%2Fwww.sap.com%2Fdocuments%2F2024%2F02%2F883d4dde-ad7e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.rc.html&#x26;pdf-asset=883d4dde-ad7e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b&#x26;page=1?url_id=ctabutton-us-hcm">read the full report</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Dan Beck is president and chief product officer for SAP SuccessFactors.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-sap-news-on-linkedin">Connect with SAP News on LinkedIn</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news">Follow us to stay up-to-date</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors-hcm-suite</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP and NVIDIA to Accelerate Generative AI Adoption Across Enterprise Applications Powering Global Industries]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/sap-and-nvidia-to-accelerate-generative-ai-adoption</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/sap-and-nvidia-to-accelerate-generative-ai-adoption</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Together, SAP and NVIDIA will bring custom generative AI to thousands of enterprises around the world. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b3fcf19084a91c9721f2b9169c59bd16f3f8e1b6.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b3fcf19084a91c9721f2b9169c59bd16f3f8e1b6.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1b3fcf19084a91c9721f2b9169c59bd16f3f8e1b6.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP and NVIDIA to Accelerate Generative AI Adoption Across Enterprise Applications Powering Global Industries" src="./media_1b3fcf19084a91c9721f2b9169c59bd16f3f8e1b6.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-and-nvidia-to-accelerate-generative-ai-adoption-across-enterprise-applications-powering-global-industries">SAP and NVIDIA to Accelerate Generative AI Adoption Across Enterprise Applications Powering Global Industries</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Customers Can Harness Their Business Data in Cloud Solutions from SAP Using Customized LLMs Deployed with NVIDIA AI Foundry Services and New NVIDIA NIM Microservices</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <table>
          <thead>
            <tr>
              <th>Text Large</th>
            </tr>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td>
                <p><strong><em>WALLDORF and SANTA CLARA, Calif.</em></strong></p>
                <hr>
                <p><a href="http://www.nvidia.com">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) and <a href="http://www.nvidia.com">NVIDIA</a> (NASDAQ: NVDA) today announced a partnership expansion focused on accelerating enterprise customers’ ability to harness the transformative power of data and generative AI across SAP’s portfolio of cloud solutions and applications.</p>
              </td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
        <p>The companies are collaborating to build and deliver SAP Business AI, including scalable, business-specific generative AI capabilities inside the Joule copilot from SAP and across SAP’s portfolio of cloud solutions and applications – all of which are underpinned by the SAP generative AI hub. The generative AI hub facilitates relevant, reliable and responsible business AI and provides instant access to a broad range of large language models (LLMs).</p>
        <p>As part of SAP’s ongoing initiative to build generative AI directly into the applications that power the world’s businesses, the partnership aims to help customers adopt generative AI capabilities at scale across their organizations. SAP will use <a href="https://www.nvidia.com/en-us/ai-data-science/generative-ai/">NVIDIA’s generative AI foundry service</a> to fine-tune LLMs for domain-specific scenarios and deploy applications with new <a href="https://nvidianews.nvidia.com/news/generative-ai-microservices-for-developers">NVIDIA NIM</a>™ microservices. SAP and NVIDIA plan to make the new integrated capabilities available by the end of 2024.</p>
        <p>“Enterprise customers want to leverage state-of-the-art technology that delivers real business value,” said Christian Klein, CEO and Member of the Executive Board of SAP SE. “Strategic technology partnerships, like the one between SAP and NVIDIA, are at the core of our strategy to invest in technology that maximizes the potential and opportunity of AI for business. NVIDIA’s expertise in delivering AI capabilities at scale will help SAP accelerate the pace of transformation and better serve our customers in the cloud.”</p>
        <p>“SAP is sitting on a gold mine of enterprise data that can be transformed into custom generative AI agents to help customers automate their businesses,” said Jensen Huang, founder and CEO of NVIDIA. “Together, NVIDIA and SAP will bring custom generative AI to the thousands of enterprises around the world that rely on SAP to power their operations.”</p>
        <h2 id="harnessing-business-data-and-generative-ai-to-advance-customer-insights">Harnessing Business Data and Generative AI to Advance Customer Insights</h2>
        <p>SAP and NVIDIA plan to collaborate to integrate generative AI into cloud solutions from SAP, which include the latest release of the SAP Datasphere solution, SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP) and RISE with SAP.</p>
        <p>SAP plans to build additional generative AI capabilities within SAP BTP using NVIDIA’s generative AI foundry service, featuring <a href="https://www.nvidia.com/en-us/data-center/dgx-cloud/">NVIDIA DGX™ Cloud</a> AI supercomputing, <a href="https://www.nvidia.com/en-us/data-center/products/ai-enterprise/">NVIDIA AI Enterprise</a> software and NVIDIA AI Foundation models. These new capabilities are designed to be the basis of SAP’s development and deployment of generative AI for customers and is expected to be accessible in the generative AI hub in SAP AI Core and SAP Datasphere.</p>
        <p>Additional generative AI initiatives include:</p>
        <ul>
          <li><strong>New capabilities for the Joule copilot</strong>: Joule can leverage <a href="https://blogs.nvidia.com/blog/2023/11/15/what-is-retrieval-augmented-generation/">retrieval-augmented generation</a> (RAG) capabilities built by NVIDIA and SAP, which can be deployed on leading hyperscalers or SAP’s own cloud environments. As a natural-language, generative AI copilot, Joule helps customers unlock the potential in their business by automating time-consuming tasks and quickly analyzing business-critical data to deliver more intelligent, personalized experiences.</li>
          <li><strong>Innovative use cases leveraging SAP S/4HANA Cloud, SAP SuccessFactors and SAP Signavio</strong>: SAP and NVIDIA are exploring more than 20 generative AI use cases where the companies can combine assets to simplify and enhance digital transformation. Among these are generative AI features that can automate enterprise resource planning with intelligent invoice matching in SAP S/4HANA Cloud; improve human resources use cases leveraging SAP SuccessFactors; and accelerate new generative AI insights from SAP Signavio to better process business recommendations and optimize SAP’s customer support processes.</li>
          <li><strong>Unifying AI data sources with SAP Datasphere</strong>: Built on SAP BTP, SAP Datasphere enables integration and a unified view of semantically rich SAP data with third-party data across the enterprise landscape to help customers adapt faster to market changes and make more efficient and better informed decisions. With SAP Datasphere, customers can confidently access a high-quality data fabric using AI and machine learning (ML) models. To accelerate SAP’s federated machine learning (FedML) capabilities for SAP Datasphere, NVIDIA and SAP are facilitating easier access to data for data scientists and enhancing ML workload performance with the support of NVIDIA accelerated computing platforms and NVIDIA AI Enterprise data science software such as <a href="https://developer.nvidia.com/rapids">NVIDIA RAPIDS</a>™.</li>
          <li><strong>Using LLMs for the ABAP programming language</strong>: To aid developers in creating domain-specific language code, SAP plans to use NVIDIA AI foundry services to assist in fine-tuning LLMs. This will build on SAP’s use of generative AI models to assist developers who use ABAP through the company’s ABAP Cloud model and SAP Cloud Application Programming model.</li>
        </ul>
        <h2 id="nvidia-ai-enterprise-powers-production-grade-generative-ai-across-cloud-solutions-from-sap">NVIDIA AI Enterprise Powers Production-Grade Generative AI Across Cloud Solutions from SAP</h2>
        <p>Once models are ready for deployment in cloud solutions from SAP, SAP plans to use NVIDIA AI Enterprise software, including NVIDIA NIM inference microservices and NVIDIA NeMo Retriever™ microservices. NVIDIA NIM can be used to accelerate and maximize inference performance across the accelerated infrastructure from SAP. Using NVIDIA NeMo Retriever microservices, SAP plans to add RAG capabilities that enable generative AI applications to more securely access data running on SAP software to improve accuracy and insights. Customers can plan to use RAG on both SAP and third-party data.</p>
        <p>To learn more about the SAP and NVIDIA partnership, <a href="https://www.nvidia.com/gtc/keynote/">watch the replay of Huang’s GTC keynote address</a>.</p>
        <p>Visit the <a href="/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
        <h2 id="about-nvidia">About NVIDIA</h2>
        <p>Since its founding in 1993, <a href="https://www.nvidia.com/">NVIDIA</a> (NASDAQ: NVDA) has been a pioneer in accelerated computing. The company’s invention of the GPU in 1999 sparked the growth of the PC gaming market, redefined computer graphics, ignited the era of modern AI and is fueling industrial digitalization across markets. NVIDIA is now a full-stack computing infrastructure company with data-center-scale offerings that are reshaping industry. More information at <a href="https://nvidianews.nvidia.com/">https://nvidianews.nvidia.com/</a>.</p>
        <table>
          <thead>
            <tr>
              <th>Text Large</th>
            </tr>
          </thead>
          <tbody>
            <tr>
              <td><strong>About SAP</strong></td>
            </tr>
          </tbody>
        </table>
        <p>SAP’s strategy is to help every business run as an intelligent, sustainable enterprise. As a market leader in enterprise application software, we help companies of all sizes and in all industries run at their best: SAP customers generate 87% of total global commerce. Our machine learning, Internet of Things (IoT), and advanced analytics technologies help turn customers’ businesses into intelligent enterprises. SAP helps give people and organizations deep business insight and fosters collaboration that helps them stay ahead of their competition. We simplify technology for companies so they can consume our software the way they want – without disruption. Our end-to-end suite of applications and services enables business and public customers across 26 industries globally to operate profitably, adapt continuously, and make a difference. With a global network of customers, partners, employees, and thought leaders, SAP helps the world run better and improve people’s lives. For more information, visit <a href="http://www.sap.com">www.sap.com</a>.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="revolutionize-how-you-interact-with-sap-business-system-while-simplifying-your-day-to-day-with-faster-work-smarter-insights-and-better-outcomes">Revolutionize how you interact with SAP business system while simplifying your day-to-day with faster work, smarter insights and better outcomes</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/ai-assistant.html">Meet Joule</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><strong>Note to editors:</strong><br>To preview and download broadcast-standard stock footage and press photos digitally, please visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/photos">www.sap.com/photos</a>. On this platform, you can find high-resolution material for your media channels.</p>
  <p><strong>For customers interested in learning more about SAP products:</strong> Global Customer Center: +49 180 534-34-24<br>United States Only: 1 (800) 872-1SAP (1-800-872-1727)</p>
  <p><strong>For further information, contact:</strong><br>SAP: Scott Malinowski, +1 (617) 538-6297, <a href="mailto:scott.malinowski@sap.com">scott.malinowski@sap.com</a><br><a href="mailto:SAP%20Press%20Room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a><br>NVIDIA: Shannon McPhee, +1 (310) 920-9642, <a href="mailto:smcphee@nvidia.com">smcphee@nvidia.com</a></p>
  <p>Certain statements in this press release including, but not limited to, statements as to: the benefits, impact, performance, features, and availability of NVIDIA’s products and technologies, including NVIDIA’s generative AI foundry service, NVIDIA NIM microservices, NVIDIA DGX Cloud AI supercomputing, NVIDIA AI Enterprise software, and NVIDIA AI Foundation models, NVIDIA accelerated computing platforms, NVIDIA AI Enterprise data science software such as NVIDIA RAPIDS, RAPIDS cuDF and cuML, NVIDIA NeMo Retriever microservices; NVIDIA’s partnership with SAP, the benefits and impact of such partnership, and the features and availability of its services and offerings; SAP sitting on a gold mine of enterprise data that can be transformed into custom generative AI agents to help customers automate their businesses; and NVIDIA and SAP bringing custom generative AI to the thousands of enterprises around the world that rely on SAP to power their operations are forward-looking statements that are subject to risks and uncertainties that could cause results to be materially different than expectations. Important factors that could cause actual results to differ materially include: global economic conditions; our reliance on third parties to manufacture, assemble, package and test our products; the impact of technological development and competition; development of new products and technologies or enhancements to our existing product and technologies; market acceptance of our products or our partners’ products; design, manufacturing or software defects; changes in consumer preferences or demands; changes in industry standards and interfaces; unexpected loss of performance of our products or technologies when integrated into systems; as well as other factors detailed from time to time in the most recent reports NVIDIA files with the Securities and Exchange Commission, or SEC, including, but not limited to, its annual report on Form 10-K and quarterly reports on Form 10-Q. Copies of reports filed with the SEC are posted on the company’s website and are available from NVIDIA without charge. These forward-looking statements are not guarantees of future performance and speak only as of the date hereof, and, except as required by law, NVIDIA disclaims any obligation to update these forward-looking statements to reflect future events or circumstances.</p>
  <p>This document contains forward-looking statements, which are predictions, projections, or other statements about future events. These statements are based on current expectations, forecasts, and assumptions that are subject to risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results and outcomes to materially differ. Additional information regarding these risks and uncertainties may be found in our filings with the Securities and Exchange Commission, including but not limited to the risk factors section of SAP’s 2023 Annual Report on Form 20-F.</p>
  <p>© 2024 SAP SE and NVIDIA Corporation. All rights reserved.</p>
  <p>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p>NVIDIA, the NVIDIA logo, DGX, NVIDIA NeMo Retriever, NVIDIA NIM, and RAPIDS are trademarks and/or registered trademarks of NVIDIA Corporation in the U.S. and/or other countries. Other company and product names may be trademarks of the respective companies with which they are associated. Features, pricing, availability, and specifications are subject to change without notice.</p>
  <p>Please consider our <a href="https://www.sap.com/corporate/en/legal/privacy.html">privacy policy</a>. If you received this press release in your e-mail and you wish to unsubscribe to our mailing list please contact <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a> and write Unsubscribe in the subject line.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
            <category>product/sap-datasphere</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Biggest Opportunity for Businesses Today: Using the Right Business Data]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2024/03/business-opportunity-use-the-right-business-data</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2024/03/business-opportunity-use-the-right-business-data</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Having a central hub for data is more critical than ever. Updates to SAP Datasphere empower businesses with more innovations.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10cb3ea6ef420b80f58847074323ded1ddf40b734.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10cb3ea6ef420b80f58847074323ded1ddf40b734.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_10cb3ea6ef420b80f58847074323ded1ddf40b734.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="The Biggest Opportunity for Businesses Today: Using the Right Business Data" src="./media_10cb3ea6ef420b80f58847074323ded1ddf40b734.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="the-biggest-opportunity-for-businesses-today-using-the-right-business-data">The Biggest Opportunity for Businesses Today: Using the Right Business Data</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>There is no doubt that generative AI for business will transform every aspect of how business is done. But the reality is that generative AI is only as good as the data that it’s trained on.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>While data may be the fuel powering the engine of AI, it’s good data that’s the real game changer. With good data, a company can automate processes — freeing up their people to do the most impactful work — and analyze the most important variables facing their business to create intelligent insights.</p>
  <p>That’s where a datasphere comes in. It makes data more complete and logical by understanding the different relationships within a company’s data. And that’s what can truly bring out the best in any business today.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="deliver-seamless-and-scalable-access-to-mission-critical-business-data">Deliver seamless and scalable access to mission-critical business data</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/datasphere.html">Explore SAP Datasphere</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Having a central hub for data is more critical than ever. It allows our customers to better model their business across all SAP business applications. That’s exactly why we introduced <strong>SAP Datasphere</strong> last year to empower businesses with insights they need – based on the right data – in the context of their business. Since then, generative AI has disrupted and simplified even more business processes, and data capture is no different. This week <a href="/2024/03/future-of-data-driven-business-new-sap-datasphere-capabilities">we announced new generative-AI features in SAP Datasphere that will transform enterprise planning</a> through simplified data landscapes and more-intuitive data interaction.</p>
  <p>Why is this important? Because having a unified data view that simplifies the data landscapes while retaining context and logic is what enables businesses to adapt faster to market changes and make better decisions. It’s also a more efficient way of working. Because while you’re busy pulling data together, competitors are circling your customers.</p>
  <p>I am constantly speaking with our customers about the value of SAP Datasphere. It’s a data architecture that harmonizes mission-critical data across an organization. I hear amazing outcomes they’re able to achieve: from PwC breaking down silos in the different countries where it stores sensitive data so its workforce can access it more efficiently and securely for customers, to the Lufthansa Group taking data from different parts of its operations like aircraft, HR, and procurement, to see how decisions from one could impact the other.<br><br>With our additional news this week, such as making our generative AI copilot Joule available in SAP Analytics Cloud and expanding our partnership with Collibra to help our customers meet compliance, privacy, and regulatory requirements related to AI as they evolve, we’re making it easier to find the right data and use it to drive deeper insights, more efficiencies, faster growth, and more trust in their business.</p>
  <p>While PwC and Lufthansa show what’s possible today with a simplified data fabric, imagine what is about to become possible when you infuse it with the power of generative AI that understands your business – and then learns from that data. This has the potential to deliver exponential value from your data.</p>
  <p>Or think of it this way: years ago, the biggest differentiators for businesses were price, location, products, and services. Today, and especially in the years ahead, it could very well be how effectively a business is training their AI models. That’s why building the right data fabric is one of the most important investments any business can make today.</p>
  <p>It’s been said that the best way to predict the future is to invent it. And in an era where data is being created exponentially, I believe that those businesses that can separate the signal from the noise when it comes to their data will be the ones that invent the future in an AI-first world.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Scott Russell is a member of the Executive Board of SAP SE.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="take-a-guided-tour-and-experience-firsthand-the-power-of-business-data-with-sap-datasphere">Take a guided tour and experience firsthand the power of business data with SAP Datasphere</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/datasphere/guided-experience.html">Start now</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/blog/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/blog/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/blog/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/blog/article-read-more</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/executive-blog</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-datasphere</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unleashing the Latest SAP Data and Analytics Innovations]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/latest-sap-data-and-analytics-innovations-sap-data-unleashed</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/latest-sap-data-and-analytics-innovations-sap-data-unleashed</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP has shared the latest innovations in data and analytics. Read on to learn more about the company's transformative announcements.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1025728cedc072568e25830043a6185f08eca8f64.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1025728cedc072568e25830043a6185f08eca8f64.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1025728cedc072568e25830043a6185f08eca8f64.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Unleashing the Latest SAP Data and Analytics Innovations" src="./media_1025728cedc072568e25830043a6185f08eca8f64.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="unleashing-the-latest-sap-data-and-analytics-innovations">Unleashing the Latest SAP Data and Analytics Innovations</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Today at <a href="/">SAP Data Unleashed</a>, SAP proudly announced the latest innovations in data and analytics.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Read on to learn more about these transformative announcements, which will enable businesses to unlock new potential in the areas of data management, AI-driven planning, and analytics.</p>
  <h2 id="access-insights-wherever-your-data-resides">Access Insights Wherever Your Data Resides</h2>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>SAP Datasphere Knowledge Graph</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP Datasphere knowledge graph will enable organizations to better represent their real-world use of data, leading to more effectively leveraging it for generative AI and better reasoning.</p>
  <p>As data is onboarded, transformed, and integrated in SAP Datasphere, SAP Datasphere knowledge graph automatically creates an ontology representing the relationships in the data, including the inherent business context from SAP application sources like SAP S/4HANA. This is then available to be extended and augmented via an ontology editor to reflect specific attributes within an organization. Finally, the data in SAP Datasphere is automatically applied to this ontology to create a knowledge graph that allows the data to be processed as a semantic web of relationships, drawing new insights from connections that are otherwise difficult to follow.</p>
  <p>These knowledge graphs are better suited for answering complex, often open-ended questions. For example, a marketing manager might ask a question like: “What type of campaign for mountain bikes works best for my highest performing cities with a population over 1 million?”</p>
  <p>Knowledge graphs can provide better context to large language models (LLMs) and prevent AI-generated “hallucinations.” SAP Datasphere knowledge graph will enable organizations to unleash the power of AI for even the most complex queries.</p>
  <p>The effort and cost of manually creating knowledge graphs is typically very high. SAP Datasphere knowledge graph overcomes this by pre-populating the knowledge graphs using all the valuable content already available in SAP Datasphere. The knowledge graph can then be used with Joule, SAP’s generative AI co-pilot, allowing business users to ask both open-ended and specific questions and get instant and well-documented answers. Sign up for a preview of SAP Datasphere knowledge graph via the link below.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15c1af20ba8e68937af5d24f99fac41cebc44dce7.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15c1af20ba8e68937af5d24f99fac41cebc44dce7.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_15c1af20ba8e68937af5d24f99fac41cebc44dce7.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_15c1af20ba8e68937af5d24f99fac41cebc44dce7.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="576">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>Auto-generated knowledge graphs enable AI to answer complex, open-ended questions</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>SAP HANA Cloud Vector Engine</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>With the next release of SAP HANA Cloud, a vector capability will be added to existing multi-model capabilities, allowing customers to gain value from all relevant types of business data using a single database. The inclusion of a vector engine further enables customers to build <a href="https://pages.community.sap.com/topics/hana/intelligent-data-applications">intelligent data applications</a> that combine the natural intuition of human interaction with powerful machine learning and multi-model processing capabilities.</p>
  <p>The vector engine in SAP HANA Cloud provides the ability to store and compare vectors using SQL. Determining similarity between vectors enables use cases such as retrieval-augmented generation (RAG), recommendations, classifications, clustering, and more. Key benefits of SAP HANA Cloud vector engine include:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Simplify data architecture and security with a single multi-model database with SQL interaction</li>
    <li>Gain new insights by combining spatial, graph, JSON, and relational data with vector queries</li>
    <li>Easily incorporate vector use cases in solutions based on the HANA Cloud ecosystem (clients, Python libraries, CAP, etc.)</li>
    <li>Integrate with open-source community tools such as LangChain via plug-ins</li>
  </ul>
  <p>SAP HANA Cloud vector engine is currently in public preview and is planned for general availability in late Q1 2024.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Simplified Consumption of Data Products in SAP Datasphere</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Data products facilitate self-service access to data as a product and enable data sharing across application boundaries. Data consumers need an easy way to explore, understand, and activate the data needed to perform their tasks — and data providers need an easy way to publish their assets and make them available to data consumers.</p>
  <p>SAP is innovating in this space with an improved user experience that drives data sharing at scale. This starts with published data products, whether produced by SAP line-of-business applications, industry solutions, or third parties, and follows with simple consumption in SAP Datasphere.</p>
  <p>In SAP Datasphere, customers will find ready access to SAP and non-SAP data products and easily install them into their SAP Datasphere instance. The procedure establishes relevant connections and creates the necessary artifacts in SAP Datasphere without the user having to enter those details. Key to this is making data provisioning easier via metadata, which are described via the Open Resource Directory (ORD) protocol. The experience will be harmonized within SAP Datasphere by bringing catalog and the data product installation closely together. Visit <a href="https://roadmaps.sap.com/board?range=FIRST-LAST&#x26;PRODUCT=73555000100800002141&#x26;q=data%20products#Q1%202024">SAP Road Map Explorer</a> for the latest updates.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15b1605af3a6110198283ea2725e4e982d88adc28.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15b1605af3a6110198283ea2725e4e982d88adc28.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_15b1605af3a6110198283ea2725e4e982d88adc28.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_15b1605af3a6110198283ea2725e4e982d88adc28.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="576">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>Data products available in catalog enhances the experience and productivity of data users</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>SAP Datasphere Semantic Onboarding Enhancements</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Semantic onboarding provides a seamless import of semantically rich objects from SAP S/4HANA and SAP BW/4HANA into SAP Datasphere. Now, we are taking the next step by adding support for SAP HANA Cloud and SAP data products through the same unified onboarding experience.</p>
  <p>Customers will be able to combine their SAP HANA Cloud modeling approach with SAP Datasphere by importing calculation views into the data layer of SAP Datasphere. This preserves the semantic information such as measures, attributes, hierarchies, aggregations, and currencies/units, while keeping SAP HANA Cloud and SAP Datasphere objects in sync — allowing customers to leverage their prior investments in SAP HANA modeling.</p>
  <p>Likewise, semantic onboarding of SAP data products will enable inheritance of business context from SAP line-of-business applications and industry solutions. By providing the semantics of the source systems and transferring that into the business data fabric as a foundation, SAP Datasphere drastically improves the analytic workflow and accelerates and simplifies data-driven insights.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>Collibra AI Governance Integration with SAP Solutions</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The SAP and Collibra partnership enables end-to-end data governance and delivers trusted data to all users across the business data fabric. As more tasks and decisions are automated by AI within critical business processes, the need to extend governance to AI has also become apparent.</p>
  <p>The partnership with Collibra is being expanded to address the data and AI governance needs of joint customers via Collibra AI Governance. We will build tailored integrations between Collibra AI Governance and SAP solutions to connect the data used for AI with the models themselves in a single platform, allowing enterprises to track and manage their AI development efforts.</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Customers will better understand data lineage and metadata of SAP data that is utilized in AI modeling. With that, users can see what data their AI models were trained on to ensure that the data is accurate and from a trusted source.</li>
    <li>Customers will benefit from a single view to understand what AI models exist in their organization, and what data is being used to power them. AI/machine learning models created with SAP technology will be registered with the Collibra AI Governance platform.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>This extension of the SAP partnership with Collibra will increase transparency and accountability for organizations, and help ensure that regulatory, compliance, and privacy policies are being met. More importantly, it will build user trust by preventing biased decision-making, inaccurate recommendations, and other risks arising from AI.</p>
  <p>Together, SAP and Collibra will help joint customers address the data and AI governance needs across their organizations. Collibra AI Governance was <a href="https://www.collibra.com/us/en/company/newsroom/press-releases/collibra-introduces-collibra-ai-governance">launched last week</a> and is available to interested customers.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>SAP Datasphere Confluent Integration</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Core to the SAP data strategy is providing customers with the ability to interoperate with the world’s leading data and AI vendors through an open data ecosystem. To this end, the newly enhanced Confluent integration enables real-time streaming of data to and from SAP Datasphere.</p>
  <p>First, the outbound capabilities were extended by taking advantage of Confluent’s proprietary schema registry capabilities. Second, the Confluent schema registry will be used to enable seamless consumption of Confluent data within SAP Datasphere.</p>
  <p>The integration is specifically tailored to Confluent and provides a superior user experience for joint customers. It allows connections on the application level without additional custom application development. The integration is a pre-established replication flow in SAP Datasphere, which already includes delta and real-time processing natively. This makes the process very efficient as it does not force customers to load all the data at every step, but only when data has changed.</p>
  <p>The first integration for data ingestion into Kafka and Confluent is generally available. Additional capabilities for Confluent specific outbound and inbound integration will be generally available at the end of Q1 and Q3, respectively.</p>
  <h2 id="transform-planning-with-a-business-data-fabric">Transform Planning with a Business Data Fabric</h2>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>SAP Analytics Cloud for Planning Deep Integration to SAP Datasphere</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP Datasphere and SAP Analytics Cloud for planning will be more closely integrated to expand the business data fabric to planning use cases. SAP Analytics Cloud planning models can be deployed into SAP Datasphere, bringing plan and actuals data together for real-time steering.</p>
  <p>Through a reduction in both data footprint and modeling efforts, SAP Analytics Cloud extends planning functionality via SAP Datasphere and its native capabilities for transformation and integration. This reduces the complexity and risk inherent in storing multiple copies of data which is prevalent today.</p>
  <p>SAP Analytics Cloud for planning will have live access to actual and plan data for extended planning and analysis scenarios, including the live usage of master data. With this, SAP Datasphere will become the platform on which planning processes and tools can integrate.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14d5d8f4cd6ea2a14b3cb7d88fc159719e39722c7.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14d5d8f4cd6ea2a14b3cb7d88fc159719e39722c7.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_14d5d8f4cd6ea2a14b3cb7d88fc159719e39722c7.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_14d5d8f4cd6ea2a14b3cb7d88fc159719e39722c7.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="558">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>In this example, third-party inflation data from the World Bank (blue box) is provisioned through Datasphere to help planners do scenario planning with SAP Analytics Cloud compass</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP is the only vendor to offer a business data fabric that seamlessly integrates planning and therefore covers the entire technology stack required to transform data into insights and future actions. Visit <a href="https://roadmaps.sap.com/board?PRODUCT=67838200100800006884&#x26;q=seamless&#x26;range=CURRENT-LAST#;INNO=1FA75F34ABA51EDEADDAB4FD3ACC8288">SAP Road Map Explorer</a> for the latest updates.</p>
  <h2 id="foster-trusted-ai-across-your-business">Foster Trusted AI Across Your Business</h2>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>SAP Analytics Cloud Generative AI Co-Pilot</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP customers will embrace the power of generative AI to create and simulate business plans in SAP Analytics Cloud. With the power of Joule, planning and analytics professionals can leverage generative AI capabilities in a wide range of business processes. Activities such as data discovery, dashboard creation, planning model maintenance, and more are benefitting from a boost in core capabilities and an unmatched user experience.</p>
  <p>With the power of natural language processing, end users can easily run analytical queries, simulate driver impacts, plan resource allocations, and auto-generate dashboards and calculations. For example, a business user seeking to understand why gross margins declined in the latest version of a plan could query Joule, which could automatically look through previous plan iterations and attached comments, and uncover the fact that planners were estimating higher commodity costs.</p>
  <p>SAP’s investment in AI and its understanding of the context of business data provides truly limitless potential in unleashing the world of planning and analytics.</p>
  <p>A preview of Joule co-pilot functionality in SAP Analytics Cloud is planned to be available in Q2 2024. Sign up for the preview via the link below.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_135bdf52547a43026234fdf26c84defd9f04f1334.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_135bdf52547a43026234fdf26c84defd9f04f1334.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_135bdf52547a43026234fdf26c84defd9f04f1334.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_135bdf52547a43026234fdf26c84defd9f04f1334.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="574">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>With Joule co-pilot, planning and analytics professionals can prompt Joule to analyze all aspects of extended planning and create new analytical views on the fly, provisioned specially for individual user types</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>SAP Analytics Cloud Compass</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In an increasingly volatile business climate, it is essential to create operational and financial plans and provision BI insights with risk mitigation in mind. This requires the ability to simulate uncertainties and the probability of their impact. Knowing how uncertainties in commodity prices, labor costs, or production volumes will hit your operational expenses or revenue means that companies can quickly prepare and plan counter measures for any scenario.</p>
  <p>SAP Analytics Cloud compass provides Monte Carlo simulation capabilities with a business user-friendly interface. This enables non-technical users to perform real-time multi-variate analysis without prior IT setup or advanced statistical skills.</p>
  <p>Users can perform business simulations directly in SAP Analytics Cloud at a fraction of the time and effort required to perform similar analysis manually. Scenario modeling capabilities will allow comparisons between assumptions, and the reporting of impact variances provides real-time insight, concept validation, and reveals the sensitivity of the drivers chosen. Now customers can identify their major drivers and combinations over time, enabling a better understanding of the dynamics between the data, and how to continuously simulate better and faster. With compass, customers can face the future with confidence.</p>
  <p>A preview of SAP Analytics Cloud compass is planned to be available at the end of Q3 2024. Sign up for the preview via the link below.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b407deea790db28d0775959ab3574632b1f5e085.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b407deea790db28d0775959ab3574632b1f5e085.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1b407deea790db28d0775959ab3574632b1f5e085.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_1b407deea790db28d0775959ab3574632b1f5e085.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>SAP Analytics Cloud compass showing distribution of impact probability on the operating income based on a simulation of uncertainty in inputs such as inflation or other relevant drivers.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="get-started-today">Get Started Today</h3>
  <p>Begin your path toward unlocking the full potential of your business data with SAP Datasphere. Embrace the opportunity to seamlessly integrate and activate your data landscape, propelling your business into a new era of insights and efficiency. Start now and transform how your organization leverages data with SAP Datasphere.</p>
  <p>Start your journey today to bring out your best with SAP data and AI:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><a href="https://www.sap.com/registration/trial.4d48ec23-eadf-4399-8595-ac3f9c66c64f.html">Take a complete tour and try the latest features of SAP Datasphere</a> with the 30-day guided experience.</li>
    <li><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/datasphere/migration.html">Begin your SAP Business Warehouse cloud modernization journey</a> with a free assessment and special offers.</li>
    <li><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/oth/business-data-fabric/index.html?campaigncode=CRM-YJ24-BTP-2560577&#x26;source=blog-glo">Save on costs and learn how to implement a business data fabric architecture</a> with the Total Cost of Ownership study and getting started package</li>
    <li><a href="https://events.sap.com/dataunleashed-previews/en/home">Sign up today for an early preview</a> of the upcoming SAP Datasphere and SAP Analytics Cloud features</li>
  </ul>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Irfan Khan is chief product officer and president for SAP HANA Database &#x26; Analytics.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="deliver-seamless-and-scalable-access-to-mission-critical-business-data">Deliver seamless and scalable access to mission-critical business data</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/datasphere.html">Explore SAP Datasphere</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-data-unleashed</category>
            <category>product/sap-datasphere</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Data Unleashed: The Future Belongs to Data-Driven Organizations]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/future-belongs-to-data-driven-organizations-sap-data-unleashed</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/future-belongs-to-data-driven-organizations-sap-data-unleashed</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With the latest updates to SAP Datasphere, SAP is empowering data-driven organizations to bring out their best. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-data-unleashed</category>
            <category>product/sap-datasphere</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Shapes the Future of Data-Driven Business Transformation with Innovations that Equip Customers to Succeed in the Era of AI]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/future-of-data-driven-business-new-sap-datasphere-capabilities</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/future-of-data-driven-business-new-sap-datasphere-capabilities</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New SAP Datasphere capabilities will drive deeper insights, faster growth and more efficiency in the era of AI. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ca92906e5e003a06f25ac5a8b837a5576894477a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ca92906e5e003a06f25ac5a8b837a5576894477a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1ca92906e5e003a06f25ac5a8b837a5576894477a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Shapes the Future of Data-Driven Business Transformation with Innovations that Equip Customers to Succeed in the Era of AI" src="./media_1ca92906e5e003a06f25ac5a8b837a5576894477a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-shapes-the-future-of-data-driven-business-transformation-with-innovations-that-equip-customers-to-succeed-in-the-era-of-ai">SAP Shapes the Future of Data-Driven Business Transformation with Innovations that Equip Customers to Succeed in the Era of AI</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced transformative data innovations that will help customers harness the full power of their data to drive deeper insights, faster growth and more efficiency in the era of AI. New capabilities in the SAP Datasphere solution, including new generative-AI features, transform enterprise planning through simplified data landscapes and more-intuitive data interaction.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“Capturing data to make better decisions is an enterprise technology imperative that’s become increasingly critical as AI – which relies on quality data – revolutionizes every aspect of business,” said Juergen Mueller, SAP Chief Technology Officer and member of the Executive Board. “Our newest SAP Datasphere innovations, as well as an expanded partnership with Collibra, represent a quantum leap in our ability to help customers drive intelligent business transformations through data.”</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="deliver-seamless-and-scalable-access-to-mission-critical-business-data">Deliver seamless and scalable access to mission-critical business data</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/datasphere.html">Explore SAP Datasphere</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>At the heart of these announcements is the business data fabric, an architecture that helps ensure data is not just an asset but also the core underpinning of strategic initiatives. The innovations and partnership announced today equip organizations to deliver meaningful data to data consumers – with business context and logic intact.</p>
  <p>“We have decided to leverage SAP Datasphere for a modern business data fabric architecture in conjunction with our SAP S/4HANA landscape. It allows us to effectively establish a modern data analytics platform that enables a business self service capability on the basis of trusted data and data models,” said Achim Welter, Senior Director ERP, Digital &#x26; IT Strategy, Hershey’s.</p>
  <p>Today’s SAP Datasphere innovations help customers achieve a unified data view that simplifies their data landscapes while retaining context and logic – enabling them to adapt faster to market changes and make more-efficient decisions. From new copilot and vector database capabilities that help ensure business context remains constant in generative AI outputs to a new knowledge graph that helps uncover insights and patterns in complex data, SAP’s data innovations help ensure customers have the full power of their data at their fingertips.</p>
  <p>Today’s key innovations include:</p>
  <h2 id="generative-ai-copilot-and-ai-governance">Generative-AI Copilot and AI Governance</h2>
  <p>SAP’s generative-AI assistant, the <a href="https://www.sap.com/joule">Joule</a> copilot, is now coming to the SAP Analytics Cloud solution to automate the creation and development of reports, dashboards, plans and more. This automation is enabled by the <strong>SAP HANA Cloud vector engine capabilities,</strong> which combine the power of large language models with the relevant data of your organization – helping ensure business context is a constant for generative-AI outputs.</p>
  <p>Incorporating generative AI across the business isn’t possible without trusted and governed data. To provide organizations with a solution to govern the policies, processes and practices of AI, SAP is announcing an <strong>expansion of our partnership with Collibra</strong> to integrate Collibra’s AI Governance with SAP data assets. This can help provide transparency and accountability for organizations and help ensure regulatory, compliance and privacy policies are met.</p>
  <h2 id="discover-hidden-insights-and-patterns-with-knowledge-graph">Discover Hidden Insights and Patterns with Knowledge Graph</h2>
  <p>With the new <strong>SAP Datasphere knowledge graph,</strong> organizations can discover hidden insights and patterns across their applications and systems. This enables both technical and business users to deeply understand the relationships between data, metadata and business processes, as well as boost the effectiveness of machine learning and large language models.</p>
  <h2 id="unified-and-advanced-planning-and-analytics">Unified and Advanced Planning and Analytics</h2>
  <p>The new SAP Datasphere integration with SAP Analytics Cloud offers a single data management system and advanced analytics to power cross-organizational planning. Planners can leverage a single flexible model to break down silos between planning using one tool for data preparation, modeling and planning.</p>
  <p>Additionally, business users can use the <strong>new compass</strong> capability in SAP Analytics Cloud to realize better outcomes in planning and analytics through data-driven simulation. It enables organizations to run complex simulations using a chat interface to evaluate predictive outcomes and continually adjust controllable variables to find the optimal plan.</p>
  <p>This supports customers to transform their planning by unifying financial, operational, supply chain and workforce planning with native connection to SAP applications and third-party data.</p>
  <p>To learn more, please read: <strong><a href="/">Unleashing the Latest SAP Data and Analytics Innovations</a></strong>.</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="take-a-guided-tour-and-experience-firsthand-the-power-of-business-data-with-sap-datasphere">Take a guided tour and experience firsthand the power of business data with SAP Datasphere</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/datasphere/guided-experience.html">Start now</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><strong>About SAP</strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP’s strategy is to help every business run as an intelligent, sustainable enterprise. As a market leader in enterprise application software, we help companies of all sizes and in all industries run at their best: SAP customers generate 87% of total global commerce. Our machine learning, Internet of Things (IoT), and advanced analytics technologies help turn customers’ businesses into intelligent enterprises. SAP helps give people and organizations deep business insight and fosters collaboration that helps them stay ahead of their competition. We simplify technology for companies so they can consume our software the way they want – without disruption. Our end-to-end suite of applications and services enables business and public customers across 26 industries globally to operate profitably, adapt continuously, and make a difference. With a global network of customers, partners, employees, and thought leaders, SAP helps the world run better and improve people’s lives. For more information, visit <a href="http://www.sap.com">www.sap.com</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Note to editors:</strong><br>To preview and download broadcast-standard stock footage and press photos digitally, please visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/photos">www.sap.com/photos</a>. On this platform, you can find high resolution material for your media channels.</p>
  <p><strong>For customers interested in learning more about SAP products:</strong><br>Global Customer Center: +49 180 534-34-24<br>United States Only: 1 (800) 872-1SAP (1-800-872-1727)</p>
  <p><strong>For more information, press only:</strong><br>Julia Fargel, +1 (650) 276-8964, <a href="mailto:julia.fargel@sap.com">julia.fargel@sap.com</a>, PT<br>Martin Gwisdalla, +49 (6227) 767 275, <a href="mailto:martin.gwisdalla@sap.com">martin.gwisdalla@sap.com</a>, CET<br><a href="mailto:SAP%20Press%20Room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>This document contains forward-looking statements, which are predictions, projections, or other statements about future events. These statements are based on current expectations, forecasts, and assumptions that are subject to risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results and outcomes to materially differ. Additional information regarding these risks and uncertainties may be found in our filings with the Securities and Exchange Commission, including but not limited to the risk factors section of SAP’s 2023 Annual Report on Form 20-F.<br>© 2024 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.<br>Please consider our <a href="https://www.sap.com/corporate/en/legal/privacy.html">privacy policy</a>. If you received this press release in your e-mail and you wish to unsubscribe to our mailing list please contact <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a> and write Unsubscribe in the subject line.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-data-unleashed</category>
            <category>product/sap-datasphere</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Grow with the Latest SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition 2402 Update]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/sap-s4hana-cloud-public-edition-2402-update</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/sap-s4hana-cloud-public-edition-2402-update</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With the SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition 2402 update, we are bringing a new round of exciting innovations. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/enterprise-resource-planning</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>product/sap-intelligent-rpa</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/ux</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Generative AI-Enabled Developers Are the Architects of the Future]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/generative-ai-enabled-developers-architects-of-the-future</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/generative-ai-enabled-developers-architects-of-the-future</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Generative AI developers are the architects of the future. Learn how SAP is enabling every developer to become a business AI developer.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-build-code</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Generative AI’s "Show Me the Money" Moment]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2023/12/generative-ai-show-me-the-money-moment</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2023/12/generative-ai-show-me-the-money-moment</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Generative AI is having a moment, one where businesses are demanding tech vendors show them the actual business value. Learn why.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_126d4ceb40bb13e68189e442c513da0611b047fe1.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_126d4ceb40bb13e68189e442c513da0611b047fe1.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_126d4ceb40bb13e68189e442c513da0611b047fe1.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Generative AI’s “Show Me the Money” Moment" src="./media_126d4ceb40bb13e68189e442c513da0611b047fe1.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="generative-ais-show-me-the-money-moment">Generative AI’s “Show Me the Money” Moment</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>In a key scene from the 1996 movie “Jerry Maguire,” a pro football player is in the midst of contract negotiations with the Arizona Cardinals. He gets tired of his agent Jerry’s slick sales pitch and shouts at him in exasperation: “Show me the money!”</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>This is the very spot the world finds itself with <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/what-is-generative-ai.html">generative AI</a>. We’re past the hype and slick generative AI sales pitches.</p>
  <p>Business leaders now want results. They are demanding tech vendors show them the money — the actual business value delivered by generative AI.</p>
  <h2 id="the-big-picture">The Big Picture</h2>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="what-is-artificial-intelligence">What is artificial intelligence?</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/what-is-artificial-intelligence.html">Get an overview</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>At a macro level, generative AI’s impact on productivity could add trillions of dollars in value to the global economy. McKinsey’s latest research estimates that generative AI could add the equivalent of $2.6 trillion to $4.4 trillion annually across just the 63 use cases the consultancy firm analyzed — by comparison, the UK’s entire GDP in 2021 was $3.1 trillion.</p>
  <p>SAP is uniquely positioned to deliver on the promise of generative AI. We deliver the broadest suite of enterprise applications that maintain customers’ most mission-critical data. When this data is combined with the power of AI, it can truly revolutionize the way business runs.</p>
  <p>Here are just a few examples of how we’re already showing customers the money with generative AI.</p>
  <h2 id="supply-chain-automation">Supply Chain Automation</h2>
  <p>We’ve built generative AI into the SAP Transportation Management solution to speed up freight verification and documentation for manufacturing customers.</p>
  <p>This transforms a historically cumbersome task that’s often still done on paper into a quick, automated, and fully digitized process. Expediting freight processing time with this capability translates into real money, delivering nearly $1 million in annual savings at a single warehouse facility — a savings customers with multiple such facilities can realize many times over.</p>
  <h2 id="human-capital">Human Capital</h2>
  <p>Delta Air Lines is another customer working toward using SAP’s business AI. <a href="/2023/09/generative-ai-employee-experience-delta">Delta</a> is an early adopter of the talent intelligence hub built into SAP SuccessFactors. Delta Air Lines is developing a generative AI proof of concept slated to automatically transform generic skill descriptions into more accurate capabilities that reflect the job’s requirements based on real-world, updated employee and customer data in context.</p>
  <p>To help employees move from an hourly, customer-facing role to the salaried corporate position of their dreams, Delta Air Lines is building a dynamic, skills-based experience for continuous employee learning using the talent intelligence hub in SAP SuccessFactors solutions. Individual employees have a growth portfolio, which is a profile that includes their current skills and competencies mapped to formal and informal learning opportunities within and outside the organization, some recommended by AI-based algorithms.</p>
  <h2 id="intelligent-collections">Intelligent Collections</h2>
  <p>Suppliers always face the risk that some of their customers won’t pay on time. Late payments impact liquidity planning and working capital requirements.</p>
  <p>Collection management for SAP S/4HANA intelligently analyzes historical data and identifies customers and invoices with a higher risk for late payment. The solution reduces customer billing, credit, and collections costs. In one customer study, the solution enabled a consumer products producer with 30,000 employees to realize up to an extra $2.9 million in earnings annually.</p>
  <h2 id="natural-language-questions-quick-intelligent-answers">Natural Language Questions. Quick, Intelligent Answers</h2>
  <p>As these examples show, time is money. <a href="/topics/joule">Joule</a>, SAP’s generative AI copilot, helps customers save even more of it.</p>
  <p>It’s like tapping your smartest coworker on the shoulder to get instant and accurate insights. Users can ask plain-language questions of Joule, which pulls reliable and relevant information from across SAP’s cloud portfolio, instead of manually hunting for answers across systems.</p>
  <p>In one Joule test, information and insights about transactional data were achieved an average of 10 minutes faster compared to manual searching and analysis. For the user, that means more time available for higher level tasks. And, for the business, that adds up across the enterprise to real resource and cost savings.</p>
  <h2 id="whats-next">What’s Next</h2>
  <p>This is just the beginning. We can expect that 2024 will see generative AI solutions create even more value for customers around the world.</p>
  <p>We <a href="https://www.sap.com/events/teched/news-guide.html">recently launched a number of AI innovations</a> — from AI-infused coding tools to a one-stop shop to create generative AI extensions and applications — that give the developers at <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence/what-is-artificial-intelligence.html">the heart of the AI</a> revolution the tools they need to transform the way businesses run.</p>
  <p>Who knows? Soon Joule may be the one to tap you on the shoulder with an offer to “Help me help you!”</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Julia White is chief marketing and solutions officer and a member of the Executive Board of SAP SE.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="see-how-you-can-benefit-from-sap-business-ai-built-into-your-core-business-processes">See how you can benefit from SAP Business AI built into your core business processes</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/blog/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/blog/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/blog/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/blog/article-read-more</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/executive-blog</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[CTO Juergen Mueller at SAP TechEd: SAP at the Forefront of Generative AI Development]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/sap-teched-cto-juergen-mueller-generative-ai-development</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/sap-teched-cto-juergen-mueller-generative-ai-development</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[On stage at SAP TechEd, CTO Juergen Mueller shared the company’s bold vision to be the leading business AI company by 2025.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-teched</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/application-development</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-build</category>
            <category>product/sap-build-code</category>
            <category>product/sap-hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Supercharging Developer Productivity with SAP Build Code]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/sap-teched-2023-sap-build-code-supercharge-developer-productivity</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/sap-teched-2023-sap-build-code-supercharge-developer-productivity</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[At SAP TechEd Bangalore, SAP has announced SAP Build Code, a true game-changer for all SAP developers. Learn more about the new offering.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-teched</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/application-development</category>
            <category>news-tag/developers</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Debuts New CX Generative AI Capabilities to Enhance Customer Experiences and Boost Business Operations]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/new-cx-generative-ai-capabilities</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/new-cx-generative-ai-capabilities</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[From SAP Customer Experience LIVE, SAP has announced new generative AI capabilities for the CX solution portfolio. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>product/sap-customer-data-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-customer-experience</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-customer-experience-live</category>
            <category>product/sap-emarsys-customer-engagement</category>
            <category>product/sap-sales-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-service-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP SuccessFactors Second Half 2023 Release: AI-Driven Innovation to Ignite the Potential in Your Workforce]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/sap-successfactors-second-half-2023-release</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/sap-successfactors-second-half-2023-release</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Our SAP SuccessFactors second half 2023 release is full of AI innovation. Read to learn how we are applying it in our solutions.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-erp-hcm</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-work-zone</category>
            <category>news-tag/ux</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Three Highlights from SuccessConnect 2023]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/three-highlights-from-successconnect-2023</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/three-highlights-from-successconnect-2023</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SuccessConnect 2023 celebrated the HR community, discussed what AI means for the future of work, and shared ideas. Here are the highlights.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_19ceecf9802c64707f3aee1c60f9ef5908b6cd90d.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_19ceecf9802c64707f3aee1c60f9ef5908b6cd90d.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_19ceecf9802c64707f3aee1c60f9ef5908b6cd90d.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Three Highlights from SuccessConnect 2023" src="./media_19ceecf9802c64707f3aee1c60f9ef5908b6cd90d.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="three-highlights-from-successconnect-2023">Three Highlights from SuccessConnect 2023</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Thousands of attendees came to Las Vegas, Nevada, to celebrate the HR community, discuss what artificial intelligence (AI) means for the future of work, and share new ideas for how to ignite the potential within every workforce and business.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Indeed, from the mainstage keynote and breakout sessions to networking with customers and partners, AI was at the center of every conversation. If you weren’t able to attend this year’s event, you can catch the latest product announcements and select content now available <a href="https://go3.events.sap.com/successconnect/virtual/2023/reg/flow/sap/sc23/catalog/page/catalog?tab.sessionplanned=1692641568884001cZ9d">on demand</a>.</p>
  <p>Here are three takeaways from this year’s SuccessConnect.</p>
  <h2 id="the-time-is-now-to-adopt-ai">The Time Is Now to Adopt AI</h2>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="igniting-workforce-potential-with-the-new-sap-successfactors-ai-innovations">Igniting Workforce Potential with the New SAP SuccessFactors AI Innovations</h3>
        <p><em><a href="/2023/10/new-sap-successfactors-ai-innovations-successconnect">Read keynote coverage</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As the pace of technological innovation continues to accelerate, organizations face an incredible opportunity to explore new ways to get work done – ways that take engagement and productivity to new heights for everyone at work. Special guest <a href="https://go3.events.sap.com/successconnect/virtual/2023/reg/flow/sap/sc23/catalog/page/catalog/session/1695684941523001eAp3">Josh Bersin</a>, global industry analyst and CEO of The Josh Bersin Company, discussed the urgent need for companies to get on board with AI, emphasizing how AI can help keep companies ahead of the curve by transforming the employee experience. Bersin also shared ways to increase everyone’s knowledge and confidence when it comes to adopting AI, as well as the real economic benefits organizations can achieve based on early case studies.</p>
  <p>In addition, Julia White, member of the Executive Board of SAP SE and chief marketing and solutions officer, shared what AI means for businesses today and <a href="https://go3.events.sap.com/successconnect/virtual/2023/reg/flow/sap/sc23/catalog/page/catalog/session/1695684941478001eFQ4">how SAP is embedding AI into its cloud HR solutions</a>. She talked about the latest addition to SAP Business AI, <a href="/2023/09/joule-new-generative-ai-assistant">Joule</a> – a natural-language, generative AI copilot designed to help improve the experiences of everyone at work by making it easy for users to find information, get answers to questions, navigate processes, and complete tasks related to HR as well as finance, supply chain, and customer relationship management. She emphasized how Joule, with its AI-powered insight and assistance, can help organizations unlock new levels of performance, productivity, and efficiency.</p>
  <h2 id="talent-intelligence-is-key-to-closing-skills-gaps">Talent Intelligence Is Key to Closing Skills Gaps</h2>
  <p>The power of talent intelligence has far-reaching implications for how organizations can more accurately and efficiently evaluate talent across all levels and address skills gaps. During the event, there was a lot of buzz around the general availability of the <a href="/2023/10/skills-based-organization-talent-intelligence-hub">talent intelligence hub</a>, an AI-powered skills framework that’s built into the foundation of <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/solutions.html?campaigncode=CRM-YI23-HXM-2055448&#x26;source=text-glo-SAPNews">SAP SuccessFactors Human Experience Management (HXM) Suite</a>. Now organizations can have the power and simplicity of a single skills model to fuel everything from recruiting and onboarding to learning and development, as well as performance and succession.</p>
  <p>Sam Passman, vice president, Product Management at SAP SuccessFactors, provided a comprehensive overview of the <a href="https://go3.events.sap.com/successconnect/virtual/2023/reg/flow/sap/sc23/catalog/page/catalog/session/1695684941379001elme">talent intelligence hub</a>, including how organizations can better understand and leverage the skills of their workforce. “An organization that is not focused on skills is going to be left behind,” he said. “Customers often struggle with having visibility into their full skills picture and having employee profile data integrated throughout talent management processes. The talent intelligence hub is how we are making sure our customers can match the right people, doing the right work, at the right time – truly helping them become skills-based organizations.”</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="put-your-people-at-the-center-of-everything-with-sap-successfactors">Put your people at the center of everything with SAP SuccessFactors</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In addition, Tim Gregory, managing director of HR Innovation and Workforce Technology at <a href="https://go3.events.sap.com/successconnect/virtual/2023/reg/flow/sap/sc23/catalog/page/catalog/session/1695684941731001exmK">Delta Air Lines</a>, shared how the company is using SAP SuccessFactors solutions, including the talent intelligence hub, to create personalized career development plans for employees based not only on the skills most important to Delta but also each individual’s capabilities, strengths, and aspirations.</p>
  <p>Other sessions provided tips for becoming a skills-based organization and focused on <a href="https://go3.events.sap.com/successconnect/virtual/2023/reg/flow/sap/sc23/catalog/page/catalog/session/1693098679964001yjIr">how to get ready for the talent intelligence hub</a> and use it to help guide actions across all areas of talent management and development. And, of course, a live demonstration brought the talent intelligence hub to life as part of the <a href="https://go3.events.sap.com/successconnect/virtual/2023/reg/flow/sap/sc23/catalog/page/catalog/session/1692366446499001bBgm">SuccessConnect keynote</a>.</p>
  <h2 id="a-powerful-cloud-foundation-drives-true-hr-transformation">A Powerful Cloud Foundation Drives True HR Transformation</h2>
  <p>Having a cloud-based HR foundation is key for achieving true HR transformation – the kind of transformation that makes data-driven insights, smarter decision-making, automation, and a positive employee experience a reality. At the event, Mihael Sutalo, vice president, People Technology at <a href="https://go3.events.sap.com/successconnect/virtual/2023/reg/flow/sap/sc23/catalog/page/catalog/session/1695672921270001Czuo">Pandora</a>, the world’s leading jewelry brand, shared how the company is digitalizing HR and adopting new technologies to create amazing employee experiences as a unified, global company. “We wanted to scale to future-proof the company, and we believe strongly in the power of the cloud,” he said. He explained how Pandora has successfully moved from a fragmented HR landscape to SAP SuccessFactors HXM Suite, improving the company’s ability to attract and retain top talent.</p>
  <p>Avery Williams, manager of HR Operations Strategy at <a href="https://go3.events.sap.com/successconnect/virtual/2023/reg/flow/sap/sc23/catalog/page/catalog/session/1693098680331001ybtw">Starbucks Corporation</a>, also discussed how the company modernized its core HR technology, service delivery, and employee and partner experience by migrating 250,000 employees and partners from the legacy, on-premise SAP ERP Human Capital Management solution to a new cloud-based platform with <a href="https://go3.events.sap.com/successconnect/virtual/2023/reg/flow/sap/sc23/catalog/page/catalog/session/1695684941222001ejfa">SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central</a>.</p>
  <p>In addition, Todd Asevedo, GVP, chief expert, SAP, shared a host of best practices for how customers can minimize risk and disruption as they <a href="https://go3.events.sap.com/successconnect/virtual/2023/reg/flow/sap/sc23/catalog/page/catalog/session/1693098680290001ycKR">make the move</a> from SAP ERP HCM to the cloud. He also outlined the various deployment options to help organizations understand the transition paths available for a smooth migration.</p>
  <p>Couldn’t attend the in-person event? You can get the best of SuccessConnect wherever you are! Be sure to access the <a href="https://go3.events.sap.com/successconnect/virtual/2023/reg/flow/sap/sc23/catalog/page/catalog?tab.sessionplanned=1692641568884001cZ9d&#x26;search.sessiontype=sessionType_keynote">keynotes</a>, <a href="https://go3.events.sap.com/successconnect/virtual/2023/reg/flow/sap/sc23/catalog/page/catalog?tab.sessionplanned=1692641568884001cZ9d&#x26;search.sessiontype=1693097660680001RkSd&#x26;search.sessiontype=1695686379399001hUNT">customer success stories</a>, and <a href="https://go3.events.sap.com/successconnect/virtual/2023/reg/flow/sap/sc23/catalog/page/catalog?tab.sessionplanned=1692641568884001cZ9d&#x26;search.sessiontype=1679388717208002sub4">expert sessions</a>, including road maps, product demos, and more, all available <a href="https://go3.events.sap.com/successconnect/virtual/2023/reg/flow/sap/sc23/catalog/page/catalog?tab.sessionplanned=1692641568884001cZ9d">on demand</a>. Plus, don’t forget to sign up to stay informed about the <a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/nl/successconnect/index.html">SuccessConnect event in 2024</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Lara Albert is global vice president of Solution Marketing for SAP SuccessFactors.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-sap-news-delivered-right-to-your-inbox">Get the latest SAP news delivered right to your inbox</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/nl/sap-news-center-newsletter/index.html">Sign up now</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-employee-central</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
            <category>sap-event/successconnect</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Unveils New Generative AI Innovations That Boost Productivity and Effectiveness in Spend Management]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/sap-spend-connect-live-generative-ai-innovations-spend-management</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/10/sap-spend-connect-live-generative-ai-innovations-spend-management</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[From SAP Spend Connect Live in Vienna, SAP has introduced new business AI and UX innovations for spend management and business network.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>product/sap-ariba-category-management</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>product/sap-ariba-buying</category>
            <category>product/sap-ariba-contracts</category>
            <category>product/sap-ariba-sourcing</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-concur</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-spend-connect-live</category>
            <category>product/sap-spend-control-tower</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>