<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/sap-sports/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Kicking Off AI with SAP Sports One]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/ai-sap-sports-one-soccer-scouting-fc-bayern</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/ai-sap-sports-one-soccer-scouting-fc-bayern</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is expanding the SAP Sports One solution with with AI-powered scouting reporting. Learn more about the new features.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-sponsorships</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-sports</category>
            <category>product/sap-sports-one</category>
            <category>industry/sports-entertainment</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Welcomes Rising Star Leylah Fernandez as New Brand Ambassador]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/leylah-fernandez-new-sap-brand-ambassador</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/leylah-fernandez-new-sap-brand-ambassador</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP has announced a partnership with tennis star Leylah Fernandez, who embodies our values of excellence, determination, and social impact.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-sponsorships</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-sports</category>
            <category>news-tag/wta</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Champions the Cameron Champ Foundation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/videos/sap-champions-the-cameron-champ-foundation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/videos/sap-champions-the-cameron-champ-foundation</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Champions the Cameron Champ Foundation Click the button below to load the content from YouTube. Always allow YouTube As golf fans worldwide tune in...]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/video</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-sponsorships</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-sports</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP and the NHL Develop NHL Venue Metrics, a New Sustainability Platform to Help Reduce the League’s Ecological Impact]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/sap-nhl-develop-nhl-venue-metrics</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/sap-nhl-develop-nhl-venue-metrics</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP and the NHL have created a new platform called NHL Venue Metrics, powered by SAP. Learn more about the sustainability platform.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/nhl</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-hana-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-sponsorships</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-sports</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Brings Real-Time Analytics to One of the World’s Biggest Esports Tournaments]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/sap-international-11-esports-tournament-real-time-analytics</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/sap-international-11-esports-tournament-real-time-analytics</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[At The International 11 in Singapore, SAP BTP and SAP HANA Cloud are providing an enhanced viewing experience to broadcasts.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/esports</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-hana-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-sponsorships</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-sports</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Equestrian Dressage Goes Digital]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/equestrian-dressage-goes-digital</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/equestrian-dressage-goes-digital</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP partner Black Horse One has set out to shake up the status quo in equestrian dressage. Learn how they have revolutionized the sport.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11b7f833c2379c3550ebe7e9e5c34d3350e8c1307.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11b7f833c2379c3550ebe7e9e5c34d3350e8c1307.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_11b7f833c2379c3550ebe7e9e5c34d3350e8c1307.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Equestrian Dressage Goes Digital" src="./media_11b7f833c2379c3550ebe7e9e5c34d3350e8c1307.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="equestrian-dressage-goes-digital">Equestrian Dressage Goes Digital</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Equestrian dressage is an art. It takes a skilled eye and a thorough understanding of horse training to see and appreciate the small nuances that turn a ride into a truly great performance. Despite the high level of mastery required for the discipline and the international audience it attracts, dressage long remained stuck in a traditional environment — until SAP partner <a href="https://blackhorse-one.com/">Black Horse One</a> set out to shake up the status quo.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In dressage, horses must train for at least eight years before they compete in a top international class where they are scored by up to seven judges who provide marks on up to 37 elements of a performance. With complex and paper-based scoring, this process required dozens of support staff to note, collect, distribute, and calculate results. At times, official scores took longer to be announced than the competition took to move on to the next rider, limiting the experience for fans, commentators, and athletes alike.</p>
  <p>As media interest declined and audience engagement reduced to die-hard enthusiasts, the need for digitalization became clear.</p>
  <p>With the introduction of e-scoring, fan engagement apps, and a virtual training platform, Black Horse One has revolutionized equestrian sports since 2017.</p>
  <h2 id="innovation-success-streak">Innovation Success Streak</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-business-technology-platform-accelerate-business-outcomes-with-integration-data-to-value-and-extensibility">SAP Business Technology Platform: Accelerate business outcomes with integration, data to value, and extensibility</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Together with the <a href="https://www.fei.org/">International Equestrian Federation (FEI)</a> and renowned dressage judge Katrina Wuest, Black Horse One collaborated with SAP to develop and enhance a rich portfolio of innovative applications – based on SAP HANA Cloud and powered by SAP Business Technology Platform.</p>
  <p><strong>eDressage™</strong> has successfully transformed paper-based processes into a digital and sustainable judging solution that enables real-time, on-the-go results. With digital scoresheets, freestyle flow analyses, standardized scoring, and a new dressage dashboard, users can compare the performance of horses at multiple events and from the perspective of different judges to identify areas for improvement.</p>
  <p>The <strong>Spectator Judging®</strong> mobile app has tapped into audiences both on-site and at home for the first time, making fan engagement an integral part of the event. The app places users in the judging seat with the ability to co-score competitions alongside official judges and see predictions displayed in real-time on arena screens. The FEI has since adapted the concept to bring dressage into the world of fantasy sports via a dedicated ‘FEI eLeague’ for each FEI Dressage World Cup™ season.</p>
  <p>“Choosing the SAP Business Technology Platform for our central services meant that we efficiently and effortlessly scaled with the demand. Today, more than half of all international dressage shows use our solutions,” said Daniel Goehlen founder of Black Horse One, alumni of the Technical University of Munich, and Grand Prix level dressage rider. “We strive to provide additional value on top of the data already received, and with new possibilities arising through machine learning, we will help to bring even more stats and analytics to fans in creative ways.”</p>
  <h2 id="training-at-home-with-expert-advice">Training at Home with Expert Advice</h2>
  <p>When the <a href="/covid-19">pandemic</a> hit, riders found themselves with few options to stay connected to the equestrian community or continue their training and development. Black Horse One and SAP bridged this gap by introducing an <strong>online training platform</strong> called “Equestrian on Demand” to the FEI and various national federations. The platform allows athletes to upload videos of their rides for review by highly qualified judges and trainers worldwide. The valuable feedback attained has quickly evolved the tool into an invaluable companion for riders of all levels.</p>
  <p>SAP employee Nadja Mayer recently had the opportunity to test the German National Federation (FN) version of the platform called “FN Level Up” to receive training tips from her idol <strong>Ingrid Klimke</strong>, SAP ambassador and Olympic champion.</p>
  <p>“It was a great experience to seamlessly receive Ingrid’s virtual feedback on my showjumping. As a rider it’s amazing to know SAP technology is also supporting my sports passions,” Mayer says.</p>
  <p>Watch the value of the platform brought to life below:</p>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1fab44dd6c6b13d12d2aeca19e350551c59545ecd.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1fab44dd6c6b13d12d2aeca19e350551c59545ecd.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1fab44dd6c6b13d12d2aeca19e350551c59545ecd.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="FN Level Up / INGRID KLIMKE reviews my ride" src="./media_1fab44dd6c6b13d12d2aeca19e350551c59545ecd.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JGOFnGtpA-A">FN Level Up / INGRID KLIMKE reviews my ride</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>To learn more about SAP technology in equestrian sports, visit the <a href="http://www.sap.com/sponsorships?campaigncode=CRM-XH21-OSP-Equestr">SAP Global Sponsorships page</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Henrike Paetz is head of Equestrian Partners for Global Sponsorships at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-sponsorships</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-sports</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP and League of Legends European Championships (LEC) Bring Live Data to E-Sports Fans]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/league-of-legends-european-championships-live-data-e-sports-fans</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/league-of-legends-european-championships-live-data-e-sports-fans</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 13 Aug 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Together, SAP and League of Legends European Championship will integrate statistics into live streams available to broadcasters and fans.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17530aac09964ec4239bdc9d178a5a7001b29d545.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17530aac09964ec4239bdc9d178a5a7001b29d545.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_17530aac09964ec4239bdc9d178a5a7001b29d545.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP and League of Legends European Championships (LEC) Bring Live Data to E-Sports Fans" src="./media_17530aac09964ec4239bdc9d178a5a7001b29d545.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-and-league-of-legends-european-championships-lec-bring-live-data-to-e-sports-fans">SAP and League of Legends European Championships (LEC) Bring Live Data to E-Sports Fans</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="start-an-sap-hana-cloud-trial-today">Start an SAP HANA Cloud trial today</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hana/cloud-trial.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today said that it is partnering with the League of Legends European Championship (LEC) to integrate statistics into live streams available to broadcasters and fans during the summer finals.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>These never-before-available insights will enable broadcasters to provide in-depth analysis to enhance the fan experience.</p>
  <p>Each live broadcast will provide innovative insights for fans and commentators, allowing them to make sense of the pros’ decisions throughout each phase of the match. By comparing structured historical game data stored in <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hana/cloud.html">SAP HANA Cloud</a> against live data using real-time data processing, player actions are put in context for players and fans.</p>
  <p>“There is no doubt SAP has carried over its vast knowledge and experience in enterprise application software into our world of e-sports,” LEC Senior Manager Zeynep Gencaga said. “SAP’s engineers have worked tirelessly with our team to help simplify the visualization of statistics to further nourish our LEC storylines, giving an extra edge to every little bit of data for our fans.”</p>
  <p>Since 2018, SAP has been innovating to bring more industry expertise to the LEC Tournament.</p>
  <p>Broadcasters and fans alike will see three analytical visualizations, providing analysis of games as they happen. With the enriched stats, broadcasters get valuable insights for better storytelling and engagement with their audience. Fans can expect to see stats around key game elements such as the use of items, time to complete an objective, and overall player performance records.</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="http://news.sap.com/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP on Twitter at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Media Contacts:</strong> Reid Strohmeier, +1 (646) 280-9290, <a href="mailto:reid.strohmeier@sap.com">reid.strohmeier@sap.com</a>, ET<br>Lisa Buehn, +49 15167834297, <a href="mailto:lisa.buehn@sap.com">lisa.buehn@sap.com</a>, CET<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>Any statements contained in this document that are not historical facts are forward-looking statements as defined in the U.S. Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995. Words such as “anticipate,” “believe,” “estimate,” “expect,” “forecast,” “intend,” “may,” “plan,” “project,” “predict,” “should” and “will” and similar expressions as they relate to SAP are intended to identify such forward-looking statements. SAP undertakes no obligation to publicly update or revise any forward-looking statements. All forward-looking statements are subject to various risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results to differ materially from expectations. The factors that could affect SAP’s future financial results are discussed more fully in SAP’s filings with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (“SEC”), including SAP’s most recent Annual Report on Form 20-F filed with the SEC. Readers are cautioned not to place undue reliance on these forward-looking statements, which speak only as of their dates.<br>© 2021 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-hana-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-sponsorships</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-sports</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Business Technology Platform Raises Equestrians to a New Level]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/05/sap-btp-riding-simulator-new-level-equestrians</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/05/sap-btp-riding-simulator-new-level-equestrians</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 May 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP has developed a dashboard for a riding simulator at Walldorf Riding Club. With SAP BTP, equestrian data can be analyzed and depicted.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1227288b9460c12a53b5dcc67953e8e47b4df2c8a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1227288b9460c12a53b5dcc67953e8e47b4df2c8a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1227288b9460c12a53b5dcc67953e8e47b4df2c8a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Business Technology Platform Raises Equestrians to a New Level" src="./media_1227288b9460c12a53b5dcc67953e8e47b4df2c8a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-business-technology-platform-raises-equestrians-to-a-new-level">SAP Business Technology Platform Raises Equestrians to a New Level</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div>As an advocate of equestrian sport for almost 10 years, SAP took another step to combine technology and sports with SAP Business Technology Platform.</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In 2019, the <a href="https://www.reit-und-rennverein-walldorf.de/">Walldorf Riding Club (RRV)</a>, working with SAP, introduced the <a href="https://www.reitsimulator-walldorf.de/#konzept">Racewood Simulator</a> to its students and teachers – a robot horse that reproduces horses’ movements in virtual training sessions. The so-called “Sir Waldo” is programmed to simulate several disciplines, such as dressage, jumping, and cross-country riding, and closely examine the saddle’s weight distribution. Furthermore, it guides riders in positioning their legs and reins. This technical innovation is located in the <a href="/2020/09/sap-equestrian-experience-center-riding-simulator">SAP Equestrian Experience Center</a> that borders the RRV riding area. That way, it is easily accessible for club members.</p>
  <p>By providing a controlled environment, beginners and professional equestrians get the chance to practice and improve their skills in a simulated training and competition setting. In close cooperation with professional trainers and guest lecturers, the riding club offers this new experience in various forms to a broad target group. The club also provides specific courses such as fear management and mental training for traumatized riders.</p>
  <p>This kind of simulation is a pioneer project in Germany. It shows the desire of the RRV to innovate, offer its members the best possible conditions, develop as a riding club, and continuously improve riders’ skills.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-equestrian-experience-center-innovative-technology-makes-sports-tangible">SAP Equestrian Experience Center: Innovative Technology Makes Sports Tangible</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="/2020/09/sap-equestrian-experience-center-riding-simulator">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="improving-training-analysis-with-sap-technology">Improving Training Analysis with SAP Technology</h2>
  <p>The initial simulator only allowed for a small data set per riding session, which was available in a printed version. This document didn’t provide all the information users needed to determine further training behaviors. Users exhibited a strong demand for detailed training information to analyze their progress and potential learning gaps to inform long-term training plans.</p>
  <p>To fully exploit the technical possibilities of the riding simulator, the SAP Global Sponsorships team connected with <a href="https://experience.sap.com/designservices/">SAP AppHaus</a> and <a href="https://blackhorse-one.com/">Black Horse One GmbH</a> to design an extensive training app using <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">SAP Business Technology Platform</a>.</p>
  <p><em>Technical Realization of the Solution</em></p>
  <p>Within two remote workshops, the SAP team applied <a href="https://experience.sap.com/designservices/approach">design thinking methods</a> and gained knowledge about every critical aspect of the project, such as the technical framework of the Racewood Simulator, user needs, and first solution approaches. The project team identified the need to collect and summarize valuable data from the Racewood Simulator and transform it into understandable analysis visualization. To reach that goal, the team leveraged <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/extension-suite.html">SAP Extension Suite</a>. With this technology, they could build the Riding Simulator Analysis Portal, the base of the application.</p>
  <p>The future Web-based solution will provide detailed training data in four main categories: seating analysis, dressage, jumping, and cross-country riding. These classifications contain several vital facts, such as program analysis (balance, reins, thighs), freeriding, and progress. Thereby, users can track their riding proficiency in detail, identify areas of improvement, and better their skills efficiently. In addition, notes and homework can be saved by students and teachers.</p>
  <p>To save individual training results and protect them from third parties, authentication and a single sign-on are guaranteed by <a href="https://www.sapstore.com/solutions/40132/SAP-Cloud-Identity-Services">SAP Cloud Identity Services</a> and stored in SAP Cloud Application Programming Model, based on <a href="https://www.sap.com/germany/products/hana/cloud.html">SAP HANA Cloud</a>.</p>
  <p>Aileen Trunk, a rider at RRV, said, “The new SAP training app gives both trainers and learners valuable insights and helps to optimize training across all disciplines – dressage, jumping and cross-country riding. I am now able to analyze my simulator sessions in detail with a wide range of possibilities. At any time, my trainer can prepare my units effectively and we can review and work on my short-term and long-term development together.”</p>
  <p><em>User interface of the new riding simulator dashboard</em></p>
  <h2 id="future-digitalization-of-equestrian-sports">Future Digitalization of Equestrian Sports</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-business-technology-platform-accelerate-business-outcomes-with-integration-data-to-value-and-extensibility">SAP Business Technology Platform: Accelerate business outcomes with integration, data to value, and extensibility</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Currently, the seating analysis is already used in training and the other components are planned for development and will be introduced soon. Thanks to the new application built on SAP Business Technology Platform, training data can be accessed and analyzed from anywhere, can be used in upcoming training units, and will pave the way for lasting progress.</p>
  <p>“The Racewood Equestrian Simulator is a great means to showcase the excitement of the sport to all interested audiences,” said Thomas Esser, innovation manager with SAP Global Sponsorships. “In particular, it is amazing to see how riders can now leverage the digital horse and take advantage of technologies like SAP HANA Cloud and SAP Business Technology Platform to bring their training to next level.”</p>
  <p>Once again, SAP has laid the foundation for next-level equestrian sports, providing virtual solutions and 100% paperless work. No doubt, the team looks forward to identifying new projects with the Walldorf equestrians in the future.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h2 id="key-results">Key Results</h2>
        <ul>
          <li>Detailed depiction of training analysis</li>
          <li>Enhanced training outcome through efficient usage of data</li>
          <li>Improved user interface to draw meaningful conclusions</li>
          <li>100% paperless work</li>
        </ul>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-apphaus</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-sponsorships</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-sports</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Innovative Insights Available for NHL Coaches Through SAP-NHL Coaching Insights App for iPad]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/sap-nhl-coaching-insights-innovative-coaches</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/04/sap-nhl-coaching-insights-innovative-coaches</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[New and significant enhancements to the SAP-NHL Coaching Insights app further simplify UX and expand on critical metrics desired by coaches.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/nhl</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-hana-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-sponsorships</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-sports</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Teams Up with Olympic Triathlon Gold Medalist and IRONMAN World Champion Jan Frodeno]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/03/jan-frodeno-brand-ambassador-sap-btp</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/03/jan-frodeno-brand-ambassador-sap-btp</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Jan Frodeno, one of the world’s most renowned and successful triathletes, is SAP's newest brand ambassador. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-sponsorships</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-sports</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP and Sloane Stephens Foundation Empower the Next Generation of Tennis Players On and Off the Court]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/03/sloane-stephens-foundation-empower-next-generation-tennis-players</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/03/sloane-stephens-foundation-empower-next-generation-tennis-players</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Together, SAP and the Sloane Stephens Foundation are working to create greater opportunity for all through a shared vision. Learn how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_174b4b46a75a3a696caf877d55ae5d8080977f8b9.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_174b4b46a75a3a696caf877d55ae5d8080977f8b9.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_174b4b46a75a3a696caf877d55ae5d8080977f8b9.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP and Sloane Stephens Foundation Empower the Next Generation of Tennis Players On and Off the Court" src="./media_174b4b46a75a3a696caf877d55ae5d8080977f8b9.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-and-sloane-stephens-foundation-empower-the-next-generation-of-tennis-players-on-and-off-the-court">SAP and Sloane Stephens Foundation Empower the Next Generation of Tennis Players On and Off the Court</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Professional WTA player and U.S. Open Champion <a href="https://sloanestephens.com/">Sloane Stephens’</a> powerful play is felt both on the court and in the communities she supports. She first picked up a racket as a nine-year-old on the public courts of South Florida, recognizing from a young age the power of tennis and the happiness and confidence it can bring to players. However, it quickly dawned on her how the cost to play can create greater inequality and barriers.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>As Stephens’ professional tennis career took off, she established the <strong>Sloane Stephens Foundation</strong> (<a href="https://sloanestephensfoundation.org/">SSF</a>) in 2013 to create an impact in Compton, California, nearby where she regularly trains, as well as in the South Florida community where she first learned her life’s passion and still resides. The foundation provides educational opportunities and encourages healthy lifestyles for underserved youth to enable them to dream and achieve big, on and off the tennis court. SSF also strives to counter limiting factors such as inequitable academic opportunities, poverty, and community violence while cultivating a new generation of tennis players.</p>
  <p>As a long-time partner of the Women’s Tennis Association (WTA), SAP is joining forces with the foundation to create greater opportunity for all through a shared vision: believing that tennis and sport have the power to change lives, and that all kids deserve access to quality education and are capable of achieving incredible things when given the opportunity.</p>
  <p>“When I started playing tennis, I didn’t realize how expensive a racket or balls were. So I started the foundation to not only break down those financial barriers to a sport that’s always given me joy, but to also help kids live healthy lifestyles and have equal access to education through tutoring and mentorship,” Stephens said. “I’m grateful to SAP for joining us on this journey, providing invaluable resources to make a unique impact on youth in the South Florida and Compton communities.”</p>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ef02b6c837a5c9f6546f7031e0d0c90ffe3f08b6.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1ef02b6c837a5c9f6546f7031e0d0c90ffe3f08b6.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1ef02b6c837a5c9f6546f7031e0d0c90ffe3f08b6.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Joins Forces with the Sloane Stephens Foundation" src="./media_1ef02b6c837a5c9f6546f7031e0d0c90ffe3f08b6.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://youtu.be/Cq7jT8tUz1s">SAP Joins Forces with the Sloane Stephens Foundation</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP will support the foundation by assisting with the formalization of a high-performance tennis program in South Florida and providing crucial program support to the existing Love, Love Compton program, as the team works to expand capacity during the safe return to in-person programming in order to combat learning loss.</p>
  <p>“Sloane’s ambition for her foundation perfectly aligns with our core values and purpose — to improve people’s lives in our local and global communities,” said Judith Williams, chief diversity and inclusion officer at SAP. “We support SSF’s mission of fostering equality for all through quality education and overall health and well-being and we are honored to support SSF as they empower underserved youth to follow their dreams.”</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d4fb1b24fd59d322a7069fa9323559ba81f967bf.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d4fb1b24fd59d322a7069fa9323559ba81f967bf.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1d4fb1b24fd59d322a7069fa9323559ba81f967bf.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Group Selfie: Diversity Camp with Sloane Stephens" src="./media_1d4fb1b24fd59d322a7069fa9323559ba81f967bf.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2000" height="1500">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p><em>Photo courtesy of the Sloane Stephens Foundation</em></p>
  <p>Since inception, 100% of SSF students have graduated high school and successfully gone on to a two- or four-year higher-education institution. Additionally, 100% of summer camp students have maintained or improved their grade-level reading abilities. However, <a href="/covid-19">COVID-19</a> has shaken the status quo of the education system. Everything from lacking reliable WiFi to not having a device or parents at home to help navigate video conferencing makes existing inequities even more significant.</p>
  <p>“As the world moves forward and continues to recover, it is crucial that no one is left behind,” said SSF Executive Director Dr. Sybil Smith, Ed.D. “SAP understands the importance of putting people first and will not only help us combat learning loss but also create opportunity through learning and development for all.”</p>
  <p>Since 2013, SAP has worked with the WTA and others across the tennis community to provide innovative technology that helps advance and grow the sport around the world. Read more stories about <a href="/topics/wta">SAP’s involvement in women’s tennis here</a>.</p>
  <h3 id="more-information-on-the-sloane-stephens-foundation-is-available-at-sloanestephensfoundationorg">More information on the Sloane Stephens Foundation is available at <a href="https://sloanestephensfoundation.org/">sloanestephensfoundation.org</a>.</h3>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="watch-the-socially-conscious-sports-episode-from-the-blank-canvas-original-series-by-sap">Watch the socially conscious sports episode from the Blank Canvas original series by SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://insights.sap.com/conversations/blank-canvas-sports-social-issues/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Bonnie Rothenstein is vice president of Global Sponsorships at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-sponsorships</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-sports</category>
            <category>news-tag/wta</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[FC Bayern Implements SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central to Improve Digital HR Capabilities]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/fc-bayern-sap-successfactors-employee-central</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/fc-bayern-sap-successfactors-employee-central</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP SuccessFactors at FC Bayern is helping standardize and optimize core HR processes and improve the experience for 1,000+ employees.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17221bbf506e9a85143673ed151423bc1bd1e1fd2.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_17221bbf506e9a85143673ed151423bc1bd1e1fd2.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_17221bbf506e9a85143673ed151423bc1bd1e1fd2.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="FC Bayern Implements SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central to Improve Digital HR Capabilities" src="./media_17221bbf506e9a85143673ed151423bc1bd1e1fd2.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="fc-bayern-implements-sap-successfactors-employee-central-to-improve-digital-hr-capabilities">FC Bayern Implements SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central to Improve Digital HR Capabilities</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>MUNICH</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced that FC Bayern, Germany’s most winning football club, has successfully implemented the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/employee-central-hris.html?btp=74873987-7925-4fc0-8240-97dea52648e4">SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central</a> solution to standardize and optimize its core human resource (HR) processes and improve the experience for its 1,000+ employees.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>By leveraging the <a href="https://www.sap.com/services/implementation/preconfigured-industry-solutions.html">SAP Model Company</a> service for accelerated solution deployment, FC Bayern benefitted from ready-to-use, preconfigured processes and best practices.</p>
  <p>Part of <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm/human-experience.html">SAP SuccessFactors Human Experience Management Suite</a>, SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central is a cloud-based human resource information system that organizations use to manage global workforces with all core HR functions.</p>
  <p>With the implementation of SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central, FC Bayern has moved from spreadsheets and manual processes to a fully integrated platform. This allows for consistent and digital HR processes and will unify data across recruiting, onboarding and performance management in the future. In addition, reports can be generated easily and efficiently for optimized workforce planning and analytics.</p>
  <p>“The SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central solution enables FC Bayern’s HR team to do what it does best — focus on strategic, value-added HR rather than transactional processes,” FC Bayern Executive Vice Chairman Jan-Christian Dreesen said. “Before implementing the solution, we worked with legacy, time-consuming processes. The integration has enabled us not only to digitalize our processes but also to innovate and redesign them. By creating a more efficient environment, our HR team can prioritize on delivering the best employee experience possible.”</p>
  <p>SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central includes self-service options to help increase employee engagement at FC Bayern. The <a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/oth/sapsuccessfactors-mobile-app/index.html">SAP SuccessFactors Mobile</a> app provides all employees — including players, coaches, managers and office employees — with a modern, intuitive mobile experience. They can access their personal data and update their employee profiles as well as enter, approve and record absences such as vacations — all tasks that previously required them to reach out to HR for approval.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-successfactors-shift-from-transactional-hcm-to-end-to-end-experiences">SAP SuccessFactors: Shift from transactional HCM to end-to-end experiences</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="hear-how-fc-bayern-employees-have-shaped-the-clubs-story-for-decades-of-success">Hear how FC Bayern employees have shaped the club’s story for decades of success:</h3>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18a9729a6cec4a11cb227a043055cf075e7ff7cd4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18a9729a6cec4a11cb227a043055cf075e7ff7cd4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_18a9729a6cec4a11cb227a043055cf075e7ff7cd4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="FC Bayern: Success is built on many shoulders" src="./media_18a9729a6cec4a11cb227a043055cf075e7ff7cd4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://youtu.be/DytM11OKogA">FC Bayern: Success is built on many shoulders</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“With the implementation of SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central, we are happy to open a new chapter in the long-standing partnership between FC Bayern and SAP,” said Andreas Jung, FC Bayern Executive Board member.</p>
  <p>“Since 2014, SAP has been an official platinum partner of FC Bayern, working together to innovative solutions that help the club reach its sports and business goals,” said Thomas Saueressig, member of the SAP Executive Board, Product Engineering. “The go-live of SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central extends this partnership to human experience management, enabling the sports club to further accelerate its growth and remain competitive at all times, both on and off the field.”</p>
  <p>For more information, visit the <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm.html">HR and People Engagement area of SAP.com</a> and the <a href="/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP on Twitter at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Media Contacts:</strong> Dana Rösiger, +49 6227 7 63900, <a href="mailto:dana.roesiger@sap.com">dana.roesiger@sap.com</a>, CET<br>Samantha Yerks, +1 (914) 918-6087, <a href="mailto:samantha.yerks@sap.com">samantha.yerks@sap.com</a>, ET<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>Any statements contained in this document that are not historical facts are forward-looking statements as defined in the U.S. Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995. Words such as “anticipate,” “believe,” “estimate,” “expect,” “forecast,” “intend,” “may,” “plan,” “project,” “predict,” “should” and “will” and similar expressions as they relate to SAP are intended to identify such forward-looking statements. SAP undertakes no obligation to publicly update or revise any forward-looking statements. All forward-looking statements are subject to various risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results to differ materially from expectations. The factors that could affect SAP’s future financial results are discussed more fully in SAP’s filings with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (“SEC”), including SAP’s most recent Annual Report on Form 20-F filed with the SEC. Readers are cautioned not to place undue reliance on these forward-looking statements, which speak only as of their dates.<br>© 2021 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-news</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-sponsorships</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-sports</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-employee-central</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Game, Set, Stat! SAP Announces Kamau Murray as Newest SAP Ambassador]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/kamau-murray-newest-sap-ambassador</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/kamau-murray-newest-sap-ambassador</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Kamau Murray is SAP's newest tennis ambassador. Hear from him about his incredible journey to becoming a top coach in the WTA today.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_174b4b46a75a3a696caf877d55ae5d8080977f8b9.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_174b4b46a75a3a696caf877d55ae5d8080977f8b9.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_174b4b46a75a3a696caf877d55ae5d8080977f8b9.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Game, Set, Stat! SAP Announces Kamau Murray as Newest SAP Ambassador" src="./media_174b4b46a75a3a696caf877d55ae5d8080977f8b9.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="game-set-stat-sap-announces-kamau-murray-as-newest-sap-ambassador">Game, Set, Stat! SAP Announces Kamau Murray as Newest SAP Ambassador</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Ahead of next week’s Australian Open, SAP is thrilled to partner with Kamau Murray, the brand’s newest tennis ambassador. Murray has had an incredible journey to become one of the top coaches in the Women’s Tennis Association (WTA) today.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Growing up in Chicago, Murray was an active participant in Chicago Park District tennis programs, learning firsthand the value of introducing athletics at an early age to instill sportsmanship, strong work ethics, self-confidence, and peer interaction, along with other important life lessons. He excelled in this environment and was subsequently offered a full scholarship to play tennis at Florida A&#x26;M University.</p>
  <p>In 2004, Murray returned to his early roots by offering tennis lessons to children. He knew that there was a continued need for a program within local communities.</p>
  <p>Four years later, he became the founder of XS Tennis and Education Foundation. Today, XS Tennis continues to transform many lives by combining Murray’s passions for tennis and education. Murray’s initial five students have gone on to win national championships, IHSA state championships, and two Junior Olympic Gold medals, while 100% of the program’s graduating seniors have received college tennis scholarships to top universities.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_181b35060c534eb1cf90a38376a8f3592dfa08319.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_181b35060c534eb1cf90a38376a8f3592dfa08319.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_181b35060c534eb1cf90a38376a8f3592dfa08319.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Kamau Murray" src="./media_181b35060c534eb1cf90a38376a8f3592dfa08319.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2500" height="3200">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <p><em>Image courtesy of the WTA</em></p>
  <p>Murray’s community work and reputation for growing youth into top college tennis players later caught the attention of rising star Sloane Stephens, which created a new path for him to become a WTA coach. In 2017, Murray coached Stephens to an historic US Open title, where he become only the third African American coach to win a grand slam in its 95-year history.</p>
  <p>To celebrate the start of this new partnership, SAP caught up with Kamau Murray to discuss his passion for tennis, his experiences coaching Sloane Stephens, and the importance of technology and analytics in today’s game.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="watch-the-blank-canvas-episode-on-socially-conscious-sports">Watch the Blank Canvas episode on socially conscious sports</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://insights.sap.com/conversations/blank-canvas-sports-social-issues/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="q-you-started-playing-tennis-at-the-early-age-of-seven-in-the-inner-city-of-chicago-can-you-tell-us-what-motivated-you-to-pick-up-the-racket-and-play">Q: You started playing tennis at the early age of seven in the inner city of Chicago. Can you tell us what motivated you to pick up the racket and play?</h3>
  <p><strong>A:</strong> In 1998, my parents took 20 youth to Africa for a cultural exchange program. When we returned to the United States, all the summer camps and programs were full and not accepting students. My godfather was an avid tennis player and told my mom that the camp at Jesse Owens Park was still accepting. My mom quickly drove by the park to inquire. She asked the coach what the cost was for the rest of the summer. When the coach told her it was only $12, I remember her quickly turning around and saying, “Boy get out of the car.”</p>
  <p>Once I got a taste of the game that summer, I became hooked and continued playing five days a week during the school year. From that point on, tennis became a major part of my life and provided me with a unique identity.</p>
  <h3 id="you-certainly-are-driven-on-and-off-the-court-in-2005-you-founded-the-xs-tennis-program-to-help-chicagos-underserved-youth-through-a-community-based-academic-sports-enrichment-program-what-is-your-biggest-accomplishment-thus-far-with-the-xs-program">You certainly are driven on and off the court. In 2005, you founded the XS Tennis program to help Chicago’s underserved youth through a community-based academic, sports enrichment program. What is your biggest accomplishment thus far with the XS program?</h3>
  <p>By far our biggest accomplishment is the students who have gone on to earn tennis scholarships to college. I witnessed firsthand the impact a college education can have on children in urban communities. I also understand that once you get on campus it’s hard to stay there.</p>
  <p>When a student earns a scholarship, they gain access to all the benefits that come with that, including free tutoring, a coach, and an athletic department that monitors graduation rates and GPAs. That support system is critical. To date, more than 55 students from XS have been able to play tennis at the collegiate level with access to a strong support system.</p>
  <p>In addition to our students playing tennis in college, we have also touched the lives of more than 1,000 students for four years in a row. There are more youth playing tennis on the south side of Chicago than ever before. I strongly believe that for tennis to grow globally, the growth needs to come from the minority community specifically. It’s our greatest challenge, but it’s also our biggest opportunity.</p>
  <h3 id="this-isnt-your-first-time-coaching-sloane-what-makes-your-partnership-so-special-on-and-off-the-court">This isn’t your first-time coaching Sloane. What makes your partnership so special on and off the court?</h3>
  <p>I think the key to any successful partnership is trust on and off the court. My partnership with Sloane got off to a great start in 2016 when she won three tournaments in four months. Previously she had only won one title in her career.</p>
  <p>I witnessed how tough she was and how well she handled the pressure in those finals. I also saw her ability to execute a plan, at times where a lot of players just revert to their lifelong tendencies. Those three quick titles allowed me to gain her trust a lot sooner than expected. Sloane knows that any advice or coaching I provide is well informed.</p>
  <p>What has kept us together for so long is our ability to make the work and the travel fun. Tennis has the longest season of any sport, so if you don’t like the person, you will not be able to stand each other for 32 weeks of the year.</p>
  <h3 id="what-is-your-overall-view-of-technology-innovation-in-sport-and-more-specifically-in-tennis-in-the-future-what-technology-would-help-you-even-more-as-a-coach">What is your overall view of technology innovation in sport and more specifically in tennis? In the future, what technology would help you even more as a coach?</h3>
  <p>The use of “in-game” technology and immediate feedback allows tennis players to adjust quicker, creating closer matches, which ultimately makes our sport more fun to watch. On the women’s side, you now see a lot of coaches using tablets and stats on the sideline. If you couple that with the allowed on-court coaching visits, we are seeing a lot of younger players having success earlier because they are now able to access coaching that closes the gap between them and the veteran opponents on the other side of the net. That can be 100% attributed to the immediate value from technology and statistics. It has created a few unlikely champions. The other part of this is that the veteran players who have played a lot of matches on big stadium courts equipped with all the cameras and technology have more data points for the younger players to study.</p>
  <p>From a training perspective, technology has taken a lot of the guesswork away. Historically, players would condition their bodies to get in good general shape without knowing exactly what that means. Now, the data can tell you how many miles are run during a match and how many feet are run during an average point so you can train your body to perform at that level in a more precise fashion.</p>
  <p>In post-match coaching situations, technology makes these conversations easier for both parties. In the past, the player says: “I feel I did this,” and the coach says: “I feel like you did that” — oftentimes resulting in a back-and-forth dialogue that lasts well into the next day. Now, SAP data is available immediately and by the time the player gets done showering, the conversation and adjustments will be based on fact, and less on feelings.</p>
  <h3 id="whats-next-on-the-horizon-for-you">What’s next on the horizon for you?</h3>
  <p>In 2021, my primary goal is to help Sloane return to the top 20. Innovation doesn’t only come in the form of technology. Players also must innovate and develop new skills to change alongside a sport that changes every six months. From year to year, the rackets are becoming more powerful, the balls are getting heavier, strings are creating more spin. My goal this year is to continue to add little innovations to Sloane’s game.</p>
  <p>Secondly, as an SAP ambassador, my goal is to continue to innovate with the WTA and SAP to increase usage of data insights available to all players and coaches.</p>
  <p>I am thrilled to work more closely with the WTA to continue to make the game more accessible and more attractive, and to reach a broader audience. They say the tide rises all ships. The more we can grow the participation and popularity of the sport, the better it becomes for everyone.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Bonnie Rothenstein is vice president of Global Sponsorships at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/discrete-industries</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-sponsorships</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-sports</category>
            <category>news-tag/wta</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Driving Change On and Off the Golf Course]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/cameron-champ-driving-change-equality</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/02/cameron-champ-driving-change-equality</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP and its newest golf ambassador, Cameron Champ, are teaming up during Black History Month to “drive change” on and off the golf course.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1450885de8d6014907cdde32170cc1b66ab1dd0b7.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1450885de8d6014907cdde32170cc1b66ab1dd0b7.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1450885de8d6014907cdde32170cc1b66ab1dd0b7.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Driving Change On and Off the Golf Course" src="./media_1450885de8d6014907cdde32170cc1b66ab1dd0b7.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="driving-change-on-and-off-the-golf-course">Driving Change On and Off the Golf Course</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Businesses, communities, and individuals recognize the urgency to not only speak up for social justice but to take actionable steps towards change. Last summer, SAP launched <a href="https://discover.sap.com/spotlight-black-businesses/en-us/index.html">Spotlight Black Businesses</a>, leveraging our platforms to elevate, promote, and support small, Black-owned businesses impacted by the pandemic and social unrest. This year we are building on the <a href="/2020/07/spotlight-black-businesses-new-sap-initiative">Spotlight Black Businesses</a> initiative in honor of Black History Month.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP and SAP’s newest golf ambassador, <strong>Cameron Champ</strong>, are teaming up to “drive change” on and off the golf course. Throughout the month of February, Champ will leverage his distance driving skills and network and SAP will allocate branding space as part of the sponsorship to increase awareness and support for some deserving businesses.</p>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1fd3de776a147d0a32859c88d0575e99b66a5d926.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1fd3de776a147d0a32859c88d0575e99b66a5d926.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1fd3de776a147d0a32859c88d0575e99b66a5d926.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Drive Change: Cameron Champ + SAP" src="./media_1fd3de776a147d0a32859c88d0575e99b66a5d926.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://youtu.be/Fs0I6GnaCSI">Drive Change: Cameron Champ + SAP</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="black-history-month">Black History Month</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="watch-the-blank-canvas-episode-to-learn-more-about-socially-conscious-sports">Watch the Blank Canvas episode to learn more about socially conscious sports</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://insights.sap.com/conversations/blank-canvas-sports-social-issues/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Black History Month, observed each year during the month of February, celebrates the contributions Black people have made to American history and culture and recognizes Black Americans’ struggle for equality. This federally acknowledged observance recognizes the meaningful endeavors of Black Americans and strengthens all Americans’ understanding of the contributions, complexity, and struggles Black people continue to face while shaping our nation’s history.</p>
  <h2 id="a-champion-for-equality">A Champion for Equality</h2>
  <p><a href="https://cameronchamp.com/">Champ</a>, an elite player on the PGA TOUR, seeks to address the underrepresentation of Black people and people of color in the workforce and foster a culture of equality in golf and in society at large. Champ is no stranger to the challenges Black people have faced in America. His late grandfather, Mack Champ, was a phenomenal, self-taught golfer but was never able to do more than caddie because of the color of his skin. He serves as a champion for equality, diversity, and inclusion and recognizes the critical role of the private sector in influencing societal change.</p>
  <p>Powered by SAP, Champ’s participation in three upcoming golf tournaments – the Waste Management Phoenix Open, Genesis Invitational, and WGC Championship – will give him the opportunity to raise money for four Black-owned businesses close to his heart. Each week Champ will play in support of one of the businesses, and if his driving distance averages 320 yards during the tournament SAP will donate US$10,000 to that week’s business.</p>
  <p>“SAP proudly supports Cameron Champ’s commitment to driving equality and transforming the lives of underserved and underrepresented communities,” shares Judith Williams, head of People Sustainability, senior vice president, and chief diversity and inclusion officer at SAP. “Our shared values guide this collaboration and provide a channel through which SAP can strengthen our commitment to social justice and our continued effort toward realizing a future where everyone is equal.”</p>
  <p>Be sure to cheer on Cameron Champ as he “drives change” and advances equality in the golf community and beyond.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Dan Fleetwood is vice president of Global Sponsorships at SAP.</em><br><em>Janis Fratamico is global head of Brand Experience at SAP.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-the-sap-news-network-on-linkedin">Connect with the SAP News Network on LinkedIn</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news-network/">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-sponsorships</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-sports</category>
            <category>news-tag/spotlight-black-businesses</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>