<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/women-in-leadership/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Helping Women-Owned Businesses Thrive in the Global Economy]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/helping-women-owned-businesses-thrive-weconnect-international</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/helping-women-owned-businesses-thrive-weconnect-international</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[WEConnect International looked to SAP Business Network and SAP Ariba to help achieve its mission of supporting women-ownedsuppliers.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1eed9a4483f7bc530c8c8f4393ca753b15c1d9c6b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1eed9a4483f7bc530c8c8f4393ca753b15c1d9c6b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1eed9a4483f7bc530c8c8f4393ca753b15c1d9c6b.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Helping Women-Owned Businesses Thrive in the Global Economy" src="./media_1eed9a4483f7bc530c8c8f4393ca753b15c1d9c6b.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="helping-women-owned-businesses-thrive-in-the-global-economy">Helping Women-Owned Businesses Thrive in the Global Economy</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>When Danielle Thomé was a teenager, she asked her father for a job. That’s not unusual, especially since her father was the founder of Projex Engenharia, a successful business in Brazil. But the business focused on civil and industrial construction, an industry where a 15-year-old girl didn’t fit the typical job description, despite her passion for civil engineering. Although Thomé would eventually take over her father’s business, her road to success was paved with many challenges.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“One of the biggest challenges I faced was the age-old problem of gender discrimination,” Thomé recalled years later. She is one of many women driven to lead businesses that reflect their life passions.</p>
  <p>Like other entrepreneurial women, she needed support. But where are the networks to help women turn their passions into successful businesses? Thomé found her network in an SAP customer. <a href="https://weconnectinternational.org/">WEConnect International</a> connects women-owned businesses to qualified buyers around the world. As a result of becoming WEConnect International certified – and a lot of hard work by Thomé and her team – Projex Engenharia’s revenue grew by a staggering 200% in just two years.</p>
  <h2 id="many-challenges-huge-potential-impact">Many Challenges, Huge Potential Impact</h2>
  <p>Women who start and lead businesses face unique challenges. Cultural and social norms, or simply being underestimated by investors, can impede their entrepreneurial efforts. <a href="https://hbr.org/2023/02/for-female-founders-only-fundraising-from-female-vcs-comes-at-a-cost">Harvard Business Review</a> observes that “women are massively under-represented among both venture-backed entrepreneurs and VC investors.” It adds that companies founded solely by women receive <a href="https://pitchbook.com/news/articles/the-vc-female-founders-dashboard">less than 3%</a> of all venture capital investments.</p>
  <p>Also, the pandemic exacerbated the imbalance in unpaid care work – managing the household or caring for children and aging parents – which disproportionally affects women in business.</p>
  <p>Women must also deal with the challenges other businesses face, including access to markets, information technology gaps, and the red tape involved with government programs designed to help new businesses.</p>
  <p>Yet despite these challenges, women-owned and women-led businesses offer the potential to make a significant impact on the global economy. The <a href="https://www.weforum.org/agenda/2018/01/this-is-why-women-must-play-a-greater-role-in-the-global-economy/">World Economic Forum (WEF)</a> observed that “societies with greater gender equality not only offer better socioeconomic opportunities for women, but also tend to grow faster and more equitably.”</p>
  <p>The WEF also reports that advancing women’s employment <a href="https://initiatives.weforum.org/accelerators-network/gender-parity">could add US$12 trillion to global GDP and boost some countries’ economic output by as much as 35%</a>.</p>
  <p>Yet despite a clear business case, the WEF sees global progress stagnating.</p>
  <h2 id="who-has-the-power-to-drive-change-all-of-us">Who Has the Power to Drive Change? All of Us.</h2>
  <p>Traditionally, the <a href="/topics/procurement">procurement</a> function within larger organizations has held the power to fill supply chain gaps and build networks of suppliers. Yet today, other voices are making themselves heard. Consumers are expressing preferences to buy from women and other diverse businesses. Around the world – for example in the United States, Australia, and Canada – government regulations are requiring increased diversity and inclusion.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-business-network-powers-transparency-resiliency-and-sustainability">SAP Business Network powers transparency, resiliency, and sustainability</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-network.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Additionally, the C-suite is reframing corporate policy to reflect more sophisticated approaches to selecting suppliers. In my role as customer officer, SAP Intelligent Spend &#x26; Business Network, I see business leaders prioritizing inclusive sourcing metrics within their procurement strategies to help ensure they have access to all the world’s best suppliers, not just the ones they always buy from.</p>
  <p>Concerned about supply chain risks, procurement leaders are increasingly adopting localization strategies. While seeking new local suppliers, they also focus on inclusive sourcing. Of course, finding diverse suppliers is not easy – even local ones. Many women-owned businesses are small entities, not well-known in the business community. They often lack access to communication technology that would help them create greater visibility for the business.</p>
  <p>How can we make it easier to connect enterprise buyers and women-owned businesses?</p>
  <h2 id="creating-connections-with-sap-technology">Creating Connections with SAP Technology</h2>
  <p>As president, CEO, and co-founder of <a href="https://weconnectinternational.org/">WEConnect International</a>, Elizabeth Vazquez is a leader in women’s economic empowerment and global supplier diversity and inclusion. Through WEConnect International, she helps women around the world grow their businesses to create wealth, hire more people, and contribute to the prosperity of their communities.</p>
  <p>Last week, she participated in panel discussions during the World Economic Forum Annual Meeting in Davos, Switzerland. The discussions focused on opportunities to direct more corporate spend to women-owned businesses, not only to do good but to close supply chain gaps.</p>
  <p>“Women-owned businesses are a valuable and under-utilized resource,” she said. “The women who run these businesses understand what their communities need most, and they are in a unique position to help solve them. In the process, they are creating entirely new industries.”</p>
  <p>WEConnect International recognizes that to compete in the global marketplace, women-owned businesses must be visible to potential customers. It developed the WECommunity platform, a global register of women-owned businesses that makes it easier for buyers to find women-owned suppliers.</p>
  <p>Unfortunately, the initial version of WECommunity relied on technology that delivered a poor user experience, making searching the register cumbersome. WEConnect International needed a scalable, global solution that offered smooth user experiences in multiple languages for buyers and suppliers.</p>
  <p>The <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/spend-management/supplier-lifecycle.html">SAP Ariba Supplier Lifecycle and Performance</a> solution and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-network.html">SAP Business Network</a> more than met these criteria. As an added advantage, many of the WECommunity member buyers were already transacting on SAP Business Network. SAP partner Premikati Inc., a women-owned business, was engaged to help deploy the SAP solutions.</p>
  <p>In its first year, the improved functionality of WECommunity produced dramatic outcomes:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Buyer membership increased by 91%, a $2 trillion increase in purchasing power.</li>
    <li>Over 6,000 women-owned businesses experienced revenue growth, creating 24,000 new jobs.</li>
    <li>Over 7,800 new registered women-owned businesses joined the database, a 95% growth.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>“By making it easier for women to register their businesses and for large buyers to find them, our online portal based on the SAP Ariba Supplier Lifecycle and Performance solution, SAP Business Network, and SAP Business Technology Platform helps women compete in a global marketplace,” Vazquez explained.</p>
  <h2 id="breaking-through-the-barriers">Breaking Through the Barriers</h2>
  <p>Remember Thomé, the teenage girl who wanted to work in her father’s construction business? Today, she is owner-director of Projex Engenharia, the business her father founded.</p>
  <p><a href="https://weconnectinternational.org/success-stories/danielle-thome/">As a noted in a recent profile</a>, Projex Engenharia earned the WEConnect International Women’s Business Enterprise Certification. Thomé leveraged the global network of women suppliers and large buyers to become a more confident and assertive leader.</p>
  <p>The relationship has also helped produce significant benefits for her business. In just six years, Projex Engenharia landed six large corporations as clients. This enabled the company to hire more people, ensure their safety and well-being, and support social, health, and environmental campaigns.</p>
  <p>SAP is committed to helping all customers achieve their diversity and equity goals. And it is gratifying to know that our technology has become a valuable tool in making this happen.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Megan O’Connor is customer officer for SAP Intelligent Spend &#x26; Business Network.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-spend</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/women-in-leadership</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How the “Broken Rung” Is Impacting Women in the Workplace and How HXM Technology Can Help]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/broken-rung-women-in-workplace-hxm-technology</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/broken-rung-women-in-workplace-hxm-technology</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Organizations are using SAP SuccessFactors solutions to address the "broken rung" and other systemic biases in the workplace.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d46530ef90cfa2cd40a0002001a263d2368e417e.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d46530ef90cfa2cd40a0002001a263d2368e417e.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1d46530ef90cfa2cd40a0002001a263d2368e417e.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="How the “Broken Rung” Is Impacting Women in the Workplace and How HXM Technology Can Help" src="./media_1d46530ef90cfa2cd40a0002001a263d2368e417e.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="how-the-broken-rung-is-impacting-women-in-the-workplace-and-how-hxm-technology-can-help">How the “Broken Rung” Is Impacting Women in the Workplace and How HXM Technology Can Help</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Representation of women in leadership has been increasing in recent years. However, only about 25% of C-suite leaders and 40% of manager-level positions are held by women today. According to psychologists, biased perceptions of women in the workplace may be partially to blame, preventing women from obtaining and being successful in leadership-level roles. The inability to access higher levels of leadership is termed the “broken rung,” and there is still a lot of work to do to repair it.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Recently, a group of psychologists at the annual Society for Industrial &#x26; Organizational Psychology conference met to present emerging research on the broken rung. Caitlynn Sendra, Ph.D., experience product scientist at SAP SuccessFactors, who hosted the session, explained that because of the roles men and women historically held in society, our stereotypes around men and women can carry over into today’s workplace, even if not intentionally. “Men are stereotypically thought to be agentic, direct, and task-focused – traits historically associated with leaders. On the other hand, women are stereotyped to be nurturing, communal, and community-focused,” explained Sendra. Although this has led women to be seen as less leader-like, Sendra presented original research on how this may actually give women leaders an advantage when it comes to influencing organizational culture.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="read-the-latest-research-from-the-sap-successfactors-growth--insights-team">Read the latest research from the SAP SuccessFactors Growth &#x26; Insights team</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/dg/hr-meta-trends-2023/index.html?campaigncode=CRM-YI23-HXM-2055448&#x26;source=ctabutton-glo-SAPNews">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Throughout the session, the researchers presented data on several different sources of potential bias around women leaders, including 360-degree reviews, “high-potential” programs, and feedback. For example, Dr. Martin Lanik, CEO of Pinsight, demonstrated that men are three times more likely than women to be identified as “high potential.” Additionally, Dr. Stefanie Mockler, co-founder of The Violet Group, showed data indicating that managers tended to “soften” their feedback to women. The message of the session was clear: businesses need to be proactive in removing this bias from people processes in order to level the playing field for women leaders.</p>
  <p>The session ended with a discussion about what <a href="/topics/human-resources">HR</a> leaders can do to help reduce bias towards women leaders. Providing training on bias awareness and reduction was one solution provided by the researchers. HR technology was also called out as a key piece of the puzzle.</p>
  <p>At SAP, we’re working with organizations of all sizes to help drive more equitable and inclusive HR strategies that empower equitable experiences for every employee, including women. With embedded features throughout <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm.html?campaigncode=CRM-YI23-HXM-2055448&#x26;source=text-glo-SAPNews">SAP SuccessFactors Human Experience Management (HXM) Suite</a>, our customers are provided with the tools they need to help detect and prevent unconscious bias while also gaining the insights required to make decisions that can cultivate a diverse and inclusive workforce.</p>
  <p>Here are three examples of how organizations are using SAP SuccessFactors solutions to help solve for the broken rung and other systemic biases in the workplace:</p>
  <h3 id="sanlam">Sanlam</h3>
  <p><a href="https://www.sap.com/asset/dynamic/2022/11/7c370ed5-4e7e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Sanlam</a> is one of the largest financial services groups in South Africa and believes building a diverse, future-ready workforce is key to becoming the unrivaled industry leader in Africa and to strengthening its position abroad. With 105,000 team members, including both permanent employees and contingent staff, Sanlam is committed to ensuring access and opportunity across its total workforce.</p>
  <p>With SAP SuccessFactors solutions, Sanlam is bridging the gap between permanent and contingent workers by providing a consistent experience for all workers. With visibility into the total workforce, management can identify skill gaps and offer all workers development opportunities that match future priorities. And with group-wide analytics, Sanlam’s leadership can set and actively track targets around race, gender, and disability.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="understand-what-your-people-need-how-they-work-and-what-motivates-them">Understand what your people need, how they work, and what motivates them</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm.html">Explore SAP SuccessFactors solutions</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“We have all the information we need at the drop of a hat,” said Ronel Pfotenhauer, SAP SuccessFactors portfolio product owner, Sanlam Life Insurance Limited. “For instance, we can report on the number of Black, African females with five years of experience and an MBA as potential candidates for a leadership role, with SAP SuccessFactors solutions acting as a type of internal recruitment portal.”</p>
  <h3 id="the-university-of-toronto">The University of Toronto</h3>
  <p>The University of Toronto’s mission is to build a community where academic and learning opportunities are given to every member of its community, including 12,000 full-time and 14,000 part-time employees across three campuses. Its recent work on the anti-Black racism task force and similar initiatives to do with anti-semitism and anti-Asian racism demonstrates the organization’s commitment to ensuring the principles of equity, diversity, and inclusion are deeply embedded in the fabric of everything it does.</p>
  <p>With SAP SuccessFactors solutions, the University of Toronto is bringing a consistent look and feel to the employee experience, providing comprehensive learning programs and empowering people leaders to create the conditions for all talent to thrive. <a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2022/12/cc9d1c23-5f7e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Watch this video to see how</a>.</p>
  <h3 id="mod-pizza">MOD Pizza</h3>
  <p><a href="https://www.sap.com/asset/dynamic/2023/07/623a5dca-807e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">MOD Pizza</a> is dedicated to making positive social impacts in the lives of its employees and the communities it serves. The company strives to create a more equitable world full of opportunities for those who face barriers to steady employment, such as people formerly incarcerated as well as individuals with intellectual or developmental disabilities. It calls its community of employees the MOD Squad, and the MOD Squad is 10,000 employees strong and growing along with the company.</p>
  <p>With SAP SuccessFactors solutions, MOD Pizza has redefined the value of HR data, processes, and experiences – putting the MOD Squad at the heart of its business success. All candidates and new hires are provided with a welcoming experience to help them feel supported and prepared. All employees are provided with on-demand digital training to encourage continuous learning and growth. And with multiple touchpoints to gather sentiment feedback, MOD Pizza can quickly identify areas for potential improvement.</p>
  <p>“SAP’s dedication to people sustainability struck a chord with us. This focus continues to show us that SAP solutions are the right choice for MOD Pizza because they’re designed to create a fair future full of opportunities for our employees,” said Tara Gambill, senior director of Enterprise Systems, MOD Pizza LLC.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Carrie Klauss is global director of Solution Marketing at SAP SuccessFactors.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-sap-news-delivered-to-your-inbox-every-week">Get the latest SAP news delivered to your inbox every week</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/nl/sap-news-center-newsletter/index.html">Sign up</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
            <category>news-tag/women-in-leadership</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Conversations about Leadership with Women in the Chemical and Steel Industries]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/women-leadership-in-chemical-and-steel-industries</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/02/women-leadership-in-chemical-and-steel-industries</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Women leaders discuss taking career risks, rising above gender stereotypes, and forging new paths in historically male-dominated industries.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/business-womens-network</category>
            <category>industry/chemicals</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>industry/mining: industry/mill-products</category>
            <category>news-tag/women-in-leadership</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Advice to My Younger Self: Challenge the Status Quo]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/04/advice-to-younger-self-challenge-the-status-quo</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/04/advice-to-younger-self-challenge-the-status-quo</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With over 27 years of experience in tech and mentoring women, SAP's Aneesha Shenoy shares advice she wishes she could tell her younger self.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>news-tag/women-in-leadership</category>
            <category>news-tag/women-in-tech</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>