<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/industry/public-sector/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Modernizing Defense for the Digital Age]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/modernizing-defense-for-digital</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/modernizing-defense-for-digital</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is ready to help unlock the transformative capabilities of cloud, AI, and digital technologies effectively for defense forces.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>industry/defense-security</category>
            <category>industry/public-sector</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Culture to Go: SAP Develops KulturPass App]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/06/sap-develops-kulturpass-app</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/06/sap-develops-kulturpass-app</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP and the German government developed the KulturPass app to support an initiative around free access to culture and art for young adults.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/public-sector</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Kick Start for the First Sovereign Cloud Platform for the Public Sector in Germany: SAP and Arvato Systems Announce Partnership]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/02/sap-arvato-systems-partnership</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/02/sap-arvato-systems-partnership</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP and Arvato Systems intend to invest in a new company that will provide a sovereign cloud infrastructure for the German public sector.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b7aaad0a3370f26330596ee7a95766f2be5855bd.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b7aaad0a3370f26330596ee7a95766f2be5855bd.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1b7aaad0a3370f26330596ee7a95766f2be5855bd.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Kick Start for the First Sovereign Cloud Platform for the Public Sector in Germany: SAP and Arvato Systems Announce Partnership" src="./media_1b7aaad0a3370f26330596ee7a95766f2be5855bd.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="kick-start-for-the-first-sovereign-cloud-platform-for-the-public-sector-in-germany-sap-and-arvato-systems-announce-partnership">Kick Start for the First Sovereign Cloud Platform for the Public Sector in Germany: SAP and Arvato Systems Announce Partnership</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) and Arvato Systems today announced the intent to invest in a new German company that will provide a sovereign cloud infrastructure for the German public sector.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>This cloud infrastructure is designed to meet the unique national requirements set out in the German cloud strategy. There will be no network dependencies on systems outside Germany, and the independent operation of all services is ensured. All data will be processed and stored in Germany, and all services will be delivered from within Germany.</p>
  <p>A completely new company is to be established to provide a sovereign cloud for the public sector in Germany. The aim of the new company is to drive digital transformation in Germany. It is planned that, in addition to SAP, Arvato Systems will also become a shareholder and additionally will take over operations.</p>
  <p>The offering will be based on the broadly adopted Microsoft Azure platform and related Microsoft services, including cutting-edge collaboration and productivity solutions of Microsoft 365 along with industry-leading SAP® business applications and tools. Approved third-party providers can also offer their applications on the platform.</p>
  <p>The planned new company will provide a broad catalog of digital solutions to support the digitalization efforts of the German government to accelerate the use of cloud technology in the German public sector and will meet the strict requirements put in place by the Bundesamt für Sicherheit in der Informationstechnik (BSI).</p>
  <p>The offering of this new company will be a vendor-neutral stack built on an open platform based on Microsoft’s secure cloud technology, and it will offer full interoperability with other tools. With that, the infrastructure can support a variety of cloud solutions from independent vendors including open source software. Already today, 60% of the workloads on Azure are Linux-based.</p>
  <h2 id="a-sovereign-cloud-platform-from-a-technical-operational-and-legal-perspective">A Sovereign Cloud Platform from a Technical, Operational and Legal Perspective</h2>
  <p>This offering is designed to meet the technical, operational and legal sovereignty requirements of the German government. It will be governed by German law and address the data sovereignty needs of the German public sector.</p>
  <p>The cloud infrastructure will be owned by the new German entity. Furthermore, it is planned that the technical operation will be taken over by Arvato Systems as an experienced infrastructure operator. The infrastructure will be strictly separated from Microsoft’s global data center infrastructure and the existing public cloud infrastructure in Germany.</p>
  <p>“This partnership represents a breakthrough approach for cloud-based innovation,” said Christian Klein, CEO of SAP. “Together we’ll provide a unique solution that not only meets the highest standards of cloud-based technology but also meets the strictest requirements of data sovereignty. This one-of-a-kind collaboration unlocks the potential of digital transformation for the German government and beyond.”</p>
  <p>“We are very pleased about the expansion of our partnership and the joint plans with SAP,” said Matthias Moeller, CEO of the Arvato Systems Group and CIO of Bertelsmann. “At Arvato Systems, we have been supporting large infrastructures, including those in the public sector, for many years and understand their unique requirements. The intended partnership offers the best outcome from various perspectives: to use the best available technology and secure German sovereignty interests while accelerating digitalization for citizens and employees alike.”</p>
  <p>“As digital technology continues to rapidly transform work and life, we have a critical opportunity to ensure these advancements benefit people and organizations everywhere, including in Germany,” said Satya Nadella, Chairman and CEO, Microsoft. “Together with SAP and Arvato Systems, we will create a cloud platform that meets the requirements of the German public sector to help drive digital transformation across the country.”</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP on Twitter at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-the-power-of-partnership-with-sap">Learn more about the power of partnership with SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/partner.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="about-arvato-systems">About Arvato Systems</h3>
  <p>Global IT specialist Arvato Systems supports major companies in Digital Transformation. About 3,000 staff in over 25 locations stand for in-depth technology expertise, industry knowledge, and focus on customer requirements. Working as a team, we develop innovative IT solutions, transition our clients into the Cloud, integrate digital processes, and take on IT systems operation and support. As a part of the Bertelsmann-owned Arvato network, we have the unique capability to work across the entire value chain. Our business relationships are personal; we work with our clients as partners so that together we can achieve long-term success. <a href="https://arvato-systems.com/">arvato-systems.com</a></p>
  <h3 id="about-sap">About SAP</h3>
  <p>SAP’s strategy is to help every business run as an intelligent enterprise. As a market leader in enterprise application software, we help companies of all sizes and in all industries run at their best: SAP customers generate 87% of total global commerce. Our machine learning, Internet of Things (IoT), and advanced analytics technologies help turn customers’ businesses into intelligent enterprises. SAP helps give people and organizations deep business insight and fosters collaboration that helps them stay ahead of their competition. We simplify technology for companies so they can consume our software the way they want — without disruption. Our end-to-end suite of applications and services enables business and public customers across 25 industries globally to operate profitably, adapt continuously, and make a difference. With a global network of customers, partners, employees, and thought leaders, SAP helps the world run better and improve people’s lives. For more information, visit <a href="http://www.sap.com">www.sap.com</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Note to editors:</strong> To preview and download broadcast-standard stock footage and press photos digitally, please visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/photos">www.sap.com/photos</a>. On this platform, you can find high resolution material for your media channels. To view video stories on diverse topics, visit <a href="http://www.sap-tv.com">www.sap-tv.com</a>. From this site, you can embed videos into your own Web pages, share video via email links, and subscribe to RSS feeds from SAP TV.</p>
  <p><strong>For customers interested in learning more about SAP products:</strong><br>Global Customer Center: +49 180 534-34-24<br>United States Only: 1 (800) 872-1SAP (1-800-872-1727)</p>
  <p><strong>For more information, press only:</strong><br>Marcus Winkler, SAP, +49 6227 7-67497, <a href="mailto:marcus.winkler@sap.com">marcus.winkler@sap.com</a>, CET<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a><br>Marcus Metzner, Arvato Systems, +49 5241 80-88242, <a href="mailto:press@arvato-systems.de">press@arvato-systems.de</a>, CET</p>
  <p>This document contains forward-looking statements, which are predictions, projections, or other statements about future events. These statements are based on current expectations, forecasts, and assumptions that are subject to risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results and outcomes to materially differ. Additional information regarding these risks and uncertainties may be found in our filings with the Securities and Exchange Commission, including but not limited to the risk factors section of SAP’s 2020 Annual Report on Form 20-F.<br>© 2022 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.<br>Please consider our <a href="https://www.sap.com/corporate/en/legal/privacy.html">privacy policy</a>. If you received this press release in your e-mail and you wish to unsubscribe to our mailing list please contact <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a> and write Unsubscribe in the subject line.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>industry/public-sector</category>
            <category>news-tag/microsoft</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Data-Use Lessons from Smart Cities]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/data-use-lessons-smart-cities</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/data-use-lessons-smart-cities</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Business leaders can learn from municipal leaders on how to use data dashboards to gain new, valuable benefits. Learn more about smart cities.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_123768eb534a77c78a05d46612dadeebd7a4e04d6.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_123768eb534a77c78a05d46612dadeebd7a4e04d6.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_123768eb534a77c78a05d46612dadeebd7a4e04d6.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="blur people and traffic on a street at night" src="./media_123768eb534a77c78a05d46612dadeebd7a4e04d6.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="3840" height="1044">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="data-use-lessons-from-smart-cities">Data-Use Lessons from Smart Cities</h1>
        <p>Collaborating with stakeholders and adopting agile project development are among the approaches the elevate public services.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In the United States during the COVID-19 pandemic, there were <a href="https://www.bostonglobe.com/2021/04/09/metro/they-came-vermont-pandemic-retreat-now-some-are-putting-down-roots/">numerous</a> <a href="https://www.marketwatch.com/story/this-is-how-life-changes-when-you-move-from-the-city-to-the-country-2019-04-02">reports</a> of urbanites moving to the <a href="https://www.weforum.org/agenda/2021/01/rural-life-cities-countryside-covid-coronavirus-united-states-us-usa-america/">country</a>. The reason was straightforward: Fewer neighbors made social distancing and, by extension, healthy living easier. Many people also learned that they could work from anywhere because their jobs did not require commuting to an office.</p>
  <p>But the truth is that <a href="/research/creating-the-cities-of-the-future">cities</a> were never going away. More than half of the world’s people – about 55% – live in urban centers, and this majority is expected to reach close to <a href="https://news.un.org/en/story/2020/10/1076532">70% by 2050</a>, according to the United Nations. Even during the pandemic, cities demonstrated their vitality by providing critical services at a time when officials raced to address both a healthcare crisis and resource constraints.</p>
  <p>Cities remain economic engines, even as people in many regions have shifted to <a href="/resources/remote-work-new-normal">at-home</a> and then <a href="/resources/tailoring-post-pandemic-work-environment-to-employee-strengths-personality">hybrid work</a> arrangements. Indeed, cities still provide critical infrastructure for business, says Anders Lisdorf, a Copenhagen-based consultant and author of <a href="https://www.amazon.com/Demystifying-Smart-Cities-Perspectives-Technologies-ebook/dp/B082KJ1HJX/ref=sr_1_2?dchild=1&#x26;keywords=anders+lisdorf&#x26;qid=1622571983&#x26;s=books&#x26;sr=1-2">Demystifying Smart Cities: Practical Perspectives on How Cities Can Leverage The Potential of New Technologies</a>.</p>
  <p>“The city is and will continue to be the space where the vast majority of business will be done,” says Lisdorf. “Cities will provide the backdrop for future business. Understanding where smart cities are going impacts the future of most businesses.”</p>
  <p>This article highlights the work of three regional governments – Newcastle upon Tyne, UK; Heidelberg, Germany; and Chattanooga, Tennessee – to illustrate the ways in which government, academic, and business collaborations have used data to serve the needs of their constituencies on a shoestring while managing multiple stakeholders. They are role models for business leaders who are looking to do more with – and get more out of – their data. They offer lessons, including how combining existing and new data sources can derive fresh sources of value, how the use of sensor data can predict demand for services, how harvesting and analyzing location data can isolate safety hazards and mitigate public safety risks – and how data that is properly prepared for sharing and analysis can make for an ever-growing set of valuable applications.</p>
  <h2 id="understanding-quality-of-life-measures-with-real-time-data">Understanding quality-of-life measures with real-time data</h2>
  <p><strong>The project:</strong> Newcastle upon Tyne, a city of 268,000 in the UK, developed an urban data <a href="https://covid.view.urbanobservatory.ac.uk/#intro">dashboard</a> powered by advanced analytics that helps city officials and residents understand metrics that affect residents’ health and safety, including compliance with social distancing measures.</p>
  <p><strong>Major benefits:</strong> The dashboard provides an accurate assessment of the population’s performance on COVID-19 safety measures along with a host of other measures, including vehicle and pedestrian movement, air quality, and wind speed measures in real time.</p>
  <p>During the pandemic, it was crucial for cities to understand how well their citizens were complying with safety guidelines such as social distancing. But other than conventional observation, for example, reviewing CCTV footage, it was difficult to systematically gauge compliance levels. The city of Newcastle upon Tyne completed a pilot project to test if it could do just that, working with Newcastle University to provide <a href="https://urbanobservatory.ac.uk/">an online data portal</a> that shows pedestrian congestion in the city center, among other highlights.</p>
  <p>Using a traffic light indicator system with red, green, and yellow lights, the Newcastle Urban Observatory uses advanced analytics to measure pedestrian density and to determine the pedestrians’ proximity to each other. The system strips out personally identifiable details, anonymously identifying people who maintain safe distances while flagging (in red) instances where social distancing measures are violated. During the height of the pandemic, the project team hypothesized that this insight could help public officials make evidence-based decisions, such as understanding what messages would best promote public health.</p>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div data-valign="middle">We can imagine a city where we manage traffic flows or charges for private vehicles based on things like air quality. You can start to tie those things together.</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div data-valign="middle">Phil James, director of the National Urban Observatory Facility, Newcastle upon Tyne, UK</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Funded by several research grants from Newcastle University and in partnership with the City Council, the Urban Observatory, which is now in production, was established long before COVID-19. Its purpose was to provide city managers with a dashboard that tracked key safety performance measures through analysis of thousands of sensors and other data sources with <a href="https://insights.sap.com/what-is-artificial-intelligence/">artificial intelligence (AI)</a> algorithms. The managers also use the dashboard to monitor movement around the city such as traffic and <a href="https://howbusyistoon.com/">pedestrian flow</a> and congestion, <a href="https://howbusyistoon.com/parking.html">car park occupancy</a>, and bus GPS trackers. It also tracks energy consumption, air quality, and noise levels.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="how-data-supports-safer-public-spaces">How Data Supports Safer Public Spaces</h3>
        <p>The Proximity Monitor helps people safely mingle in a post-pandemic world.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="https://news.sap.com/2021/06/proximity-monitor-real-time-data-post-pandemic-world/">Read the news</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>A key value driver for the dashboard: real-time data. The main goal for the project was to measure the impact of policy decisions (such as the recommendation to maintain social distance) in real time, says Phil James, director of the National Urban Observatory Facility and professor of Urban Data at Newcastle University. Having the data enables fundamentally new types of policies, says James. For example, if the dashboard shows congestion in the city center, the city could elect to assess pollution charges on drivers who come into town. To be clear, Newcastle upon Tyne is not doing this now – and may not ever – but having the data enables what James calls “thought experiments.”</p>
  <p>“We can imagine a city where we manage traffic flows or charges for private vehicles based on things like air quality. You can start to tie those things together,” he says.</p>
  <p><strong>Key takeaway:</strong> The dashboard project sets the table for future public service improvements and improved quality of life.</p>
  <p>Jenny Nelson, digital program manager for the city of Newcastle, believes analytics technology that observes and extrapolates from human behavior will be a pillar of future urban management because the results of <a href="https://insights.sap.com/what-is-analytics/">analytics</a> can drive informed policy discussions.</p>
  <p>“Real-time data gives you the potential to create new and different types of decision-making” and to adjust as needed according to conditions, says Nelson.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_177a134706807ce5d4f92bf431c77509ea7253ebf.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_177a134706807ce5d4f92bf431c77509ea7253ebf.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_177a134706807ce5d4f92bf431c77509ea7253ebf.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Garbage truck" src="./media_177a134706807ce5d4f92bf431c77509ea7253ebf.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2600" height="1733">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="sensor-data-enables-smart-resource-management">Sensor data enables smart resource management</h2>
  <p><strong>The project:</strong> Smart waste management powered by sensor data helped Heidelberg, Germany optimize trash and recycling collection as needs proved variable during the pandemic.</p>
  <p><strong>Major benefits:</strong> Fewer truck runs saves time, labor, and fuel consumption and reduces emissions without affecting service quality.</p>
  <p>With 160,000 residents, Heidelberg, a city in the German state of Baden-Württemberg, is a leader at deploying digital technology to improve life for its citizens while boosting sustainability. The city’s digital spinoff, <a href="https://www.heidelberg.de/1192695.html">Digital-Agentur Heidelberg GmbH</a>, features a number of projects, including more efficient <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2019/11/07/how-governments-use-ai-to-create-better-experiences-for-citizens/?sh=1084056a799c">trash collection driven by sensor data</a>. Trash receptacles outfitted with sensors help city managers track the waste levels in real time through a cloud-based dashboard.</p>
  <p>“Instead of traveling to very isolated parts of the city in the forest every second week, the [truck fleet provider can] make data-based decisions on whether to make the trip. On the other hand, we will get an early notice if containers are overflowing, which leads to a nicer cityscape and fewer citizen complaints,” says Sebastian Warkentin, managing director, Digital-Agentur. Trash collection is therefore a more efficient and eco-friendly option during a time of volatile trash needs, helping the city achieve its sustainability goals.</p>
  <p>The smart waste-management system has significantly reduced the noise level, street congestion, and air quality for residents, says Warkentin. It also helps Heidelberg analyze and forecast future waste management needs. The system uses a host of technologies, including <a href="https://insights.sap.com/what-is-iot-internet-of-things/">Internet of Things (IoT)</a> sensors, low-power wide-area network, cloud storage, and software.</p>
  <p>As cities slowly come back, waste management systems powered by real-time sensor data prevent the inefficiency of doing pickups in areas that have not yet come back to their previous waste levels.</p>
  <p>The smart waste management system has significantly reduced the noise level, street congestion, and air quality for residents. It also helps the city of Heidelberg forecast future waste-management needs.</p>
  <p><strong>Key takeaway:</strong> Agile methodology successfully applied to data projects can lead to new opportunities.</p>
  <p>Most business leaders don’t have to ponder the nuances of trash collection to this degree, but Heidelberg showcases how something that starts as a germ of an idea can grow in unexpected ways.</p>
  <p>Heidelberg did not start this waste collection project with the idea that the city would end up establishing a business. Project managers used an agile methodology to experiment with what worked and what needed improvement, and they kept going. The project resulted from co-innovation development among all the providers – including software, hardware, and garbage trucks – to which every partner brought expertise and technology to be tested.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_114f038a38b095c7990427b85da6042f73d1e4451.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_114f038a38b095c7990427b85da6042f73d1e4451.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_114f038a38b095c7990427b85da6042f73d1e4451.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Lines on a road" src="./media_114f038a38b095c7990427b85da6042f73d1e4451.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="2121" height="1414">
    </picture>
  </p>
  <h2 id="dashboard-pinpoints-road-crash-hotspots-improving-public-safety">Dashboard pinpoints road crash hotspots, improving public safety</h2>
  <p><strong>The project:</strong> To address a rise in road crashes, Tennessee’s Hamilton County built a system using multiple data sources for law enforcement to pinpoint the most crash-prone spots.</p>
  <p><strong>Major benefits:</strong> The resulting dashboard is able to visualize likely hotspots for vehicle collisions, enabling emergency services to position personnel to potentially respond more quickly.</p>
  <p>Just one more sad fact about the pandemic: contrary to reasonable expectations (given that there were fewer cars on many roads), the number of fatal car crashes <a href="https://apnews.com/article/pandemics-health-traffic-coronavirus-pandemic-799e455b73902b1638cc2ac46a172972">increased in the state of Tennessee during the shutdown period</a> when there were fewer vehicles on the road. In fact, the number of people killed on U.S. highways rose nearly 5% in the first nine months of 2020, according to the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration. Tennessee fared worse than the national average, with a 6% rise to 1,004 <a href="https://www.timesfreepress.com/news/local/story/2020/nov/07/tennessee-sees-more-traffic-fatalities/535656/">traffic deaths</a> in 2020.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="virtual-safety-simulations">Virtual Safety Simulations</h3>
        <p>Learn how virtual testing is expanding to mitigate more risks in the real world.</p>
        <p><strong><a href="/resources/road-to-virtual-safety-simulations">Learn more</a></strong></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Hamilton County, which includes Chattanooga, had been working since 2019 to build a sophisticated dashboard using a wealth of geographic information system (GIS) data, state crash data from the Chattanooga Department of Transportation, and other public data sources (including Dark Sky weather information) to visualize where the next crash was likely to take place. Funded by the city of Chattanooga, the project cost in the mid-six figures, and the work was done by the Center for Urban Informatics and Progress (CUIP) at the University of Tennessee-Chattanooga, according to Reid Belew, marketing manager, CUIP.</p>
  <p>One goal was for law enforcement to use the dashboard to mitigate conditions that are ripe for car crashes, hopefully reducing actual crashes in the process, according to Jeremy Roland, a recent graduate of the CUIP. Another important goal was to enable both local law enforcement and emergency services to more efficiently allocate resources. The hypothesis, still being tested with data, is that strategically locating officers has the potential to reduce response times and improve crash victim outcomes. “This affects things like where they position their police cars for a given day, where they set patrol routes for a given day,” says Roland.</p>
  <p>Urban areas provide business leaders with takeaways on how municipal leaders use data. That includes their development of dashboards that start with one goal and – because the data quality is strong – lead to new, valuable benefits.</p>
  <p>The third goal for the project was to give prescriptive insights to local governments about high-incident crash sites, enabling them to make improvements in some cases that would make the locations safer. For example, Roland says analysts took a closer look at one location in northern Chattanooga with a very high concentration of crashes happening throughout the data set time span.</p>
  <p>“It turns out that at that location, there was a utility pole that had been placed a little too close to the main roadway, often causing crashes,” Roland says. Once the officials made the connection, they were able to move the pole. They plan to track activity in the area to determine if the move correlates with fewer collisions.</p>
  <p><strong>Key takeaway:</strong> Pilot projects are critical to test data analytics hypotheses.</p>
  <p>Location data is just one indicator that the project team is analyzing to measure the dashboard’s effect. Most importantly, the Chattanooga team plans to examine whether emergency response times were reduced and by how much. In the meantime, Roland and his colleagues say they have gotten a very positive reaction from the police department. The team is evaluating future uses of the data.</p>
  <p>In spite of the pandemic, the central role that cities play in our lives, and the economic life of the regions in which we live and work, is <a href="https://www.weforum.org/agenda/2020/08/future-of-cities-covid-19/">not likely to change much</a>. Pressed to do more with less and to work with academic and business partners, urban areas provide business leaders with takeaways on how municipal leaders use data. That includes their development of dashboards that start with one goal and – because the data quality is strong – lead to new, valuable benefits.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/insights/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/business-transformation</category>
            <category>topic/data-analytics</category>
            <category>industry/public-sector</category>
            <category>content-type/trends-predictions</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Closing the Sale with a Contract on the Spot]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/01/syncpilot-helps-close-sale-live-contract</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/01/syncpilot-helps-close-sale-live-contract</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Available on SAP App Center, Live Contract from SYNCPILOT digitalizes complex sales processes and helps enable agents. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/discrete-industries</category>
            <category>industry/public-sector</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Creating the Cities of the Future]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/research/creating-the-cities-of-the-future</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/research/creating-the-cities-of-the-future</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Just as business is embracing a future driven by customer experience, cities must develop a collaborative, urban, smart city experience with constituents.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>topic/business-transformation</category>
            <category>industry/public-sector</category>
            <category>content-type/original-research</category>
            <category>stage/awareness</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sydney Water Runs SAP]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/videos/sydney-water-runs-sap</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/videos/sydney-water-runs-sap</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Water is an increasingly rare commodity. That is why a responsible use of water becomes more important than ever. Sydney Water, a water supplier, is...]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_104b3d7e7bd50d1207db074f773214640c5276652.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_104b3d7e7bd50d1207db074f773214640c5276652.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_104b3d7e7bd50d1207db074f773214640c5276652.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Sydney Water Runs SAP" src="./media_104b3d7e7bd50d1207db074f773214640c5276652.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sydney-water-runs-sap">Sydney Water Runs SAP</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="embed">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_104b3d7e7bd50d1207db074f773214640c5276652.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_104b3d7e7bd50d1207db074f773214640c5276652.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_104b3d7e7bd50d1207db074f773214640c5276652.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Sydney Water Runs SAP" src="./media_104b3d7e7bd50d1207db074f773214640c5276652.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="480" height="360">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qxp7fzZsok0">Sydney Water Runs SAP</a></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Water is an increasingly rare commodity. That is why a responsible use of water becomes more important than ever.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Sydney Water, a water supplier, is aware of this responsibility that covers an area of more than 12.000 km2. In order to continue providing world class service to its customers, Sydney Water has updated its billing processes to optimize its workflows and help provide its customers bills that are easy to understand. Together with SAP, the water supplier decided to act and replaced the outdated system with a modern and flexible billing platform.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/financial-management</category>
            <category>content-type/video</category>
            <category>news-tag/climate-change</category>
            <category>industry/public-sector</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>industry/utilities</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>