<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/non-sap-event/cop28/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fusing Sustainability and AI for Inclusive Global Progress]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/fusing-sustainability-and-ai-for-global-progress</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/fusing-sustainability-and-ai-for-global-progress</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP's strides in sustainability and AI spotlight the transformative potential of technology in addressing pressing global challenges.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f29678d2dd5a96294e959a47b0429eb656706b10.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1f29678d2dd5a96294e959a47b0429eb656706b10.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1f29678d2dd5a96294e959a47b0429eb656706b10.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Fusing Sustainability and AI for Inclusive Global Progress" src="./media_1f29678d2dd5a96294e959a47b0429eb656706b10.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="fusing-sustainability-and-ai-for-inclusive-global-progress">Fusing Sustainability and AI for Inclusive Global Progress</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>The echoes of the 28<sup>th</sup> UN Climate Change Conference’s (<a href="/topics/cop28">COP28</a>) groundbreaking commitments lingered as the annual <a href="/topics/sap-at-davos">World Economic Forum (WEF) in Davos</a> became the epicenter of global dialogues this month. Against this backdrop, SAP’s innovative strides in sustainability and artificial intelligence (AI) spotlighted the transformative potential of technology in addressing pressing global challenges.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP’s presence at both events exemplifies the seamless connection between environmental commitment and technological innovation. The nearly 100 initiatives SAP was involved in at COP28 last month demonstrated the company’s unwavering focus on fostering collaboration across governance, the private sector, and civil society, which, coupled with a commitment to transparency, also resonated with Davos’ core values.</p>
  <p>For example, the “From Farm to Consumer” showcase emphasizing intelligent agriculture solutions at COP28 and the WEF Collaboration Village at Davos both showed the power of technology, such as how AI can optimize all industry practices and foster collaboration across the supply chain. This embodies SAP’s multifaceted approach to innovation.</p>
  <p>The company’s strategies involve valuing carbon assets, supporting collaborative supply chains, and actively backing local climate initiatives. <a href="/2024/01/what-industry-analysts-say-about-sap-sustainability">Recent studies</a> highlight how SAP solutions can seamlessly integrate sustainability into core business strategies, giving companies a competitive edge. By treating emissions tracking with the same rigor as financial transactions, <a href="https://www.sap.com/sustainability.html">SAP solutions can enable data-driven decision-making for positive environmental impact</a>.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="record-report-and-act-with-sap-sustainability-solutions">Record, report, and act with SAP Sustainability solutions</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/sustainability.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="navigating-the-ai-landscape-responsibly">Navigating the AI Landscape Responsibly</h2>
  <p>As the WEF in Davos unfolded, the pervasive enthusiasm for AI became evident along the promenade. A dedicated pavilion called “AI House” served as a testament to the technology’s significance in shaping the future. SAP’s commitment to innovation aligns with the forum’s pulse, offering a glimpse into how AI can transform industries and societies.</p>
  <p>AI’s impact on the global workforce was a central concern at Davos. The International Monetary Fund (IMF) warns that the AI revolution could affect almost 40% of jobs worldwide, including highly skilled ones. In industrialized countries, this number could surge to 60%. The integration of AI in various industries can exacerbate inequalities, especially in terms of job displacement. However, SAP believes the time is right to explore the implications and the steps required for this future. One of the first mind shifts may be seeing AI as a coworker rather than a software tool.</p>
  <p>SAP’s approach seeks to mitigate potential inequalities. The company didn’t merely showcase innovation at Davos; it actively engaged in discussions to address the complexities surrounding AI and find solutions for a responsible approach.</p>
  <h2 id="striking-the-balance-a-global-perspective">Striking the Balance: A Global Perspective</h2>
  <p>SAP recognizes the broader, global context of responsible AI, particularly with varying regulatory standards in the U.S. and China. The discussions at Davos provided a platform for SAP to advocate for a harmonized approach to AI regulation, which is especially relevant for the EU. The company’s commitment to finding the right balance resonated in discussions about regulatory standards, emphasizing the need for global cooperation to navigate the evolving landscape of AI. This global perspective gains profound meaning when viewed through the lens of COP28.</p>
  <p>COP28 concluded with a landmark decision by nearly 200 countries to transition away from fossil fuels in energy systems. The renegotiated text emphasized a just, orderly, and equitable shift, aiming to achieve net-zero emissions by 2050. This signifies a global move, committing nations to tripling renewable energy use by 2030 and doubling energy efficiency. The resolution proposes the first-ever phase-out of fossil fuels, accelerating coal’s exit, boosting renewable energy, and emphasizing energy efficiency. However, the resolution falls short of a complete commitment due to opposition from economically reliant countries like Saudi Arabia. And despite progress, vulnerable island nations stress the need for inclusive decision-making, as they face immediate threats from climate change and depend on global solidarity for survival.</p>
  <h2 id="hand-in-hand-ai-and-climate-action">Hand-in-Hand: AI and Climate Action</h2>
  <p>It’s crucial to recognize AI’s broader role in climate action. Scaling proven applications and technology, AI has the potential to unlock insights that could help mitigate 5% to 10% of global greenhouse gas emissions by 2030 and significantly bolster climate-related adaptation and resilience initiatives. Approximately 87% of executives view AI as having the potential to address climate issues, making it a key player in the fight against climate change.</p>
  <p>AI contributes to climate protection not only by helping to reduce emissions but also by helping to navigate unavoidable climate change impacts and provide essential capabilities that enable climate action. SAP, alongside its dedication to AI ethics, wants to ensure that <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence.html">its AI solutions</a> drive sustainability strategies and contribute to a more resilient and adaptive world.</p>
  <p>SAP believes that working together and being open and transparent are key to solving bigger challenges. It’s not just about cool tech; it’s about creating real connections. As AI evolves, SAP’s dedication to a responsible and inclusive future shows the power of teamwork in making a difference.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="connect-with-us-on-linkedin-to-stay-up-to-date">Connect with us on LinkedIn to stay up-to-date</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news">Follow SAP News</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>non-sap-event/cop28</category>
            <category>non-sap-event/wef-davos</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Insights from COP28: Harnessing the Power of Business for Climate Action]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/cop28-insights-power-of-business-climate-action</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/cop28-insights-power-of-business-climate-action</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Reflecting on sustainability measures discussed at COP28, we are seeing a shift towards data sharing and a transition to sustainable energy.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/climate-action</category>
            <category>non-sap-event/cop28</category>
            <category>news-tag/net-zero</category>
            <category>news-tag/renewable-energy</category>
            <category>product/sap-green-token</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-data-exchange</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[COP28 Spotlights Youth in Combatting Climate Change]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/cop28-spotlights-youth-in-combatting-climate-change</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/cop28-spotlights-youth-in-combatting-climate-change</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP has four-pronged approach to empower youth against climate change, spotlighted at the RewirED Summit during COP28. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/climate-change</category>
            <category>non-sap-event/cop28</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP at COP28: Navigating Climate Change Together]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/sap-at-cop28-navigating-climate-change-together</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/sap-at-cop28-navigating-climate-change-together</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Read to learn more about SAP's innovations and youth-focused initiatives aimed to transform climate action at COP28.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d07c04d3ed1e6ad051b5a3361ceab103e7b331db.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d07c04d3ed1e6ad051b5a3361ceab103e7b331db.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1d07c04d3ed1e6ad051b5a3361ceab103e7b331db.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP at COP28: Navigating Climate Change Together" src="./media_1d07c04d3ed1e6ad051b5a3361ceab103e7b331db.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-at-cop28-navigating-climate-change-together">SAP at COP28: Navigating Climate Change Together</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>The world is watching as tens of thousands of leaders gather for the 28<sup>th</sup> UN Climate Change Conference (<a href="/topics/cop28">COP28</a>) at Expo City in Dubai, UAE, from November 30 to December 12. The primary goal is to negotiate agreements that will limit global warming to 1.5 degrees Celsius.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The conference participants face complex challenges as they strive to turn these aspirations into concrete action. Amidst the vibrant backdrop of Dubai, the objective stands tall: to ensure that all nations, particularly the less affluent, aren’t disproportionately burdened in pursuing a sustainable world. Yet, can these ambitious goals truly be achieved?</p>
  <p>The UN Climate Change Conference is a platform for governments to collaborate on creating policies against rising global temperatures and confronting the consequences of climate change. Over the years, these gatherings have shown progress, but many say they are too slow in creating tangible results. Recent assessments suggest a potential warming of 3 degrees Celsius, highlighting the urgent need for collective action to achieve the crucial 1.5-degree target.</p>
  <p>COP28 aims to be more than just another meeting; it seeks to serve as a significant moment where the international community reflects on and evaluates the progress made since the 2015 Paris Agreement. Above all, it represents a critical self-assessment, examining what actions are required to bridge the gap by 2030.</p>
  <h2 id="sap-promotes-sustainable-innovation-making-progress-together">SAP Promotes Sustainable Innovation: Making Progress Together</h2>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="truly-sustainable-businesses-gain-a-competitive-advantage">Truly Sustainable Businesses Gain a Competitive Advantage</h3>
        <p><em><a href="/2023/11/sap-sustainability-research-study-wave-3">Read the feature</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP is participating in COP28 and advocating for ambitious policy action and the adoption of technology for corporate sustainability management. Through the active participation of CEO and Member of the Executive Board of SAP SE Christian Klein, SAP Chief Marketing &#x26; Solutions Officer and Member of the Executive Board of SAP SE Julia White, and Chief Sustainability and Commercial Officer Sophia Mendelsohn, SAP showcases its critical role in advancing sustainability. SAP underscores its commitment to climate action by engaging in nearly 70 initiatives during COP28 on various fronts like carbon accounting, climate justice, and the circular economy.</p>
  <p>Businesses of every stripe are reshaping their processes and how they operate to not only adjust to increasing regulation but to thrive in an era demanding zero emissions. “SAP’s customers generate 87% of the world’s global commerce, about US$46 trillion. That puts us in a unique position in which we play a critical role in the global economic ecosystem,” says Mendelsohn. “SAP can help 87% of total global commerce organize its supply chain, transportation, and financial data in a way that enables a circular and net zero economy.”</p>
  <p>A <a href="https://www.sap.com/insights/research/to-profit-from-sustainability-be-resolute.html">recent study</a> conducted by SAP revealed a significant advantage for businesses that proactively incorporate sustainability into their strategies, surpassing those that merely respond to external pressures. SAP’s solutions can help by streamlining data collection, enabling comprehensive analysis, sharing standardized data, and seamlessly integrating sustainability measures into core business processes. This transparency and integration can empower businesses to effectively navigate regulatory landscapes and make well-informed, sustainable decisions across their entire value chain.</p>
  <p>SAP’s advocacy of managing carbon, fostering collaborative supply chain ecosystems, and supporting local initiatives in combating climate change and societal challenges exemplifies its strategic priorities driving this significant global shift towards sustainability. This underscores the urgency for all companies, regardless of size or industry, to prioritize sustainability. Climate change poses an unparalleled challenge that necessitates collective effort – a challenge no single entity can tackle alone.</p>
  <p>That’s why SAP is working with a broad set of partners for sustainability. Alicia Lenze, global marketing head of Sustainability Marketing at SAP, says, “Collaborating with our global sustainability ecosystem is essential to our customer success. We work with partners of all kinds – institutional, strategic, consulting, and technology – to achieve our sustainability goals together. We actively engage with institutional partners such as The World Business Council for Sustainable Development <a href="https://www.wbcsd.org">(WBCSD)</a>, The International Chamber of Commerce (<a href="https://iccwbo.org/">ICC</a>), and We Mean Business <a href="https://www.wemeanbusinesscoalition.org/">(WMB)</a> to demonstrate how we are helping companies take concrete actions to tackle climate change.”</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="record-report-and-act-on-your-sustainability-goals-with-sap">Record, report, and act on your sustainability goals with SAP</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/sustainability.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP also strives to be a trusted sustainability partner to governments, international organizations, and civil society. By fostering meaningful relationships, SAP drives climate action through technology and advocates for effective climate policies and youth inclusion in a just transition. COP28 is an opportunity for governments to implement a balanced approach to addressing climate challenges, combining mitigation and adaptation with crucial technological support. “I’m hopeful for an ambitious and impactful set of outcomes, which will send a strong signal to all stakeholders, including businesses, that we need to act with urgency and scale to meet the goals of the Paris Agreement for our people and planet,” says Pete Selfridge, head of Global Government Affairs at SAP.</p>
  <h2 id="empowering-change-through-education-and-youth-action">Empowering Change Through Education and Youth Action</h2>
  <p><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/innovation/next-gen-innovation-platform/university-alliances.html">SAP University Alliances</a> is teaming up with Abu Dhabi University to host a special Academic Community Conference. Dr. Karina Edmonds, senior vice president and global head of SAP Academies and University Alliances, will lead the talks, focusing on the critical mix of education, sustainability, and technology. This partnership aims to teach the next generation of leaders, equipping them to navigate and work in our changing world. “Engaging academia and youth in SAP’s sustainability efforts is paramount. We are very proud to team up with our academic partners and innovation ecosystem during COP28 to facilitate dialogue around the power of emerging technologies in addressing climate change and its impact,” says Edmonds.</p>
  <p>SAP also focuses on climate justice initiatives, particularly empowering youth through events like the Green Rising Showcase and Youth to the Table’s COP28 Collaborator Roundtable, highlighting the significance of youthful involvement in shaping a sustainable and equitable future. The private sector plays a big role in climate justice by bringing people together, speaking up, teaching new skills, and giving resources. Projects like <a href="https://www.generationunlimited.org/documents/green-rising-concept-note">Green Rising</a> aim to involve 10 million young people in climate action. Ensuring youth representation in decision-making forums is vital for inclusive policies.</p>
  <p>Climate justice is a critical element in addressing the challenges posed by climate change on a global scale. It emphasizes the need to tackle the uneven effects it has on various regions and populations, particularly those that are more susceptible. Projections suggest that by 2050, approximately 1.2 billion individuals could face displacement due to climate-related disasters, underlining the pressing need for action. These forecasts also indicate heightened health risks for nearly all of the world’s 2 billion children, potentially resulting in a 20% increase in malnutrition cases. Among the most affected are young people whose futures might encounter disruptions amidst these unfolding crises.</p>
  <p>COP28 marks an important moment for global action on climate change. It represents an opportunity for collective effort, emphasizing the need for collaboration and a shared commitment to addressing this critical issue. SAP’s engagement goes beyond mere attendance – it entails spearheading initiatives toward a sustainable future, encouraging collective responsibility, innovation, and progress.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Claudia Cortes is part of Global Sustainability Communications at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-sap-news-delivered-to-your-inbox-once-a-week">Get the latest SAP news delivered to your inbox once a week</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/nl/sap-news-center-newsletter/index.html">Sign up now</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>non-sap-event/cop28</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-university-alliances</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Role of Partnerships in Tackling Climate Change]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/the-role-of-partnerships-in-tackling-climate-change</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/the-role-of-partnerships-in-tackling-climate-change</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Addressing the global crisis of climate change requires global partnerships. Learn more about SAP's efforts.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/circular-economy</category>
            <category>news-tag/climate-action</category>
            <category>non-sap-event/cop28</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Truly Sustainable Businesses Gain a Competitive Advantage]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/sap-sustainability-research-study-wave-3</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/sap-sustainability-research-study-wave-3</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Ahead of the UN Climate Change Conference COP28 in Dubai, UAE, SAP Insights has released the results of its Wave 3 sustainability study.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/catena-x</category>
            <category>non-sap-event/cop28</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-insights</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>