<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/sap-university-alliances/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Game On: Business Builders Prepares Future Business Leaders for a Data-Driven World]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/business-builders-sap-university-alliances</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/business-builders-sap-university-alliances</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Business Builders, built from a partnership between SAP University Alliances and HEC Montréal, is where education meets real-world needs.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-university-alliances</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP at COP28: Navigating Climate Change Together]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/sap-at-cop28-navigating-climate-change-together</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/sap-at-cop28-navigating-climate-change-together</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Read to learn more about SAP's innovations and youth-focused initiatives aimed to transform climate action at COP28.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d07c04d3ed1e6ad051b5a3361ceab103e7b331db.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d07c04d3ed1e6ad051b5a3361ceab103e7b331db.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1d07c04d3ed1e6ad051b5a3361ceab103e7b331db.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP at COP28: Navigating Climate Change Together" src="./media_1d07c04d3ed1e6ad051b5a3361ceab103e7b331db.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-at-cop28-navigating-climate-change-together">SAP at COP28: Navigating Climate Change Together</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>The world is watching as tens of thousands of leaders gather for the 28<sup>th</sup> UN Climate Change Conference (<a href="/topics/cop28">COP28</a>) at Expo City in Dubai, UAE, from November 30 to December 12. The primary goal is to negotiate agreements that will limit global warming to 1.5 degrees Celsius.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The conference participants face complex challenges as they strive to turn these aspirations into concrete action. Amidst the vibrant backdrop of Dubai, the objective stands tall: to ensure that all nations, particularly the less affluent, aren’t disproportionately burdened in pursuing a sustainable world. Yet, can these ambitious goals truly be achieved?</p>
  <p>The UN Climate Change Conference is a platform for governments to collaborate on creating policies against rising global temperatures and confronting the consequences of climate change. Over the years, these gatherings have shown progress, but many say they are too slow in creating tangible results. Recent assessments suggest a potential warming of 3 degrees Celsius, highlighting the urgent need for collective action to achieve the crucial 1.5-degree target.</p>
  <p>COP28 aims to be more than just another meeting; it seeks to serve as a significant moment where the international community reflects on and evaluates the progress made since the 2015 Paris Agreement. Above all, it represents a critical self-assessment, examining what actions are required to bridge the gap by 2030.</p>
  <h2 id="sap-promotes-sustainable-innovation-making-progress-together">SAP Promotes Sustainable Innovation: Making Progress Together</h2>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="truly-sustainable-businesses-gain-a-competitive-advantage">Truly Sustainable Businesses Gain a Competitive Advantage</h3>
        <p><em><a href="/2023/11/sap-sustainability-research-study-wave-3">Read the feature</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP is participating in COP28 and advocating for ambitious policy action and the adoption of technology for corporate sustainability management. Through the active participation of CEO and Member of the Executive Board of SAP SE Christian Klein, SAP Chief Marketing &#x26; Solutions Officer and Member of the Executive Board of SAP SE Julia White, and Chief Sustainability and Commercial Officer Sophia Mendelsohn, SAP showcases its critical role in advancing sustainability. SAP underscores its commitment to climate action by engaging in nearly 70 initiatives during COP28 on various fronts like carbon accounting, climate justice, and the circular economy.</p>
  <p>Businesses of every stripe are reshaping their processes and how they operate to not only adjust to increasing regulation but to thrive in an era demanding zero emissions. “SAP’s customers generate 87% of the world’s global commerce, about US$46 trillion. That puts us in a unique position in which we play a critical role in the global economic ecosystem,” says Mendelsohn. “SAP can help 87% of total global commerce organize its supply chain, transportation, and financial data in a way that enables a circular and net zero economy.”</p>
  <p>A <a href="https://www.sap.com/insights/research/to-profit-from-sustainability-be-resolute.html">recent study</a> conducted by SAP revealed a significant advantage for businesses that proactively incorporate sustainability into their strategies, surpassing those that merely respond to external pressures. SAP’s solutions can help by streamlining data collection, enabling comprehensive analysis, sharing standardized data, and seamlessly integrating sustainability measures into core business processes. This transparency and integration can empower businesses to effectively navigate regulatory landscapes and make well-informed, sustainable decisions across their entire value chain.</p>
  <p>SAP’s advocacy of managing carbon, fostering collaborative supply chain ecosystems, and supporting local initiatives in combating climate change and societal challenges exemplifies its strategic priorities driving this significant global shift towards sustainability. This underscores the urgency for all companies, regardless of size or industry, to prioritize sustainability. Climate change poses an unparalleled challenge that necessitates collective effort – a challenge no single entity can tackle alone.</p>
  <p>That’s why SAP is working with a broad set of partners for sustainability. Alicia Lenze, global marketing head of Sustainability Marketing at SAP, says, “Collaborating with our global sustainability ecosystem is essential to our customer success. We work with partners of all kinds – institutional, strategic, consulting, and technology – to achieve our sustainability goals together. We actively engage with institutional partners such as The World Business Council for Sustainable Development <a href="https://www.wbcsd.org">(WBCSD)</a>, The International Chamber of Commerce (<a href="https://iccwbo.org/">ICC</a>), and We Mean Business <a href="https://www.wemeanbusinesscoalition.org/">(WMB)</a> to demonstrate how we are helping companies take concrete actions to tackle climate change.”</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="record-report-and-act-on-your-sustainability-goals-with-sap">Record, report, and act on your sustainability goals with SAP</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/sustainability.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP also strives to be a trusted sustainability partner to governments, international organizations, and civil society. By fostering meaningful relationships, SAP drives climate action through technology and advocates for effective climate policies and youth inclusion in a just transition. COP28 is an opportunity for governments to implement a balanced approach to addressing climate challenges, combining mitigation and adaptation with crucial technological support. “I’m hopeful for an ambitious and impactful set of outcomes, which will send a strong signal to all stakeholders, including businesses, that we need to act with urgency and scale to meet the goals of the Paris Agreement for our people and planet,” says Pete Selfridge, head of Global Government Affairs at SAP.</p>
  <h2 id="empowering-change-through-education-and-youth-action">Empowering Change Through Education and Youth Action</h2>
  <p><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/innovation/next-gen-innovation-platform/university-alliances.html">SAP University Alliances</a> is teaming up with Abu Dhabi University to host a special Academic Community Conference. Dr. Karina Edmonds, senior vice president and global head of SAP Academies and University Alliances, will lead the talks, focusing on the critical mix of education, sustainability, and technology. This partnership aims to teach the next generation of leaders, equipping them to navigate and work in our changing world. “Engaging academia and youth in SAP’s sustainability efforts is paramount. We are very proud to team up with our academic partners and innovation ecosystem during COP28 to facilitate dialogue around the power of emerging technologies in addressing climate change and its impact,” says Edmonds.</p>
  <p>SAP also focuses on climate justice initiatives, particularly empowering youth through events like the Green Rising Showcase and Youth to the Table’s COP28 Collaborator Roundtable, highlighting the significance of youthful involvement in shaping a sustainable and equitable future. The private sector plays a big role in climate justice by bringing people together, speaking up, teaching new skills, and giving resources. Projects like <a href="https://www.generationunlimited.org/documents/green-rising-concept-note">Green Rising</a> aim to involve 10 million young people in climate action. Ensuring youth representation in decision-making forums is vital for inclusive policies.</p>
  <p>Climate justice is a critical element in addressing the challenges posed by climate change on a global scale. It emphasizes the need to tackle the uneven effects it has on various regions and populations, particularly those that are more susceptible. Projections suggest that by 2050, approximately 1.2 billion individuals could face displacement due to climate-related disasters, underlining the pressing need for action. These forecasts also indicate heightened health risks for nearly all of the world’s 2 billion children, potentially resulting in a 20% increase in malnutrition cases. Among the most affected are young people whose futures might encounter disruptions amidst these unfolding crises.</p>
  <p>COP28 marks an important moment for global action on climate change. It represents an opportunity for collective effort, emphasizing the need for collaboration and a shared commitment to addressing this critical issue. SAP’s engagement goes beyond mere attendance – it entails spearheading initiatives toward a sustainable future, encouraging collective responsibility, innovation, and progress.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Claudia Cortes is part of Global Sustainability Communications at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-sap-news-delivered-to-your-inbox-once-a-week">Get the latest SAP news delivered to your inbox once a week</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/nl/sap-news-center-newsletter/index.html">Sign up now</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>non-sap-event/cop28</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-csr</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-university-alliances</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ENGAGE.EU Think Tank: Students Talk Robust Supply Chains]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/engage-eu-think-tank-students-talk-robust-supply-chains</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/12/engage-eu-think-tank-students-talk-robust-supply-chains</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[At the ENGAGE.EU Think Tank at the University of Mannheim, SAP CFO Luka Mucic and others talked about disruptive supply chains.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-skills</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-university-alliances</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Houston SAP Program Graduate Comes Full Circle to Attain Dream Job with HISD Mentors]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/houston-hisd-sap-program</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/10/houston-hisd-sap-program</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[An SAP University Alliances program in the Houston Independent School District (HISD) aims to empower youth with SAP technology skills.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-education</category>
            <category>news-tag/education</category>
            <category>industry/higher-education-research</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-university-alliances</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Creating a Sense of Belonging for the Next Generation of Female Data Scientists]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/09/next-generation-female-data-scientists</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/09/next-generation-female-data-scientists</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In support of the next generation of female data scientists, SAP is committed to creating a sense of belonging. Learn how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/business-womens-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-university-alliances</category>
            <category>news-tag/women-in-tech</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[TUMO Labs Students Put Their Skills to Work in Innovation Challenges]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/tumo-labs-students-put-their-skills-to-work-in-innovation-challenges</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/tumo-labs-students-put-their-skills-to-work-in-innovation-challenges</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[A program from SAP and TUMO Labs supports university students in understanding, utilizing, and shaping digital technologies. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/future-of-work</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-innovation-center-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-university-alliances</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP's Vision for Supporting Business Transformation and the Workforce of the Future]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/vision-business-transformation-workforce-of-the-future</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/vision-business-transformation-workforce-of-the-future</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP has a vision for supporting the workforce of the future as humanity enters one of its most transformative phases. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/learning</category>
            <category>news-tag/opensap</category>
            <category>non-sap-event/wef-davos</category>
            <category>product/sap-learning-hub</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-training-and-adoption</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-university-alliances</category>
            <category>news-tag/un-sdgs</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Business Partner Challenge Network: Innovative Partnerships at Eye Level]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/siemens-sap-and-dartmouth-innovative-partnerships</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/siemens-sap-and-dartmouth-innovative-partnerships</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[When a fast-paced co-innovation project connected Siemens, SAP, and Dartmouth, four students developed an automated forecast within 10 weeks.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-university-alliances</category>
            <category>news-tag/siemens</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP and the EU TUMO Convergence Center Team Up to Boost Digital Education]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/sap-eu-tumo-convergence-center-digital-education</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/10/sap-eu-tumo-convergence-center-digital-education</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP and the EU TUMO Convergence Center are helping students and recent graduates understand, utilize, and shape digital technologies.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1712136a51fe7abe9956a3c324ab5b20621fe243a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1712136a51fe7abe9956a3c324ab5b20621fe243a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1712136a51fe7abe9956a3c324ab5b20621fe243a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP and the EU TUMO Convergence Center Team Up to Boost Digital Education" src="./media_1712136a51fe7abe9956a3c324ab5b20621fe243a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-and-the-eu-tumo-convergence-center-team-up-to-boost-digital-education">SAP and the EU TUMO Convergence Center Team Up to Boost Digital Education</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="test-drive-sap-learning-hub-today-with-a-free-trial">Test drive SAP Learning Hub today with a free trial</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/td/sap-learning-hub.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) and the <a href="https://www.convergence.center/">EU TUMO Convergence Center for Engineering and Applied Science</a>, which helps bridge the gap between higher education and industry in Armenia, today said they launched a strategic collaboration aimed at helping university students and recent graduates understand, utilize and shape digital technologies.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“Innovation is what supercharges any science and technology ecosystem, and our collaboration with SAP deploys an innovation platform that is full of promise, not only from an industry perspective but also in terms of leading-edge research and education,” TUMO chief development officer Pegor Papazian said.</p>
  <p>As part of this collaboration, the EU TUMO Convergence Center is now an associate member of the <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/innovation/next-gen-innovation-platform/university-alliances.html">SAP University Alliances program</a>. As such, it will have access to SAP software and learning content, and a partnership with the SAP network, including SAP Next-Gen Labs around the world.</p>
  <p>The SAP Innovation Center Network in Potsdam, Germany, has developed 22 <a href="https://blogs.sap.com/2021/09/27/sap-innovation-center-network-invites-university-students-to-solve-real-world-business-technical-challenges/">innovation exploration challenges</a> for <a href="https://www.convergence.center/tumo-labs">TUMO Labs</a>, a technology, applied science and engineering education hub that is part of the EU TUMO Convergence Center. Students can explore emerging topics such as the future of self-service, augmented access control or augmented extended planning and analysis. In close collaboration with experts at the SAP Innovation Center Network, they will work to formulate proven and validated solutions to industry challenges. The expected outcomes range from user interface mockups and use-case ideas to data exploration and prototype code.</p>
  <p>“Students have the opportunity to put their creativity to work and connect research ideas to real-world business challenges,” said Lukasz Ostrowski, development manager at the SAP Innovation Center Network in Potsdam. “Working with educational institutions like TUMO Labs offers us the chance to find new talent and shape the next generation of enterprise software together.”</p>
  <p>The EU TUMO Convergence Center is currently registering for SAP learning resources, including SAP Learning Hub, <a href="https://learninghub.sap.com/academicedition/registration">academic edition</a> and SAP Learning Hub, <a href="https://learninghub.sap.com/next-gen">edition for SAP Next-Gen</a>. Plans to expand the collaboration are being evaluated and could include <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/innovation/next-gen-innovation-platform/young-thinkers.html">SAP Young Thinkers</a> programs, an SAP Next-Gen Lab in the EU TUMO Convergence Center and a research collaboration with TUMO Labs Berlin.</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="http://news.sap.com/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP on Twitter at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Media Contact:</strong> Benjamin Nickel, +49 170 4920616, <a href="mailto:benjamin.nickel@sap.com">benjamin.nickel@sap.com</a>, CET<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p>Any statements contained in this document that are not historical facts are forward-looking statements as defined in the U.S. Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995. Words such as “anticipate,” “believe,” “estimate,” “expect,” “forecast,” “intend,” “may,” “plan,” “project,” “predict,” “should” and “will” and similar expressions as they relate to SAP are intended to identify such forward-looking statements. SAP undertakes no obligation to publicly update or revise any forward-looking statements. All forward-looking statements are subject to various risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results to differ materially from expectations. The factors that could affect SAP’s future financial results are discussed more fully in SAP’s filings with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (“SEC”), including SAP’s most recent Annual Report on Form 20-F filed with the SEC. Readers are cautioned not to place undue reliance on these forward-looking statements, which speak only as of their dates.<br>© 2021 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-innovation-center-network</category>
            <category>product/sap-learning-hub</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-next-gen</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-university-alliances</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Launches Free Student Offering: SAP Learning Hub, Edition for SAP Next-Gen]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/05/launch-sap-learning-hub-edition-for-sap-next-gen</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/05/launch-sap-learning-hub-edition-for-sap-next-gen</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The new SAP Learning Hub, edition for SAP Next-Gen, provides knowledge and opportunities to the next generation of talent.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/training</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>product/sap-learning-hub</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-next-gen</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-training-and-adoption</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-university-alliances</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A More Equal World: Fostering Female Leaders in Data Science]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/03/wids-sap-female-leaders-data-science</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/03/wids-sap-female-leaders-data-science</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[For International Women's Day, join the WiDS Worldwide Conference and learn about WiDS @ SAP events happening throughout 2021.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/diversity-and-inclusion</category>
            <category>non-sap-event/international-womens-day</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-university-alliances</category>
            <category>news-tag/women-at-sap</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>