<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/product/sap-successfactors-people-analytics/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Eastman Energizes HR Reporting to Deliver One-Stop Insights to Leaders]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/eastman-hr-reporting-deliver-insights-to-leaders</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/eastman-hr-reporting-deliver-insights-to-leaders</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Eastman accelerated HR reporting for improved efficiency and insights using story reports in SAP SuccessFactors People Analytics. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>topic/data-analytics</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-preferred-success</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-employee-central</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-people-analytics</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-recruiting</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dynamic Teams: How to Optimize the Outcomes of Increasingly Fluid Work Experiences]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/06/dynamic-teams-optimize-fluid-work-experiences</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/06/dynamic-teams-optimize-fluid-work-experiences</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Cohesive and cross-functional team strategies that support organizational agility unlock the door to dynamic teams. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/dynamic-teams</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-opportunity-marketplace</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-people-analytics</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-performance-goals</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Measuring the Carbon Footprint of Employees Can Help You Make More Informed and Strategic Business Decisions]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/measuring-employee-carbon-footprint-business-decisions</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/11/measuring-employee-carbon-footprint-business-decisions</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Executives can make informed decisions when considering the social and actual carbon footprint of employees in planning. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/experience-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/people-sustainability</category>
            <category>news-tag/qualtrics</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-product-footprint-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-employee-central</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-people-analytics</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-workforce-analytics</category>
            <category>product/sap-sustainability-control-tower</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Five Things to Look Forward to at SuccessConnect 2022]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/five-things-look-forward-to-successconnect-2022</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/five-things-look-forward-to-successconnect-2022</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[For new or longtime SAP SuccessFactors customers as well as companies looking to make a move, here’s what to expect at SuccessConnect 2022.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-people-analytics</category>
            <category>sap-event/successconnect</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP SuccessFactors Earns Top Rated Awards from TrustRadius in Eight Categories]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/sap-successfactors-top-rated-awards-trustradius</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/sap-successfactors-top-rated-awards-trustradius</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[TrustRadius has recognized SAP SuccessFactors with eight Top Rated Awards this year. Read to learn more about this recognition.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/future-of-work</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-compensation</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-opportunity-marketplace</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-people-analytics</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Solving Diversity Problems: One Dream and A Lot of Data]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/01/solving-diversity-problems-dream-data</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/01/solving-diversity-problems-dream-data</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn how people analytics, like SAP SuccessFactors solutions, can help HR to solve diversity problems through a data-driven HR culture.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1381148cc7bc7bd04a2ac63a702d499a37236c656.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1381148cc7bc7bd04a2ac63a702d499a37236c656.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1381148cc7bc7bd04a2ac63a702d499a37236c656.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Solving Diversity Problems: One Dream and A Lot of Data" src="./media_1381148cc7bc7bd04a2ac63a702d499a37236c656.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="solving-diversity-problems-one-dream-and-a-lot-of-data">Solving Diversity Problems: One Dream and A Lot of Data</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>On the third Monday of January each year, Martin Luther King Jr.’s birthday is honored in the U.S. King was an American Baptist minister and activist in the American civil rights movement. At the age of 35, he was the youngest man to have received the Nobel Peace Prize.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>For many, Martin Luther King Jr.’s name is synonymous with his dream of a United States void of segregation and racism. And while his dream has been recognized globally, there is still much work to do to realize it.</p>
  <p>I recently sat down with <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/nigeldias/">Nigel Dias</a> to discuss how people analytics can support organizations’ diversity, equity, and inclusion (DE&#x26;I) strategy. Dias is the managing director of <a href="https://www.3nstrategy.com/">3n Strategy</a> as well as the chair and founder of the <a href="https://www.hranalyticsthinktank.com/">HR Analytics ThinkTank research</a>. He specializes in supporting businesses to make better HR decisions using people analytics and enabling data-driven HR culture.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="drive-performance-and-results-with-data-driven-insights-across-all-your-hr-processes-in-the-cloud">Drive performance and results with data-driven insights across all your HR processes in the cloud</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm/workforce-planning-hr-analytics.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="q-how-does-people-analytics-help-hr-to-solve-diversity-problems">Q: How does people analytics help <a href="/topics/human-resources">HR</a> to solve diversity problems?</h2>
  <p><strong>A:</strong> What areas of your business have the lowest levels of diversity and inclusion, and how bad is the imbalance? Over the years, which HR decisions have caused and added to that inequality? Do different types of employees get promoted differently? Rewarded differently? Hired and retained faster or slower? If you do not change anything, how much worse will the inequality get? If you want to reduce inequality within five years, what HR strategies are most likely to achieve that goal?</p>
  <p>With or without data, organizations are making decisions to try to become fairer and more equal. The purpose of people analytics is to enable organizations to make better people decisions; in this case, about achieving diversity goals and solving inequality. By using HR data to answer questions, people analytics helps organizations to make better decisions increasing the likelihood of achieving diversity outcomes across the entire employee experience.</p>
  <h2 id="what-types-of-diversity-questions-are-sap-successfactors-customers-answering-using-their-data">What types of diversity questions are SAP SuccessFactors customers answering using their data?</h2>
  <p>In the 2020 Benchmarking study by the HR Analytics ThinkTank, <a href="https://www.hranalyticsthinktank.com/news-and-updates/hr-analytics-thinktank-benchmark-2020-release-r30/">93% of people analytics functions said they were actively working with diversity data</a>, which is no surprise given DE&#x26;I is a priority for most organizations.</p>
  <p>These people analytics functions are empowering their HR leaders to solve diversity problems by supplementing HR expertise with answers gleaned directly from data. From day one, people analytics teams can answer descriptive questions, providing facts about what happened in the past and over time. For example, within a particular job family or location, a specific minority group was three times more likely to be promoted than another. Other functions may go one step further, answering questions that diagnose a problem and use data to answer why an outcome has occurred in the past. For example, they might be able to answer why minority groups are more like to resign in particular locations.</p>
  <p>The more advanced functions, which research shows take two to three years to build, will create even more value. Some will be asked to spend more time answering critical questions, predicting how the gender equity gap will increase if nothing changes. The most advanced will provide answers to questions by prescribing what should be done; for example, what strategies are most likely to achieve 25% ethnic minority representation at board level within six years.</p>
  <h2 id="how-are-sap-successfactors-customers-using-workforce-analytics-and-report-stories-to-tackle-diversity-problems">How are SAP SuccessFactors customers using Workforce Analytics and Report Stories to tackle diversity problems?</h2>
  <p>The SAP SuccessFactors People Analytics solutions has the functionality to support organizations to tackle their diversity issues.</p>
  <p>In order to support strategic decision-making, they use SAP SuccessFactors Workforce Analytics to transform HR data into metrics and dashboards, showing end users the answers to questions about what has happened in the past, displaying insights and trends over time. For example, where is minority representation worsening? In particular grades, job families or geographies is there a difference in the way in which different workers are promoted or hired? Using SAP SuccessFactors Workforce Analytics, HR leaders can create better strategies and track progress over time.</p>
  <p>Using report stories, SAP SuccessFactors software can provide anyone in the entire business with a snapshot view of their business area. Stories will allow end users to check an answer at any given moment; for example, whether their recruitment pipeline contains a diverse selection of candidates or if all the resignations in the last month have been women.</p>
  <h2 id="what-steps-can-sap-successfactors-customers-take-to-prepare-for-diversity-analytics">What steps can SAP SuccessFactors customers take to prepare for diversity analytics?</h2>
  <p>The first thing that organizations should do is confirm the objectives that leaders are trying to achieve and identify the questions they need answered to make better choices. In our 2020 study, 94% of SAP SuccessFactors People Analytics leaders said their function was directly sponsored by an HR executive but only 32% were positive that they knew what their leader’s goals were. HR leaders need to clearly articulate what their diversity goals are and establish what questions they would like answered by the people analytics team.</p>
  <p>The second thing they should do is audit the foundations for data-driven HR success and prepare for the journey. According to the same study, only 42% of SAP SuccessFactors customers had a plan for what data to capture, only 16% were sure they knew how the people analytics team should be structured, and only six percent were confident that decision-makers understood how to use their insights in decision-making. A lot of diversity questions can be answered on day one using standard SAP SuccessFactors data, but a plan will be required to provide more complex answers over time.</p>
  <p>The final tip is to provide answers with evidence to help ensure that decision-makers are empowered to actually use the insight. If given the option, most HR and business professionals will welcome evidence that helps them achieve their goals, but they will only use the evidence if it is easy to access and formatted in a way that makes it easy to use in the context of their job. The organizations most successful with data-driven HR make sure that decision-makers are enabled with the right skills, and their dashboards create the best experience for users to find the answers they are looking for.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>To hear more on this topic, <a href="https://gateway.on24.com/wcc/eh/1892128/lp/3582695/jan-2022-solving-diversity-problems-using-your-successfactors-data">register</a> for the upcoming webinar (or listen to the recording), “<a href="https://gateway.on24.com/wcc/eh/1892128/lp/3582695/jan-2022-solving-diversity-problems-using-your-successfactors-data">Solving Diversity Problems using Your SAP SuccessFactors Data</a>” on January 26, or visit <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/human-resources-hcm/workforce-planning-hr-analytics.html">the HR Analytics and Workforce Planning area of sap.com</a>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/data-analytics</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-people-analytics</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-workforce-analytics</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Taking a Data-Driven Approach to Creating More-Effective Data Visualizations]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/effective-data-visualizations-data-driven-approach</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/09/effective-data-visualizations-data-driven-approach</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 06 Sep 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Next-generation reporting tools from SAP enable compelling, easy-to-understand data visualizations. Learn more about how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-people-analytics</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Telling Your Story with SAP SuccessFactors People Analytics]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/06/telling-your-story-sap-successfactors-people-analytics</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/06/telling-your-story-sap-successfactors-people-analytics</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In the experience economy, a standard report with a lot of data doesn’t do the trick. Create engaging visual stories with SAP SuccessFactors People Analytics.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14a2fbcf7f26e50cb5305ec721988bfb841a59ff4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14a2fbcf7f26e50cb5305ec721988bfb841a59ff4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_14a2fbcf7f26e50cb5305ec721988bfb841a59ff4.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Telling Your Story with SAP SuccessFactors People Analytics" src="./media_14a2fbcf7f26e50cb5305ec721988bfb841a59ff4.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="telling-your-story-with-sap-successfactors-people-analytics">Telling Your Story with SAP SuccessFactors People Analytics</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>In the experience economy, a standard report with a lot of data doesn’t “do the trick.” While it may provide the data we want to share, it doesn’t share the story we want convey – or help how viewers will be able to absorb it. Now, more than ever, data visualization has proven to be a powerful methodology to present the information you want viewers to “experience.”</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Data and analytics presented visually make it easier for decision-makers to grasp difficult concepts or identify new patterns and are easier for humans to perceive and digest. Where possible, consider using data visualizations over text in reports and always consider how it will look on a computer, tablet, PDF, or a mobile screen.</p>
  <p>I recently had the opportunity to speak to Mike Hoekstra, People Analytics lead at GP Strategies, to discuss how to use and create stories to share data that may have traditionally been “just a report.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="tap-into-the-power-of-people-analytics">Tap into the power of people analytics</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/people-analytics">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h3 id="q-i-hear-a-lot-about-visualizations-and-storytelling-when-it-comes-to-data-what-does-that-mean">Q: I hear a lot about visualizations and storytelling when it comes to data. What does that mean?</h3>
  <p><strong>A:</strong> The brain processes visuals 60,000 times faster than text and 90% of data transmitted to the brain is visual (“Communicating Through Data Visualization,” Gartner 2019). Simply put, you will not be able to effectively influence others with data dumps alone. Effective data visualizations are imperative!</p>
  <p>That said, the amount of data that HR teams are amassing in their SAP SuccessFactors solutions is enormous. There are many potentially impactful insights that can be pulled out of this treasure trove of data, but you need the right tools to create effective visuals and craft stories around these outputs to have an impact on your audience.</p>
  <h3 id="how-are-stories-in-sap-successfactors-people-analytics-different-from-the-existing-sap-successfactors-solutions-and-how-can-it-help-customers-create-visualizations">How are stories in SAP SuccessFactors People Analytics different from the existing SAP SuccessFactors solutions? And how can it help customers create visualizations?</h3>
  <p>Like the existing reporting tools, stories are included with your SAP SuccessFactors module licenses. Queries are built upon your SAP SuccessFactors transactional data and data access is protected by role-based permissions.</p>
  <p>The stories in SAP SuccessFactors People Analytics include the capability to create bold, impactful charts and dashboards with data from across the SAP SuccessFactors portfolio. They use modern visualization tools from SAP Analytics Cloud and provide end users with the ability to easily interact with the charts and dashboards created.</p>
  <p>In addition, SAP SuccessFactors Onboarding (formerly SAP SuccessFactors Onboarding 2.0) reporting is exclusively available in stories. And beginning in June 2021, learning data will become available.</p>
  <h3 id="in-this-pandemic-era-the-strategic-spotlight-has-been-shone-on-many-hr-programs-including-employee-experience-wellness-and-skill-development-however-hr-is-not-always-perceived-as-a-strategic-leader-how-can-a-sap-successfactors-people-analytics-help-change-this">In this pandemic era, the strategic spotlight has been shone on many HR programs, including employee experience, wellness, and skill development. However, HR is not always perceived as a strategic leader. How can a SAP SuccessFactors People Analytics help change this?</h3>
  <p>Indeed, HR is often challenged by an administrative or operational perception, and still today the impact of their value-add programs is not always appreciated. In a recent pulse survey, 95% of CHROs felt that they played a lead role in their organization’s <a href="http://news.sap.com/covid-19">COVID-19</a> response (“The 2020 Lesson for HR: Think Big and Play the Long Game,” KPMG, August 2020).</p>
  <p>However, the C-suite is still skeptical of HR’s strategic abilities: About 60% of CEOs and executive vice presidents still consider HR to be an “administrator” rather than a value driver (“The Future of HR in the New Reality,” KPMG, October 2020).</p>
  <p>The ability for HR to showcase its strategic side hinges on being able to timely and accurately report on people data to demonstrate its impact.</p>
  <h3 id="who-can-hr-impact-with-stories-in-sap-successfactors-people-analytics">Who can HR impact with stories in SAP SuccessFactors People Analytics?</h3>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="make-hr-decisions-based-on-accurate-workforce-intelligence--not-guesswork">Make HR decisions based on accurate workforce intelligence – not guesswork</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/workforce-analytics.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>I’d argue that every single employee in an organization should be using data to make decisions. With stories in SAP SuccessFactors People Analytics, you can share reports and dashboards with any employee in your organization and they will see only the data that is permissioned to them. You can get interactive visualizations and stories into the hands of nearly anyone in your organization, including line managers, division heads, and senior leaders inside and outside of HR. The potential scope of influence for HR is nearly limitless!</p>
  <h3 id="how-are-stories-in-sap-successfactors-people-analytics-different-from-sap-successfactors-workforce-analytics-do-stories-replace-sap-successfactors-workforce-analytics">How are stories in SAP SuccessFactors People Analytics different from SAP SuccessFactors Workforce Analytics? Do stories replace SAP SuccessFactors Workforce Analytics?</h3>
  <p>No, stories do not replace SAP SuccessFactors Workforce Analytics. Both solutions provide the ability to create dynamic visualizations with your HR data. But while story queries are against live SAP SuccessFactors transactional data, SAP SuccessFactors Workforce Analytics extracts your data and transforms it into time-trending metrics and dimensions for more strategic analysis, including benchmarking, and can include non-HR data as well.</p>
  <h3 id="since-stories-will-eventually-replace-the-existing-reporting-tools-some-customers-are-concerned-about-needing-to-recreate-dozens-or-even-hundreds-of-reports-how-do-you-suggest-they-approach-this-transition">Since stories will eventually replace the existing reporting tools, some customers are concerned about needing to recreate dozens or even hundreds of reports. How do you suggest they approach this transition?</h3>
  <p>First, the sunset of the existing tools is likely years away, so you don’t have to immediately recreate your reports in stories. That said, now is a good time to begin to learn about story features in SAP SuccessFactors People Analytics. Upon seeing the dynamic capabilities of stories, customers often quickly think of a dashboard or analysis that would be a good fit and then use stories to develop and share it. Going forward, existing reports can be recreated in stories over time.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>To hear more on this topic, be sure to <a href="https://gateway.on24.com/wcc/eh/1892128/lp/3192927/july-2021-use-stories-in-sap-successfactors-people-analytics-to-maximize-hrs-impact-in-your-organization">register</a> for the upcoming webinar, “<a href="https://gateway.on24.com/wcc/eh/1892128/lp/3192927/july-2021-use-stories-in-sap-successfactors-people-analytics-to-maximize-hrs-impact-in-your-organization">Use Stories in SAP SuccessFactors People Analytics to Maximize HR’s Impact in Your Organization</a>” on July 13, at 11:00 a.m. ET, or visit <a href="http://www.sap.com/people-analytics">sap.com/people-analytics</a>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Tammie Eldridge works in Solution Marketing at SAP SuccessFactors.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-people-analytics</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>