<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/customer-story/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[German National Team Relies on SAP Technology at the European Championship]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/german-national-team-dfb-sap-technology-european-championship</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/06/german-national-team-dfb-sap-technology-european-championship</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The coaches and analysts of the German Football Association (DFB) use SAP Sports One to analyze opponents and share tactics with players.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>topic/data-analytics</category>
            <category>news-tag/joule</category>
            <category>product/sap-sports-one</category>
            <category>industry/sports-entertainment</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Kyndryl Adopts Next-Generation Tools for Sales Performance Management]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/kyndryl-adopts-tools-for-sales-performance-management</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/kyndryl-adopts-tools-for-sales-performance-management</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Kyndryl adopted SAP SuccessFactors sales performance management solutions to streamline compensation and territory and quota management.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/sales-performance-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Preh Eases Product Costing for Hundreds of Projects with SAP]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/how-preh-eases-product-costing</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/how-preh-eases-product-costing</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Preh uses SAP Product Lifecycle Costing to help increase cost transparency, improve design, and achieve time savings. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/automotive</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-supply-chain</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Is on the Cutting Edge of How to Best Manage Company Spend]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-cutting-edge-company-spend-management</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/sap-cutting-edge-company-spend-management</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP has been on the cutting edge of how to best manage company spend. Read about some recent updates to SAP spend management solutions.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11441be6b25f7c09e02cd28d0b0aa9997b84c22a1.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11441be6b25f7c09e02cd28d0b0aa9997b84c22a1.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_11441be6b25f7c09e02cd28d0b0aa9997b84c22a1.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Is on the Cutting Edge of How to Best Manage Company Spend" src="./media_11441be6b25f7c09e02cd28d0b0aa9997b84c22a1.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-is-on-the-cutting-edge-of-how-to-best-manage-company-spend">SAP Is on the Cutting Edge of How to Best Manage Company Spend</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>As a pioneer of spend management software, SAP has been on the cutting edge of how to best comprehensively manage company spend and supplier relationships.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Like at home, identifying every dollar you spend and getting the most out of it is more critical than ever for your business. And as we continue to roll out SAP Business AI technology, the teams behind SAP solutions are working on ways to help you reduce the time spent on mundane tasks so you can focus on executing your strategy, unlocking spend potential, and unleashing efficiency.</p>
  <p>The first quarter of 2024 was among the most productive in my 18 years at SAP. We debuted new AI capabilities in various SAP spend management solutions. Check out some of these highlights:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>SAP Ariba Category Management</strong>: We’ve incorporated <a href="https://community.sap.com/t5/spend-management-blogs-by-sap/generative-ai-powered-content-recommendations-in-sap-ariba-category/ba-p/13640447?campaigncode=CRM-YD24-ISM-2422141&#x26;source=blog-glo-JCollierQ124">generative AI-enabled features</a> that can assist category managers by generating recommendations in the solution’s category segmentation, market dynamics, and cost structure tools.</li>
    <li><strong>Scoutbee Discovery</strong>: SAP partnered with Scoutbee, a leading AI-powered supplier intelligence and discovery platform, to launch <a href="https://store.sap.com/dcp/en/product/display-2001012892_live_v1/scoutbee-discovery?campaigncode=CRM-YD24-ISM-2422141&#x26;source=blog-glo-JCollierQ124">Scoutbee Discovery</a>. This SAP endorsed app can rapidly identify qualified suppliers that meet specific criteria and can help advance strategic business imperatives. <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/events/7176993552332140544/comments/">Watch the recording</a> of me participating in a recent LinkedIn Live with the Scoutbee team.</li>
    <li><strong>Concur Request:</strong> Now, this service uses generative AI to help provide <a href="https://www.concur.com/blog/article/sap-concur-delivers-enriched-travel-and-expense-experiences-at-fusion-2024?campaigncode=CRM-YD24-ISM-2422141&#x26;source=blog-glo-JCollierQ124">intelligent cost estimates</a> for trip planning.</li>
    <li><strong>ExpenseIt</strong>: Users can upload receipt images to the ExpenseIt solution, which taps AI to help <a href="https://www.concur.com/blog/article/sap-concur-delivers-enriched-travel-and-expense-experiences-at-fusion-2024?campaigncode=CRM-YD24-ISM-2422141&#x26;source=blog-glo-JCollierQ124">automatically create a new expense</a> with several key fields prepopulated. Plus, ExpenseIt can now itemize hotel folios using generative AI.</li>
    <li><strong>Generative AI search</strong>: A new capability within Concur Support allows SAP Concur customers to type questions in natural language and get quick answers using generative AI, <a href="https://www.concur.com/blog/article/sap-concur-delivers-enriched-travel-and-expense-experiences-at-fusion-2024?campaigncode=CRM-YD24-ISM-2422141&#x26;source=blog-glo-JCollierQ124">without submitting a support ticket</a>.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>SAP’s market-leading spend and business network solutions are getting even smarter, working to unlock greater value for our customers. We have many resources devoted to spend management and that’s why we continue to deliver innovation in spend management.</p>
  <p>And we are only getting started. By the end of 2024, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-network.html?campaigncode=CRM-YD24-ISM-2422141&#x26;source=blog-glo-JCollierQ124">SAP Business Network</a> is planning the following enhancements:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Generative AI RFI/RFP responses in SAP Business Network Discovery</strong>: With generative AI-enabled responses for postings in SAP Business Network Discovery, suppliers will be able to respond to RFIs promptly and more accurately, helping to save time and reduce costs associated with manual labor and resource allocation.</li>
    <li><strong>Catalog enrichment using ChatGPT recommendations</strong>: This feature can enable suppliers to generate and improve product descriptions and overall catalog quality based on prompts and keyword recommendations from ChatGPT.</li>
    <li><strong>Intelligent error simplification using generative AI</strong>: This feature uses machine learning and a large language model to interpret and categorize invoice rejection reasons, allowing suppliers to reduce the number of failing invoices, improve rapid invoice submission and payment, and optimize cash flow.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>For more on how AI is transforming business networks, read <a href="/2024/04/business-networks-accelerate-ai-value">this recent article</a> from my colleague Joern Keller.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="eliminate-the-mundane-and-elevate-the-strategic-in-spend-management-with-generative-ai">Eliminate the mundane and elevate the strategic in spend management with generative AI</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/spend-management/innovations.html#ai">Discover SAP solutions</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="but-what-are-our-customers-saying">But What Are Our Customers Saying?</h2>
  <p>Each quarter, G2 highlights the top rated solutions in the industry, chosen by the source that matters most: customers. Spring 2024 is no different, and once again our suite of spend and business network solutions scored extremely well.</p>
  <ul>
    <li><a href="https://www.g2.com/products/sap-sap-fieldglass/reviews">SAP Fieldglass</a> is a G2 Spring Leader in Vendor Management.</li>
    <li><a href="https://www.g2.com/products/sap-ariba/reviews">SAP Ariba</a> is a G2 Spring Leader in Procure to Pay, Purchasing, Strategic Sourcing, Supplier Relationship Management, and Contract Lifecycle Management.</li>
    <li><a href="https://www.g2.com/products/sap-concur/reviews">SAP Concur</a> is a G2 Spring Leader in Expense, Travel &#x26; Expense, and Invoicing.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>What’s more, G2 recently announced its <a href="https://www.g2.com/best-software-companies">2024 Best Software Award winners</a>, with SAP Fieldglass and SAP Concur receiving high honors:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>SAP Fieldglass came in at No. 26 in G2’s Best Software Awards across all products and No. 12 in G2’s Best Software Awards for best midmarket products.</li>
    <li>SAP Concur came in at No. 4 in G2’s Best Software Awards for the account and software product category.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>My colleagues are also getting their flowers. Etosha Thurman, chief marketing and solutions officer of Intelligent Spend and Business Network, and Steve Seide, global head of Adoption for Intelligent Spend and Business Network, were named Top Procurement Pros in the <a href="https://issuu.com/supplydemandchainfoodlogistics/docs/sdc0324_digital?fr=sNGVkZTcxMzY1NTY">Supply &#x26; Demand Chain Executive 2024 Pros to Know awards</a>. A big congratulations also goes out to Darcy MacClaren, CRO for SAP Digital Supply Chain, who received a Pros to Know Lifetime Achievement award.</p>
  <h2 id="driving-success-for-our-customers">Driving Success for Our Customers</h2>
  <p>Hearing me spotlight our direct and indirect procurement, external workforce, and travel and expense management solutions is one thing. Seeing them in action is something way more powerful. Here are a few recent customer success stories to take in:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>American Eagle Outfitters</strong> (AEO), a leading global specialty retailer offering high-quality on-trend clothing, accessories, and personal care products through its portfolio of brands, needed to evaluate indirect purchasing processes and vendor relationships to maximize efficiency. See how <a href="https://www.sap.com/asset/dynamic/2023/10/2ed3b1af-917e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.htm?campaigncode=CRM-YD24-ISM-2422141&#x26;source=blog-glo-JCollierQ124l">SAP Business Network for Procurement and SAP Ariba solutions</a> helped simplify processes and deliver compliant purchasing protocols across the company.</li>
    <li>Power provider to over 900,000 electric customers, <strong>Oklahoma Gas &#x26; Electric Company</strong> (OG&#x26;E) faced challenges with the complexity of third-party and cross-department management of contingent workers. After transitioning SAP Fieldglass solutions to internal management, OG&#x26;E <a href="/2024/02/oge-and-brightspeed-manage-employees-contingent-workers">gained the visibility</a> to make more informed financial decisions, like supplier negotiations.</li>
    <li><a href="https://www.sap.com/idea-place/sap-innovation-awards/entries/2024-award.html#winners?campaigncode=CRM-YD24-ISM-2422141&#x26;source=blog-glo-JCollierQ124">2024 SAP Innovation Award winner</a> <strong>Vestas Wind Systems</strong>, the world’s largest manufacturer of wind turbines, launched a large-scale quality initiative powered by SAP Business Network to help mitigate product defects in a highly complex supply chain. Now, using SAP Business Network, suppliers complete predefined quality tests and document them before confirming or sending an order. This enables Vestas employees to be warned in advance of any quality issues further up the supply chain, so they can <a href="/2024/02/vestas-powering-quality-in-supply-chain">take corrective action</a>.</li>
    <li>Most <strong>KUKA</strong> employees are based in Germany, where tax regulation is complex and submitting hotel and entertainment expenses is anything but simple. The KUKA team worked together to develop a simple process using SAP Concur solutions, connected to SAP ERP, that allows employees to create hotel and entertainment expenses <a href="https://www.concur.com/en-us/casestudy/kuka?campaigncode=CRM-YD24-ISM-2422141&#x26;source=blog-glo-JCollierQ124">seven times faster</a> with fewer errors and fewer rejected expense reports.</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="join-us-at-sap-sapphire">Join Us at SAP Sapphire!</h2>
  <p>SAP Sapphire &#x26; ASUG Annual Conference is June 3-5 in Orlando, Florida, this year and I can’t wait to meet with customers, partners, and my fellow colleagues. This is the best event in the industry in my opinion and you don’t want to miss out. Join us by registering on the <a href="https://www.sap.com/events/sapphire.html?campaigncode=CRM-YD24-ISM-2422141&#x26;source=blog-glo-JCollierQ124">SAP Sapphire event website</a>, where you can also save your spot at the SAP Sapphire Virtual and SAP Sapphire Barcelona events. See you there!</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Jeff Collier is chief revenue officer for SAP Intelligent Spend and Business Network.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-network</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>product/sap-ariba-category-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-spend</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-ariba</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-concur</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fieldglass</category>
            <category>topic/spend-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Driving Progress in Sustainability, Adoption, and AI: The 2024 SAP Innovation Award Winners]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2024/04/2024-sap-innovation-award-winners</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/blogs/2024/04/2024-sap-innovation-award-winners</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The 2024 SAP Innovation Award winners have utilized SAP solutions and AI to achieve remarkable results. Learn more about the winners.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/executive-blog</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>core-topic/generative-ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/innovation</category>
            <category>sap-award/sap-innovation-awards</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Chemicals Supplier BYK Harmonized Supply Chain Planning Processes]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/byk-harmonized-supply-chain-planning-processes</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/04/byk-harmonized-supply-chain-planning-processes</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[BYK, a global supplier of specialty chemicals, has implemented a new supply chain demand planning system using SAP solutions. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/chemicals</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>product/sap-integrated-business-planning-for-supply-chain</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-preferred-success</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
            <category>product/sap-supply-chain-control-tower</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Convista Harmonizes Workplace Culture with SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central and SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/convista-harmonizes-workplace-culture-with-sap-successfactors</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/convista-harmonizes-workplace-culture-with-sap-successfactors</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Convista's people culture and respected brand built on trust and transparency is supported by SAP S/4HANA Cloud and SAP SuccessFactors.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11a18052b07fa380b0a184821d2508dc2d57d515a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_11a18052b07fa380b0a184821d2508dc2d57d515a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_11a18052b07fa380b0a184821d2508dc2d57d515a.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Convista Harmonizes Workplace Culture with SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central and SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition" src="./media_11a18052b07fa380b0a184821d2508dc2d57d515a.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="convista-harmonizes-workplace-culture-with-sap-successfactors-employee-central-and-sap-s4hana-cloud-public-edition">Convista Harmonizes Workplace Culture with SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central and SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>In a merger between two well-matched organizations, cultural integration can be the key to successfully transforming into a single high-performing entity ready to take on new opportunities. Notably, more than a few high-profile mergers have failed due to cultural incompatibility. Add a third organization into the merger and the cultural complexities increase exponentially. But some multi-organization mergers do successfully navigate these challenges and reap the transformational benefits.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="https://www.convista.com/en/">Convista</a>, a consultancy and SAP partner based in Cologne, Germany, emerged stronger and better positioned to serve its clients following a <a href="https://www.convista.com/en/news/axxiome-health-and-enowa-become-part-of-the-new-convista/">recent merger</a> that brought together three former consultancies: Axxiome Health, ConVista Consulting, and enowa. With 25 years of experience delivering transformation projects to its clients, Convista used that expertise in its own rebranding to present its capabilities to clients and employees: a vibrant people culture as well as a respected and trusted brand supported by <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/s4hana.html">SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition</a> for ERP and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/employee-central-hris/features.html">SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central</a> for core HR.</p>
  <p>“Trust and transparency are common values that we share at Convista,” declares Convista CEO Martin Hinz. “Combined with a dynamic team spirit and passion, it’s what we bring to our clients every day.”</p>
  <p>With a workforce of around 1,200 employees, Convista has made a name for itself through its dedication and expertise providing end-to-end solutions to clients throughout the world with a presence in Germany, Austria, Switzerland, Poland, Spain, Brazil, Israel, and further locations across the globe. It supports client projects primarily in four sectors: insurance, industry, healthcare, and energy/utilities. In recent years, Convista has twice been awarded SAP <a href="https://www.convista.com/en/news/for-the-second-time-in-a-row-sap-partner-of-the-year-award-in-the-financial-services-sector/">Partner of the Year</a> in the Financial Services sector.</p>
  <p>“At Convista you meet everyone on the same level, independent of your skill level or where you are in your career,” says Stefanie Weber, project lead of People and Culture – HR Systems, Convista. “Also, when we’re working with customers, we try to approach them at eye level, which makes quite a good working environment. The implementation of SAP SuccessFactors came as a natural extension to our brand and our culture.”</p>
  <h2 id="the-challenges-of-data-siloed-in-three-systems">The Challenges of Data Siloed in Three Systems</h2>
  <p>Weber says one of the reasons she joined Convista in 2012 while studying business at university was the high priority its leaders place on trust and transparency, values that permeate the entire organization and empower employees in their work and career development. “Trust is one of our main values,” she underscores. “Also, the trust that people are willing to do their best to get motivated and move the company ahead.”</p>
  <p>Convista grew quickly both organically and as a result of mergers with other consultancies. In 2019, IT service provider Axxiome Health joined the ConVista Group to deepen the organization’s expertise in the health insurance sector. In 2021, enowa joined the group, infusing its knowledge of industries and insurance. With the mergers complete, the incipient organization became <a href="https://www.convista.com/en/news/axxiome-health-and-enowa-become-part-of-the-new-convista/">the new Convista</a> on January 1, 2023.</p>
  <p>Though team members were highly motivated to collaborate from the start, Convista’s vision for itself as a modern organization was held back in both its daily work for projects and internal services. Using disparate tools based on older technology and a patchwork of third-party solutions that lacked integration proved to be inefficient and unsuitable as a basis for decision-making.</p>
  <p>“Whenever we wanted to have a report, even something as simple as a headcount, we always had to go into three different systems, collect the data, and report on that,” Weber recalls. “It’s just one of the many examples of why we really urgently needed one IT platform.”</p>
  <h2 id="project-one-achieves-milestone-integration">Project ONE Achieves Milestone Integration</h2>
  <p>To build a strong foundation for future growth, Convista embarked on “Project ONE” with the goal to have one digital platform flexible and powerful enough for the entire organization. For this, it chose SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition and SAP SuccessFactors solutions with self-service capabilities for employees to log time-off.</p>
  <p>Overall, implementing SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central with SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition can result in streamlined HR processes; end-to-end integration with seamless connectivity between HR and finance functions for accurate and up-to-date employee data across the organization; greater transparency of data for analytics and reporting on workforce trends, costs, and profitability to enable better strategic planning and resource allocation; and compliance with regulatory requirements and data security.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sap-successfactors-solutions-can-fuel-the-success-of-every-individual-and-drive-org-agility-at-scale">SAP SuccessFactors solutions can fuel the success of every individual and drive org agility at scale</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm.html">Learn how</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Among the key advantages is the ability for employees to access their own HR-related information, such as personal details and time-off balances. This self-service capability helps empower employees, improve transparency, and enhance the overall employee experience.</p>
  <p>Convista’s project team decided for a phased approach to the implementation by first introducing the SAP solutions in Poland and later in Germany, Austria, and Switzerland – with SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition planned to launch in the German-speaking countries during the course of 2024. To optimize success, the project team used the combined best practices of Convista and SAP and hosted regular meetings that provided clear communication to steer the project. “We were always aligned on the requirements of the other teams,” says Weber, who managed the HR workstream. “We all knew the main goal of the implementation. This was helpful for everyone on the project.”</p>
  <p>In-house experts from Convista certified on SAP SuccessFactors solutions contributed valuable knowledge for the implementation. Consultants from SAP Services and Support successfully integrated the cost center replication from SAP S/4HANA Cloud to SAP SuccessFactors and the workforce replication from SAP SuccessFactors to SAP S/4HANA Cloud, and delivered a detailed administration guide on the integration setup for Convista. Additionally, they provided an overview, the architecture guidance, and the navigation through major hurdles in performing the configuration to set up identity access governence (IAG), identity provisioning service (IPS), and identity authentication services (IAS). The SAP Early Adopter Care program supported Convista for the master data integration (MDI) during the implementation and helped to solve all roadblocks efficiently.</p>
  <p>On January 1, 2023, Convista’s 80-person team in Poland was the first to go live with the new SAP solutions. “It was really a great experience for them and quite an advancement,” says Weber, citing the benefits of the new solutions that provide optimizations and intuitive workflows. The project took a pivotal turn on January 1, 2024, with the launch of SAP SuccessFactors solutions for Convista’s 800 employees in the German-speaking countries.</p>
  <p>“The biggest milestone was to have [SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition and SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central] speaking with each other,” says Weber, who emphasizes how valuable it is for the team “to have an end-to-end process within one platform.” With an integrated IT platform in place, she says that it is no longer necessary to do workflows, authorizations, or any other processes in other systems.</p>
  <p>The seamless synchronization of data by using a common data model for SAP business applications helps reduce the need for manual data entry and redundant processes. This means, for example, employee data that is maintained in SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central is available in real-time in SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition; while master data, like cost center data, flows seamlessly from SAP S/4HANA Cloud Public Edition to SAP SuccessFactors Employee Central. Eliminating data silos enables the HR and finance teams to work with consistent, accurate data for all-important employment decisions and legal reporting obligations.</p>
  <p>Now Convista’s team is unified in its brand, values, spirit – and employee data.</p>
  <h2 id="more-transparency-and-intuitive-workflows-are-just-the-beginning">More Transparency and Intuitive Workflows Are Just the Beginning</h2>
  <p>Feedback has been overwhelmingly positive, according to Weber, with employees speaking favorably about the improved transparency and workflows. “The first thing I heard from everyone was, well, this is simple and intuitive. They were so happy about it,” she says. “They are big fans of the mobile application. They find it very transparent and easy to use.”</p>
  <p>For some colleagues, the new solution lets them view their own data for the first time. “When we went live, everyone was viewing their profile,” says Weber. “This was also quite new that you are able to see what data is maintained for your person, your address, but also job information – to view it and have this transparency. People like this very much and also the ability to have the self-services in SAP SuccessFactors.”</p>
  <p>To strengthen communication between HR and employees, Convista will bring more people processes onto the new digital platform. In fact, the team very recently implemented the SAP SuccessFactors Performance &#x26; Goals solution for annual employee appraisals, goal setting, and project feedback. “It’s just the beginning,” Weber says. “There’s still a lot of work ahead of us.”</p>
  <p>Hinz says, “We have been careful to preserve our workplace culture during the transformation. Now that we are rebranded as one organization, we are seeing the benefits of that early effort. With SAP, we now have the digital platform to build people-centered processes that advance our vision as a unified, high-performing organization serving our clients.”</p>
  <p>Find out more about <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/solutions.html?url_id=ctabutton-us-hcm-convista">SAP SuccessFactors solutions</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Jacqueline Prause is a journalist at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-sap-news-delivered-to-your-inbox-once-a-week">Get the latest SAP news delivered to your inbox once a week</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/nl/sap-news-center-newsletter/index.html">Sign up today</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-employee-central</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[HomeMade: Self-Service Home Care Because There Is No Place Like Home]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/homemade-self-service-home-care-sap-btp</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/homemade-self-service-home-care-sap-btp</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[HomeMade, an Australian startup working to empower its customers in the home care sector, used SAP BTP to help scale, grow, and innovate.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_132610f4998fda9f546e77509f74312e342bbea68.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_132610f4998fda9f546e77509f74312e342bbea68.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_132610f4998fda9f546e77509f74312e342bbea68.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="HomeMade: Self-Service Home Care Because There Is No Place Like Home" src="./media_132610f4998fda9f546e77509f74312e342bbea68.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="homemade-self-service-home-care-because-there-is-no-place-like-home">HomeMade: Self-Service Home Care Because There Is No Place Like Home</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>People over age 65 made up 16% of the Australian population in 2020, and they’re on track to represent more than 22% by 2026. This growing cohort is increasingly forgoing traditional facility care models to remain at home. The Australian government offers financial support to qualifying citizens, who can use those funds to support in-home care.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>These government funds are typically managed by a traditional provider who establishes a plan within the customer’s budget and assigns caregivers. They offer limited to no choice regarding providers and little transparency on how the funds are being spent. This inefficient and costly approach reduces available funds for actual care with limited and often unfamiliar providers.</p>
  <p>Enter HomeMade, a startup looking to disrupt the home care sector with a transformative solution that would empower customers to not only stay in their own homes but also to oversee their spending and self-select their providers. With an initial staff of only six, HomeMade set out to create a <a href="/topics/business-technology-platform">technology platform</a> that would deliver efficiency, flexibility, transparency, and ease of use for customers and a scalable model that would grow and evolve with the company.</p>
  <h2 id="a-rock-solid-technology-foundation-for-a-digitally-native-startup">A Rock-Solid Technology Foundation for a Digitally Native Startup</h2>
  <p>Technology is at the heart of HomeMade’s business model, so choosing the right technology partner and the right digital platform was essential. “We wanted a solution that would give us that ability to scale rapidly and with confidence knowing that the rails weren’t going to fall off, because to be digitally enabled is what makes us different,” <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/laura-westhorpe/?originalSubdomain=au">Laura Westhorpe</a>, HomeMade general manager, said.</p>
  <p>HomeMade found the perfect partner in Bourne Digital, part of Accenture, which steered the startup to <a href="http://sap.com/btp">SAP Business Technology Platform</a> (SAP BTP). In choosing the platform, HomeMade benefits from a locally hosted, high-performance cloud architecture that can scale across its network. As a React Native open-source Cloud Foundry runtime service, the HomeMade application is intuitive, user-friendly, and easy for the company to maintain and support long term. Add SAP Integration Suite and SAP HANA data storage into the mix and HomeMade emerged with a secure, integrated, and scalable technology foundation to offer efficient care and support to Australia’s at-home care population.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="bring-out-your-best-with-data-and-ai-from-sap-btp">Bring out your best with data and AI from SAP BTP</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="young-company-makes-an-outsize-impact">Young Company Makes an Outsize Impact</h2>
  <p>In just two years, HomeMade has grown its business to 2,500 customers and reduced new user onboarding time from 14 days to 48 hours. The company has empowered qualifying citizens to manage their budgets and choose their care while saving 14 million Australian dollars and counting.</p>
  <p>Customers and families rave about the solution’s functionality and ease of use. HomeMade’s team members, who have grown to over 100, can happily focus on the customer instead of the endless paperwork they might find in traditional care management. Service providers appreciate timely payment, and another critical stakeholder – the Australian government – conducted a regulatory compliance audit and found that HomeMade scored 100% across 42 requirements for the Age Care Quality Safety Standards.</p>
  <p>And this is only the beginning for a new company already making an appreciable impact. “As the needs of HomeMade grow and evolve, the platform will grow and evolve with HomeMade,” <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/selimahmed/?originalSubdomain=au">Selim Ahmed</a>, managing director of Bourne Digital, part of Accenture, explained. For example, Ahmed continued, “We leverage AI business services to read documents…and we’re feeling really confident that those AI services will continue to play a part in the future evolution of HomeMade as the company moves more and more towards automation and self-service.”</p>
  <h2 id="adding-value-through-innovation">Adding Value Through Innovation</h2>
  <p>An SAP Innovation Award winner in 2023, HomeMade continues to grow and think creatively about how its foundational SAP BTP-based technology can enable it to continue to innovate and add value for customers. “There are endless opportunities,” Westhorpe said, from increasing efficiency to leveraging data to identify falls or other incidents to using large language models to recognize clinical deterioration in users and launch preventative interventions.</p>
  <p>For other startups looking to build technology solutions that will make a dramatic impact, Westhorpe offered to consider, “You want to build everything and you’ve got all these grand ideas, but what are the biggest things that will add value for customers?” Ahmed adds that resilience, a strong partnership, and hard work are critical: “Adapt, learn, grow together, and accept feedback…To build something innovative, you must be prepared to roll up your sleeves.”</p>
  <h2 id="the-full-episode">The Full Episode</h2>
  <p>Special thanks to <a href="https://apphaus.sap.com/">SAP AppHaus</a>, a hub for fostering human-centered innovation, for collaborating on this <a href="https://www.sap.com/programs/btp-better-together-customer-series.html">Better Together: Customer Conversations</a> on SAP Business Technology Platform episode. Learn more about how HomeMade built a better solution for qualifying citizens:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong>Thought leadership podcast:</strong> Thulium’s CEO <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/tamaramccleary/">Tamara McCleary</a> sat down with Westhorpe and Ahmed to discuss the change in caring for older adults, home-based care, and how technology can deliver on a promise dedicated to purpose.</li>
    <li><strong>Practitioners’ video</strong>: Westhorpe, Ahmed, and I discussed the challenges and opportunities in creating a world-class digital solution for a small but rapidly scaling startup.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>Explore more success stories of customers leveraging SAP BTP to help optimize processes for the sake of people and purpose:</p>
  <ul>
    <li><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/asset/dynamic/2023/04/ac38cbd6-6d7e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Colsubsidio</a></strong>: This nonprofit provider of wide-ranging social services chose SAP BTP and SAP HANA Cloud to enable extensive solution integrations, helping deliver better data connectivity and operational efficiency.</li>
    <li><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/assetdetail/2023/07/b457bfbe-837e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b.html">Heartland Dental</a></strong>: Administratively supporting over 1,700 dental practices, Heartland Dental leverages SAP BTP to help improve the business assistant’s user experience, increase productivity, and reduce turnover.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>For the full episode and the on-demand Better Together: Customer Conversations series, visit <a href="https://www.sap.com/programs/btp-better-together-customer-series.html">sap.com/btp</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Timo Elliott is vice president and a global innovation advocate for SAP BTP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>industry/healthcare</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-apphaus</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>sap-award/sap-innovation-awards</category>
            <category>news-tag/startups</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Importance of Intelligent Asset Management and Maintenance for Petrobras]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/petrobras-sap-intelligent-asset-management-maintenance</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/03/petrobras-sap-intelligent-asset-management-maintenance</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Petrobras improves operational efficiency and machine availability with SAP Intelligent Asset Management. Learn how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>industry/oil-gas-energy</category>
            <category>product/sap-intelligent-asset-management</category>
            <category>product/sap-predictive-asset-insights</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Vestas: Powering Quality in the Supply Chain]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/vestas-powering-quality-in-supply-chain</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/vestas-powering-quality-in-supply-chain</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Vestas, a major wind turbine manufacturer, launched a supply chain quality initiative powered by SAP solutions and SAP Business Network.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>industry/oil-gas-energy</category>
            <category>news-tag/renewable-energy</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Total Workforce Management Evolution: How OG&E and Brightspeed Manage Employees and Contingent Workers]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/oge-and-brightspeed-manage-employees-contingent-workers</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/oge-and-brightspeed-manage-employees-contingent-workers</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[OG&E and Brightspeed highlight the importance of strategic planning and the effective use of technological tools in managing the workforce.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/contingent-workforce-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-fieldglass</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>news-tag/total-workforce-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[CEV Technologies and SAP Fuel E-Mobility Revolution in Croatia’s Retail Sector]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/cev-technologies-e-mobility-croatia-retail-sector</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/02/cev-technologies-e-mobility-croatia-retail-sector</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[To realize the potential of convenient charging within the customer experience, CEV Technologies implemented SAP E-Mobility in Croatia.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/automotive</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/electric-vehicles</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
            <category>product/sap-e-mobility</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Palm Oil and SAP Software Give Ugandan Farmers New Hope]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/kopgt-sap-ugandan-oil-palm-farmers</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/kopgt-sap-ugandan-oil-palm-farmers</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The Kalangala Oil Palm Growers Trust (KOPGT) works with SAP software to support Ugandan oil palm farmers sustainably. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/agribusiness</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-rural-sourcing-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cloud Technology Empowers Ugandan Island Community]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/videos/cloud-technology-empowers-ugandan-island-community</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/videos/cloud-technology-empowers-ugandan-island-community</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[KOPGT, which educates farmers on improved agricultural practices, recognized the need for a digital solution to meet the rising demand for palm oil and chose SAP Rural Sourcing Management.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/video</category>
            <category>industry/agribusiness</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-one</category>
            <category>product/sap-rural-sourcing-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Eastman Energizes HR Reporting to Deliver One-Stop Insights to Leaders]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/eastman-hr-reporting-deliver-insights-to-leaders</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/eastman-hr-reporting-deliver-insights-to-leaders</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Eastman accelerated HR reporting for improved efficiency and insights using story reports in SAP SuccessFactors People Analytics. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>topic/data-analytics</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-preferred-success</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-employee-central</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-people-analytics</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-recruiting</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Jowat Creates Seamless, Just-in-Time Operations with SAP Digital Manufacturing]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/jowat-creates-seamless-operations-sap-digital-manufacturing</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/jowat-creates-seamless-operations-sap-digital-manufacturing</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With SAP Digital Manufacturing, Jowat is on its way to having transparent factories with a reduction in risks, errors, and process costs.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1751a2980ab4eaba557c46a3624a271a2fe09bc21.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1751a2980ab4eaba557c46a3624a271a2fe09bc21.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1751a2980ab4eaba557c46a3624a271a2fe09bc21.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Jowat Creates Seamless, Just-in-Time Operations with SAP Digital Manufacturing" src="./media_1751a2980ab4eaba557c46a3624a271a2fe09bc21.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="jowat-creates-seamless-just-in-time-operations-with-sap-digital-manufacturing">Jowat Creates Seamless, Just-in-Time Operations with SAP Digital Manufacturing</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><a href="https://www.jowat.com/en/">Jowat Group</a> is one of the world’s top adhesive manufacturers for industrial use. Tradition and experience from 100 years of corporate development and experience allow it to act as a leading company in technology and innovation in numerous markets and application areas.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Jowat SE’s annual production amounts to 100,000 tons of industrial adhesives. Production is complex and requires high volumes of specialized chemicals and a tremendous amount of power. With raw materials and energy costs skyrocketing, premium manufacturer Jowat looked to get a tighter grip on its inventory management and production processes.</p>
  <p>To ensure maximum efficiency, Jowat requires enough raw materials to fulfill orders while minimizing waste and inventory costs. Moreover, the company needs smooth workflows, as any delay in order placement, production, or the delivery of raw materials can have huge cost implications for the company. As a result, Jowat works hard to ensure that its 24/7 manufacturing processes always run like clockwork.</p>
  <p>With demand for industrial adhesives surging, the company was eager to ensure that its production processes could scale to meet increasing order numbers and still deliver optimum efficiency.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="deliver-individualized-sustainable-and-smart-equipment-products-and-components-in-industrial-manufacturing">Deliver individualized, sustainable, and smart equipment, products, and components in industrial manufacturing</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/industries/industrial-manufacturing.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="targeting-seamless-digital-workflows">Targeting Seamless Digital Workflows</h2>
  <p>Originally established in 1919, Jowat is no stranger to innovation. Leaders at Jowat identified that the next stage of the company’s evolution would require a radical digital transformation of its production and inventory management processes.</p>
  <p>“Our factory workers relied heavily on paper-based processes,” explained Dirk-Alexander Segger, Detmold plant manager at Jowat. “For instance, when employees had finished mixing and decanting adhesives, they handwrote notes to track the volume and type of raw materials that they used during the process. Shortly after decanting, workers would then input the information from their notes into our inventory management and manufacturing execution systems, adding to their workload and increasing the risk of errors.”</p>
  <p>Tracking materials usage manually created time delays, potential for human errors, and discrepancies between the stock numbers recorded in Jowat’s inventory system and the actual volume of raw materials available on the factory floor. Moreover, with information stored across multiple systems and in different formats, plant managers had no clarity to identify process bottlenecks or potential enhancements.</p>
  <p>Annette Podleschny-Borchardt, project lead at Jowat, commented: “To enhance efficiency, improve transparency, and prepare for growth, we decided it was time to go entirely paperless. Building digital processes would give us a more detailed, up-to-date picture of our stock position, which would help drive smarter raw materials purchasing decisions and production improvements.”</p>
  <p>“We aimed to take a more proactive approach to our manufacturing processes. Developing robust, reliable, end-to-end digital workflows was the perfect way to achieve this goal,” explained Christine Künne, head of IT and Business Process Services at Jowat SE.</p>
  <h2 id="embracing-digital-transformation">Embracing Digital Transformation</h2>
  <p>To find the best solution to support its digital transformation initiative, Jowat invited multiple technology vendors to outline the strengths of their solutions. To keep customization low, Jowat targeted a solution that it could easily adapt to meet the highly specialized nature of just-in-time chemicals manufacturing.</p>
  <p>After reviewing 15 different solutions, Jowat selected <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/digital-manufacturing-cloud.html">SAP Digital Manufacturing</a>. In addition to providing a solid foundation for digitalization, SAP Digital Manufacturing can also integrate seamlessly with Jowat’s existing SAP solutions, including <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/s4hana.html">SAP S/4HANA</a>, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/extended-warehouse-management.html">SAP Extended Warehouse Management</a>, and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform.html">SAP Business Technology Platform</a> (SAP BTP).</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="sustainable-risk-resilient-manufacturing-is-here">Sustainable, risk-resilient manufacturing is here</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/digital-manufacturing-cloud.html">Learn more about SAP Digital Manufacturing</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“We were immediately interested in SAP Digital Manufacturing because it is a cloud-native solution,” commented Segger. “Previously, we used on-premise solutions that required us to carry out extensive and disruptive updates. With SAP Digital Manufacturing, we get instant access to the latest features thanks to the quarterly release schedule.”</p>
  <p>Jowat also valued SAP’s proactive engagement with the chemicals manufacturing industry. “We really appreciate that SAP is eager to co-innovate with industry leaders like Jowat to develop next-generation manufacturing solutions,” said Podleschny-Borchardt. “Through the SAP Customer Engagement Initiative, we can help expert developers at SAP build smart factory solutions that meet the needs of our sector down to the finest detail.”</p>
  <h2 id="sticking-with-the-experts">Sticking with the Experts</h2>
  <p>To ensure a smooth implementation of SAP Digital Manufacturing, Jowat relied on support from SAP Services and Support.</p>
  <p>“Whenever we hit a stumbling block, the experts helped us work through the issues. For instance, we wanted to develop a dedicated production operation dashboard, which would give plant managers fast access to key production metrics. As this was uncharted territory, it naturally took a lot of time and energy to work through and SAP was behind us every step of the way,” said Segger.</p>
  <p>Currently, Jowat is completing the first phase of the SAP Digital Manufacturing implementation at its Detmold factory before expanding the solution across all plants. Künne explained: “With a phased implementation, we can ensure that the processes we build at our Detmold plant are tried and tested to deliver maximum efficiency. This will give us the best chance of success when we roll out these processes across all our facilities.”</p>
  <p>“Consultants from SAP Services and Support brought not only their expertise to the project, but also the willingness to listen to the needs and the challenges of our industry. Because of this, we were able to collaborate extremely effectively,” added Podleschny-Borchardt.</p>
  <h2 id="driving-efficient-manufacturing-with-high-quality-data">Driving Efficient Manufacturing with High-Quality Data</h2>
  <p>With SAP Digital Manufacturing, Jowat left error-prone, manual processes behind and now benefits from seamless digital workflows with end-to-end transparency. This helps increase quality and ease work for shop floor operators. The activity confirmation is automatically done in the SAP system, enabling real-time inventory insight.</p>
  <p>Consequently, Jowat gained the following benefits:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>100% digitalized manufacturing process</li>
    <li>One source of truth for detailed production information</li>
    <li>Time savings of three person days per week through automated raw material consumption updates allowing employees focus on higher value activities</li>
    <li>100% accurate inventory</li>
  </ul>
  <p>“Today workers feed consumption information at the point of production. Previously, it would take one full-time employee three days a week to track raw materials consumption,” said Segger. “With SAP Digital Manufacturing, we have a real-time, accurate picture of our raw materials usage and needs. This is helping us optimize usage and reduce costs.”</p>
  <p>Podleschny-Borchardt added: “Production processes are so much faster now that we have built streamlined digital processes. Before, our paper-based ways of working could add up to five days to production timelines. With SAP Digital Manufacturing, we’ve shaved off this time, allowing us to produce and distribute products to our customers much faster, boosting satisfaction.”</p>
  <h2 id="planning-ahead-for-an-ai-driven-future">Planning Ahead for an AI-Driven Future</h2>
  <p>With reliable, up-to-date information in SAP Digital Manufacturing, plant managers and leaders at Jowat can have full visibility across the entire manufacturing cycle. “SAP Digital Manufacturing has helped improve the traceability of our products and given us a much more detailed understanding of our manufacturing operations. Ultimately, that helps to enhance planning and provides new insights into potential process improvements,” said Künne.</p>
  <p>Jowat’s plans for SAP Digital Manufacturing go far beyond a global rollout. The company is already exploring the potential to scale and streamline manufacturing processes further with artificial intelligence (AI) and Internet of Things (IoT) technologies.</p>
  <p>“AI holds tremendous potential for us,” reflected Podleschny-Borchardt. “We’re excited to explore how it can help us to ensure consistently excellent quality across heavily customized product lines and how we can enhance production uptime with IoT-driven predictive maintenance. Having an AI-ready solution like SAP Digital Manufacturing at the heart of our operations makes taking these next steps in our innovation journey much easier.”</p>
  <p>Summarizing the overall benefits, Künne concluded: “With the implementation of SAP Digital Manufacturing through SAP Services and Support, we see ourselves on the way to becoming a transparent factory with a reduction in risks, errors, and process costs thanks to optimized processes.”</p>
  <p><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/customer-stories/smart-press-shop.html">Discover benefits other companies have gained</a>, including improved quality with AI-assisted visual inspection. Be sure to listen to the <a href="https://event.on24.com/eventRegistration/console/apollox/mainEvent?&#x26;eventid=4294893&#x26;sessionid=1&#x26;username=&#x26;partnerref=web&#x26;format=fhvideo1&#x26;mobile=&#x26;flashsupportedmobiledevice=&#x26;helpcenter=&#x26;key=2A85021F45D14DF9C657C622AA74D180&#x26;newConsole=true&#x26;nxChe=true&#x26;newTabCon=true&#x26;consoleEarEventConsole=false&#x26;text_language_id=en&#x26;playerwidth=748&#x26;playerheight=526&#x26;eventuserid=626283838&#x26;contenttype=A&#x26;mediametricsessionid=550094581&#x26;mediametricid=6052808&#x26;usercd=626283838&#x26;mode=launch">webinar</a> about how a renowned manufacturer revolutionizes manufacturing with Industry 4.0. Also, read this <a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/dg/risk-resilient-supply-chain-manufacturing/typ.html">report</a> from Oxford Economics about making supply chains more resilient and sustainable.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>Karin Fent is senior director of Global Customer Success for Digital Supply Chain at SAP.</p>
        <p>Top image courtesy of Jowat.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>industry/mining: industry/mill-products</category>
            <category>product/sap-digital-manufacturing</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-services-and-support</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Top Retailers Using Tech to Build Lifelong Customer Relationships]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/retail-sap-customers-using-tech-to-build-lifelong-relationships</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/retail-sap-customers-using-tech-to-build-lifelong-relationships</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP customers in retail leverage tech to drive meaningful customer experiences, adopt sustainability, and position for success. Read more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/nrf</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-analytics</category>
            <category>product/sap-commerce-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Corvias Combines SAP S/4HANA Cloud and SAP BTP to Streamline Efficiency and Maximize Results]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/corvias-sap-streamline-efficiency-maximize-results</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/01/corvias-sap-streamline-efficiency-maximize-results</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Corvias selected SAP S/4HANA Cloud, private edition and SAP BTP to help modernize its business processes. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16b00da7ad89aecaccd983d3343285162838738c3.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_16b00da7ad89aecaccd983d3343285162838738c3.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_16b00da7ad89aecaccd983d3343285162838738c3.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Corvias Combines SAP S/4HANA Cloud and SAP BTP to Streamline Efficiency and Maximize Results" src="./media_16b00da7ad89aecaccd983d3343285162838738c3.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="corvias-combines-sap-s4hana-cloud-and-sap-btp-to-streamline-efficiency-and-maximize-results">Corvias Combines SAP S/4HANA Cloud and SAP BTP to Streamline Efficiency and Maximize Results</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><a href="https://www.corvias.com/">Corvias</a> is known for its unwavering commitment to addressing critical infrastructure challenges. The company’s work isn’t merely about providing housing or energy – it’s about enhancing quality of life and promoting collaboration within communities.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>This vision is underpinned by concrete plans that will help turn it into a reality. That’s why Corvias recently began modernizing its business processes for the future. Together with <a href="https://www.avvale.com">Avvale</a>, the company embarked on a journey that led to the adoption of SAP S/4HANA Cloud, private edition and SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP).</p>
  <h2 id="a-vision-for-optimization">A Vision for Optimization</h2>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15c36d38c8030e9f6e88a0cf9cdb1cdba127470ce.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_15c36d38c8030e9f6e88a0cf9cdb1cdba127470ce.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_15c36d38c8030e9f6e88a0cf9cdb1cdba127470ce.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Row of houses. Photo courtesy of Corvias" src="./media_15c36d38c8030e9f6e88a0cf9cdb1cdba127470ce.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="600" height="400">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>Photo courtesy of Corvias</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Before choosing SAP, Corvias was grappling with a complex organizational structure, one characterized by disconnected systems and processes across accounting and purchasing. The allocation process was cumbersome and required redundant updates in multiple parts of the system, causing administrative headaches.</p>
  <p>Executive leadership quickly identified the need to simplify workflows so that they could deliver information to the right stakeholders effectively and quickly and create an integrated system that could move data seamlessly between processes without human intervention.</p>
  <h2 id="choosing-sap-for-success">Choosing SAP for Success</h2>
  <p>To help overcome its challenges, Corvias selected two primary SAP solutions: <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/s4hana-private-edition.html">SAP S/4HANA Cloud, private edition</a> and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform.html">SAP BTP</a>. With them, Corvias hoped to primarily centralize its data, enabling integrated purchasing and accounting capabilities. The implementation also leveraged SAP Fiori to help develop customized applications for allocating segment costs.</p>
  <p>Today, Corvias’ processes are simplified and streamlined, thanks to real-time, actionable information accessible by key members of leadership through SAP. This allows them to be more strategic in their decision-making with greater visibility into real costs and profitability at both the individual and project levels, contributing to a more efficient financial management system for the company overall.</p>
  <h2 id="far-reaching-benefits">Far-Reaching Benefits</h2>
  <p>The adoption of SAP has empowered the company to concentrate on enhancing its working capital through ongoing improvements. This has fostered a culture of innovation and encouraged a proactive approach to operational challenges and enhancements within the organization.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-tailored-to-fit-cloud-erp-that-adapts-to-your-organizations-unique-transformation">Get tailored-to-fit cloud ERP that adapts to your organization’s unique transformation</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/s4hana-private-edition.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In accounts payable, for instance, the implementation of automated purchase order management processes has resulted in a notable decrease in touch points. The accounts payable team has seen a reduction from seven to two touch points in 75% of cases. This not only enhances efficiency but reduces the likelihood that errors will occur as often as they would with manual processes. The streamlined purchase-order management system has become a valuable asset in optimizing the company’s financial workflow.</p>
  <p>Corvias has also embraced a more unified and secure information management system. By standardizing data security roles throughout the entire organization, SAP provided a reliable and protected method for managing information. This consistency has made it easier for site teams to handle administrative tasks, freeing up their time to focus on more strategic initiatives.</p>
  <p>Best of all, these SAP solutions provided a flexible and scalable platform that allows Corvias to seamlessly incorporate acquired or new companies.</p>
  <h2 id="looking-ahead-to-the-future">Looking Ahead to the Future</h2>
  <p>Corvias’ journey with SAP and Avvale showcases the transformative power of streamlined systems and integrated solutions. By addressing the challenges of a complex organizational structure and disparate workflows, Corvias not only achieved operational efficiency but also laid the groundwork for future scalability. The collaboration with Avvale unlocked expert guidance and support throughout the process, highlighting the importance of strategic partnerships in navigating the evolving landscape of technology integration.</p>
  <p>Today, as Corvias continues to oversee diverse projects in partnership with the military, higher education institutions, and communities, the adoption of SAP stands as a testament to the company’s commitment to innovation and excellence across all its mission-critical endeavors.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Mike Kaszuk is SVP and COO for Midmarket at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/sme</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>industry/mining: industry/mill-products</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Putzmeister Digitalized Global Field Service Management Processes to Increase Efficiency and Customer Satisfaction]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/putzmeister-digitalized-global-field-service-management</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/putzmeister-digitalized-global-field-service-management</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Putzmeister implemented SAP Field Service Management to help harmonize field service management processes locally and globally. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-supply-chain</category>
            <category>news-tag/field-service-management</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Zamora Company Is Helping Create a Better World by Reducing Packaging with SAP Responsible Design and Production]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/zamora-company-reducing-packaging-sap-responsible-design-and-production</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/zamora-company-reducing-packaging-sap-responsible-design-and-production</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Responsible Design and Production helped Zamora Company adhere to new packaging taxes in Spain. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18070844b43147c00d535b4fc2b7e284b2b6e0bcf.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18070844b43147c00d535b4fc2b7e284b2b6e0bcf.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_18070844b43147c00d535b4fc2b7e284b2b6e0bcf.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Zamora Company Is Helping Create a Better World by Reducing Packaging with SAP Responsible Design and Production" src="./media_18070844b43147c00d535b4fc2b7e284b2b6e0bcf.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="zamora-company-is-helping-create-a-better-world-by-reducing-packaging-with-sap-responsible-design-and-production">Zamora Company Is Helping Create a Better World by Reducing Packaging with SAP Responsible Design and Production</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>As a consumer you may not have heard of <a href="https://zamoracompany.com/conscious-company/">Zamora Company</a>, but it will surely ring a bell when you hear the names of some of its most popular premium spirit and wine brands, such as Licor 43, Martin Miller’s Gin, Yellow Rose, Ramón Bilbao, Champagne Pommery, and many others.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The international enterprise with headquarters in Spain and operations in more than 80 countries has been including environmental protection and economic growth into its DNA and is constantly working on achieving a sustainable business model that will be its future legacy to society and to the planet. Its commitment to the planet is based on four pillars: climate action, biodiversity protection, circularity, and conscious suppliers.</p>
  <p>The mission of Zamora Company toward its suppliers is to encourage them to be more sustainable by collaborating closely to substitute product and packaging materials with more sustainable alternatives and to use more recyclable packaging materials to support circular economy principles. It’s no wonder that, for Zamora, <a href="/topics/sustainability">sustainability</a> goes hand in hand with innovation without compromising the highest quality standards. <a href="https://zamoracompany.com/conscious-company/">Zamora Company’s strategy</a> as a conscious company is also focused and aligned with the achievement of the <a href="https://www.un.org/sustainabledevelopment/">Sustainable Development Goals (SDGs)</a> set by the United Nations 2030 agenda.</p>
  <h2 id="accelerating-innovation-through-new-packaging-legislation">Accelerating Innovation Through New Packaging Legislation</h2>
  <p>Since the introduction of a <a href="https://sede.agenciatributaria.gob.es/Sede/en_gb/impuestos-especiales-medioambientales/impuesto-especial-sobre-envases-plastico-reutilizables.html">new packaging tax</a> in Spain on January 1, 2023 on non-reusable plastic packaging, companies are required to meet comprehensive reporting requirements.</p>
  <p>The tax is an indirect excise tax with an environmental purpose. It aims to internalize the environmental costs related to the manufacturing and consumption of plastic packaging in the price of final products.</p>
  <p>The taxable event is the manufacturing, import, or intra-community acquisition of non-reusable plastic packaging for its use within the Spanish market. The plastic packaging tax captures a broad concept of “non-reusable plastic packaging” in its scope, which includes:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Non-reusable plastic containers – the law provides definitions of “non-reusable,” “plastic,” and “container” for the purpose of this tax</li>
    <li>Semi-finished plastic products, such as preforms and thermoplastic sheets, intended for production of non-reusable plastic containers</li>
    <li>Plastic products aimed to facilitate the closing, trading, or presentation of non-reusable containers</li>
  </ul>
  <p>“The new legislation required us to respond to governmental requisitions and was an additional driver to accelerate our sustainability efforts,” Enrique Gonzalo Mecández, SAP manager in Operations at Zamora Company, explained. “With a cross-departmental team, we were looking to find the most appropriate and scalable software solution to meet the country’s regulatory requirements and help us with data management, a tax monitor, and reporting and insights.”</p>
  <h2 id="keeping-all-data-in-one-central-place">Keeping All Data in One Central Place</h2>
  <p>As a result, Zamora Company found that <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/responsible-design-and-production.html">SAP Responsible Design and Production</a>, an industry cloud-based solution, would best meet its needs. SAP Responsible Design and Production can support manufacturers and retailers in calculating extended producer responsibility (EPR) obligations and fees, plastic taxes, and corporate commitments to optimize material choices. In addition, it helps improve design decisions based on costs and planetary impact.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="start-acting-on-a-circular-economy-and-eliminate-waste-with-sap">Start acting on a circular economy and eliminate waste with SAP</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/responsible-design-and-production.html">Learn how</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“From a process standpoint, SAP Responsible Design and Production facilitates the incorporation of everything related to sustainability data linked to the material, so that all relevant information is unified in the material master,” Gonzalo Mecández said. “As all information is kept in one place, purchasing work and master data maintenance required to ensure regulatory compliance is centralized, without the need to manually replicate information in different systems.”</p>
  <p>“Moreover, leveraging a single and integrated platform with <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/erp/s4hana.html">SAP S/4HANA</a> provides the security of working with up-to-date and correct data. Additionally, the data quality application allows our users to detect any lack of information and correct it,” he added. “With deep knowledge and solution experience, our trusted partner <a href="https://www.indracompany.com/en/minsait">Minsait</a>, an <a href="https://www.indracompany.com/en/">Indra</a> company, closely supported us during the implementation of SAP Responsible Design and Production, as well as the integration with our SAP S/4HANA platform.”</p>
  <p>The benefits Zamora Company achieved include:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Ability to rely on 100% correct data, fully aligned with material registration processes</li>
    <li>Cost savings thanks to less administrative work, eased reporting, and a central data repository</li>
    <li>Reduced risk of non-compliance with extended producer responsibility regulations in Spain</li>
    <li>A simple, user-friendly tool to support legal reporting requirements in a timely manner</li>
    <li>Ability to expand solution usage to meet upcoming EPR legislation in other countries, like Italy</li>
  </ul>
  <h2 id="positive-impact-on-customers-economy-society-and-environment">Positive Impact on Customers, Economy, Society, and Environment</h2>
  <p>“The project helped us learn more about our products and incorporate their packaging details, so that our company knows exactly how much plastic and non-recycled plastic is being used. In a more strategic phase, this will allow us to evaluate alternative materials and compositions, which can create cost savings for the company and positively contribute to the environment by being able to transition to more sustainable elements,” Gonzalo Mecández concluded.</p>
  <p>Watch a solution <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/responsible-design-and-production.html?video=d287b342-047e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b">overview video</a> to learn how to start acting on a circular economy, design products sustainably, and eliminate waste with SAP Responsible Design and Production. <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/scm/responsible-design-and-production.html?pdf-asset=6e06c630-667e-0010-bca6-c68f7e60039b&#x26;page=1">Read</a> about what benefits other enterprises achieved.</p>
  <p>To explore how the comprehensive, cloud-based sustainability solution portfolio from SAP can support carbon footprint management, reducing material waste, and becoming a socially responsible business, visit <a href="https://www.sap.com/sustainability.html">here</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Karin Fent is senior director of Global Customer Success, Digital Supply Chain, at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="stay-in-touch-by-following-sap-news-on-linkedin">Stay in touch by following SAP News on LinkedIn</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news">Connect with us</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/circular-economy</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>product/sap-responsible-design-and-production</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Intelligent Document Processing: Unlocking Hidden Insights with AI]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/intelligent-document-processing-unlocking-hidden-insights-ai</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/intelligent-document-processing-unlocking-hidden-insights-ai</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Intelligent document processing is becoming a vital ally for process optimization, innovation, and delivering exceptional user experiences.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/opentext</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Jowat Doubles Productivity with Smarter Maintenance and Strategic Insight into Asset Management]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/jowat-smarter-maintenance-strategic-insight-asset-management</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/jowat-smarter-maintenance-strategic-insight-asset-management</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With SAP solutions, Jowat empowered its technicians to prioritize work more effectively and make smarter decisions about asset investments.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/asset-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-enterprise-support</category>
            <category>product/sap-integrated-business-planning-for-supply-chain</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Coles Reimagines Volume Hiring with AI and Automation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/coles-reimagines-volume-hiring-with-ai-and-automation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/coles-reimagines-volume-hiring-with-ai-and-automation</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Coles uses an AI-powered solution integrated with SAP SuccessFactors to help revolutionize its hiring process and gain speed and efficiency.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_149ed3b06f07dcdc3485b441db14e19620bea42c6.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_149ed3b06f07dcdc3485b441db14e19620bea42c6.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_149ed3b06f07dcdc3485b441db14e19620bea42c6.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Coles Reimagines Volume Hiring with AI and Automation" src="./media_149ed3b06f07dcdc3485b441db14e19620bea42c6.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="coles-reimagines-volume-hiring-with-ai-and-automation">Coles Reimagines Volume Hiring with AI and Automation</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div><a href="https://www.colesgroup.com.au/home/">Coles Group</a>, one of Australia’s most trusted and iconic brands, is steadfast in delivering on its purpose to help Australians eat and live better every day. Through its core business as a full-service supermarket retailer, Coles engages with millions of customers every week in its 860 supermarkets throughout Australia. The group’s other areas of business include its Click &#x26; Collect online platform, network of liquor stores, and financial services with nearly 1,000 additional retail outlets.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Guided by the organization’s clear <a href="https://colescareers.com.au/au/en/culture">vision, purpose, and strategy</a>, Coles’ team of 120,000 employees is dedicated to making a difference in the lives of customers and the local communities it serves.</p>
  <p>In fiscal year 2020/21, Coles Group hired nearly 30,000 people to deliver on its business needs. Mike Virgo, head of Talent Acquisition for Coles Group, said this hiring volume was necessary to make sure the company was “positioned well to support our customers.”</p>
  <p>The business environment, however, dramatically shifted as the public health crisis of the pandemic unfolded, resulting in repeated lockdowns and restrictions. As a neighborhood retailer dependent on in-person interaction to deliver most of its services, Coles found its workforce impacted by the pandemic. Faced with supply chain disruptions, panic buying behaviors by consumers, high employee absenteeism, and increased turnover, Coles urgently needed to step up its volume and pace of hiring to support its customers.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="create-ai-powered-experiences-that-drive-real-competitive-advantage-with-sap-successfactors">Create AI-powered experiences that drive real competitive advantage with SAP SuccessFactors</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>“Around 2020-2021, we started to experience one of the most significant shifts in the employment market we’d ever seen,” Virgo said in a <a href="https://go3.events.sap.com/successconnect/virtual/2023/reg/flow/sap/sc23/catalog/page/catalog/session/1693098679863001ykJ6">session</a> at <a href="https://www.sap.com/events/successconnect/virtual.html?campaigncode=CRM-YI23-HXM-2055448&#x26;source=text-glo-SAPNews">SuccessConnect Virtual</a>. “It started to create huge challenges for organizations around the world – around how we attract, retain, and hire talent.”</p>
  <h2 id="catalyst-for-change-and-a-new-way-of-working">Catalyst for Change and a New Way of Working</h2>
  <p>To meet pressing business demands, Coles doubled its hiring volume from 30,000 to 60,000 people and increased recruitment advertising spend by a factor of three. Its talent acquisition team grew proportionally to manage the increased workload – but then labored under manual transactional activities that slowed processing times. As a result of the huge strain, variability in the candidate and hiring manager experience became noticeable.</p>
  <p>Due to the volume of work, Coles looked for ways to evolve its system to create more speed, efficiency, and scalability. With a list of criteria, Coles began to review technology solutions on the market to find one that could support its vision for a new way of working. “We wanted to reimagine how we recruit for our stores,” Virgo said. “We needed automation and AI to remove a lot of the manual work in our systems. We wanted to create more consistency and uplift the experiences we were giving our candidates and our hiring managers. And ultimately, [the solution] needed to drive commercial benefit for us.”</p>
  <p>As a key requirement, the new solution needed to integrate with <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hcm/what-is-hxm-suite.html">SAP SuccessFactors Human Experience Management (HXM) Suite</a>. In 2020, as part of an organization-wide <a href="/australia/2021/09/08/how-coles-group-is-transforming-hr-during-the-global-pandemic">digital transformation</a> that introduced SAP S/4HANA and SAP Ariba solutions, Coles modernized its HR and payroll processing, replacing a patchwork of outdated systems with SAP SuccessFactors solutions. It became the first organization in the southern hemisphere to launch all modules of the SAP SuccessFactors portfolio in one go. With all HR processes unified on a single platform, Coles benefits from having a single source of truth for people data that is accurate and available in real time for the entire organization.</p>
  <h2 id="two-way-integration-ensures-single-source-of-truth-in-data">Two-Way Integration Ensures Single Source of Truth in Data</h2>
  <p>To help with the project, Coles chose <a href="https://www.phenom.com/">Phenom</a>, an SAP partner whose AI-powered Intelligent Talent Experience platform provides two-way integration with SAP SuccessFactors solutions. Virgo said the two-way integration “allows us to have a holistic view of the candidates that progress through the process, no matter whether the team is operating in Phenom or SAP SuccessFactors, and it allows SAP SuccessFactors to be our single source of truth.”</p>
  <p>There are several key benefits of Phenom’s solution at Coles. One is candidate attraction and engagement, which is achieved primarily through the Coles career site and chatbot. Another is recruiter automation and interview management, which provides automation and process efficiencies from when a job requisition is created in SAP SuccessFactors solutions and replicated into Phenom until a hiring manager chooses a candidate for the job. Once a candidate is chosen, the two-way integration enables the HR team to access the data in SAP SuccessFactors solutions and complete all compliance aspects, such as working rights, contract generation, and onboarding.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-how-phenom-can-compliment-sap-successfactors-recruiting">Learn how Phenom can compliment SAP SuccessFactors Recruiting</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://store.sap.com/dcp/en/product/display-2001007992_live_v1">Find out</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The Coles team gains additional efficiencies in its onboarding programs through the application of robotic process automation (RPA) powered by two bots that work in the background: <em>Ashbotty</em> processes the working rights and <em>Usain Bot</em> processes onboarding and manages pending recruits. “They take a lot of the transactional, manual work that we used to have team members doing. It can do that quickly, accurately, and it can do that 24/7 – which is particularly important for us as a seven-days-a-week business,” Virgo said.</p>
  <h2 id="ai-powered-experiences-for-candidates-and-recruiters">AI-Powered Experiences for Candidates and Recruiters</h2>
  <p>Coles reimagined the candidate experience to launch a modern, tech-enabled career site – which has been chosen as a two-time winner of Australia’s Best Careers Site. The site includes an AI-powered chatbot to guide candidates as they look for information, search relevant job postings, and submit their applications. It also includes Coles’ Expression of Interest, always-on advertising that drives the growth of its talent pool and advances its talent marketing by reducing the need to advertise every role. A Hosted Apply process, facilitated by integrations with Phenom, presents a consistent candidate experience and increases the conversion rate on applications.</p>
  <p>Phenom AI Scheduling, a key part of Coles’ hiring experience, enables candidates to book themselves an available interview slot and automates the coordination of hiring team calendars. The new solution provides a fully mobile-enabled experience to meet the demands of candidates for an omni-channel, real-time experience where they can learn, read, and apply for jobs where and when they want.</p>
  <p>Inundated by nearly 1 million applications each year to review, Coles also took steps to elevate the recruiter experience and increase the speed and accuracy of candidate screening and job matching. It implemented Phenom Fit Score, an AI-powered feature that assesses a candidate’s suitability for an open role, based on location and optimal travel distances, availability, and working rights; then, assigns a fit score and surfaces the most closely matched candidates to the recruiters. In addition, the new solution empowers in-store managers to collaborate with recruiters to review candidates and make quick hiring decisions with confidence.</p>
  <h2 id="talent-pools-grow-with-improvements-to-hiring-speed-and-efficiency">Talent Pools Grow with Improvements to Hiring Speed and Efficiency</h2>
  <p>With the new augmented solution, Coles is experiencing tangible benefits across multiple categories and key metrics for success: time-to-fill is down six days; time-to-hire is down two days, which is impressive considering candidates can book the in-store interview up to two weeks in advance; and advertising spend is down 50%.</p>
  <p>Most notably for Coles as a people-centric organization is the development of its talent pool, now numbering 2 million potential candidates. It achieves an 85% application conversion rate on up to 1 million applications per year. Through its <a href="https://www.colesgroup.com.au/media-releases/?page=coles-group-ranked-1-for-recruitment-of-aussies-with-disabilities">commitment</a> to be a safe, inclusive, and diverse workplace, Coles has applied the new solution to provide greater accessibility for more diverse candidates, resulting in an increase of 24% more hiring for people who identify as having a disability.</p>
  <p>Virgo said that the talent acquisition team will continue to evolve its solution and assess more opportunities for AI and automation to bring value to the recruitment process. Although these technologies are not cure-alls for every recruitment scenario, they can save recruiting teams precious time and resources to focus on more high-touch interactions further down the recruiting funnel. In sharing lessons learned, Virgo noted, “I think the important call out is the level of automation you can inject in your process will likely diminish as the seniority, complexity, and requirements of your roles increase because they are likely to be more high touch, perhaps need more interpretation or judgment calls from your recruiters to identify who the right talent is for your organization.”</p>
  <p>Watch <a href="https://www.sap.com/events/successconnect/virtual.html?campaigncode=CRM-YI23-HXM-2055448&#x26;source=text-glo-SAPNews">SuccessConnect Virtual</a> on demand.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="follow-sap-news-on-linkedin-to-stay-up-to-date">Follow SAP News on LinkedIn to stay up-to-date</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/automation</category>
            <category>industry/consumer-goods-cpg</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>news-tag/recruiting</category>
            <category>industry/retail</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
            <category>sap-event/successconnect</category>
            <category>news-tag/talent-acquisition</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Digital Transformation Helps Companies Keep Promises]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/digital-transformation-helps-keep-promises-blue-diamond</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/digital-transformation-helps-keep-promises-blue-diamond</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Innovation Award winner Blue Diamond Growers transformed for brand success, enhanced customer relationships, and supply chain visibility.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/scm</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/consumer-goods-cpg</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>sap-award/sap-innovation-awards</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Empowering the City of Antibes to Redefine Digital Contract Management]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/city-of-antibes-redefines-digital-contract-management</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/city-of-antibes-redefines-digital-contract-management</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The City of Antibes and SAP Innovation Center Network are revamping digital contract management with a focus on public procurement processes.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10b8e8e68a4e4aa39731dd6f73e4b22d1f8d1d59f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10b8e8e68a4e4aa39731dd6f73e4b22d1f8d1d59f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_10b8e8e68a4e4aa39731dd6f73e4b22d1f8d1d59f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Empowering the City of Antibes to Redefine Digital Contract Management" src="./media_10b8e8e68a4e4aa39731dd6f73e4b22d1f8d1d59f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="empowering-the-city-of-antibes-to-redefine-digital-contract-management">Empowering the City of Antibes to Redefine Digital Contract Management</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>In the era of digital transformation, multi-company processes governed by legal contracts are becoming increasingly common. With the untapped potential of decentralized processes, there is a growing prospect for digitizing and automating collaborative contract management, streamlining operations, and reducing risks and costs.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Recognizing this potential, the City of Antibes and <a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/innovation/icn.html">SAP Innovation Center Network</a> have joined forces to redefine digital contract management with a focus on public procurement processes. Patrick Duverger, chief technology officer of the City of Antibes, describes its previous procurement operations as follows: “Although we achieved a high level of operational proficiency, our business processes lacked full traceability. This resulted in process opacity when it comes to recurring delays, delivery errors, or administrative sanctions. By gaining a deeper understanding of our processes, we can optimize them, reduce costs, and minimize business risks.”</p>
  <h2 id="transparent-and-traceable-collaboration">Transparent and Traceable Collaboration</h2>
  <p>The lack of visibility and traceability in these processes hindered automation, cross-organizational data and process mining, and intelligence. This directly affected how disputes were resolved and impacted organizational budgets.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="build-and-deploy-intelligent-data-applications-at-scale-with-sap-hana-cloud">Build and deploy intelligent data applications at scale with SAP HANA Cloud</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/technology-platform/hana.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>To address this challenge, SAP Innovation Center Network developed a prototype based on the <a href="https://d.dam.sap.com/a/1vxdhV8/Cross-Company%20Workflow%20-%20One%20pager%289%29%20%20-%20%20Read-Only.pdf?rc=10">SAP Cross-Company Workflow Collaboration</a> service, combined with a blockchain-based shared ledger on SAP HANA Cloud. “This prototype aims to replace manual practices with automated, cross-company orchestrations. By using an SAP HANA Cloud shared ledger, organizations like the City of Antibes can benefit from a permissioned, publicly verifiable, and immutable audit trail of cross-organizational interactions,” says Benjamin Stoeckhert, innovation product manager at SAP Innovation Center Network, illustrating the potential of this innovation.</p>
  <p>“Leveraging the full potential of an SAP HANA Cloud shared ledger allows us to connect digital platforms that unite businesses and government to track the compliance of services and product deliveries according to contractual terms and conditions,” explains Duverger. “We can leverage data from different parties, such as logistics companies and quality certification bodies, and move beyond the era of cumbersome paperwork and manual processes. For example, this pattern is applicable to procurement processes where multiple parties verify the compliance of suppliers and their deliveries.”</p>
  <h2 id="complete-control-of-unencrypted-data">Complete Control of Unencrypted Data</h2>
  <p>However, opening up collaborative processes directly conflicts with customer privacy concerns. This dilemma poses a significant challenge for next-generation contract management. How can businesses ensure transparency without compromising the privacy of private business information and processes? Duverger emphasizes the importance of protecting sensitive public procurement secrets: “Confidentiality, including negotiated prices and deal sizes, is paramount for us and our suppliers.”</p>
  <p>In response to this pressing need, the SAP Security Research team, in collaboration with the SAP Innovation Center Network blockchain team, has extended SAP Cross-Company Workflow Collaboration with a hardware-based privacy-enhancing technology (PET) innovation. Dr. Laurent Gomez, who led this innovation with Antibes, explains: “Before committing a transaction to the shared ledger, organizations encrypt it along with its associated sensitive information, using their own managed cryptographic material. Encrypted data and processes are only processed within secure and trusted hardware modules, with the explicit consent of each stakeholder.”</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="future-focused-solutions-can-solve-todays-challenges-and-shape-the-next-generation-of-enterprise-software">Future-focused solutions can solve today’s challenges and shape the next generation of enterprise software</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/about/company/innovation/icn.html">Learn how</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>This innovation can unlock significant business value by helping to automate cross-company operations and protect the privacy of customer data while still allowing for analysis. The key contribution of this approach is that it gives customers complete control and ownership of their encrypted material. “SAP can never access unencrypted data; the only data that leaves our information system is encrypted by us,” says Duverger. “SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP) allows us to hold our own encryption keys, which is different from competing solutions.”</p>
  <h2 id="less-late-payment-penalty-costs">5% Less Late Payment Penalty Costs</h2>
  <p>The co-innovation has revealed the bottlenecks that slow down the procurement process at the City of Antibes and lead to late payment penalties for suppliers and delivery delays. “By adopting this secure distributed ledger approach, we have improved these key performance indicators without changing the process itself. We can now reliably manage all our procurement transactions,” says Duverger. “A key achievement was that we reduced our delinquency rate by 5%, which significantly minimized the impact of late payment penalty costs on our global spend budget.”</p>
  <p>The project was recently recognized at the highest national level with the Territoria Gold Award by the French Ministries of the Interior, Ecological Transition, and Territorial Cohesion.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a39ac04a061b0b54756921e032f354640f916943.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1a39ac04a061b0b54756921e032f354640f916943.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1a39ac04a061b0b54756921e032f354640f916943.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_1a39ac04a061b0b54756921e032f354640f916943.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="681">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>© Niclas Fagot Studio9</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>To find out more about SAP Cross-Company Workflow, get in touch with us at <a href="mailto:icn@sap.com">icn@sap.com</a>.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Corinna Schmidt is part of NVT Communication at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="stay-in-touch-and-connect-with-sap-news-on-linkedin">Stay in touch and connect with SAP News on LinkedIn</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/showcase/sap-news">Follow us</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/blockchain</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>product/sap-hana-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-innovation-center-network</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Beyond Gravity’s All-Out Mission to the Cloud]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/beyond-gravity-all-out-mission-to-cloud</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/beyond-gravity-all-out-mission-to-cloud</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Beyond Gravity wants its new ERP system to leverage all the benefits of the cloud. That’s why it chose SAP S/4HANA Cloud, public edition.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_113a605ea1984c28f221f383c1bceeb834e36b214.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_113a605ea1984c28f221f383c1bceeb834e36b214.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_113a605ea1984c28f221f383c1bceeb834e36b214.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Beyond Gravity’s All-Out Mission to the Cloud" src="./media_113a605ea1984c28f221f383c1bceeb834e36b214.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="beyond-gravitys-all-out-mission-to-the-cloud">Beyond Gravity’s All-Out Mission to the Cloud</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>As it seeks to modernize its software environment, Beyond Gravity wants to take full advantage of the cloud. That’s why this leading supplier to the space industry is on an all-out mission to move its enterprise resource planning (ERP) system to SAP S/4HANA Cloud, public edition.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>While catastrophic asteroid impacts have been rare in Earth’s history, the threat asteroids pose to life on our planet is very real. With that in mind, NASA and ESA launched a mission in 2021 to test a method of planetary defense that involved deflecting Dimorphos – one part of the Didymos double-asteroid system – from its orbit by crashing a spacecraft into it. In part two of the mission, due to begin in October 2024, an orbiter known as “Hera” will lift off and, in October 2026, begin examining the effects of the test on Dimorphos.</p>
  <h2 id="beyond-gravity-space-technology-that-protects-the-planet">Beyond Gravity: Space Technology That Protects the Planet</h2>
  <p>“Protecting Earth from asteroids that could pose a threat to us all is an exciting and important task,” says Johan Eckerstein, CIO at <a href="https://www.beyondgravity.com/en">Beyond Gravity</a>. Headquartered in Switzerland, Beyond Gravity is one of a group of suppliers of high-tech equipment for Hera and is responsible for delivering the spacecraft’s two solar wings. In addition to a variety of satellite components, the space technology specialist also builds launch vehicles, and a third, smaller division serves the growing lithography market. According to <a href="https://tracxn.com/d/companies/beyond-gravity/__QK2dffK8fa4oRH-CPhnHBwvcMXuZWSoULX-BlkhJ9pg">market intelligence platform Tracxn</a>, Beyond Gravity ranks third among 21 competitors in its field.</p>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_108755bdc5e12d7d14543f48c7855cb4f4c61bb27.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_108755bdc5e12d7d14543f48c7855cb4f4c61bb27.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_108755bdc5e12d7d14543f48c7855cb4f4c61bb27.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_108755bdc5e12d7d14543f48c7855cb4f4c61bb27.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="742">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>Image courtesy of Beyond Gravity.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="lightbox">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14b0ad30a9b8b56ddb5fda4631cadf07d864b5982.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_14b0ad30a9b8b56ddb5fda4631cadf07d864b5982.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_14b0ad30a9b8b56ddb5fda4631cadf07d864b5982.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="" src="./media_14b0ad30a9b8b56ddb5fda4631cadf07d864b5982.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1024" height="681">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <p><em>Johan Eckerstein. Image courtesy of Beyond Gravity.</em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="ezyone-transformation-project-flight-path-to-the-future">EZYOne Transformation Project: Flight Path to the Future</h2>
  <p>“Our ambition is to be the No. 1 space technology supplier, the most innovative and most exciting company to work for,” says Eckerstein. As CIO, his job is to put the technology in place to make that vision a reality. The EZYOne program he initiated in October 2022 was a crucial first step in that process.</p>
  <p>Beyond Gravity is the legal successor to RUAG Space, the space division of Swiss technology group RUAG International. So while it only began operating as a startup under its new name in May 2022, it has decades of experience in the space industry. With the company due to be privatized soon, its EZYOne digital transformation project is as necessary as it is challenging.</p>
  <p>As the name implies, the idea is to make things easier. Beyond Gravity has historically grown from various companies and locations. Currently, there are various sites with different IT systems that are not linked to each other.</p>
  <p>With EZYOne, Beyond Gravity is preparing to become a digital-first company that will leverage artificial intelligence (AI), machine learning, augmented reality (AR), and many other emerging technologies. The first step is to build a common digital core that will enable the company to unlock tremendous value and new ways to serve customers.</p>
  <h2 id="sap-s4hana-cloud-public-edition-seven-becomes-one">SAP S/4HANA Cloud, Public Edition: Seven Becomes One</h2>
  <p>Each of Beyond Gravity’s business divisions has built up its own vast pool of expertise over the years. But when it comes to IT, the company’s colorful history means it now has a mishmash of legacy systems – comprising seven different ERP systems alone – and, thus, an array of complex, inefficient, and costly processes.</p>
  <h2 id="it-solutions-in-use-at-beyond-gravity-in-2023">IT solutions in use at Beyond Gravity in 2023</h2>
  <ul>
    <li>7 ERP systems</li>
    <li>8 product lifecycle management (PLM) systems</li>
    <li>5 business process management systems</li>
    <li>2 manufacturing execution systems (MES)</li>
  </ul>
  <p>EZYOne lifted off in October 2022. “We began by defining the architecture we wanted for our new IT landscape,” explains Eckerstein. That process led to a number of design principles aimed at ensuring the project was a success. They included:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>One solution of each type for all business units</li>
    <li>Cloud first</li>
    <li>Standard first (out of the box)</li>
    <li>No technical data in the ERP system</li>
    <li>Rapid go-live in the first quarter of 2024</li>
  </ul>
  <p>When it came to selecting an ERP solution – and based on these criteria – Beyond Gravity opted for SAP S/4HANA Cloud, public edition. “From the perspective of an agile startup and the global market leader we aspire to become, cloud is the only way to go,” says Eckerstein. “When you choose a cloud solution, you are committing more to a provider’s road map than to a static product. And, as a midsize company, we can benefit from a vendor like SAP that has the infrastructure and resources to provide the solution reliably and securely.” This, he adds, eases the pressure on IT teams and frees up time for value-adding tasks.</p>
  <h2 id="standard-covers-92-of-processes">Standard Covers 92% of Processes</h2>
  <p>Eckerstein points out, however, that if you want to enjoy the benefits of the public cloud, you have to be consistent in your approach. Essentially, when you transform business processes, that means sticking as far as possible to the standard version of the public cloud solution. Beyond Gravity defined the following rules:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>80% of processes must be covered by the standard – and adapted to it if necessary.</li>
    <li>Key processes not covered by the standard must be added to SAP’s to-do list and implemented within a specified time frame.</li>
    <li>Where non-key processes are not covered by the standard, alternatives must be explored, such as a third-party solution, manual process, or other neat solution.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>The result of this approach surprised even Eckerstein: “We managed to cover 92% of all processes with the standard solution. And in finance, we didn’t find a single gap!” There were many other practical benefits, such as:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Managers can be able to call up a status overview of all projects in real time – for any country or currency – with just a few clicks.</li>
    <li>Intracompany processes can become more efficient, thanks to the option of using fully automated ordering and confirmation and in-transit goods tracking.</li>
  </ul>
  <p>The percentage of processes not covered by the standard may be small, but it can represent a huge gap if even one of those processes is mission-critical.</p>
  <p>Beyond Gravity has also got SAP – SAP Switzerland, to be precise – on board as an implementation partner to give it the most direct line possible to the SAP developers working on the cloud ERP solution.</p>
  <h2 id="public-cloud-erp-a-calculated-risk">Public Cloud ERP: A Calculated Risk</h2>
  <p>Beyond Gravity is now halfway along the project timeline. The solution was completed in September 2023 and is currently in its initial testing phase – with the first go-live scheduled for March 2024 in Sweden. “This kind of speed is only possible in the public cloud,” says Eckerstein, “and only if you adopt the right mindset.” In other words, if you want to enjoy the benefits of the public cloud, you have to be willing to take a certain amount of risk that you would avoid with an on-premise installation and trust that the provider’s road map will take you where you want to go. But, as Eckerstein adds, “This has nothing to do with blind trust; it’s about objectively calculating the risks involved.”</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Top image courtesy of SAP employee Trupti Warad</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/aerospace-defense</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Solarpack Scales Up Renewable Energy for the World Stage]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/solarpack-scales-up-renewable-energy-for-world</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/solarpack-scales-up-renewable-energy-for-world</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Working with a combination of experts and solutions from SAP empowered Solarpack to rethink its digital landscape. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>topic/sustainability</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/grow-with-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/renewable-energy</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ATS Connects HR Processes to Build a Future-Ready Workforce]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/ats-connects-hr-processes-future-ready-workforce</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/ats-connects-hr-processes-future-ready-workforce</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[To modernize its core HR and talent management systems, ATS chose SAP SuccessFactors and its next-generation cloud HR technology. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/employee-experience</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-successfactors</category>
            <category>product/sap-successfactors-hxm-suite</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Western Sugar Cooperative Achieves Cost Optimization and Efficiency with SAP S/4HANA Cloud, Public Edition]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/western-sugar-cooperative-sap-s4hana-cloud-public-edition</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/western-sugar-cooperative-sap-s4hana-cloud-public-edition</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The adoption of SAP S/4HANA Cloud marked a significant moment in the technological transformation of Western Sugar Cooperative. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/sme</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>industry/agribusiness</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>product/sap-s4hana-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Driving Business Outcomes for ONEX Holding with Digital Customer Engagement]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/onex-holding-digital-customer-engagement</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/onex-holding-digital-customer-engagement</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The relationship between ONEX and SAP shows how virtual immersive engagements can enable and scale human interactions, not diminish them.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-engagement</category>
            <category>news-tag/customer-story</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>