<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/news-tag/business-process-transformation/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Signavio Again Leads the 2024 SPARK Matrix™ for Digital Twin of an Organization]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/sap-signavio-leads-2024-spark-matrix-digital-twin-organization</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/sap-signavio-leads-2024-spark-matrix-digital-twin-organization</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Signavio is a Leader in the 2024 SPARK Matrix for Digital Twin of an Organization (DTO) for the fourth consecutive year. Read more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/business-process-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/business-process-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-twin</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-signavio</category>
            <category>product/sap-signavio-process-explorer</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Signavio Is a Leader in the 2024 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Process Mining Platforms]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/sap-signavio-a-leader-2024-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-process-mining-platforms</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2024/05/sap-signavio-a-leader-2024-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-process-mining-platforms</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In the 2024 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Process Mining, SAP Signavio has again been recognized as a Leader. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_138b3ef0b5b24b564b18da25ef3b2cde982bba0f8.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_138b3ef0b5b24b564b18da25ef3b2cde982bba0f8.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_138b3ef0b5b24b564b18da25ef3b2cde982bba0f8.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Signavio Is a Leader in the 2024 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Process Mining Platforms" src="./media_138b3ef0b5b24b564b18da25ef3b2cde982bba0f8.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-signavio-is-a-leader-in-the-2024-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-process-mining-platforms">SAP Signavio Is a Leader in the 2024 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Process Mining Platforms</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>In the 2024 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Process Mining, SAP Signavio has once again been recognized as a Leader in the market based on Completeness of Vision and Ability to Execute.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="complimentary-copy-2024-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-process-mining-platforms">Complimentary copy: 2024 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Process Mining Platforms</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.signavio.com/downloads/analyst-reports/2024-gartner-magic-quadrant-process-mining/">Download yours here</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>This is the second year in a row that SAP Signavio has been positioned as a Leader in the report. We believe that this positioning implies that SAP Signavio is a key driver for SAP’s growth and long-term strategy.</p>
  <p>According to the Gartner Magic Quadrant research methodology, “Leaders execute well against their current vision and are well positioned for tomorrow.”</p>
  <p>Our solutions solve today’s real and diverse customer use cases — operational excellence, compliance, automation, transformation, etc.– and recognizes that we have a compelling vision for a future in which process automation and process AI open up new opportunities for our customers and partners.</p>
  <p>SAP Signavio continues to focus on ensuring the long-term success of all of our customers and partners.</p>
  <h2 id="revenue-nsw">Revenue NSW</h2>
  <p>In the Australian state of New South Wales, the tax collected by Revenue NSW accounts for more than 35% of finances, helping fund essential services, from healthcare to education and policing.</p>
  <p>With a vision to be the world’s most innovative and customer-centric revenue agency, Revenue NSW set out with a very specific objective: it wanted to analyze cases in which clients had overpaid land tax to identify why these overpayments occur and what experience clients received when obtaining refunds. This analysis would not only help reduce overpayment volumes and improve the client experience, but also enable the agency to work more efficiently for its diverse stakeholders.</p>
  <p>“As part of our Aspire 2032 strategy, our vision is to be the world’s most innovative and customer-centric revenue collection agency,” shared Jocelyn Yem, director of Strategy and Innovation at Revenue NSW.”‘Embrace Innovation’ is one of our strategic focus areas, where we can respond to our customers’ needs by embedding a culture of continuous improvement. SAP Signavio Process Intelligence has helped us achieve our first stage in this journey.”</p>
  <p>“SAP Signavio Process Intelligence has painted a clear picture of why clients pay too much land tax and how we can process refunds smoothly, along with a detailed road map to help us put these insights into action,” confirmed Sabrina Bazouni, director of Land Tax at Revenue NSW.</p>
  <h2 id="fujitsu-limited">Fujitsu Limited</h2>
  <p>Recognizing the wide-ranging effect of business process transformation solutions, Fujitsu Limited has embraced SAP Signavio solutions across its operations and portfolio.</p>
  <p>At one of its manufacturing plants in Japan, Fujitsu used the SAP Signavio Process Intelligence solution to gather process execution data directly from the shop floor into the continuous improvement model the company had been using for many years. Integrating process data into the Kaizen discussions delivered never-before-seen insights, which helped the company further optimize its shop-floor processes and transform their Kaizen from traditional to digital, using process mining to generate data-driven insights.</p>
  <p>This firsthand experience of the solutions has also allowed Fujitsu to enrich its customer offerings with new frameworks, insights, and tools that can help customers realign their organizations and make changes at speed.</p>
  <p>Having seen the potential of SAP Signavio solutions, Fujitsu now plans to extend its use both internally and externally. One such planned initiative involves combining the concepts of the digital twin on an organization and the intelligent enterprise, using business process transformation solutions as the mechanism of change.</p>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Download a <a href="https://www.signavio.com/downloads/analyst-reports/2024-gartner-magic-quadrant-process-mining/">complimentary copy of the report here</a>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Dee Houchen is global head of Market Impact for SAP Signavio.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="optimize-and-transform-business-processes-fast-and-at-scale">Optimize and transform business processes fast and at scale</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-process-transformation.html">Learn how</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Gartner, Magic Quadrant for Process Mining Platforms, Marc Kerremans, David Sugden, Nick Duffy, 29 April 2024</p>
  <p>GARTNER is a registered trademark and service mark of Gartner, Inc. and/or its affiliates in the U.S. and internationally, and MAGIC QUADRANT is a registered trademark of Gartner, Inc. and/or its affiliates and are used herein with permission. All rights reserved. Gartner does not endorse any vendor, product or service depicted in its research publications, and does not advise technology users to select only those vendors with the highest ratings or other designation. Gartner research publications consist of the opinions of Gartner’s research organization and should not be construed as statements of fact. Gartner disclaims all warranties, expressed or implied, with respect to this research, including any warranties of merchantability or fitness for a particular purpose.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/customers</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/business-process-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/magic-quadrant</category>
            <category>news-tag/process-mining</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-signavio</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Future of Process Optimization Is Powered by AI]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/future-process-optimization-powered-by-ai</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/12/future-process-optimization-powered-by-ai</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The future of process optimization in enterprises is an exciting landscape, and AI is at its core. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10cadca47ca5934553211f92ce47fff1de251e879.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_10cadca47ca5934553211f92ce47fff1de251e879.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_10cadca47ca5934553211f92ce47fff1de251e879.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="The Future of Process Optimization Is Powered by AI" src="./media_10cadca47ca5934553211f92ce47fff1de251e879.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="the-future-of-process-optimization-is-powered-by-ai">The Future of Process Optimization Is Powered by AI</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>In today’s fast-paced world, AI-powered personal assistants have become ubiquitous in helping us navigate our daily lives. From suggesting the fastest route to work to recommending our favorite movies, these virtual companions have seamlessly integrated into our routines.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="see-how-you-can-benefit-from-sap-business-ai-built-into-your-core-business-processes">See how you can benefit from SAP Business AI built into your core business processes</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/artificial-intelligence.html">Learn more</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>But what about a personal guide to navigate the complex realm of enterprise technology? The future of process optimization is closer than you might think, and it’s being powered by AI.</p>
  <p>Leading business software providers are making significant strides in embedding personalized guidance and strategies for enhancing business processes directly into the enterprise solutions that companies already use.</p>
  <p>Looking to grow your business? Streamline specific processes? Or maybe derisk your supply chain? Imagine the future where the software itself could tell you how to best use it to achieve your specific business goals. In fact, <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/patrickmoorhead/2023/05/30/sap-wants-to-future-proof-businesses-with-ai/?sh=153760295df9">software providers</a> are hard at work embedding personalized guidance and strategies for improving business processes directly into the enterprise solutions you already use. And they’re putting AI up to the task.</p>
  <h2 id="realizing-the-art-of-the-ai-possible">Realizing the Art of the AI Possible</h2>
  <p>Your phone can tell you how much time you spend using it, providing insight into how often you tap into specific apps. But capabilities like these leave you to analyze and act on that usage data all by yourself. For example, if you’re scrolling for three hours a day on a social media site, your phone probably is not going to tell you that’s too much time, let alone suggest steps for taking a social media detox.</p>
  <p>Future enterprise software will be much more intelligent than this. Right now, you can likely tap into that same sort of data on how often employees use individual enterprise software solutions, or even how much time they spend on specific processes. However, it is hard to know what to do with these data insights other than wonder why your workers are spending so long processing invoices, onboarding new employees, or completing any number of other tasks.</p>
  <p>By combining your software usage data, existing processes, and business goals, AI will be able provide you with actionable steps toward better business processes that help achieve those goals. All this, embedded right into the solutions you already use. It’s this combination of human and artificial intelligence that adds the most value and enables your organization to become an <a href="https://www.sap.com/intelligent-enterprise.html">intelligent enterprise</a>.</p>
  <h2 id="creating-the-intelligent-enterprise">Creating the Intelligent Enterprise</h2>
  <p>Say your company implemented SAP Concur solutions to help employees book and expense business travel. For many businesses, processing travel expense documentation is not a core competency so the opportunity to streamline the process creates efficiencies for the business. Using AI and machine learning, SAP Concur taps years of expense user data that helps identify hard-to-detect spend issues and anomalies. That same technology powers <a href="https://www.concur.com/blog/article/making-impact-with-verify">Verify</a>, a self-serve audit function within the solution, that is then augmented with a team of human auditors to create great accuracy.</p>
  <p>The same can said about <a href="/2023/09/hr-flow-of-work-ux-evolution">generative AI use cases</a> that enable leaders and recruiters to create job descriptions and find ideal candidates or help employees find personalized learning recommendations to fuel their career progression. These efforts help organizations hire and develop employees at scale, creating a future-ready workforce.</p>
  <p>Or perhaps you need to anticipate supply chain issues impacted by incoming weather — AI can enhance supply chain efficiency by predicting demand, optimizing inventory levels, and identifying potential disruptions before they occur. According to McKinsey, implementing AI-enabled supply chain management solutions has already <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2023/11/07/how-ai-makes-it-easier-to-bring-your-holiday-meal-to-the-table/?sh=fc10e94404b8">allowed those early adopters to improve their logistics costs by 15%, their inventory levels by 35%, and their service levels by 65%</a> compared to those who do not use them. No matter the business problem you are trying to solve, the potential for process optimization with AI is endless and, combined with human intelligence, can deliver better results than either could independently.</p>
  <h2 id="unlocking-an-ai-guide-to-the-cloud">Unlocking an AI Guide to the Cloud</h2>
  <p>The future of process optimization in enterprises is an exciting landscape, and <a href="https://www.gatesnotes.com/AI-agents">AI is at its core</a>. Often, the first step for businesses on the path to digital excellence is embarking on cloud transformation. The futures of the cloud and AI are intrinsically linked. As business software providers embed the power of AI — such as our <a href="/2023/09/joule-new-generative-ai-assistant">generative-AI copilot Joule</a> — into their offerings, it allows for data-driven insights that are relevant, reliable, and responsible.</p>
  <p>If you have already begun a digital transformation in the cloud, AI can equip you to optimize your processes for cloud-based operations. Modern core business technology, such as SAP S/4HANA Cloud, serves as an innovation engine that enables you to take advantage of next-generation technology virtually without limits. In the future, when you integrate AI-enhanced software solutions with SAP S/4HANA Cloud, you will ideally be able to optimize processes from end to end across your entire software landscape.</p>
  <p>It’s akin to the way modern luxury vehicles can tell you how to drive in more fuel-efficient ways by analyzing all the parts — and their individual functions — that come together to move you forward. But good business practices shouldn’t be a luxury. As AI technology continues to advance, it promises to revolutionize various aspects of enterprise technology, creating a more connected, intelligent, and optimized business environment.</p>
  <p>The AI-powered guide to the world of enterprise technology is already here, and it’s taking businesses to new heights.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>Claudio Muruzabal is president of Cloud Success Services at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/cloud</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/business-process-transformation</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Process Observability: Your Business Is More Than a Sum of Its Parts]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/process-observability-business-more-than-its-parts</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/11/process-observability-business-more-than-its-parts</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Process observability provides a better understanding of the state and performance of how work is getting done within an organization.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_19b273d79858e2abb30e355ef1eb651a331198d4f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_19b273d79858e2abb30e355ef1eb651a331198d4f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_19b273d79858e2abb30e355ef1eb651a331198d4f.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Process Observability: Your Business Is More Than a Sum of Its Parts" src="./media_19b273d79858e2abb30e355ef1eb651a331198d4f.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1920" height="600">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="process-observability-your-business-is-more-than-a-sum-of-its-parts">Process Observability: Your Business Is More Than a Sum of Its Parts</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>The promise of digital transformation has been to leverage technology in ways that simplify and streamline our work lives. We love Amazon’s “click to buy” button, which sends nearly any product we can think of to our doorsteps in a matter of hours. In our work lives, we can now collaborate on documents in real time, take video conferencing for granted, look to AI bots to record our action items, and more.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Luckily, as consumers, we rarely have to look underneath the surface, onto the complexity required to make these systems function. Businesses aren’t that lucky. As business processes become more and more digitized, it is more important than ever to understand the impact of operational systems on business outcomes and to align business strategy with IT architecture.</p>
  <p>It’s like watching your favorite professional sports team – everyone can be an armchair expert, but fielding a winning team week after week and year after year takes consistent and ongoing effort. Coaches and players need to work together, pulling in data from various sources and applying creative, exploratory analysis to discern the best strategy, mental and physical fitness, and tactics needed to win a particular match. Every business decision is like a new match and the schedule has become more crowded and the stakes higher.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="learn-more-about-process-observability-in-an-idc-report">Learn more about process observability in an IDC report</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.signavio.com/downloads/white-papers/business-process-observability/">Download it</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>In the same way, businesses need to take a holistic team view that looks at the health of the overall business, identifies key processes and functions, and creates the opportunity for improvement and change. This team view requires understanding end-to-end business processes, the operational systems they touch, and how well they meet business goals as well as the needs of customers and employees. As businesses look to drive complicated business and technology transformation faster, at scale, and with more confidence, they are turning to the emerging practice of process observability.</p>
  <h2 id="what-is-process-observability">What Is Process Observability?</h2>
  <p>At its most basic level, ‘observability’ is the ability to measure the internal states of a system by examining its outputs. It also implies an ability to separate critical information from routine information. A ‘process’ is simply a description of how something gets done. So ‘process observability’ provides a better understanding of the state and performance of how work is getting done within an organization. A process is observable if stakeholders and systems understand how it operates – where the process outcomes are known – and actions can be derived to improve or change these outcomes.</p>
  <p>Of course, anything that sounds that simple is usually extremely difficult to execute. Here, the challenge is ensuring that the right observations based on the right data are being collected and that the right people have the right tools to analyze that data in real or near-real time. Identifying patterns, trends, anomalies, and potential issues in this way requires strong alignment of business strategy and IT architecture, as well as the ability to directly connect business processes to the underlying IT landscape they rely on.</p>
  <h2 id="where-to-start">Where to Start</h2>
  <p>Supporting better business outcomes must always be the driving force behind ongoing process analysis, insights, and change. Increasing process observability is not about vanity metrics for executives but the alignment needed to make change easier. This depends on three key pillars – data, models, and benchmarks.</p>
  <p>Obviously, a key part of observability is accessing the data that tells you what is happening at a granular level. Every business process produces data in the form of event logs, metrics, and traces. There’s also data from application monitoring and data on the cycle times or costs for processes. Experience data can be gathered from customers, employees, or other stakeholders. In other words, there’s no lack of data sources.</p>
  <div class="promo blue">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="business-process-is-at-the-center-of-digital-transformation">Business process is at the center of digital transformation</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://dam.sap.com/mac/app/p/video/asset/preview/jmE6B7V?ltr=a&#x26;rc=10">Watch a video</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>The bad news is that a recent research study with IDC* found that simply having access to multiple sources of insight was not enough by itself. In fact, when organizations leverage multiple data sources but do not integrate them, they encounter significant challenges. The good news is that the organizations that perform best are significantly more likely to integrate different data sources to analyze processes than the organizations performing less well.</p>
  <p>Just like the pre-game stratagems of your favorite team, business process models are more of an idealized version of reality that rarely survives unscathed at first contact with the reality of the opposing team or the reality of the business. Because of this, it is necessary to bridge the gap between the results of modeling and what is happening in real life. This requires feedback from human experts about underlying issues that cannot be captured by the data alone. Keep in mind that perfect observability is an unattainable goal. It is important to avoid analysis paralysis by understanding the interplay of process models and data, and make conscious, reasonable trade-offs between maximizing process observability and making efficient use of limited time and resources. Don’t let perfect be the enemy of good when you see a clear goal in front of you. You can take one right step at a time.</p>
  <p>Benchmarking is a great way to take one such step towards increased overall observability of your processes. Comparing your outcomes to best-in-class performers in similar organizations provides useful insights on its own. In addition, it can help identify which processes can provide the most competitive differentiation for your business. Benchmarks are most useful when they show us more than just our destination – they need to provide content and guidance on the best way to arrive at that destination.</p>
  <h2 id="at-the-end-of-the-day-its-about-people">At the End of the Day, It’s about People</h2>
  <p>For decades, business leaders have been waiting for technology to fully deliver on the promise of seamless and delightful customer experience; ubiquitous, clean, and secure data; robust and complete applications; and a way to easily test and embed new technologies. In other words, they want to know how technology is supporting business outcomes. This is the promise and the challenge of process observability.</p>
  <p>As in any team sport, communication – frequent, data-driven, curious – is vital for success. Historically, one of the toughest communication gaps has been linking business strategy with technology architecture, mapping business outcomes with underlying operational systems. Bridging this gap is critical to success. The good news is that we are hearing from our most innovative customers that their teams are finally starting to have the right conversations. Instead of IT reporting to the business about system performance and the like, the conversation is now centered on how processes are performing and what needs improving.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>*IDC White Paper, sponsored by SAP, Business Process Observability: A Collaborative Approach to Transformation Enablement, doc #EUR251308223, November 2023.</p>
        <p>Dee Houchen is global lead for the Market Impact Team at SAP Signavio.</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-the-latest-sap-news-delivered-to-your-inbox-every-week">Get the latest SAP News delivered to your inbox every week</h3>
        <p><em><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/nl/sap-news-center-newsletter/index.html">Sign up now</a></em></p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/business-process-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/business-process-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/digital-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-signavio</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Further Expands Focus on Business Transformation with LeanIX Acquisition]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/leanix-acquisition-sap-expands-focus-business-transformation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2023/09/leanix-acquisition-sap-expands-focus-business-transformation</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With the LeanIX acquisition, SAP will further enhance its ability to digitize and simplify business transformations. Learn how.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>news-tag/business-process-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/enterprise-architecture-management</category>
            <category>product/sap-leanix</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-signavio</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Top Reasons to Attend the SAP Signavio Business Process Transformation Forum]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/09/sap-signavio-business-process-transformation-forum-reasons-to-attend</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/09/sap-signavio-business-process-transformation-forum-reasons-to-attend</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Attend the SAP Signavio Business Process Transformation Forum and learn why a strategic approach is the foundation for true business agility.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/business-process-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-signavio</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-signavio-business-process-transformation-forum</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Signavio and LeanIX Bring Process Excellence and Enterprise Architecture Closer Together]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/06/sap-signavio-leanix-process-excellence-enterprise-architecture</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/06/sap-signavio-leanix-process-excellence-enterprise-architecture</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Signavio and LeanIX bring together process excellence and enterprise architecture management, connecting IT and business leaders.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/business-process-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-endorsed-apps</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-signavio</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-store</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Turn Business Process Intelligence into the Next Frontier for Growth]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/business-process-intelligence-next-frontier-for-growth</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/05/business-process-intelligence-next-frontier-for-growth</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Business process intelligence (BPI) delivers more than process improvement. Read how SAP partners uncover the full potential with SAP BTP.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/business-process-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/manufacturing-2</category>
            <category>news-tag/partners</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-partneredge-build</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Accelerating Innovation and Time to Market with SAP BTP]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/04/idc-study-on-sap-btp-partners-accelerate-innovation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/04/idc-study-on-sap-btp-partners-accelerate-innovation</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In a January 2022 IDC study on SAP BTP, partners communicated seeing a steady rise in customer interest and adoption of the platform.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/ecosystem</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/business-process-transformation</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-partneredge</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-partneredge-build</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Business Process Transformation as a Growth Driver]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/03/business-process-transformation-growth-driver</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/03/business-process-transformation-growth-driver</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[To thrive in a future you can’t predict, business process transformation can be your growth driver. Learn more about SAP Signavio.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/business-process-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-signavio</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Signavio Leverages Experience Data to Expand the Value of Business Process Transformation]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/03/sap-signavio-experience-data-business-process-transformation</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/03/sap-signavio-experience-data-business-process-transformation</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP Signavio correlates experience data with underlying IT systems so businesses can optimize their end-to-end business processes.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/business-process-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-signavio</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Business Process Intelligence Is Changing the Approach to Digital Modernization]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/business-process-intelligence-digital-modernization</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/11/business-process-intelligence-digital-modernization</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[With software from SAP and Signavio, companies like Jabil are on a continuous journey focused on identifying, creating, and realizing value.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b4655e82edb61b609c72070576a66cc2ed013627.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1b4655e82edb61b609c72070576a66cc2ed013627.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1b4655e82edb61b609c72070576a66cc2ed013627.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="How Business Process Intelligence Is Changing the Approach to Digital Modernization" src="./media_1b4655e82edb61b609c72070576a66cc2ed013627.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="how-business-process-intelligence-is-changing-the-approach-to-digital-modernization">How Business Process Intelligence Is Changing the Approach to Digital Modernization</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>When it comes to digital transformation, success is absolutely imperative. The stats prove it. Digital “leaders,” as defined in a <a href="https://www.bcg.com/publications/2020/increasing-odds-of-success-in-digital-transformation">recent BCG survey</a>, achieve earnings growth 1.8 times higher than digital “laggards” and experience more than double the growth in total enterprise value.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="https://www.ciodive.com/news/hackett-group-digital-world-class-cost-savings/604928/?utm_source=Sailthru&#x26;utm_medium=email&#x26;utm_campaign=Issue:%202021-08-13%20CIO%20Dive%20%5Bissue:36075%5D&#x26;utm_term=CIO%20Dive">Other research</a> has found a strong correlation between increased tech spending and enterprise cost reduction — as much as 29% overall. This is all while equipping “leaders” with modern platforms, those necessary for future growth, business model reinvention, and continuous innovation.</p>
  <p>The methods and technology are sound — and proven — and yet transformation remains complex and difficult to execute for many companies. Why the challenges? Let’s examine today’s business landscape a bit more closely.</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="excel-in-transformation-with-intelligent-process-management-and-drive-operational-excellence-at-scale">Excel in transformation with intelligent process management and drive operational excellence at scale</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-process-intelligence.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="reinventing-the-transformation-process">Reinventing the Transformation Process</h2>
  <p>It is true that many companies are currently running on decades-old software, and that many of them are under-prepared to manage new developments — whether sophisticated supply chain gain share applications, artificial intelligence (AI) technologies, or sustainability accounting. But we should consider that a solution-focused approach is not necessarily the only solution.</p>
  <p>“Customers don’t care about how you slice and dice your software or how you build your technology,” said <a href="https://www.signavio.com/">Signavio</a> CEO Gero Decker <a href="https://searcherp.techtarget.com/feature/Signavio-aims-to-transform-SAP-software-development-model">in an interview last month</a>. “Customers care about how they can operate well, how they can serve their customers well, and how they can be agile enough to switch to the operating model they need.”</p>
  <p>This mindset shift can be radical for companies looking to digitally transform. Rather than focusing on technology alone, this approach equips them to analyze their current operating model <em>as it is</em> and look toward their target state instead, opening the door for a more modern and intelligent enterprise that works for both them and their customers.</p>
  <p>“Signavio technology can essentially provide customers with an MRI of the entire business — whether it’s running on SAP ECC, SAP S/4HANA, or a different vendor’s systems entirely — and help them mine data and produce process models that show business users how things are really running, identifying potential improvement areas, and ensuring customers can maximize returns on their digital investment,” Decker said.</p>
  <h2 id="myth-of-modernization">Myth of Modernization</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="explore-business-process-intelligence-solutions">Explore business process intelligence solutions</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-process-intelligence.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>SAP <a href="https://www.signavio.com/news/sap-acquisition-signavio/">acquired Signavio</a> in order to help drive an evolution in the transformation paradigm, and to put a renewed focus on the customer in the process. “Implement and forget” cannot be the mindset for digital leaders. In fact, digital transformation should never be viewed as a one-time achievement nor a one-system project; it’s a continuous journey focused on identifying, creating, and realizing value for your company.</p>
  <p>Signavio’s approach is disrupting the entire <a href="/topics/business-process-intelligence">business process intelligence</a> and process management space. By focusing on operating models and processes, the solutions spotlight the most useful application capabilities for what companies want to achieve. When you can see the opportunities, finding support to change company behavior or processes becomes a much easier discussion.</p>
  <p>Look at some of the outcomes customers have already achieved through working with Signavio and our business process intelligence portfolio:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>80% reduction in process improvement cycle times</li>
    <li>20% decrease in the overall number of business processes</li>
    <li>99% fewer manual errors</li>
    <li>Five times the efficiency for complex global projects</li>
    <li>$6.5 million reduction in total operational costs</li>
  </ul>
  <p>One specific success story we have seen in this space is that of American end-to-end manufacturing solutions provider <a href="https://www.jabil.com/">Jabil</a>. The company turned to Signavio in 2018 to help standardize core processes across approximately 100 sites. By putting its current practices into Signavio’s “MRI tube,” Jabil was able to leverage the breadth of knowledge and experience in its workforce and harness innovation at sites all around the world — enabling rapid change and adoption in the process.</p>
  <h2 id="looking-inward-looking-ahead">Looking Inward, Looking Ahead</h2>
  <p>Many enterprises today lack the visibility needed across their business operations. Agile organizations of the future will be ones where everyone knows their place in the enterprise — how upstream processes affect them and how their execution affects everyone downstream.</p>
  <p>The business benefit potential is enormous:</p>
  <ul>
    <li>Making better and more transparent process decisions based on data</li>
    <li>Ensuring standard processes are executed as intended — and quickly identifying exceptions</li>
    <li>Understanding what is happening from end to end in your organization</li>
    <li>Monitoring and improving accurate as-is processes to extract knowledge for root-cause analysis</li>
  </ul>
  <p>This is only the beginning. Business process intelligence is real and having an impact, accelerating the value and mitigating the risks associated with transformation today. Get your company prepared; chart your path forward. Because, as discussed above, success is not an option — it’s an imperative.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>John Tully is senior vice president and managing director of the South Region for SAP North America.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/business-process-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP CEO Christian Klein at SAPPHIRE NOW: Together We Are Reinventing How Businesses Run]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/06/sapphire-now-keynote-ceo-christian-klein</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/06/sapphire-now-keynote-ceo-christian-klein</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In his SAPPHIRE NOW keynote, CEO Christian Klein covered how, together with customers, partners, and employees, SAP is reinventing how businesses run.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>sap-event/[any]</category>
            <category>topic/hcm</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/spend-management</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/business-process-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/industry-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/intelligent-enterprise</category>
            <category>news-tag/qualtrics</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Empowering Customers with New Innovations Announced at SAPPHIRE NOW]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/06/sapphire-now-innovations-empower-customers</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/06/sapphire-now-innovations-empower-customers</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[To further empower customers, SAP has announced a number of new innovations to transform businesses. Read the news from SAPPHIRE NOW.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>topic/crm-customer-experience</category>
            <category>sap-event/sap-sapphire</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/business-process-transformation</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-business-network</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-concur</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Most Resilient Businesses Let Intelligent Data Speak for Itself]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/05/bpi-and-rise-with-sap-resilient-businesses-intelligent-data</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/05/bpi-and-rise-with-sap-resilient-businesses-intelligent-data</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Businesses have one digital transformation imperative: intelligently transform for a more resilient future. BPI and RISE with SAP can help.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1847e4b104fd30424a0bd273d5386de9aa5b3e8f5.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1847e4b104fd30424a0bd273d5386de9aa5b3e8f5.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_1847e4b104fd30424a0bd273d5386de9aa5b3e8f5.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="The Most Resilient Businesses Let Intelligent Data Speak for Itself" src="./media_1847e4b104fd30424a0bd273d5386de9aa5b3e8f5.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="the-most-resilient-businesses-let-intelligent-data-speak-for-itself">The Most Resilient Businesses Let Intelligent Data Speak for Itself</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Over a year into the <a href="/covid-19">pandemic</a>, past, present, and future have imploded into one digital transformation imperative for business leaders: Intelligently transform daily processes for a more resilient future. Leaders have discovered much more than the link between in-person contact and business vulnerability</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>They’ve found that the next phase of <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2021/02/16/the-four-most-important-digital-automation-trends-circa-2021/?sh=201b5ed3e74b">digital automation</a> delivers far greater efficiencies from far more connected business processes company-wide. Think of it as digitalization on steroids.</p>
  <p>“Companies are faced with a business reality that demands digital transformation in a holistic way,” said Rouven Morato, general manager of <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-process-intelligence.html">Business Process Intelligence</a> at SAP. “Leaders are adopting an end-to-end, data-driven perspective to better understand how they run their business today and decide how they want to run it in the future.”</p>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="take-control-of-your-business-transformation-journey-rise-with-sap">Take control of your business transformation journey: RISE with SAP</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/rise.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="business-led-data-intelligence-ends-the-it-backlog">Business-Led Data Intelligence Ends the IT Backlog</h2>
  <p>Today’s business process intelligence is emphatically not yesterday’s approach to increasing efficiencies. Take robotics, which are hardly revelatory. What’s brilliant are the data-driven analyses fueling the latest intelligent robotic process automation (<a href="https://www.sap.com/products/robotic-process-automation.html#:~:text=SAP%20Intelligent%20Robotic%20Processes%20Automation,prebuilt%20bots%20to%20accelerate%20automation.&#x26;text=See%20how%20an%20SAP%20Intelligent,the%20information%20in%20Accounts%20Payable.">RPA</a>) solutions. Using connected information from all relevant processes, companies can precisely identify areas for automated, intelligent, and innovative improvements that will make the biggest difference. The impact of this business-led strategy is profound.</p>
  <p>“With low-code/no-code tools, educated citizen developers outside of the IT department can determine where the problems are and, working together with IT, automate processes for significant efficiencies and business results,” said Morato.</p>
  <h2 id="automation-solves-business-problems-that-matter">Automation Solves Business Problems That Matter</h2>
  <p>Intelligent automation can address numerous business pain points by revealing gaps in process execution, making correlations to find the root cause. For example, data can show that late paying customers received their invoice without the purchase order, which needed to be manually attached. Employees may find it cumbersome to manually locate and attach each purchase order to the invoice, or they may forget to include it. An RPA-based bot can automatically bring the invoice and purchase order together to solve this problem. Speeding up the order-to-cash process has financial and operational benefits for the entire company.</p>
  <p>In procurement, intelligent automation can quickly root out so-called ‘maverick buying’ where people circumvent company policy to source products and services. Automated data intelligence can surface procurement anomalies anywhere in the workflow, connecting these transactions across finance and other parts of the business. Companies can use the data for employee education – “Here’s our cost savings from company buying policies” – adding automation to prevent future non-compliance.</p>
  <h2 id="establish-process-management-as-a-discipline">Establish Process Management as a Discipline</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="lay-the-foundation-for-the-intelligent-enterprise-with-business-process-intelligence">Lay the foundation for the Intelligent Enterprise with business process intelligence</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-process-intelligence.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>Disconnected projects, however well intentioned, are among the biggest pitfalls in <a href="https://insights.sap.com/what-is-digital-transformation/">digital transformation</a>. It’s not unusual for companies to forge ahead with what appeared to be effective improvements, only to become mired in worsening problems a year or two later.</p>
  <p>“Make process management a discipline with the tooling to understand how much a process actually costs, how many steps are required, and the impact on other processes throughout the company and beyond,” said Morato. “That’s why SAP acquired <a href="https://www.signavio.com/news/sap-acquisition-signavio/">Signavio</a>. Its process management and mining tool sets complement our process analyses, KPIs, and process flows that are on top of <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/s4hana-erp.html">SAP S/4HANA</a>. Together, we help organizations simulate changes so they can make process improvements using intelligent automation, helping transform their process landscape.”</p>
  <h2 id="translating-jargon-into-business-value">Translating Jargon Into Business Value</h2>
  <p>End-to-end business process transformation is one of those jargony terms that’s easy to dismiss. In the context of business process automation, its meaning is particularly important. It translates to making sure that people using new processes understand what’s changed and are able to actually carry out those changes. It also means people can capture the value of those changes to the business for continuous improvements. The only valuable end game is a never-ending quest for greater efficiencies and differentiation.</p>
  <p>Bear in mind too that transformation for its own sake has no business value. Make the commitment to analyze problems and then figure out how to solve them in sustainable ways.</p>
  <p>“You need to get away from gut feelings. Look at your data and use the technology to teach you where the problems are and how to fix them,” said Morato. “Let the data speak for itself. Business process transformation is part of <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/rise.html">RISE with SAP</a>, helping companies generate more business value from their technology investments, in this case, with process efficiencies. Think of it as the door opener to the next chapter of your digital journey.”</p>
  <p>Well into 2021, it’s clear that <a href="https://insights.sap.com/digitization-vs-digitalization/">digitalization</a> is the difference between success and failure. Leaders have found intelligent technologies represent a major opportunity for business differentiation and resiliency.</p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Follow me: @smgaler</em><br><em><a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/sap/2021/05/11/the-most-resilient-businesses-let-intelligent-data-speak-for-itself/?sh=68179bff3b77">This story originally appeared on SAP BrandVoice on Forbes</a></em>.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/business-process-transformation</category>
            <category>topic/procurement</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-s4hana-2</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Independent Research Firm Evaluates RPA Solutions: “SAP’s RPA Solution Is a Strong Alternative for SAP Customers…”]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/03/forrester-rpa-solution-sap-strong-performer</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/03/forrester-rpa-solution-sap-strong-performer</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[In a Forrester Wave, SAP's RPA solution was cited as a “Strong Performer.” Learn more about the benefits of SAP Intelligent RPA.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18fb71dccf06b3a70fedce35b961551ca23f61866.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_18fb71dccf06b3a70fedce35b961551ca23f61866.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_18fb71dccf06b3a70fedce35b961551ca23f61866.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="Independent Research Firm Evaluates RPA Solutions: “SAP’s RPA Solution Is a Strong Alternative for SAP Customers…”" src="./media_18fb71dccf06b3a70fedce35b961551ca23f61866.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="independent-research-firm-evaluates-rpa-solutions-saps-rpa-solution-is-a-strong-alternative-for-sap-customers">Independent Research Firm Evaluates RPA Solutions: “SAP’s RPA Solution Is a Strong Alternative for SAP Customers…”</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>Forrester invited SAP to participate in The Forrester Wave™, Robotic Process Automation, Q1 2021. In this evaluation, SAP was cited as a “Strong Performer.” This is the result of a three-year effort to create the best robotic process automation (RPA) solution for SAP customers.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="easily-build-intelligent-bots-with-a-low-code-design-studio-for-hyperautomation">Easily build intelligent bots with a low-code design studio for hyperautomation</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/robotic-process-automation.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <h2 id="2020--how-sap-became-an-rpa-vendor">2018-2020 — How SAP Became an RPA Vendor</h2>
  <p>Let me tell you how SAP started in the RPA market: Three years ago, after having been part of SAP’s machine learning initiative, I decided to focus on creating further value for SAP customers by automating business processes. For this, we put together a strategy and a business case and built a development team. We merged SAP technology with proven RPA technology from Contextor, <a href="/2018/11/sap-acquires-contextor-robotic-process-automation">acquired in 2018</a>.</p>
  <p>May 8, 2019, was a great day for us, with the launch of SAP Intelligent RPA at SAPPHIRE NOW; our booth and our sessions were fully packed and we received a lot of positive feedback from SAP customers and partners.</p>
  <p>We rapidly closed our first customer deal with <a href="/2021/02/process-automation-villeroy-boch-bots-decide">Villeroy and Boch</a>, and the solution spread further. It received a lot of interest from more customers and partners that experienced our <strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/td/sap-intelligent-robotic-process-automation-free-trial.html">free trial</a></strong> to experience the outcomes of our solution in their own IT landscape.</p>
  <p>Via many interactions with our ecosystem and analysts, sharing our road map, and getting new ideas, we constantly improved SAP Intelligent RPA. We enabled more than 50 partners worldwide, which helped us grow our customer base in any industry and any region of the world. End of 2020 we reached a major milestone with 1 million automations over the year:</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d2390bfa1f9980e4dafdc57d89cb8f6bfc19564e.gif?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1d2390bfa1f9980e4dafdc57d89cb8f6bfc19564e.gif?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/gif" srcset="./media_1d2390bfa1f9980e4dafdc57d89cb8f6bfc19564e.gif?width=2000&#x26;format=gif&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Intelligent RPA: 1 million automations" src="./media_1d2390bfa1f9980e4dafdc57d89cb8f6bfc19564e.gif?width=750&#x26;format=gif&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1280" height="720">
    </picture>According to a survey from another analyst firm in the fourth quarter of 2020, SAP is already in the Top 3 Automation Product Suppliers across the Global 2000 companies. <a href="https://www.forbes.com/global2000/">Global 2000</a> is an annual ranking of the top 2,000 public companies in the world created by Forbes magazine. Published since 2003, it is based on a mix of four metrics: sales, profit, assets, and market value. These very large companies are the core of SAP customers, many of them having deployed SAP ERP and other SAP software for decades.
  </p>
  <p>This survey shows that we have succeeded in providing these customers with an SAP solution that fits their needs. Three months ago at <a href="https://blogs.sap.com/2020/12/14/sap-intelligent-rpa-2.0-sap-teched-2020-is-a-wrap/">SAP Teched</a>, we unveiled SAP Intelligent RPA 2.0, a major release of our product geared toward democratization of automation. It offers bot-building capabilities following a low-code or no-code approach, enabling non-technical business process experts to create customizable automations with clicks, not code. In addition, <a href="https://store.irpa.cfapps.eu10.hana.ondemand.com/">more than 170 prebuilt bot templates</a> are available to automate and drive efficiencies in 12 lines of business for any industry, with about 60 prebuilt bots only for <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/s4hana-erp.html">SAP S/4HANA</a>.</p>
  <p>This new release of SAP Intelligent RPA provides high flexibility while helping ensure IT governance. It received great feedback from the customers: “Great job, we saw and experienced many steps that have become much easier during the robot creation process,” said Balbir Singh Dhillon, Associate Director Intelligent Solutions at Zuellig Pharma. “Just the email capabilities alone save a lot of time and places that functionality in the hands of the citizen user and no longer dependent on experienced developers. The look and feel and the user experience were really great, and I can only see the product getting richer with additional features.”</p>
  <h2 id="sap-named-a-strong-performer-in-the-forrester-wave-robotic-process-automation-q1-2021">2021 — SAP Named a “Strong Performer” in The Forrester Wave™: Robotic Process Automation, Q1 2021</h2>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="register-for-a-free-trial-of-sap-intelligent-rpa-now">Register for a free trial of SAP Intelligent RPA now</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/td/sap-intelligent-robotic-process-automation-free-trial.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>At the end of last year, Forrester invited SAP to participate in its evaluation, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/robotic-process-automation.html?campaigncode=CRM-PM21-SIP-INTTECHFOR&#x26;rc=https%3A%2F%2Freprints2.forrester.com%2F%23%2Fassets%2F2%2F702%2FRES161538%2Freport">The Forrester Wave™, Robotic Process Automation, Q1 2021</a>. The report is now published, and in this evaluation, SAP was cited as a Strong Performer.</p>
  <p>According to the Forrester report, “SAP’s RPA solution is a strong alternative for SAP customers, particularly for enterprises concerned with bots disrupting core SAP systems and those usually needing the central SAP development team to design, develop, and maintain RPA for clear accountability, or for companies seeking a feature-rich RPA tool that comes with a broad ecosystem of partners.”</p>
  <p>We could not agree more. Creating an RPA solution for SAP customers, our aim was to bring an automation tool that fits in their IT landscape and fulfills all of their governance requirements. Because their enterprise resource planning (ERP) is a key component of their daily operations, it is finely tuned by the IT department to run smoothly. For sure, our customers do not want any disruption in the way their ERP runs and need that any software robot interacting with the ERP to be fast and efficient, but without any risk of generating extra system load.</p>
  <p>The prebuilt bot templates available in our SAP Intelligent RPA store are directly created and maintained by major SAP product teams, such as SAP S/4HANA already and soon SAP SuccessFactors and SAP Ariba. This approach offers a strong cohesion among existing SAP systems in place, increasing the bots’ performance. Our prebuilt bots are constantly updated and upgraded to support our customers’ latest ERP, HR, or <a href="https://www.ariba.com/solutions/solutions-overview/procurement">procurement software</a> releases.</p>
  <p>We aim to provide the best RPA solution for SAP customers and this will go far beyond robotic process automation. The <strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-process-intelligence.html">business process intelligence</a></strong> portfolio is a strategic initiative from SAP to deliver process excellence by analyzing, improving, and monitoring processes. Together with SAP Workflow Management, SAP Intelligent RPA turns process insights into actions to help drive digital transformation. It allows non-technical users to create automation scenarios without code, and to deliver outcomes quickly with predefined content.</p>
  <p>
    <picture>
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1fd3a2d29639e1c57bcef58406e1172da2787c444.png?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_1fd3a2d29639e1c57bcef58406e1172da2787c444.png?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
      <source type="image/png" srcset="./media_1fd3a2d29639e1c57bcef58406e1172da2787c444.png?width=2000&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
      <img loading="lazy" alt="Graphic: components business process intelligence" src="./media_1fd3a2d29639e1c57bcef58406e1172da2787c444.png?width=750&#x26;format=png&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1597" height="725">
    </picture>Let us accelerate your business transformation journey — I would be very happy to welcome you as our customer or partner, to do this automation journey together.
  </p>
  <div class="footnote">
    <div>
      <div><em>Sebastian Schroetel is vice president and head of SAP Intelligent RPA.</em></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="buy-sap-intelligent-rpa-on-the-sap-store-today">Buy SAP Intelligent RPA on the SAP Store today!</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sapstore.com/solutions/42831/SAP-Intelligent-Robotic-Process-Automation">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>topic/erp</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/business-process-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/rpa</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-intelligent-rpa</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Completes Acquisition of Signavio]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/03/signavio-acquisition-complete</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/03/signavio-acquisition-complete</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP has completed the Signavio acquisition. Its products become part of SAP’s business process intelligence portfolio. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>news-tag/business-process-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/business-process-transformation</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP to Acquire Business Process Intelligence Company Signavio]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/01/sap-to-acquire-signavio</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/01/sap-to-acquire-signavio</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP will acquire Signavio, a leader in the enterprise business process intelligence and process management space. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/corporate</category>
            <category>content-type/press-release</category>
            <category>news-tag/business-process-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/business-process-transformation</category>
            <category>news-tag/rise-with-sap</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>