<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>SAP Sponsorships Archives | SAP News Center</title>
        <link>https://www.sap.com/topics/product/sap-data-intelligence/feed/</link>
        <description>Company &amp;#38; Customer Stories &amp;#124; Press Room.</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>AEM SAP News feed generator (GitHub action)</generator>
        <language>en-US</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Recognized as a Leader in 2022 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Data Integration Tools]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/2022-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-data-integration-tools-sap-a-leader</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/2022-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-data-integration-tools-sap-a-leader</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP is a Leader in the 2022 Magic Quadrant for Data Integration Tools for the 15th consecutive year. Learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/data-fabric</category>
            <category>news-tag/data-integration</category>
            <category>news-tag/database-and-data-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/magic-quadrant</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-data-intelligence</category>
            <category>product/sap-data-intelligence-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Data and Analytics Solutions Earn Multiple 2022 Top Rated and Best of Awards from TrustRadius]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/sap-data-and-analytics-solutions-2022-trustradius-awards</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/08/sap-data-and-analytics-solutions-2022-trustradius-awards</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP data and analytics solutions have been recognized by TrustRadius with multiple wins in both the Top Rated and Best of Award categories.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/data-analytics</category>
            <category>news-tag/database-and-data-management</category>
            <category>product/sap-analytics-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-data-intelligence</category>
            <category>product/sap-hana-cloud</category>
            <category>product/sap-master-data-governance</category>
            <category>news-tag/trustradius</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Named a Leader among Enterprise Data Fabric Solutions by Forrester Research, Inc.]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/06/sap-leader-enterprise-data-fabric-solutions-forrester-research</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/06/sap-leader-enterprise-data-fabric-solutions-forrester-research</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Forrester Research, Inc., has recognized SAP in "The Forrester Wave: Enterprise Data Fabric, Q2 2022" report. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/database-and-data-management</category>
            <category>news-tag/forrester</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-data-intelligence</category>
            <category>product/sap-data-intelligence-cloud</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Receives TrustRadius Awards in Multiple Data Management and Integration Categories]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/06/sap-receives-trustradius-awards-data-management-and-integration</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/06/sap-receives-trustradius-awards-data-management-and-integration</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[TrustRadius has recognized SAP solutions for data management and integration with Top-Rated awards. Read to learn more.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/database-and-data-management</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-data-intelligence</category>
            <category>product/sap-integration-suite</category>
            <category>product/sap-master-data-governance</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ITZBund and SAP Bring AI to German Federal Agencies]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/06/itzbund-sap-bring-ai-to-german-federal-agencies</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2022/06/itzbund-sap-bring-ai-to-german-federal-agencies</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[The ITZBund and SAP joined forces to accelerate the digital transformation of the German Federal Office of Administration with an AI platform.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"message":"Service Unavailable"}]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>topic/ai</category>
            <category>product/sap-data-intelligence</category>
            <category>news-tag/sap-hana</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Named a Leader in 2021 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Data Integration Tools for the 14th Year in a Row]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/sap-a-leader-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-data-integration-tools</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/sap-a-leader-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-data-integration-tools</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[For the 14th consecutive year, SAP has been named a Leader in the Magic Quadrant for Data Integration Tools. Read the news.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_118130ba999d251626784244ba258cc2c6d0cd409.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_118130ba999d251626784244ba258cc2c6d0cd409.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_118130ba999d251626784244ba258cc2c6d0cd409.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Named a Leader in 2021 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Data Integration Tools for the 14th Year in a Row" src="./media_118130ba999d251626784244ba258cc2c6d0cd409.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-named-a-leader-in-2021-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-data-integration-tools-for-the-14th-year-in-a-row">SAP Named a Leader in 2021 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Data Integration Tools for the 14th Year in a Row</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="turn-data-chaos-into-data-value-with-data-intelligence">Turn data chaos into data value with data intelligence</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/data-intelligence.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p><strong><em>WALLDORF</em></strong></p>
        <hr>
        <p><a href="http://www.sap.com/">SAP SE</a> (NYSE: SAP) today announced that independent analyst firm <a href="http://www.gartner.com/technology/home.jsp">Gartner Inc.</a> has named SAP a Leader in its <a href="https://www.sap.com/cmp/dg/gartner-data-integration-tool-mq/index.html">Magic Quadrant™ for Data Integration Tools* report</a>. Gartner evaluated 18 vendors and named SAP a Leader based on “ability to execute” and “completeness of vision.”</p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p>This is the 14th consecutive year that SAP has been named a Leader in the Magic Quadrant for Data Integration Tools.</p>
  <p>According to Gartner, “The data integration tool market is seeing renewed momentum, driven by requirements for hybrid and multicloud data integration, augmented data management, and data fabric designs. This assessment of 18 vendors will help data and analytics leaders choose a best fit for their data integration needs.”</p>
  <p>“This latest recognition from Gartner acknowledges SAP’s ongoing commitment to improving our customers’ data integration across the enterprise,” said Andreas Wesselmann, senior vice president, SAP HANA Database &#x26; Analytics, Common Data Services at SAP. “As part of the information management layer of SAP Business Technology Platform, SAP’s data integration offerings deliver trusted, relevant and timely information to drive better business outcomes for our customers.”</p>
  <p><a href="https://corporate.evonik.com/en">Evonik Industries AG</a>, headquartered in Germany and one of the largest specialty chemicals companies in the world, is using the SAP Data Intelligence solution. “We have witnessed efficiency improvements for data management as well as higher data quality,” said Frank Schmalle, head of Enterprise Data Management, Global IT, Evonik Industries AG. “Using SAP Data Intelligence, we will continue our journey to streamline the handling of complex materials data across our business.”</p>
  <p>SAP’s data integration offerings include <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/data-intelligence.html">SAP Data Intelligence</a>, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/data-services.html">SAP Data Services</a>, <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/landscape-replication-server.html">SAP Landscape Transformation Replication Server</a> and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/cloud-platform/capabilities/integration.html">SAP Integration Suite</a>, along with integration capabilities of <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/hana.html">SAP HANA</a>. These offerings are part of <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/business-technology-platform.html">SAP Business Technology Platform</a> and focus on delivering comprehensive integration by providing users with intelligent and contextual insights through integration across the IT landscape.</p>
  <p>Visit the <a href="http://news.sap.com/">SAP News Center</a>. Follow SAP on Twitter at <a href="http://twitter.com/sapnews/">@SAPNews</a>.</p>
  <p><strong>Media Contact:</strong> Julia Fargel, +1 (650) 276-8964, <a href="mailto:julia.fargel@sap.com">julia.fargel@sap.com</a>, PT<br><a href="/press-room">SAP Press Room</a>; <a href="mailto:press@sap.com">press@sap.com</a></p>
  <p><em>*Gartner, Magic Quadrant for Data Quality Solutions, published on August 25, 2021.</em><br><em>Gartner does not endorse any vendor, product or service depicted in its research publications, and does not advise technology users to select only those vendors with the highest ratings or other designation. Gartner research publications consist of the opinions of Gartner’s research organization and should not be construed as statements of fact. Gartner disclaims all warranties, expressed or implied, with respect to this research, including any warranties of merchantability or fitness for a particular purpose.</em><br><em>GARTNER and Magic Quadrant are registered trademarks and service mark of Gartner, Inc. and/or its affiliates in the U.S. and internationally and are used herein with permission. All rights reserved.</em></p>
  <p>Any statements contained in this document that are not historical facts are forward-looking statements as defined in the U.S. Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995. Words such as “anticipate,” “believe,” “estimate,” “expect,” “forecast,” “intend,” “may,” “plan,” “project,” “predict,” “should” and “will” and similar expressions as they relate to SAP are intended to identify such forward-looking statements. SAP undertakes no obligation to publicly update or revise any forward-looking statements. All forward-looking statements are subject to various risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results to differ materially from expectations. The factors that could affect SAP’s future financial results are discussed more fully in SAP’s filings with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (“SEC”), including SAP’s most recent Annual Report on Form 20-F filed with the SEC. Readers are cautioned not to place undue reliance on these forward-looking statements, which speak only as of their dates.<br>© 2021 SAP SE. All rights reserved.<br>SAP and other SAP products and services mentioned herein as well as their respective logos are trademarks or registered trademarks of SAP SE in Germany and other countries. Please see <a href="https://www.sap.com/copyright">https://www.sap.com/copyright</a> for additional trademark information and notices.</p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/solutions</category>
            <category>content-type/newsbyte</category>
            <category>news-tag/gartner</category>
            <category>news-tag/magic-quadrant</category>
            <category>product/sap-business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>product/sap-data-intelligence</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAP Receives Award by TrustRadius in Multiple Data Management Categories]]></title>
            <link>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/sap-receives-trustradius-awards-for-data-management</link>
            <guid>https://www.sap.com/news/2021/08/sap-receives-trustradius-awards-for-data-management</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 05 Aug 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[SAP has received TrustRadius awards for data management. Learn why SAP Master Data Governance and SAP Data Intelligence were recognized.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div>
  <div class="hero">
    <div>
      <div>
        <p>
          <picture>
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_161d736f1f8909faa946ca3de7493588f42e18e60.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <source type="image/webp" srcset="./media_161d736f1f8909faa946ca3de7493588f42e18e60.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=webply&#x26;optimize=medium">
            <source type="image/jpeg" srcset="./media_161d736f1f8909faa946ca3de7493588f42e18e60.jpeg?width=2000&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" media="(min-width: 600px)">
            <img loading="lazy" alt="SAP Receives Award by TrustRadius in Multiple Data Management Categories" src="./media_161d736f1f8909faa946ca3de7493588f42e18e60.jpeg?width=750&#x26;format=jpeg&#x26;optimize=medium" width="1900" height="476">
          </picture>
        </p>
        <h1 id="sap-receives-award-by-trustradius-in-multiple-data-management-categories">SAP Receives Award by TrustRadius in Multiple Data Management Categories</h1>
      </div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="promo">
    <div>
      <div>
        <h3 id="get-complete-control-of-your-data-landscape-with-an-end-to-end-view-of-all-data-through-one-single-gateway">Get complete control of your data landscape with an end-to-end view of all data through one single gateway</h3>
      </div>
      <div><strong><a href="https://www.sap.com/products/database-data-management.html">Learn more</a></strong></div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <div class="text-large">
    <div>
      <div>At SAP, we are committed to enabling our customers to use data and analytics as a differentiator and competitive strength: focused on the strategic role of data in transformation and channeling data to create value.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="https://insights.sap.com/what-is-data-management/">Data management</a> solutions from SAP power SAP Business Technology Platform (SAP BTP), delivering solutions that drive a data strategy and maximize the value of data. Combined with data management, SAP BTP brings together database, analytics, integration, and extension capabilities with intelligent enterprise applications into one platform for both cloud and hybrid environments.</p>
  <p>By making data management a priority, customers can take advantage of the volume and variety of data, successfully driving business processes and innovations. A data management approach helps your company drive success in the future.</p>
  <p>We are honored that customers value our data passion and recently expressed their appreciation through <a href="https://www.trustradius.com/products/sap-data-intelligence/reviews">online reviews</a>, earning SAP the Top Rated award in both the <a href="https://www.trustradius.com/master-data-management-mdm#toprated">Master Data Management category</a> and the <a href="https://www.trustradius.com/data-fabric#toprated">Data Fabric category</a>.</p>
  <p>“Buyers have many options when it comes to selecting a master data governance solution,” said Megan Headley, vice president of Research at TrustRadius. “SAP Master Data Governance earned a Top Rated award based entirely on feedback from its customers. Reviewers on TrustRadius highlight the product’s high performance, ease of data management, and flexibility of integrations.”</p>
  <p>“SAP Data Intelligence has earned a Data Fabric Top Rated award based directly on feedback from its customers,” Headley continued. “Reviewers on TrustRadius value SAP Data Intelligence features for transforming data, as well as its ability to accept data from a wide variety of sources.”</p>
  <p>This acknowledgement is a great honor for multiple reasons. Not only are the Trust Radius Top Rated awards the industry standard for unbiased recognition of the best technology products; more importantly, they are the direct result of our customer engagement. We view this recognition as a testament to our customer-focused data management approach, validating our solution strategy and vision for <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/master-data-governance.html">SAP Master Data Governance</a> and <a href="https://www.sap.com/products/data-intelligence.html">SAP Data Intelligence</a> to deliver next-generation data management capabilities for our customers.</p>
  <p>TrustRadius helps drive collaboration with our customers and partners by continuously capturing and acting on customer input to drive relevant improvements. Listening to our data-passionate customers and focusing on active listening combined with effective feedback loops to drive solution improvements enables SAP to better serve customer challenges and continuously deliver innovative industry solutions.</p>
  <div class="quote">
    <div>
      <div>Read the reviews on <a href="https://www.trustradius.com/">TrustRadius</a> for both <a href="https://www.trustradius.com/products/sap-master-data-governance/reviews/top-rated-badge">SAP Master Data Governance</a> and <a href="https://www.trustradius.com/products/sap-data-intelligence/reviews">SAP Data Intelligence</a>.</div>
    </div>
    <div>
      <div>Andreas Wesselmann is senior vice president of SAP HANA and Analytics, Data Management at SAP.</div>
    </div>
  </div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-details">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-details</a></p>
</div>
<div>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/article-read-more">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/article-read-more</a></p>
  <p><a href="/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription">https://main--builder-prospect-prod--sapudex.hlx.page/fragments/news/newsletter-subscription</a></p>
  <div class="section-metadata">
    <div>
      <div>location</div>
      <div>document-footer</div>
    </div>
  </div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
            <category>news-topic/business-technology-platform</category>
            <category>news-topic/technology</category>
            <category>content-type/feature</category>
            <category>news-tag/database-and-data-management</category>
            <category>product/sap-data-intelligence</category>
            <category>product/sap-master-data-governance</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>